<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I haven't posted in awhile so sorry about that if anyone is reading this.   It has been an interesting week to say the least.&nbsp; My now ex-girlfriend came home for the weekend.&nbsp; Friday night we watched a movie and then she even kissed me.&nbsp; It was a nice pleasant evening.&nbsp; However, it was kind of weird considering she had just told me the day before that she had gone to the bars again with this guy.&nbsp; Now we are not together but it still hurts.&nbsp; Kicker is is that she asked him to go with her this time.&nbsp; I don't think that she is telling me everything about him or her ex-boyfriend before me that she has admitted to liking.   Anyways, Saturday we got into this big fight.&nbsp; She said that she couldn't get over the Ryan situation.&nbsp; (Ryan is the girl that I met and am friends with that&nbsp;my ex-girlfriend&nbsp;and I had huge fights and problems over last semester)&nbsp;&nbsp; Well, I finally got up enough guts to tell her off a little.&nbsp; I told her that I did nothing wrong with Ryan.&nbsp; That I have never&nbsp;cheated on her or have even come close to cheating on&nbsp;her.&nbsp; I also told&nbsp;her&nbsp;some other things.&nbsp; Well, she started&nbsp;crying.&nbsp; I didn't mean for this to happen but I had to tell her these things.&nbsp; There are many more things I want to tell her like that I don't believe her when she tells me&nbsp;she has done nothing more than kiss these guys that she has cheated on me with.   Sunday, her and I went up to the Bear Trap Festival&nbsp;up on Casper Mountain.&nbsp; It was nice...hot though.&nbsp; I got sunburned&nbsp;pretty bad.&nbsp;   Well, I will try to write more tomorrow.&nbsp;&nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I had a ton of relatives stay at my place this weekend on top of my aunt moving in with my family.  To sum it up quickly, I had two aunts and one uncle actually staying at my house and two cousins and their four very young children running around the house the rest of the time.  All and all it wasn't that bad of a weekend....just long.  The only really bad thing is what is still happening with my girlfriend/ex-girlfriend.  She and I are still talking.  It now sounds as if she wants to keep talking and hangout and even still be together.  She says that she sees that she was just being dumb.  Ok, I will give her that but this isn't the first time that this has happened.  Am I just supposed to forget everything and take her back.  It hurts being cheated on or having the person you like think that she is falling in love with another guy.  Especially when those guys are really geeky looking and ugly.  That just makes me feel like a dog ugly person.  I guess maybe I am.  I just don't know what to do with that situation.  I am scared to move on and leave her.  Speaking of being scared.  I am absolutely mortified about law school starting in a month.  I am afraid that I can't handle it or that I won't like it.  What then, I would have wasted five years of my life studying for something that I don't want to be.  I should have just become a professional golfer and worked at some golf course.  Work is alright too.  The twins (two friends of mine and the brothers of one of my dear friends) will be leaving work too this year.  I will miss those two.  Over the years working at Blimpies I have grown to love them, their sister, and my bosses.  I will miss them a lot since this will be my last summer returning to Blimpies to work.    Well, off to read just thought I drop a line to whoever might be reading my blog.     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is just scary how well I can see bad things coming when it involves my girlfriend...well, I guess that would be ex-girlfriend now.&nbsp; We never stay broken up for too long but I am almost wishing that this one will stay permanent.&nbsp; I am tired of being hurt....  &nbsp;  Well, I guess you would like to know what happened.&nbsp; She came back this weekend from Laramie where she is going to summer school.&nbsp; I planned a nice day today to go to the Natural Bridge Park.&nbsp; We had fun walking around and talking.&nbsp; She held my hand and everything on the drive there and back.&nbsp; However, I could just tell that something was bothering her.&nbsp; It took her until tonight to tell me what.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Well, this is how it went...HER: "I just don't know what to do."&nbsp; ME: "Why because you like Kyle (her ex-boyfriend she has been hanging out with)?"&nbsp; HER:"Yes"&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Now, this freaking thing seems to happen every year.&nbsp; This is now like the sixth time this has happened in the four and a half years that we have been going out.&nbsp; Granted that she says that she hasn't done anything with the guy this time but the other times she had.&nbsp; I don't know what is worse: having the girl&nbsp; you think you love with all your heart do this to you, breaking up with the girl you thought you would someday marry, or actually being so used to these things happening that I don't have an emotional reaction to it.  &nbsp;  I do feel very very upset and hurt...but did I cry...no....did I get mad at her and yell...no...what did I do...just sat there trying to think of what I want to do.&nbsp; Maybe we should break up because I can't stop her from doing this over and over again and I can't stop her from feeling jealous because I talk to other people.&nbsp; Why don't girls love me and stay with me?&nbsp; Why can't I have someone who will love me and never cheat on me?&nbsp; I have never ever cheated on one of my girlfriends.&nbsp; I have had some opportunities but I have never put myself in those situations that anything might happen from them.&nbsp; Why can't I expect the same?&nbsp; &nbsp;  This sucks!!!!&nbsp; I have no idea what to do now.     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just don't get women sometimes especially my girlfriend.  Here's a little background first.  My girlfriend and I have been dating for about four and half years.  We go through ups and downs like most relationships; however, she thinks that we go through more downs than ups.  This past semester in school, I had made a new friend who happened to be a girl.  Now my girlfriend thought that this other girl liked me.  (Granted that I did think this other girl was pretty) I didn't like this other girl so there shouldn't have been a problem.  To put a long story short... a lot of terrible things resulted from that situation even though I never cheated on my girlfriend or even did anything with this other girl.   Ok, back to what's been going on.  This week, my girlfriend tells me that "I went to the bars tonight with this guy from my class.  We hung out for sometime talking and  having fun."  Ok, while I can't tell her what to do...it makes me mad that she thinks that she can just go out to the bars alone with some guy she just met.  However, this isn't what gets me.  She has started talking to and hanging out with her ex-boyfriend a lot.  They  go for hikes together and dinners.  Oh, and he pays for them!!!  She thinks it is just fine even though he has admitted to liking her to her.  She tells me that what she is doing isn't worse than what I did with that other girl.  OK!!! For one, I didn't do anything with her.  Two, she didn't like me.  Three, we hadn't previously dated.   The situation just makes me mad, upset, and mostly scared.  My girlfriend has cheated on me four times before (that I know of).  I feel like this is going to be number five with at least one of the two guys.  And what makes it worse is that I can't stop it from happening.  I don't want to get hurt like I did before but who can stop  yourself from being hurt without not having a life.    Oh, well.  I guess I will just wait and see.   
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, I will eventually update my template and things but this first post is more of a test than anything.  I wanted to create this blog for one reason, I want to have some place to put my thoughts about things happening in my life.  My good friend and also my girlfriend have blogs as well.  I might eventually link them but for right now this blog is unknown to them.  I really don't want them to read it because I want to remain honest and open to my feelings when I write.  So hopefully I will.  But in the mean time...hello blogging world.
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, Megan and I went camping last night up in the Snowies. It was a good time for most of it and awkward for the rest. We got up there, set up the tent and then went hiking to find some firewood. Then we had dinner and then went for a long hike. Eventually, we ended up just hanging out by the fire and talking a little. The strange and awkward part was when we went to sleep. Megan gives me such mix signals about what she wants me to do. I feel like she wanted me to be close to her last night but then she says stuff like "You know, even if we do stuff, I just can't be with you anymore." What the hell is that supposed to mean? She would rather be with an ass hole like Kyle. You could tell though that he was always on her mind because she keeps talking about voting and declaring Democrat so that she can vote. This means that she has been volunteering at his work a lot more than what she admits to. This just sucks. I feel lost again. I wish I knew what I could or should do. I guess time will tell.  Long day ahead of me. I have to go to the school, get my books, buy stuff and Wal-Mart, and probably even go to Denver now too. 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I am off in about an hour to go camping. I was going to go backpacking but my ex-girlfriend wants to go camping with me so I am doing that instead. I don't know how to act around her. Sometimes I feel like she wants to get back together with me and that she misses me. Other times, she yells at me and gets mad at me very quickly. Also, I sit around thinking that I really really want to be with her and how much I miss her. I don't know if this means that I truly am in love with her or if I am just lonely. I know that I am really really really lonely. I feel lost right now. For five years, I always had Megan to hang out with and now I don't. It is just a real shock because I don't have anyone to talk to or hang out with. Oh well, we will see how camping goes this weekend. 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I am back home in Laramie. I arrived yesterday pretty late at night. I have now been really busy trying to get all settled back in. I went and bought a wireless router so now I am typing this post on my new computer sitting on my couch watching the Olympics. It is soooo cool. I love my new computer.  Oh, embarrassing thing happened to me to day. I went shopping at Wal-Mart for some food and some other things. Well, I went to grab a thing of mayo and it slipped from my hands. It fell and shattered on the ground. Since when does mayo come in glass jars again. It sucked!!! It was such a mess and I was so embarrassed that I just had to get out of there and didn't get all the things that I needed. I guess I will have to go to Albertsons some time this week to get the rest of the food that I need.  Well, back to the Olympics and cleaning my place. 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was my last day of work. I have been working at Blimpies Subs and Salads for about four and a half years while on my breaks from college. It was an easy job but not a dream job. I guess one of the reasons that I stayed there so long is because of my bosses. Scott and Venee (my bosses) own the restaurant. While they were my bosses, they were much more to me than that. I truly love them and think of them as close to my real family as anyone can be. Over the years, they have done so much for me that I don't know how I will ever be able to repay them for it. I will hopefully keep in touch with them as my life goes on.  Related to my last days at Blimpies. This week, one of the regular customers who seems just to come in to see Cindy and me. (Well, since Cindy was not there this summer it was more just like me this summer) Anyway, she came in to say good-bye to me this week. She stayed there and talked to me for a little while. She told me that I was one of the great people out there and that she was going to miss me. She also told me that she hoped I had a good life. It was a really nice thing for her to do and I really needed to hear those things right now. Before she left, she asked for a hug, which I also needed during this time as well. I am really going to miss her and all of the other regular customers at Blimpies. I pray that their lives are filled with happiness.  It is sad to think that I probably won't be going back to Blimpies to work ever again. I am really going to miss talking to Scott and Venee. Their stories were always interesting and funny. They always cared for me and did a lot for me. And their personalities and love helped brighten up my days no matter how down of a mood I was in at the time. So from the bottom of my heart, I thank them for that.  Well, it is getting late so I must go to bed now. Tomorrow, I head back to Laramie. I start law school next Thursday and have a lot to do before that day comes. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why, why, why? Am I that ugly, that stupid, that horrible that this happens to me. I just found out right now that Megan has now kissed this f#$%ing Kyle guy. What the hell!!!! I can't stop crying right now. She has been hanging out with him every night after she hangs out with me during the day. She didn't get home until late last night and when I asked her if she is going to date him she said I don't know. I asked her if it was heading that way and she said she didn't know. Then I asked her if she has made out with him and she said "Made out...no." So I asked her if they have kissed, her response...."Why do this to your self Keith"  Please, oh, please kill me. I don't know what to do. I care for her so much and still can't sleep at night. All I think about is her and thinking about what she is doing. The scary thing is is that I know her so much that I had a gut feeling last night that something was going on!!!!! Please kill me. I want to die right now sooooooo bad. I can't take this....I wish I had someone to be with me for once instead everyone else having someone I like or even love like Megan.  I mean I had been with Megan for about five years and I don't know if I have every had her completely to myself. That just means that I deserve to be dead....doesn't it. I mean no one wants me....I wish Jesus could help me right now. I so desperately need Him to help me.  K, I have to go throw up now. The good thing about this is that maybe I will lose weight!!! 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend has been a roller coaster of ups and downs in my quest to search for some answers and also to try to be Megan's friend instead of boyfriend. She came into town Friday night and I got to see her right after work. However, I ended up hanging out with my mom and then my dad that night. Megan had a "date" with Kyle as I put it. He cooked her dinner and then they watched a movie together. I knew that she was doing this and I have no say in what she does anymore so I can just bare it. I also couldn't sleep last night. I didn't get to sleep until like four in the morning. Not being able to sleep is a common thing for me actually. I have never been able to sleep very well at all. It usually takes me two to three hours to fall asleep each and every night.  So you might be wondering why I can't sleep and what do I think about. Well the answer is is that I think about a lot of things that are bothering me and how maybe things could have been or could be different. For example, last night I thought about Megan and everything that was going on. I thought about how I really do care for her and that part of me can't bare the thought of losing her. I also thought about other girls I have liked over the years I have dated Megan.   OK....OK I will finally admit it to myself and everyone else
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I only have one week left of work and then I am off for another year or even for good. It has been good working at Blimpies for the past four years but it is time to move on. I will only miss a few people I work with and of course my two bosses and their son. Four the past four years I have had the privilege of working for two of the best human beings that have ever lived. They have done so much for me and have cared for and loved me through all of my ups and downs. I don't think I can ever repay them for what they have done for me. All I can say is that I love them dearly and hopefully I will get to stay in contact with them as well.  On to other notes. I am scared for school but starting to get used to the idea of me as a law school student. However, what is scaring me more is the fact that I will be alone this year. I have never been totally alone at school. I have either had friends to hang out with or a girlfriend to talk to. This year their are neither. My friends/friend lives in Denver and I haven't even talked to him in a week. Megan has dumped me and has moved on to other guys already (Amazing how fast she can get over me). And well the other few friends (at least I called them my friends---I don't really know if they would ever do the same) are either moved back home (Melissa O.), moved to Denver (Megan B., Aaron, and Cindy), or I just don't know how to ask them to talk to me or hang out with me (Brandon, Jeremy, Nathan, David, and Ryan). I guess this is part of me being alone. It sucks but at least I am hanging in there.   
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel so lost right now.  It looks like this is the final time that Megan and I will break up.  She is bound and determined to make this break up last and who can blame her.  I don't know who in their right mind would want to date me.  I just feel so lost right now and this past weekend did nothing to help the matters but I will write about that tomorrow.  Right now I feel like getting into my car and just leaving....maybe then I can do what will make everyone happy----LEAVE 
    
</post>


</Blog>