<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The  last day  at work has come...I woke up this morning, with a terrible nervous pain in my stomach. I kept thinking that everything I was doing was for the last time, even waking up in my bed. So everything this morning seemed  more important  that ever before.  I took my time coming to work, I wasn't in a hurry at all. I kind of wrapped up my unfinished projects and then headed for lunch at my favourite place, the Fresh 'n' Wild restaurant for a vegetable curry and brown rice. Absolutely delicious! No more curries for me in Greece I am afraid.  Now the last 2 hours seems unbearable...I wish I could just go without a word, I hate saying goodbye. Just disappear, I never going to see any of them again.  I leave my cactus here, hoping is going to be ok. I threw everything away, I just kept 2 of my favourite origami on the monitors.  I even got back the money from Air Berlin today ,after more than  4 months of waiting.  I don't know when I am going to blog again, its going to take a few weeks until I have my own place.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since yesterday everything is packed and ready to go. Thankfully Panos is a master of packing and he was a great help in arranging everything. It was like he was creating a 3D jigsaw although he didn't seem to enjoy making it that much. But I did!  Tomorrow is set as the pick up day, I just hope we can lift the boxes and move them to the entrance. I wish my kidneys will stay in place. After that I am going to be carefree for a week until I go. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        It's been quite stressful so far and its only half day, but with deep breathing I can take a bit more...  3 cubic metres are my possessions, at least the ones that I 'll take with me. I didn't know how expensive is to move things; I came with 2 suitcases and a racksack ... but time changes everything... so they became 15 (approx.)  I think I will have to part from the 21" monitor, instead I 'll be content with my laptop's monitor (12").
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That is what I say to myself, in an effort to calm down and relax. In these stressful situations, my immune system reaches the bottom of the ocean and I have to deal with other health problems on top of everything that's on at the time. I haven't eaten a proper meal since last week.  Having to work while I try to arrange everything else is not helping, but I need the money so no option there.  I have been materialistic in the last years and I have accumulated lots of stuff. I wouldn't want to part from them so I 'll take them with me. I am not a person that keeps everything though, I tend to get a pleasurable feeling when I get rid of things that I don't really use or need. I feel lighter and liberated. Every time I moved to a new flat, I really enjoyed the getting rid process.  It would be great if I could just take one luggage and off I go, without any worries...I just want to close my eyes and when I open them to be settled in a new place with everything in its place... oh yes I can certainly visualise that. * bliss * 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Monday, monday ... 2 more weeks to go and then I am off to Greece for some sunshine!  I have to pack all my things until Sunday evening, that's plenty of time, if I start today after work. Its quite emotional, it's like leaving a life behind. Fortunately its also very exciting...I was my decision to go... and I am sticking with it. The only thing I am going to leave behind its my plants and boyfriend. It's all about decisions and priorities, isn't.  --------------------------------------------------------------- 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, what should I write about?? eh? Its always difficult starting, have too many things in my mind at the moment and there are all over the place. I am trying desperately to put them in some kind of order. Moving is stressful always, and its even worse if you are moving in another country...what a mess. Many things to do in so little time...strange thing time. I don't think I make much sense, but it's not necessary anyway.  I have to remind myself when I go home to phone up those b*st*rds at Air Berlin and try to get my money back. I paid for my ticket 4 months ago and one day they decided to cancel the flight; ok yes, but refund me my money. Oh no, we are terribly sorry, but you have to wait for 3 months to initiate the refund. What! Why! You took my money straight away, u didn't have any problem with that did u? I am so upset with this situation, I can't even sleep at night if I start thinking about it.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since yesterday, I am home alone, everybody had somewhere else to go, except me. I need to be alone and have private time to relax and just be, I can't change that so soon.  I am trying not to get caught in the pace that everyone thinks I should follow. I want to stick to my initial plans, plans that I have been thinking about the last 4-6 months.  I never let myself believe that relocating would be a piece of cake, I kept reminding myself that I would have to adapt to a new way of life and to a culture that although I was born in, I left behind in my early twenties. I am honestly very confident that I will be back on my feet pretty soon. I just have to listen to my inner self  and act accordingly. 
     

    
</post>


<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, I had a class with one of my favourite teachers, she is not a regular teacher (that's why I could never remember her name), but every time she does a different class.     We used the wall a lot in different poses, like the dog pose (Adho Mukha Svanasana), first with the hands on the wall and then turned around and put our heels on the wall. You feel the stretch differently and it doesn't mean that because you use the wall to help you it gets any easier.     One posture that I feel very strange in is Uttanasana, having my back touching the wall, I get a feeling of dizziness and I lose my sense of direction.    Then we moved to supta budha konasana with our backs at the wall and the heels as close to the body as possible, here again the wall keeps you 'honest' and erect. I think using the wall just gives you an idea of how asanas are supposed to feel. It acts as a reminder that keeps you 'truthful' (you cannot cheat) to your practice.    It's really very good to have different teachers and not just one or two, at the moment I have 5 and from each of them I get a different approach. I am just so sad that I will have to leave them so soon.
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday is always a killer, tiredness hits me. -  specially in the head - I have  2 hours to relax before I get to class; looking forward to be in child pose, have a few nice deep breaths and then off to dogpose.  I find that my mood before the class plays a major role in my flexibility in that particular day. So, it's not only the time I spend in class but before as well. I 've read that is very beneficial is you have a lukewarm shower before practicing asanas or pranayama.      
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It wasn't love at first sight,  maybe I don't believe in it , it was something that came from the heart & in time. It was the getting to know process that floorished into a deeper relationship.   I still have a long way to cross in several lives ahead of me, but I am not in a rush. I trust evolution.  I started taking Iyengar yoga lessons in Bristol (Uk), at Yogawest, I was lucky to have such good teachers. My body started moving like never before and together my whole energy field started changing.  I start this blog to express my ups & downs in my effort to become.  Good days are not every day phenomenon in my practice, I have many lows which I try to overcome or just observe and let aside.  Hari Om 
    
</post>


</Blog>