<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Finally I got a look at  urlLink Whidbey Beta 1  and SQL Server 2005 Express Edition Beta 1 over the weekend.   So far I am really impressed with the new products. Even the Express Editions which are available for free while in beta have the most improved features built-in.  Cool things:    new keybindings (they definitely make more sense than the VS.NET 2002/2003 ones. If you don't like them, just change to the old ones)  Tracepoints (right-click -> Breakpoints -> insert Tracepoint): No more Trace.WriteLine when debugging. Extremely cool.  much improved intellisense. No more need for some addIns that ongoingly crash the IDE ...  Visual Studio settings can be exported to and imported from an xml file. No more redundant or registry based hacks when setting up more than one machine.  Many more settings available via the options dialog in the IDE  the MultiLine Property of the WinForms TextBox-Control is automatically set to true when you drag the textbox larger. Cool!    What sucks:    still no intellisense for sql.  Inconsistent Project defaults. SqlServerProjects put AssemblyInfo.cs in the root, not within Properties Directory (like winapps). I think this will be fixed.    Gewöhnungsbedürftig    Partial classes. Cool, but my first reaction was: Where is the damn code? (after adding controls to an asp.net page). Designer generated code goes to a hidden file. MVC!    I like it!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I relocated to Hamburg (largest city in the north of germany) at the beginning of july and on monday the world's largest cruise ship, the Queen Mary 2 from Cunard visited Hamburg for 24hrs. When the ship arrived, several thousand people were at the river Elbe at six o'clock in the morning to watch the ship enter the harbour. During the 24 hour stint almost 400.000 people came to Hamburg to watch the ship. The coolest thing was that it was extremely good wheather (sunny and hot). But after the ship had left, it started to rain almost instantly :-(  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Great BizTalk Blogger Martijn Hoogendoorn has published a  urlLink pipeline component wizard  and there is also the (really helpful)  urlLink Adapter wizard  from Scott Woodgates blog. Makes development for BizTalk 2k4 even more delightful.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Microsoft has published a PDF version of  urlLink Integration Patterns  from their Patterns and Practices Group.  Just gallopped through it but seems worth spending a weekend. Grab it!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I participated in the Microsoft EMEA Security Contest 2004 and made it all the way to the finals in Amsterdam. Eight people (out of several thousand who participated in the Microsoft Security initiative 2004 either by ordering the Microsoft Security DVD or participating in special user group tour events or Microsoft Tech Talks) were invited by Microsoft EMEA to an all expenses paid trip to Amsterdam, including tickets for Tech Ed EMEA 2004, for the Finals. One candidate from South Africa missed the event (visa problems I think) and the seven other candidates came from Ireland (1), Great Britain (2), Germany (2), Austria (1) and Portugal (1) participated in the final round.  The Final, a knock-out quizshow, was filmed in a small TV Studio in Amsterdam on June 28th (the day before the Tech ed began). I made it to the last round but fell against Eamon O’Tuathail (with a score of 4 points vs. 5 points). Unlucky, but it was really a great experience. You can watch the winner's bio at  urlLink here  and be sure not to miss the webcast (live stream with  urlLink 56k ,  urlLink 100k  or  urlLink 300k  WMV format). It is definitely fun watching.  The whole final was done in english and we did not see the questions as in the video.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A few days ago I watched the Blue Man Group live at Berlin, Germany, where they perform "The Complex". I knew only little about the group (almost everything from the intel pentium commercials) and hence I did not know what to expect from the show. But it was extremely cool. The show is a ingenious combination of rock music, light show, very funny and sudden actions which also includes a wobble pudding. The show is definitely worth every penny.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just started working at a new company. Main focus lies on developing EAI solutions with   urlLink BizTalk server 2004  . Nerver used the software before, but it really seems to be pretty easy developing software things like pipeline components or adapters. Microsoft really did a nice job integrating all the tools into VS.net.  The only things that really seems to suck is  Enterprise single sign-on , which seems to offer only command-line tools for configuration. Nice work, M$. The only thing which cannot be administered using graphical tools or wizards is a security feature.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>