<Blog>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    just me&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						                                  RESUME                                                  GEORGE W. BUSH                         1600 Pennsylvania Avenue                          Washington, DC 20520                           EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE Law Enforcement:  I was arrested in Kennebunkport, Maine, in 1976 for driving under the influence of alcohol. I pled guilty, paid a fine, and had my driver's license suspended for 30 days. My Texas driving record has been "lost" and is not available.                                                   Military:  I joined the Texas Air National Guard and went AWOL. I refused to take a drug test or answer any questions about my drug use. By joining the Texas Air National Guard, I was able to avoid combat duty in Vietnam.                                                   College: I graduated from Yale University with a low C average. I was a cheerleader.                                                   PAST WORK EXPERIENCE:                          I ran for U.S. Congress and lost. I began my career in the oil business in Midland,Texas, in 1975.                           I bought an oil company, but couldn't find any oil inTexas. The company went bankrupt shortly after I sold all my stock. Ibought the Texas Rangers baseball team in a sweetheart deal that took land using taxpayer money.                           With the help of my father and our friends in the oil industry (including Enron CEO Ken Lay), I was elected governor of Texas.                                                   ACCOMPLISHMENTS AS GOVERNOR OF TEXAS                          I changed Texas pollution laws to favor power and oil companies, making Texas the most polluted state in the Union. During my tenure, Houston replaced Los Angeles as the most smog-ridden city in America.                           I cut taxes and bankrupted the Texas treasury to the tune of billions in borrowed money.                           I set the record for the most executions by any governor in American history.                           With the help of my brother, the governor of Florida, and my father's appointments to the Supreme Court, I became President after losing by over 500,000 votes.                                                   ACCOMPLISHMENTS AS PRESIDENT:                          I am the first President in U.S. history to enter office with a criminal record.                           I invaded and occupied two countries at a continuing cost of over one billion dollars per week.                           I spent the U.S. surplus and effectively bankrupted the U.S. Treasury.                           I shattered the record for the largest annual deficit in U.S. history.                           I set an economic record for most private bankruptcies filed in any 12-month period.                           I set the all-time record for most foreclosures in a 12-month period.                           I set the all-time record for the biggest drop in the history of the U.S. stock market. In my first year in office, over 2 million Americans lost their jobs and that trend continues every month.                           I'm proud that the members of my cabinet are the richest of any administration in U.S. history. My "poorest millionaire," Condoleeza Rice, has a Chevron oil tanker named after her.                           I set the record for most campaign fund-raising trips by a U.S. President.                           I am the all-time U.S. and world record-holder for receiving the most corporate campaign donations.                           My largest lifetime campaign contributor, and one of my best friends, Kenneth Lay, presided over the largest corporate bankruptcy fraud in U.S. History, Enron.                           My political party used Enron private jets and corporate attorneys to assure my success with the U.S. Supreme Court during my election decision.                           I have protected my friends at Enron and Halliburton against investigation or prosecution. More time and money was spent investigating the Monica Lewinsky affair than has been spent investigating one of the biggest corporate rip- offs in history.                           I presided over the biggest energy crisis in U.S. history and refused to intervene when corruption involving the oil industry was revealed. I presided over the highest gasoline prices in U.S. history.                           I changed the U.S. policy to allow convicted criminals to be awarded government contracts.                           I appointed more convicted criminals to administration than any President in U.S. history.                           I created the Ministry of Homeland Security, the largest bureaucracy in the history of the United States government.                           I've broken more international treaties than any President in U.S. history.                           I am the first President in U.S. history to have the United Nations remove the U.S. from the Human Rights Commission.                           I withdrew the U.S. from the World Court of Law.                           I refused to allow inspector's access to U.S. "prisoners of war" detainees and thereby have refused to abide by the Geneva Convention.                           I am the first President in history to refuse United Nations election inspectors (during the 2002 U.S. election).                           I set the record for fewest numbers of press conferences of any President since the advent of television.                           I set the all-time record for most days on vacation in any one-year period. After taking off the entire month of August, I presided over the worst security failure in U.S. history.                           I garnered the most sympathy for the U.S. after the World Trade Center attacks and less than a year later made the U.S. the most hated country in the world, the largest failure of diplomacy in world history.                           I have set the all-time record for most people worldwide to simultaneously protest me in public venues (15 million people), shattering the record for protests against any person in the history of mankind.                           I am the first President in U.S. history to order an unprovoked, pre-emptive attack and the military occupation of a sovereign nation. I did so against the will of the United Nations, the majority of U.S. citizens, and the world community.                           I have cut health care benefits for war veterans and support a cut in duty benefits for active duty troops and their families -- in wartime.                           In my State of the Union Address, I lied about our reasons for attacking Iraq and then blamed the lies on our British friends.                           I am the first President in history to have a majority of Europeans (71%) view my presidency as the biggest threat to world peace and security.                           I am supporting development of a nuclear "Tactical Bunker Buster," a WMD.                           I have so far failed to fulfill my pledge to bring Osama Bin Laden [sic] to justice.                                                   RECORDS AND REFERENCES:                          All records of my tenure as governor of Texas are now in my father's library, sealed and unavailable for public view.                           All records of SEC investigations into my insider trading and my bankrupt companies are sealedin secrecy and unavailable for public view.                           All records or minutes from meetings that I, or my Vice-President, attended regarding public energypolicy are sealed in secrecy and unavailable for public review.                                       PLEASE CONSIDER MY EXPERIENCE WHEN VOTING IN 2004.                    

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As the Senate voted down the anti-gay Federal Marriage Amendment, leaders in the House of Representatives advanced a bill aimed at reigning in courts on same-sex marriage. Under the measure approved Wednesday by a House panel, the U.S. Supreme Court  and other federal courts would be stripped of jurisdiction over federal legislation that gives states the right to decide whether to recognize same-sex marriages. Specifically, the legislation would prevent federal court challenges to the Defense of Marriage Act, a federal law passed in 1996 that defines marriage as a relationship between a man and a woman and holds that states are not bound to recognize same-sex marriages that might be legally recognized in other states. It never ceases to amaze me, how a group can claim to Hate the sin but not the sinner and yet attempt to Enact legislation to not only cover their inability to Constitutionally Discriminate, but seeks to block challenges on the federal level (Supreme Court), knowing full well its not only Unconstitutional, but just plain wrong. This to me is the Ultimate Act of Homophobia, craven and cowardly. You, authors of this bill, Mr. HOSTETTLER (for himself, Mr. PENCE, Mr. SMITH of Michigan, Mr. GARRETT of New Jersey, Mr. GOODE, Mr. AKIN, Mr. GUTKNECHT, Mr. WELDON of Florida, Mr. JONES of North Carolina, Mr. BARTLETT of Maryland, Mr. FORBES, and Mr. PAUL)  are the Beginnings of the American Taliban. Your names belong on a wall of infamy right next to Adolph Hitler. Never in my life did I believe, another American(s) could be Guilty of such cowardice, ignorance or fear without having first donning their ceremonial sheets. Light the house on fire but make sure you nail the door shut first. Why don't you allow us to register for Licenses and then when we come foreward just put us in the Gas Chamber. You are talking about dictating love, invalidating all other beliefs but your own, and making it impossible for many to have any say whatsoever in their own lives. What's next, public stoning? What is the Honest subtext to all of the current right wing agenda on the floor of Congress right now you may ask?  It isn't homosexual marriage. That is all a front, a smokescreen, to cover the real underlying issue. Separation of Church and State. In the most simple terms, using the bible to run everyone's life. You have the right to worship as you see fit but you must go by this book to live within the law of the US of A. No wonder many Muslim Countries make it a crime to try to convert their people. In trying to save the country, you would make it as oppressive as Iraq under the Hussein regime. You Dishonor all Americans who have fought and DIED to establish the Rights we have in this Nation. Remember Jimmy Swaggart, and Jim Baker? I hope you do because your day will also come, and I will be watching with popcorn and a soda. 

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Political correctness is a joke. By the time you actually get around to the subject of your conversation you have forgotten half of it. I understand not calling someone retarded, (a word even they can understand as bad) and referring to them as Intellectually challenged, or Emotionally challenged, but when does it all end. If a word has negative connections to it, and many do, why must we substitute larger and more precise words that often do not cover the gist of exactly what is perceived as "wrong" with someone else. For example, once in the middle of a conversation with some co-workers a guy mentioned that his supervisor,"was being a Fag". I, knowing both the person who said it (lets call him Cee) and knowing his supervisor, (Andy, sorry I won't change the name of the Guilty,) knew exactly what he was talking about. Andy was,and is today I am sure, Anal retentive, Meticulous on details, but also unaware of the outside effects of his , dry, hostile, way of being. I did not take it to mean he was homosexual, as is one often used negative explicative, but meaning he was, in better terms, useless as a ciggarette butt. Still Cee came back and apologized to me a few minutes later for talking that way in front of me, and he meant no offense.I told him honestly, the fact that without thinking you felt comfortable enough with me to use that word, makes me feel good about myself. I am Gay. I admit it openly. I hold no shame whatsoever in being attracted to another man. While I could have questioned his choice of words I understood his meaning and was not offended. If someone else had overheard and was offended, sorry thats what you get for evesedropping. The real point is that there IS understanding and communication. Sometimes, just sometimes, the old way is best, and most universally understood. As In Bush is an Arrogant Jackass. 

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What is gender? Is it a determination made on primary sexual characteristics (as in having a penis or vagina), or is it genetically determined by chromosomes.  A better question still, is the defense of marriage act going to require all people to be genetically tested in order to validate their marriage? In many Olympic qualifications in addition to being tested for performance enhancing drugs, a test of gender is conducted, regardless of outward sexual characteristics, to insure that the woman (or man) in the event scheduled is qualified to compete as such, a male or female. Some did not pass and were not allowed to compete. This is not saying the person in question was transgendered, and most of those found to be the opposite sex never even had a clue that they were in fact, not who they thought they were, genetically speaking. By those same medical standards, if I (a male) or my mate (also male), were tested and one of us were found to be genetically female, should I/we be legally allowed to marry, regardless of our appearance? If during an exam, a married woman, discover she was actually a male genetically speaking, should her marriage be dissolved, and should the doctor be Legally Obligated to report the findings of the tests?  Perhaps this line of reasoning should be further explored in order to put the debate to an end.  I was taught as a child not to judge by outward appearance, that an ugly person may in fact be a handsome loving individual, and vice versa. In this day with equal rights for both male and female, all races, creeds, ad infinitum, why are so many people worried about what I have in my pants, what I do with it, and with whom? 

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    The U.S. House of Representatives passed on Thursday a rare type of bill that restricts federal courts from hearing challenges from same-sex couples to the Defense of Marriage Act.  The 233-194 vote on the Marriage Protection Act (MPA) comes one week after the Senate defeated a constitutional amendment to ban same-sex couples from marrying. The bill, H.R. 3313, was sponsored by Rep. John Hostettler, R-Ind     Step Up, John Hostettler, and receive your sentence. I cannot believe such a Bigoted, Unconstitutional, and Hate Filled, bill could even be conceived in the United States, much less passed, and you were the author. It is quite obvious to anyone that the 1996 law, was and still is unconstitutional, and now you seek to deny we, the taxpaying, law -abiding, Gay citizens of the United States, the right of due process. Words Cannot express my rage and yes absolute Hate I feel Right now. What's wrong John...did the bad preacherman try to touch your wee wee, John? Did your First Girlfriend leave you for another woman? Are you a member of Fred Phelps congregation?    Worse yet...It passed. I try My best to have faith in my country, but no more. I am sick of being required to pay taxes to support children that I will never have. I am sick of seeing people pass laws based on religious doctrine and force them on others. I am tired of The goverment enforcing monopolies like Microsoft and the RIAA. ENOUGH. I am finished with it all. I want out.    Talk about a Hate Crime... to be driven to give up the country of your birth because of the Religious Bias...yet honestly, what choice do any of us have. Persuit of Happiness my ass.     

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Too funny!! In reading a little email that I have subscribed to for a little fun I found a letter posted in the Paranormal Insider that read,    Dear Sir:  "I have become aware of your newsletter the Paranormal Insider that was forwarded to me by an unknown source. The newsletter in question was about Ouija boards and people who attempt to contact the dead using such devices. I then subscribed to your newsletter so that I could monitor the activities of people such as those reading this publication right now. In some of the issues that followed, you have featured the writings of a woman who contacts her children via ESP, UFO buffs and other such muddle-headed thinking.  "Finally I can keep still no longer. Let me tell you some- thing, those of you who consider yourself psychics, witches or whatever—The United States is founded on one belief system only! If you can't handle that, contact the Founding Fathers during one of your demonic séances. They'll set you straight. Or, better yet, leave the planet with your UFO buddies. Because we are at war, people. We are under attack by outsiders who want to destroy us. Why? Because we represent the truth—and that scares them.  "So, if you want to play your childish paranormal games, go right ahead. I won't stop you. But remember this—while you are messing around with unproven beliefs, the enemy is watching and laughing. Which means you are endangering our way of life. And that makes you unpatriotic.  "This may just be my well-educated opinion, but to tell you the truth, you can take it to the bank."     Sounds like a Job for "Rowan Foxfyre, Bigot Slayer"!!!    I replied to him:    WOW I am amazed. You would think this gentleman (term very loosely used), would be out trying to "kill a commie for mommy", but no his "muddle-headed thinking" has him jumping at every turn. Obviously cowardice prevents him from actually leaving his home, so he tries to "monitor" email for the taint of "the Enemy." He Chatters on about being well educated meaning exactly what, a kindergarten level education in the Constitution, or even a Doctorate from a so called Bible College where facts of history are skewed to fit religious myth? This Country was founded on the theory of Religious Tolerance, the term theory is used to describe the fact that we DO fall short on the practice of the idea. It was also founded on the principles of free speech and thought, the fact that the diversity of our people bring strength and richness to our nation, it doesn't weaken it. If we give up the Real principles and liberties that Honestly Were the Ideas of the True Founders of this Nation, then your "enemy" has already won. It is obvious to me that this person has mistaken Democracy and freedom for Theocracy, a rule style not unlike that of the Taliban, a person who wants to indeed write Discrimination and hatred into the Constitution, with one way to think and believe which at the best is as oppressive as the Regime of Hussein and Hitler, and at the worst, treason. With the Homeland Security Gestapo running throughout this land , locking up people who are "innocent until proven guilty", denying them the RIGHT of due process, he really needs to watch his big YAP, language to the effect of calling people unpatriotic, could be seen as damage to someones reputation and therefore be construed as SLANDER. AS for his comments of,"So, if you want to play your childish paranormal games, go right ahead. I won't stop you." I just laugh. Stop me. Please try. Oh thank you, by the way, I like writing about bigots and narrow minded people in my blog. Rowan Foxfyre    and I thought this was going to be a dull day :-)   

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Listening to the News, hearing the African-American Community calling for people to throw down their guns, and I felt good, until the next sentence that was spoken. "Stop Black on Black crime, " suggest that a criminal should rob or kill others not of their race as if that would be more acceptable. I do understand their concerns but, A call to stop all violence would be far more appropriate, to campaign for a stop of black on black violence, is racist and suggest a concern for only themselves. All life is Holy, your skin color doesn't matter. Either we are a true Community of all ethnic groups, or we are divided. You can't be both. Divided, we Fall.  

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    I read this off the Net about what Reverend Sharpton Had to say, (Paraphrazed)   This is not about a party. It is about living up to the promise of America.  The promise of America says that we will guarantee quality education for all children, and not spend more for metal detectors than computers in our schools.  The promise of America guarantees health care for all of its citizens, and does not force seniors to travel to Canada to buy prescription drugs they cannot afford here.  The promise of America provides that those who work in our health care system can afford to be hospitalized in the very beds that they clean everyday.  The promise of America is government that does not seek to regulate your behavior in the bedroom but to guarantee your right to provide food in the kitchen.  The promise of America is that we stand for human rights - whether it's fighting slavery in Sudan, AIDS in Lesotho, or police brutality in this country.  The promise of America is one immigration policy for all who seek to enter our shores, whether they come from Mexico, Haiti, or Canada.  The promise of America is that every citizen's vote is counted and protected, and election schemes do not decide elections.  I often hear the Republican party preach about family values, but I can tell them something about family values. Family values don't just exist for those with two-car garages and retirement plans. Family values exist in homes with only one parent in the household making a way against the odds.  I stand here tonight, the product of a single parent home, from the depths of Brooklyn, New York. My mother was a domestic worker who scrubbed floors in other people's homes for me. And because she scrubbed those floors, I was proud to stand as a presidential candidate.  Those are family values.  I recall that a few days after the September 11 terrorist attacks I was in a radio station that played "America the Beautiful," as sung by Ray Charles.  As you know, we lost Ray several weeks ago, but I can still hear him singing: "Oh beautiful for spacious skies, for amber waves of grain, for purple mountains majesty, above the fruited plain."  We must leave here committed to making Ray Charles' song a reality and to making America beautiful for everyone.   These are words from Al Sharptons Speech to the Democratic convention. While I may Not always agree with Reverend Sharpton, It does seem like he is on the right Track.    Maybe there is some Hope, That the True Americans may Yet wake up and do the Right Thing.  Vote the Bigot and Liar in Chief Out of Office and into a War Crimes Tribunal where He belongs, he should be a cellmate of Saddam. I think they might get Married.....  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    This was found on the 'net  YOU WILL RECEIVE A BODY... You may like it or hate it, but it will be yours for the entire period you're around.  YOU WILL LEARN LESSONS... You are enrolled in a full-time informal school called life. Each day in this school you will have the opportunity to learn lessons. You may like the lessons or think them irrelevant and stupid.  THERE ARE NO MISTAKES, ONLY LESSONS... Growth is a process of trial and error, experimentation. The "Failed" experiments are as much a part of the process as the experiment that ultimately "works".  A LESSON IS REPEATED UNTIL LEARNED... A lesson will be presented to you in various forms until you have learned it. When you have learned it, you can then go on to the next lesson.  LEARNING LESSONS DOES NOT END... There is no part of life that does not contain its lessons. If you are alive, there are lessons to be learned.  "THERE" IS NO BETTER THAN "HERE"... When your "There" has become a "Here", you will simply obtain another "There" that will, again, look better than "Here".  OTHERS ARE MERELY MIRRORS OF YOU... You cannot love or hate something about another person unless it reflects to you something you love or hate about yourself.  WHAT YOU MAKE OF YOUR LIFE IS UP TO YOU... You have all the tools and resources you need. What you do with them is up to you. The choice is yours.  YOUR ANSWERS LIE INSIDE YOU... The answers to life's questions lie inside you. All you need to do is look, listen and trust.  YOU WILL FORGET ALL THIS... Unless you consistently stay focused on the goals you have set for yourself, everything you've just read won't mean a thing.  

						
</post>


</Blog>