<Blog>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to the Science Foundations blog. This is your online 24/7 source for everything you need to know about our class - just as a reminder, since I know everyone always comes to class and gets the info first hand. :-) You might also learn a little about blogging, too, if you're unfamiliar. There are some great discussions on the blogging phenomenon on www.blogger.com/knowledge/.  Check this blog each and every time you have a question about our class. All the information you need to know will be posted here, so you can check it at any time. You can also use the Comment functionality to ask questions of me or your classmates, make comments (of course), or snide remarks, although I'd like to keep these to bare a minimum. :-)  So bookmark this site and visit often! Cheers,
    
</post>


<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      County fair food makes me feel a little sick. But I guess it's worth it. As a friend said, you can't very well start fall without having a funnel cake and a lemon shake up. I think she's right. Denny Hastert was at the little auction, he bought a pig from one of the 4H'ers. He wore a faded red polo shirt and just blended in with all the other farmers there. I only noticed one body guard with an earpiece. There was a demolition derby, where five beat up old cars ran into eachother in the mud until most of them stopped running. And the beef producers' booth and the pork producers' booth, always busy, always yummy. The moon was full last night, and starting to wane tonight, beautiful and bright in the clear night sky, tinged a bit orange while it lingers near the horizon over the trees.
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So the car that I bought yesterday is in the shop now. Grrrrr. The parking brake is stuck. And of course there's no one to fix it until Monday. How aggravating is that! I thought I was all squared away with a reliable car for once in my life, but no, it's got to go back in the shop less than 24 hours after I drive it off the lot. Better be the last thing wrong with it for a very long time. Well, at least I know it wasn't just that I forgot how to drive a stick. I /thought/ I was having to give it way too much gas to get going. So for the second year in a row, I've missed the Barnes' get together up at the lake. This is an improvement over last year, however, when Patrick and I were in the ER. Funny story, I'll tell you about it sometime. The year before that we got a flat tire, but did eventually make it to the lake. Well, seems like we're not fated to get there. Sometimes it's nice to have a quiet evening at home, though. So I took a nap instead of driving to Wisconsin. Much more restful. And Mom is fond of saying things like, perhaps it prevented us from being involved in a firey wreck. And when you look at it like that, it doesn't seem like such a bad deal.
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, really, I've got the new car now. Yay! Also went yesterday to see  the opening of Domestic Tranquility over in Clinton, at the theatre  where Patrick is working. Pretty funny show. Had a good time. Miss  Patrick now I am home alone again. Patrick got blue flames painted  (decaled?) on his car today, he likes them very much, I haven't seen  them, had to leave before they were done. Only killed the new car twice  today, still getting used to where the clutch catches. Too tired to  write any more, more later.  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An absolutely lovable 2003 Subaru Forester, manual transmission, gold. Have to wait for the money issue to resolve, can't wait to pick it up! I have no wish to deal with a car salesperson ever again. Hopefully I can keep this car another ten years before I have to. It's been a long day, definitely time for sleep. Had some spectacular storms in the area today, oh, and the new car has weather radio built right in! So cool.
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I don't have one yet. Unfortunately, I had to go out looking by myself, and I think my gender attracts high prices. I threw out a low number and left. We'll see if they'll budge later. Meanwhile, found 3 other cars I'm going to look at tomorrow. All of them are cheaper, I just have to decide whether I can live without the heated seats. Mmm, heated seats... 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went shopping today (eek) with a friend who is pregnant. I never saw someone talk to their belly so much. :-) I mean, sometimes I talk to my belly but only if I'm hungry or really full, mostly. We found out there is no actual Crate & Barrel in Naperville, only the outlet store, and we got lost around downtown Naperville for a while, but we finally found the other store she was looking for and actually made a purchase, so it was a successful trip after all. Afterwards went over to the show choir rehearsal going on at the high school. Grabbed a cd that Patrick needs to choreograph the other song they will learn next week, and helped them clean up the one they're working on now. They are hard working kids. Managed to offload some cake on Mom and Grandma and Grandpa. They seemed to like it. So the majority of it is gone now, yay. Still thinking about that car...
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sarah came over to visit today, a friend from UIUC Geology. She is still there trying to finish her masters, or as she puts it, either finishing or killing her advisor, either one would do the job, and I understand completely. :-) We chatted for a while, then went out to the grocery store and got things for dinner and dessert making. We split a $3 steak that was really good grilled, and I made up a sort of au pauvre sauce for it, awesome. Had some taters too. And we made a lemon zest yellow cake with cream cheese frosting that is so delicious! Sarah took home some pieces but I still have lots left, so come over and have some, I can't eat it all. So after we stuffed ourselves good and proper, we went out for a walk around the "lake", or detention pond. It's pretty big, I guess you could call it a lake. They have planted some baby willows around it, they will be nice when they are bigger. There are lots of wildflowers all over the banks, too, and we walked back up along the creek side. It was pretty warm and humid, but not too bad. No mosquitos at all, very nice. Sarah is going with her family to Hawaii tomorrow for two weeks vacation, should be a neat-o trip. She promised to bring me some basalt, and I gave her the rock she requested from Australia. Other than that, missing Patrick and wishing he was done with his shows.
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I started thinking about getting a car, since I have this job and all. And car insurance is scary. Does anyone know a good website that explains car insurance? Please advise. But other than that, Mom and I had a nice drive south of Yorkville hunting for a stone barn that her friend had told her about. It is, of course, now owned by people who want to "develop" that land and tear down the cool old barn and build a subdivision all over the beautiful rolling countryside. Mom will try to paint it quick before they tear it down. It must date to the 1830's or so. The house on the property is neat, too, it has limestone hitching posts and getting-on-your-horse stairs. Mom stopped to talk to a local farmer who was mowing and he told her all about it. He seemed to think Denny Hastert is in the group that owns the place now, and is gunning for development. Politicians suck. But anyway, Mom got some good pictures to paint from, but really she wants to go back for the "morning light", and I got some nice pictures to share with all of you, once I buy more storage. But again, putting that off till August (paycheck time). Well, probably September will be paycheck time, but my free .mac trial ends before that so I will have to bite the bullet.
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a job today. A sort of real job. I'll teach one class at Aurora University, called Science Foundations. So for the first time since I deposited my thesis in December I'll actually be in charge of something. And actually have a boss. But I'm not sure who that is. But, most importantly, I'll have a regular, albeit small, paycheck. I really liked the dean who interviewed me, and I think she really liked me. I just hope I can keep up the energy I showed off in the interview. Hopefully with only one class, I'll be able to do it. Well, better be off to bed now. I'll try to dream up some good lectures. Mmm, science...
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Visit my photo albums on the web  urlLink here . As explained  there, only the Australia photos are up now till I can buy more  storage. Hopefully by August, so check back.
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mmm... polish sausage and pasta. Half of it's low carb, right? ;-) Goes well with Baz Luhrmann works. Ah, the subtle science and exact art that is... cooking? At least my cooking doesn't usually go all glowy green or explode. Usually. What is it that a mind possesses to look 12 moves ahead in chess and be able to predict what a certain combination of ingredients will taste like? My brain doesn't do that. Or, moreso, be able to say, this food needs _____ to taste better. I just know it tastes bad.   Aux Italiens Edward Robert Bulwer-Lytton, 1st earl of Lytton (1831–91)  AT Paris it was, at the Opera there;—    And she look’d like a queen in a book, that night,  With the wreath of pearl in her raven hair,    And the brooch on her breast, so bright.     Of all the operas that Verdi wrote,         5    The best, to my taste, is the Trovatore;  And Mario can soothe with a tenor note    The souls in Purgatory.     The moon on the tower slept soft as snow:    And who was not thrill’d in the strangest way,         10  As we heard him sing, while the gas burn’d low,    “Non ti scordar di me”?     The Emperor there, in his box of state,    Look’d grave, as if he had just then seen  The red flag wave from the city-gate         15    Where his eagles in bronze had been.     The Empress, too, had a tear in her eye.    You ’d have said that her fancy had gone back again,  For one moment, under the old blue sky,    To the old glad life in Spain.         20     Well! there in our front-row box we sat,    Together, my bride-betroth’d and I;  My gaze was fix’d on my opera-hat,    And hers on the stage hard by.     And both were silent, and both were sad.         25    Like a queen she lean’d on her full white arm,  With that regal, indolent air she had;    So confident of her charm!     I have not a doubt she was thinking then    Of her former lord, good soul that he was!         30  Who died the richest and roundest of men,    The Marquis of Carabas.     I hope that, to get to the kingdom of heaven,    Through a needle’s eye he had not to pass.  I wish him well, for the jointure given         35    To my lady of Carabas.     Meanwhile, I was thinking of my first love,    As I had not been thinking of aught for years,  Till over my eyes there began to move    Something that felt like tears.         40     I thought of the dress that she wore last time,    When we stood, ’neath the cypress-trees, together,  In that lost land, in that soft clime,    In the crimson evening weather;     Of that muslin dress (for the eve was hot),         45    And her warm white neck in its golden chain,  And her full, soft hair, just tied in a knot,    And falling loose again;     And the jasmine-flower in her fair young breast,    (O the faint, sweet smell of that jasmine-flower!)         50  And the one bird singing alone to his nest,    And the one star over the tower.     I thought of our little quarrels and strife,    And the letter that brought me back my ring.  And it all seem’d then, in the waste of life,         55    Such a very little thing!     For I thought of her grave below the hill,    Which the sentinel cypress-tree stands over;  And I thought … “were she only living still,    How I could forgive her, and love her!”         60     And I swear, as I thought of her thus, in that hour,    And of how, after all, old things were best,  That I smelt the smell of that jasmine-flower    Which she used to wear in her breast.     It smelt so faint, and it smelt so sweet,         65    It made me creep, and it made me cold!  Like the scent that steals from the crumbling sheet    Where a mummy is half unroll’d.     And I turn’d, and look’d. She was sitting there    In a dim box, over the stage; and dress’d         70  In that muslin dress with that full soft hair,    And that jasmine in her breast!     I was here; and she was there;    And the glittering horseshoe curv’d between:—  From my bride-betroth’d, with her raven hair,         75    And her sumptuous scornful mien,     To my early love, with her eyes downcast,    And over her primrose face the shade  (In short from the Future back to the Past),    There was but a step to be made.         80     To my early love from my future bride    One moment I look’d. Then I stole to the door,  I travers’d the passage; and down at her side    I was sitting, a moment more.     My thinking of her, or the music’s strain,         85    Or something which never will be exprest,  Had brought her back from the grave again,    With the jasmine in her breast.     She is not dead, and she is not wed!    But she loves me now, and she lov’d me then!         90  And the very first word that her sweet lips said,    My heart grew youthful again.     The Marchioness there, of Carabas,    She is wealthy, and young, and handsome still,  And but for her … well, we ’ll let that pass,         95    She may marry whomever she will.     But I will marry my own first love,    With her primrose face: for old things are best,  And the flower in her bosom, I prize it above    The brooch in my lady’s breast.         100     The world is fill’d with folly and sin,    And Love must cling where it can, I say:  For Beauty is easy enough to win;    But one is n’t lov’d every day.     And I think, in the lives of most women and men,         105    There ’s a moment when all would go smooth and even,  If only the dead could find out when    To come back, and be forgiven.     But O the smell of that jasmine-flower!    And O that music! and O the way         110  That voice rang out from the donjon tower,    Non ti scordar di me,      Non ti scordar di me!
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's truly amazing how you can spend an entire day, first hearing about blogger, researching blogger, then getting an account on blogger and writing a post. It's dinner time now, so I suppose I should stop blogging and eat. Mmm pork roast...
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Someone tell me why it's 65F in August. That's global warming for you. Hey, this is cool:  urlLink the latest Mars news . Do you ever get the feeling that  it's starting ? For example,  urlLink this article  on human hibernation for use during space flight. Well, now to clear some space for yoga.
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm over in Clinton, Patrick's at rehearsal. I came over to surprise him last night on opening night, he was glad.  A Funny Thing Happened On The Way To The Forum  is  very  funny indeed. Patrick is playing Hysterium, the slave in chief who tries to hold all the antics under wraps, and doesn't succeed, but does succeed in being hilarious. Everyone else did a great job too. It is fun in such a small space. Wish everyone could come see it, but most of the people I know live two hours away (or a lot more) and aren't really interested in driving that far for theatre. Oh well, I enjoy it.  Got an offer to do a PhD in Australia on Tongan arc basalt chemistry, but wait I hate academia. So I'm trying to figure out if I want to do that. The project sounds so cool, but probably not enough to dedicate several years of my life too...? In the wise words of Bender: "Arr, science be a harsh mistress." Why must learning be so seductive?
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Their titan arms churn the thin air, purposefully, steadily. They stand gleaming white, smooth, and thin in the pale sun. Tall, incredibly tall. The power lines towering above me shrink to a parade of marching ants as they wind their way unnoticed below the herd of stationary giants, intent on their work as they stand watch on the hill.
    
</post>


</Blog>