<Blog>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight is Wisdom's Folly's first show. Wisdom's Folly is the band I play drums in. I'm&nbsp; a little nervous about a few of the songs, especially #28 (the instrumental) where I play guitar and Alonzo plays the drums. I'm more worried about the crowd though. I don't know if we could have gotten a worst time to play. I know it's our first show and we have to prove ourselves, but I don't think anyone would show up for an established band at midnight on a Tuesday much less a brand new one. Oh well, I guess you have to start somewhere. I just hope their are some people there. I'm praying now that the other two guys in the band get saved and then we could become a Chrsitian band or at least Christians in a band. I told the Lord it's up to Him whether I stay in this band or not. I just want to see them happy even if that means the band breaking up.  
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another day at work. I'm really glad I have the internet at work. I feel God leading me to stay in touch with people and get in touch with people. I'm really bad about not staying touch. I especially need to try and stay in touch with my family. I miss them alot and hope that one day The Lord brings them or me closer to each other. I never get to see them living 8 hours away.  
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel much better today! Of course I did eat cheesecake for breakfast. I practiced my songs last night, and I think I am going to try and make a demo this week to send to Ray.&nbsp; I hate when&nbsp;I get in the mood to write and I am at work. I always say&nbsp;I am going to start carrying a tape recorder but I never do.&nbsp; I can't wait until school starts, it's my first semester. I hope to meet some musicians and get something going. I like being solo but sometimes I need to feed off others. Wow, that sounded cannibalistic.  
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another day....................anotehr day........................another day.....................death..........etc. That's what I am thinking about. I need to do something significant. Please God show me the impact of my life.  
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I didn't write a song yesterday. I ended up sleeping for five hours. I was a little disappointed in myself but it was much needed rest. I don't know why I said that anyways, I usually can't make myself write a song. I have been writing for the band I play drums in though. It's a good thing too because I just can't get into what the singer writes. I wish I didn't have to work tonight so I could work on some music. I have an idea for a rap but I need some beats first. I've always wanted to write a rap song but never had a good idea for one.&nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today is like any other day. Early morning, short work, and alot of daydreaming. Today I decided to start this journal. I hope to use this to remind myself of what I would like to do with my life. I don't want to spend my whole life dreaming. I am starting to put together my ideas for an album. I need to make a real effort to record and talk to Eric about some distribution. I am going to write a song today.   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now I know why I never have been able to keep a journal. Consistency is a difficult thing to be consistent with. I am trying so hard to motivate myself to work on my music. Of course time is an ever eluding thing. I'm really tired of having to spend time practicing for Wisdom's Folly! I don't even enjoy playing the music and then the fact that I don't really enjoy being around the two other guys makes it even more trying. I made a commitment though and I plan to keep it as long as I have to. I have made some good contacts recently though. I have possibly found someone to record my stuff for cheap and at my house. 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, Wisdom's Folly made it through the first show. Their weren't masses of people gathered to hear us, but some showed up and they all seemed to enjoy themselves. The owner of the club liked us and wants us to come back so that is good. We should be going in the studio soon, I'm excited about that. I've been thinking alot about my own music though. I may talk to Mark at the studio and see about recording some of my stuff. I can't decide what exactly I want to record. I wish I had someone to collaborate with.   
    
</post>


</Blog>