<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I found some lovely decorative additions to my amoebic looking torso yesterday.&nbsp; Stretch marks.&nbsp; STRETCH MARKS!&nbsp; Or for to sound more scientific, striae.&nbsp; Just what I need for the good ole' self esteem.&nbsp; Now I share the same physical attributes with pregnant women.&nbsp; Great.&nbsp; If reduction of love handles means I get to adorn these ridiculous looking things, I need to start getting back onto a steady diet of pure fat and carbohydrates to stretch these monstrosities back out.&nbsp; I remember an exgirlfriend of mine had them on her breasts, and remorsefully I thought they were rather funny looking.&nbsp; I guess God heard me, he has such a twisted sense of humor.&nbsp; If anyone wants to see them, the price is $5.   After staring at my new stretch marks yesterday while resisting the urge to dive out my window, I headed to the YMCA.&nbsp; Not much of a story to tell here, except while I was lifting weights.&nbsp; I was doing dumb bell presses in the weight room, and when I finished one set, rather than resting them one at a time on either side of me, I just dropped them both.&nbsp; Not only did it make a loud pop, but one landed right on my water bottle, crushing the end of it and launching a stream of water one quarter of the way across the weight room.&nbsp; I was a little embarrassed by this and immediately looked around to see if anyone noticed.&nbsp; The only person who did was a retarded man whose handler left him working on the cables.&nbsp; So I figured, "Well that's okay, he's retarded.&nbsp; All I have to do is make a silly face at him and go 'Whoops!', and give the guy a little giggle."&nbsp; Nope.&nbsp; He just looked at me with this look of disappointment, like he was thinking to himself, "Now that guy's retarded."&nbsp;Do you ever get the idea that retarded people have some kind of extrasensory abilities, like a sixth&nbsp;sense?&nbsp; I do.&nbsp; Something in the way they look at you, like they can read minds or have the&nbsp;ability to see into your future.&nbsp; I'm such an ass.   Last night I watched the History of Torture, on the History channel.&nbsp; I was glued to&nbsp;the&nbsp;television for the entire two hours it was on.&nbsp; Gave me a bunch of great ideas for a children's book.&nbsp; One&nbsp;method I found particularly amusing was,  urlLink "the pear" .&nbsp; Here's a pretty good&nbsp;description I took off of some website:   " The pear had more than one implementation, with the most popular being the oral use. The pear was also used in the rectum and in the vagina. The pear was expanded by force of the screw to the maximum aperture of their segments. The inside of the cavity in question is irremediably mutilated, nearly always fatally so. The pointed prongs at the end of the segments serve better to rip into the throat or the intestines. When applied vaginally, the spikes wreaked havoc on the woman's cervix. The vaginal use was devised for women who had been found guilty of sexual union with the Devil or his familiars. &nbsp;"   That sounds like fun.&nbsp; My question is, why aren't we&nbsp;using shit like that today,&nbsp;on Al Qaeda detainees?&nbsp; I don't care how strong your faith in Allah is,&nbsp;some sticks the pear up your ass, YOU ARE TALKING.&nbsp; If I was a&nbsp;Muslim I would gladly&nbsp;eat ten pounds of Canadian bacon if it would keep me from having&nbsp;that thing jammed up my pooper.&nbsp; I read in the news that we just captured some high ranking Al&nbsp;Qaeda operative&nbsp;the other day.&nbsp; He was on the most wanted terrorist list and allegedly was involved in the Tanzania embassy bombing.&nbsp; I think he needs to be introduced to the pear.&nbsp; Sadly, there's liberal pussies out there who would probably deem this "cruel and unusual".&nbsp; I mean, these guys kill&nbsp;innocent&nbsp;people for a living, but  they &nbsp;have rights.&nbsp; Thanks to some left wingers, we can't even use water boarding anymore.&nbsp; What is the world coming to?&nbsp; What are the approved&nbsp;interrogation methods?&nbsp; Forcing a person to stand&nbsp;up for no more&nbsp;than four hours and having a&nbsp;dog bark at them?&nbsp; Before you know it the only approved interrogation method will be tickling.&nbsp; Bring on the pear, I say!     &nbsp;        

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   (So here's last Thursday nights escapade in it's entirety.&nbsp; I did finish it last friday but got distracted and left the computer and when I got back my session expired and logged me off, pissing away everything I just typed.&nbsp; That and I've just been insanely busy at work.&nbsp; Enjoy)  So I live alone now as much of know.&nbsp; I came to that decision some time ago when I got tired having to live in other peoples filth.&nbsp; Now I just live in my own and that's the way I like it.&nbsp; It also gives me the opportunity to walk around my apartment naked without having to hear someone whine about it and feel the need to call a house meeting.&nbsp; Most of the time I find it very peaceful and satisfactory, except when the occasional bouts of cabin fever set in.&nbsp; Last night was one of those nights.   I was feeling pretty tired from work and just decided to chill out for the evening.&nbsp; The landlords had me down for dinner which was very pleasant, except for the fact that the meat loaf we ate gave me some fierce indigestion.&nbsp; That and I had to sit and listen to my landlord tell me how she&nbsp;wants to set me up were her friend's daughter.&nbsp; "She's really sweet and I think she'd be perfect for you."&nbsp; Why do I have the sneaky suspicion that "perfect for me" includes a permanent limp and a lazy eye?.&nbsp; Anyway, I retired upstairs for the night, fiddled with my guitar like a monkey with autism, and decided to watch the tube.&nbsp; I flipped a coin between WWE Smackdown and HBO, and HBO won.&nbsp; I later wished I had gone with the half naked men in tights.&nbsp; HBO was showing The Tuxedo, with Jackie Chan, which didn't surprise me in the least because for the last month it seems HBO has been alternating this movie and the Medallion every other friggin night and it pisses me off.&nbsp; Jackie's such a lovable, happy guy, and I bet he'd be really, REALLY fun to snort meth with and pick up hookers....And then get him to do karate on the hookers, but his movies really suck.&nbsp; Jennifer Love Hewitt was in it as well, who I can't abide in films either, she stinks.&nbsp; Don't get&nbsp;me wrong, I'd gladly let her sit on my face until my feet turn blue, but watching her jump around with Jackie Chan trying to be funny&nbsp;made me want to burn my eyes out with a sodering iron.&nbsp; So after sitting through 30 minutes of the movie in complete emotional paralysis, I&nbsp;felt that restless feeling come over me.&nbsp; &nbsp;So I got dressed and decided to go out and grab a few beers.   I ended up at C.C. O'Briens in Pawcatuk.&nbsp; Sat at the bar and watched the Sox highlights, chitchatted with the bartender a little and some little league coach who was at the bar.&nbsp; There were a bunch of young lovely females there, some with other ladies, some with men.&nbsp; Naturally I didn't talk to any of them.&nbsp; I am the Rainman of pickup artists when it comes to meeting women at bars.&nbsp; I've crashed and burned like the Challenger on many attempts that I generally chicken out because I know something stupid is going to come out of my mouth.&nbsp; When I'm alone it's worse because I got no support group to fall back on when I fuck up.&nbsp; Go up to girl and say some shit like, "Hiya doing?&nbsp; I'm Mike.......and I like.....spaghetti!&nbsp; I saw you sitting over here and couldn't help but wonder if you need your ears swabbed."&nbsp; The only followup to something like that would be to start giggling erratically while scratching myself like a meth addict in need of a fix, and then run out of the bar as fast as I can.&nbsp; So I sat and thought, "where's a place I can go where I know I can confidently talk to women?"&nbsp; So, I decided to go to a strip club.   I ended up at Silk Stockings on Route 12 in Groton.&nbsp; I'd rate it about a 5 on the strip club scale.&nbsp; I particularly enjoy it because it's cheap.&nbsp; There was only a $5 cover and the drinks were fairly priced.&nbsp; But like all things in America, you get what you pay for, so the selection of good looking dancers there was very thin.&nbsp; The lighting also sucked as well.&nbsp; I may seem a little anal, but I believe ambience is very important in a gentlemans club (I use that term loosely in this case).&nbsp; You can't have it too bright, because nothing ruins a table dance more than when you have to stare at some strippers acne and stretch marks.&nbsp; This place is the exact opposite, it was too dark.&nbsp; I was sitting at one end of the stage, the stripper was riding a pole at the other and I couldn't tell if she was black or white, woman or man, or transexual for that matter.&nbsp; So once I get my vision adapted, I start viewing my options for possible lap dances.&nbsp; One thing that just pisses me off at strip clubs is strippers asking me if I'd like them to give me a lap dances.&nbsp; This one no word of a lie asked me three times.&nbsp; I politely said no thank you each time but her persistance really bugged me.&nbsp; And she was a pretty big girl, junk in the trunk type.&nbsp; Had I said yes to her I probably would need a full hip replacement.&nbsp; I was at the stage watching her earlier.&nbsp; She bent over in front of me and for a second I didn't know if I was at a strip clup or getting ready to embark on a spelunking expedition.&nbsp; I&nbsp;fired up my miners helmet and everything.&nbsp; At one point she asked if I was ready to let her "rub that nipple".&nbsp; How about when you start laying off the bovine growth hormones, you nightmare in a g-string.&nbsp; I wanted to offer her $20 just to stop talking to me.&nbsp; Then I started to feel bad because I noticed her propositioning other guys and they all turned her down.&nbsp; It was a pretty pathetic site to behold.&nbsp; I decided sometime I'll have a canned ham sent to her so she can feed herself and presumably fatherless kids.&nbsp; So after careful consideration and interviewing, I finally found my girl.&nbsp; A sweet looking brunette who couldn't have been a day older than 19.&nbsp; Yes sir, starting life out on the right track indeed.&nbsp; She was absolutely beautiful, which ended up being the problem.&nbsp; I had gotten there so late that her schedule was pretty much booked for the rest of the night.&nbsp; She was the best looking girl in the place, so it didn't suprise me.&nbsp; So I set my sights a little lower, and I decided on Mystic (or Mistic, however she spells it).&nbsp; She did her act with glasses on, which gave her a little bit of Van Halen, "Hot For Teacher" appeal to her.&nbsp; She also had a metal stud protruding from her lip and corn rows.&nbsp; You take the good with the bad.&nbsp; So we were ready to go, just had to take a leak first.&nbsp; The bathroom was awful, and I pitty any poor fool that would actually decide to shit there.&nbsp; The stench was unbearable.&nbsp; It made me think that this is what my balls would smell like after a long bike ride if I smeared vinager all over them.&nbsp; Eeeech!&nbsp; So we started the lap dance, and engaged in idle stripper/spooky guy conversation.&nbsp; She asked me my name, to which I replied Lance.&nbsp; She didn't believe me, which was very astute of her.&nbsp; I said, yeah, well your name's not Mistic either so I'm going to take the same route, now continue bucking.&nbsp; At one point I had to tell her to slow down before before either she got whiplash or I ended up with a broken dick.&nbsp; And, at the conclusion of whatever Nelly song was playing at the time, or session was up.&nbsp; I was fullfilled, so I weeble-wobbled back to my car and headed home.&nbsp;  I made sure to stop at Taco Bell on the way home and order some nachos (no wonder I still have a fat neck and ugly abdomen).&nbsp; I got home and flipped on the tv, ready to revel in my nachos and success of he evening, and what is on HBO....The Medallion, starring Jackie Chan.&nbsp; What do I have to do to get away from this guy?            

						
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I suppose everyone has heard by now that over the weekend that California Governor Ahhhnold Schwartzenegger, addressed an L.A. mall crowd and called the state's Democratic leaders, "girlie men", for skirting budget issues and catering to special interest groups.&nbsp; So in a typical liberalist response, the Dems resorted to the usual biparitisan school yard finger pointing an whining which has become one of the building blocks for my loathing of politics these days.&nbsp; After Arnie made the comment the Democrats jumped all over him, calling him a sexist and resorting to "blantant homophobia" to muster support.&nbsp; The Schwartzenegger camp has gone public and said it has no plans to issue an apology.&nbsp; And why should they?&nbsp; If the Democrats are going waste oxygen bitching about this, then they're just proving his point.&nbsp; And saying the phrase "girlie men" is sexist and homophobic is sooooo over the top, even for Liberal ideals.&nbsp; Now if he called the Democrats "Cock Goblins", "Ass Pirates", or "Limp-wristed Faggots", OK, there you would have grounds for calling Arnie a homophobe.&nbsp;&nbsp;Now they're just skirting the issues which they've been accused of skirting even more by&nbsp;embarking on fantasy crusade against what they consider hate speech.   It's very hard for myself to categorize myself as being either liberal or conservative, as I agree with some of the ideaologies of both.&nbsp; I guess in that sense I'd be thought of as a third party voter.&nbsp; I would say that a lot of my own beliefs are more shifted to the left, though, rather than the right.&nbsp; But extreme leftists annoy the diarrhea out of me so much more than the extreme right, and I'll tell you why.&nbsp; With conservatives you always know what you're going to get.&nbsp; For the most part they're a bunch stiff, humorless jerkoffs who disagree with anyone who's ideas are remotely different from their own, always blindly following their party's leadership without blinking an eye.&nbsp; If George Bush did his State of the Union address doing the Jim Carrey talking asshole impression from Ace Ventura, and declared himself the new king of Iraq, Ann Coulter would be on Larry King Live the next night praising the President for doing what's best for America while screaming Bill Clinton is an unpatriotic traitor.&nbsp; But who would&nbsp;honestly&nbsp;be suprised by that?   Liberals are supposed the ones out there that are all for&nbsp;progressive change for the betterment of society, and to uphold the principals&nbsp;that make this country great, like the freedom of speech.&nbsp; A lot of times though they use the freedom&nbsp;of speech as a double edged sword to hide behind.&nbsp; They're fully behind the freedom of speech, as long as it adheres to their own ideas.&nbsp; If you convey a belief that's contrary to theirs in the slightest, you're labeled a sexist, or&nbsp;a racist, or a homophobic, or you're arrogant.&nbsp; They end up sounding just like the same authoratarian politics that they hated so much when they were kids.&nbsp; I think they can be so contradictory as well.&nbsp; Take PeTA for example, who I just want to  annihilate .&nbsp; They are a&nbsp;group which I absolutely despise, not for their cause, but for there extremest, irrational, bullying tactics they use to try to force others to conform to their beliefs.&nbsp; I'd be willing to bet that about 80 to 90 percent of their members consider themselves Pro-Choice (which just for the record, I am too).&nbsp; What makes me honestly angry about that is here's a bunch of people that are saying that abortion is okay, but eating a cheeseburger while modeling leather pants is wrong.&nbsp; To me that's as prepostorous as watching a gang bang film which all the men that are involved in it are wearing contraceptives.&nbsp; It doesn't make sense!&nbsp; But that's just me.   Uggghhh....I know my political knowledge in reality absolutely sucks, and if anyone with a real solid grasp of the subject were to debate me on this they would proabably kick my ass.&nbsp; After all, it took me about 2 hours to gather these thoughts together so I didn't sound like a complete and utter retard.&nbsp; Ahh, retard.&nbsp; Such a fun word.&nbsp; It makes me sad to know that at the rate this country's going, my children will never know the joy of being able to use that word against an inferior classmate without threat of persecution.&nbsp; Tis troubled times we live in.   On a more health conscience note, here's the  urlLink greatest thing since the Supersized Value Meal .         

						
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, Monday has come and gone, with no HR meeting or any other mention of the coffee-slappy incident.&nbsp; I think the whole thing was just a ruse, which kind of pisses me off because I was extremely pissed about the whole thing and was ready to go into yesterday with both barrells loaded.&nbsp; Now it seems I just got riled up over nothing.&nbsp; One thing's for sure, they all should consider themselves lucky they didn't discover the true nature of  urlLink my rage .&nbsp; Anyway, sorry to disappoint some of you people.&nbsp; I know you were looking foreward to an exciting conclusion to this debacle, complete with ethinic slurs, tears, and scarred careers.....but what can I tell you?&nbsp; I could just start a new office identity as "that angry guy who's always slapping things out of peoples hands."  &nbsp;  It's actually a good thing I didn't have that meeting yesterday, because it gave me ample time during the day to complete my performance self evaluation.&nbsp; This is that thing that&nbsp;was about 6 months overdue that had me all in a tizzy last week.&nbsp; I&nbsp;did plan on doing it on&nbsp;Sunday afternoon, but I got distracted.&nbsp; It was raining and my internet was down, so....I bought a new porno dvd (which I'll cover&nbsp;at a&nbsp;another time).&nbsp; Anyway, the corporate office emailed&nbsp;the evaluation form&nbsp;to my boss here, who maybe took a half a glance at it and then handed it back to me and said, "OK, you fill it out, I'll comment on it."&nbsp; Great.....more work.&nbsp; You know, most people would probably say they'd love to do a self-evaluation, as who wouldn't want to write a review of themself.&nbsp; Not me.&nbsp; For some reason I'm  terrible  at it.&nbsp; I seem to be much better at self-deprecating myself on a blog.&nbsp; Life would be so much&nbsp;easier&nbsp;if I didn't get fired from my circus geek&nbsp;job.&nbsp; But I did take advantage of the opportunity to make myself seem important and really put those 10th grade creative writing skills to work.&nbsp; I used phrases like, "timely and effective", "clear and concise", and "shown superb ability in self-management and multitasking".&nbsp; Oh!&nbsp; I'm getting wet!&nbsp; I should write these for other people.&nbsp; One think I'd like to especially point out, in light of recent events, I did grade myself as excellent, under the subject, "Displays tact in dealing with key personnel".&nbsp; Is slapping coffee out of a fuck-mook's hand because he deserved it and his head is big and stupid looking, considered tact?  &nbsp;  One more thing.&nbsp; Saturday night I went to Chinese restaraunt in Woonsocket with those wacky kids, Tim and Melissa.&nbsp; Ordinarily, one probably wouldn't have driven to Woonsocket for Chinese food, except this one specialized in live blues and jazz.&nbsp; So I took those two up on their invite and checked it out.&nbsp; While there we watched John Hammond, as I was told a very accomplished blues musician.&nbsp; I had never heard of him before but I will say he kicked ass.&nbsp; But that wasn't the highlight of the night.&nbsp; What was the highlight was I got to watch this dumb,&nbsp;blonde,&nbsp;bimbo sitting next to me shovel&nbsp;a piece of Sterno into her mouth thinking it was food.&nbsp; Yeah, you heard me right, she tried to eat it.&nbsp; For those of you that don't know, Sterno is a brand of blue or pink gelatenous fuel that comes in a can which you place under a banquet tray or in her case in the center of a Pu Pu Platter.&nbsp; To think of it another way, it's very similar to napalm, you know, the stuff we used to spray all over the North Vietnamese from our airplanes.&nbsp; So she starts taking food off the platter and then placing it on top of the sterno flame, because it wasn't hot enough, I guess.&nbsp; She then drops a piece of chicken into it, and when she pulls it out with her fork, it's got a glob of sterno on it.&nbsp; She then proceeds to pick it up, give it a quick examination, then put it in her mouth.&nbsp; Naturally she spits it out and starts to gag for about 5 minutes, which&nbsp;everone else at the table thought was just a hoot.&nbsp; Finally when&nbsp;she was finished and her friends asked her why she&nbsp;would do such a thing, she says she thought it was a tomato.&nbsp; Now, I don't know where she picks her vegetables from, but where I get mine, tomatoes don't maintain their density after burning for 15 minutes.&nbsp; Moron.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I sure wish I had asked her for her number.&nbsp;       

						
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This was bugging the shit out of me since yesterday afternoon.&nbsp; At the risque of sounding techie and nerdy, and hurting my jock reputation, how friggin hard is it to type 8 God damn characters on a keyboard.&nbsp; I take back what I said, this isn't even a technical issue.&nbsp; This is something you should be able to do without a frontal lobe.&nbsp; So why does some jackass have to call me up three times in fifteen minutes because he can't complete the brainless task of changing a password.&nbsp; &nbsp; "Yeah, I called a few minutes ago to get my password reset, and it doesn't work." &nbsp; "Did you use Groton11?" &nbsp; "No you said you reset it so I put in a new one, but it says invalid login." &nbsp; "Ok, you have to use Groton11 first" &nbsp; "Oh.........OK.&nbsp; Thank you." &nbsp; "Anything else I can help you with" &nbsp; "Umm......well, I kinda got my hand stuck in this jar......." &nbsp; Christ....people like this make me angry.&nbsp; I swear to God if this kid ever needs his password reset again, I'm going to tattoo it into his&nbsp;cornea with a Number 2. pencil. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;  

						
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What a great way to start a Friday,&nbsp;being told that a meeting must be held regarding behavioral issues between myself and a coworker.&nbsp; Working in such a laid back atmosphere has always led to constant barrages of ball-busting, and this includes everyone in here.&nbsp; Same at a lot of jobs I suppose.&nbsp; But does anyone else work with someone who just thinks he's a teensy-weensy&nbsp;bit funnier than&nbsp;the rest of the clowns.&nbsp; The guy that I generously put it, "Doesn't know when to shut his fucking mouth while he's ahead."&nbsp; We'll that's what I got here, and I inevitably was pushed to an outburst of negative emotions.&nbsp; Don't get me wrong, I love a good chuckle at someone elses expense, be it the handicapped, Amish, flood victims, whatever....but I know when to back off.&nbsp; I had been the butt of the same joke for a few weeks...the same joke.&nbsp; At first I was laughing along, then it got kind of old, then it turned into "could you just stop, you're seriously annoying me now and I want to urinate on you."&nbsp;  &nbsp; Now take into account that after leaving two weeks worth of voicemail with my employers as to why I've been working here for 19 months without review or raise, my boss (who I've never met in person) calls me to apologise, because "he forgot" about me.&nbsp; You can imagine this set off a propane torch under my ass and was none too pleased.&nbsp;  &nbsp; So, I'm heading to the head, and there's the Get-A-Long Gang hanging out in the hallway, and my friend sees me and starts his little act, and all the others start giggling with him like a couple of little girls who just discovered that each of them had a clitoris.&nbsp; As I walked by, I did the only thing that came to mind, and that was to slap the large Dunkin Donuts coffee out of the deusche bag's hand.&nbsp; It was full, I might add.&nbsp; Then I calmly kept walking towards the mens room.&nbsp; I didn't hear any giggling anymore after that.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Now, I do have respect for others (well, some people.....a couple of people), and I did clean up the mess and even bought him a coffee the next day to show no hard feelings.&nbsp; I'll tell you what gives me ultimate pleasure though. 1) He never saw it coming 2) I know I embarrased the living shit out of him because he thinks he's the office George Carlin around here and he  hates  it when anyone gives him shit.&nbsp; So, he put on a disgusted face and told on me, which brings us to Monday's yet to be held meeting.&nbsp; I do regret doing it though.&nbsp; I&nbsp;should have gone with my first instinct in the hallway, yesterday.....but sadly I didn't have a tack hammer in my hand.  

						
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    RIP: 1946 - 1993&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This past weekend was an interesting one to say the least, and a first in the respect that I spent both Friday and Saturday night in CT. For one I am pleased to to say that on Friday afternoon, my nuts finally dislodged themselves from my throat and I asked out that particular blonde corpsman I had mentioned in one of my previous entries, and we'll get back to her in a little bit.  I ended up meeting out with a coworker for happy hour on Friday evening. I met him out at Margarita's around 5:30 and he was accompanied by his girl friend, her cousin, and a guy who was completely deaf. The deaf guy didn't hang for very long, leaving me absolutely no cannon fodder to direct at the handicapped. Mind you as well, I was now full on engaged with the "30 something" crowd, which I am not accustomed to in the least, but I didn't let it hold me back at all. So we're joking laughing, sipping margaritas, and this cousin that's with them, Victoria, you can tell is just a wild one and seemed to take quite an interest in me. Must have been my personality or robustly good looks. She's asking me all sorts of questions and I'm trying to maintain eye contact, but this lady had big enormous breasts, and it was very hard not to look. They could have used this lady's cleavage as a landing beacon at O'Hare airport during a snowstorm. And I make no mistakes about it, no female jacks their breasts up in a bra and top that's obviously too small and doesn't expect men to look. And if they do, they should be forced to wear a scarlet "T", for Titty, for being such an arrogant wench. So she keeps asking me what my feeling would be towards dating an older woman. So ask, how old? She says 34. I ask how old are you? She says, 34. OK, gee, where are we going with this one?  So the hours in the evening start to add on, as well as the cocktails. We left Margaritas and then hit the Harp and Hound, were the two women I was with started getting louder and crazier. Victoria is flirting with me a lot and seems to be doing everything in her power to make me blush. Like pulling down her pants to show me her lack of tan lines. And she was right, she had no tan lines. I'm three margaritas and two Guiness into the shit now, and I'm starting to think to myself, "Pascoe, you got a pretty damn good shot here." So the drinks and flirting continue, and she keeps ribbing me. At one point, and I'm still not sure why, she accused me of not believing her breasts were natural. I assured her I did, but that wasn't good enough for her. She grabbed me by my wrist and put my hand right on her left breast. "Feel that, squeeze it, they're real!" OK, at that point she got me. My little sailor was standing now at full attention (I can't believe I just referred to my penis as "my little sailor"). 10 minutes after that, I'm giving the lady a foot massage in the middle of some restaraunt lounge. I'm thinking "it's on now". The other two mooks are looking tired and made it apparent that they wanted to go home and smoke weed, which Victoria told me she wasn't into. So I suggested that we stay out and I'd give her a ride home later. Well, her whole attitude changed at that point. She told me she thought I was very attracted and she liked me, but she wasn't into the whole "casual sex thing". She did want to exchange numbers, though, but at that point I was like, yeah whatever. I'm such a snob. So we're walking back to the cars and I decide to throw up a hail mary. I told her, "You know, back in there when I was giving you the foot massage, I was really turned on" (I can't believe I said that, let alone rubbed her feet). Suddenly her eyes light back up, "Really???" Apparantly so was she, and all of a sudden, I'm back in the ball game. So we're walking far ahead of the other two, who look like they ducked under an awning for a quicky. So as we're standing at the car waiting, the other two nowhere in sight now, I'll casually ask, "Do you want to make out?" She says, "You mean just kiss?" No stupid! Making out is my codeword for fucking you with a Corona bottle! "Yeah, that's what I mean". She oblidges to my suprise, and then says, "Let's go over to that bench over there." Right at the moment, Mike and his girlfriend pop back out of nowhere, like a pair of drunk, horny Caped Crusaders. "Ready to go???" Errrr......assholes!!!! So they invited me back to there place, which I learned was out by Mohegan Sun, and I didn't feel like driving out there or having to crash at there place at that point. I was much to drunk anyway. So I decided to head home. Victoria gave me a little kiss on the mouth and told me to call her. I said sure, lying. I would have done like Vince Vaughn in Swingers and just torn it up had I wrote it down rather than programed it into my phone. Because of her I was now going home to have sex with my hand.....again. Ehh, I shouldn't blame her, she was just a gal having a good time probably with no expectations, and I got to respect a lady who doesn't want to whore herself out after just meeting a guy. No...wait...actually, I don't in this case. I blame her completely. I'm sooo bitter.  So I got home and popped in the Best of Metro's Girls, but before I hit play, I saw that A&amp;E had the Andre The Giant biography on, which ended up saving me from forbidden carnal pleasure. The Giant's life was just so damn intriguing and sad, and lifes little chores were extremely stressful on this huge man, yet he lived every day to it's fullest and never looked back. Such a way to model your life, I thought, and was angry no more. I went to sleep after and slept like a baby, knowing that tomorrow was another day and that's this nights shortcomings were now the past. And Saturday went on to be a damn good one at that. Thank you Andre, thank you....   urlLink    RIP: 1946 - 1993  urlLink      

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I don't know how many of you read Craigslist.org, the online classified, but it sure can be a good source of personal amusement. Some people post some real zingers on there. Take for example this posting under the Hartford, CT, Strictly Platonic-Personals:   Reply to:   urlLink  anon-39004871@craigslist.org       Date: 2004-08-10, 10:41PM EDT hello I am a college girl seeking a Generou$ person to help me out. With the money, I would be able to go to the gym and keep myself toned. I would also be able to work on my msuic and study more often. In return, I would love to hang out, walk around your place in whatever outfit you might like, perform for you, be your special friend. let me know if we can work something out. ~K    OK, so first thing I assume is that there were no positions open at the local Starbucks, so this young lady decided to explore other means of gaining financial stability. Apparantly whoring hereself out on the internet seemed like a viable solution. She's a little vague on the details of her offer, but to me, being someone's "special friend" for money doesn't sound very platonic. Still though, the gal peaked my curiosity. Not saying I'm going to be a part of her money making scheme, but I just wanted a tad more insight on the individual. So I emailed her. Here's what we have so far:   mpascoe77@cox.net wrote:>    I like your proposal. Ponder this: What amount of funds would you require to dance the Macarena, while wearing a bikini entirely made of bacon? Money is no object.     From: Spech >    Date: 2004/08/12 Thu PM 03:18:46 EDT>    To: mpascoe77@cox.net>    Subject: Re: college girl seeks funds - w4m>    wow bacon...is this serious? Well, I am a vegetarian, but this sounds very intersting. Would you make the bikini? Where would you get it? Dancing the Macerena... How long would you like me to dance? An hour? Longer?     urlLink  mpascoe77@cox.net    wrote:>    If pork conflicts with your animal free diet, I'm sure some alternative organic bikini substitute could be thought of. Also would want to make sure you don't have any specific allergies, to food, latex rubber, etc. The duration of the dance of course require on your physical condition and endurance level. What can you run the 100 meter in? Perhaps the Electric Slide would be better suited to you.Name your terms!     From: Spech   urlLink    Date: 2004/08/12 Thu PM 03:49:31 EDT    To:   urlLink  mpascoe77@cox.net       Subject: Re: Re: college girl seeks funds - w4m    I'll wear whatever you want and dance whatever dance. (you might need to refresh my mind for the macerana, but the electric slide I can do.) It sounds like it would be a really great workout as well. I would definatly want to take a shower afterwards. How does 200$ an hour sound? are you anywhere near Springfield? Do you have a place, or would we meet in a hotel?    $200 an hour? For that much money I need to know pretty damn good and well this person isn't a transexual or John Wayne Gacy. Plus, Springfield, MA is a little out of way to watch someone shame themselves for my amusement when I can drive 2o minutes to Silk Stalkings and watch someone do it for a lot less money. Doesn't know the Macarena??? Still, all is not lost. I think I'm going to get try and string her along a little, maybe get a picture. With any luck, she looks just like Aileen Wuornos, and has the same sparkling personality to boot.   urlLink    Could this be the new gal of my dreams???  urlLink     By the way, if I do get a picture, you can sure as shit bet it's going up on here. Man I got issues :)  

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I had a silly idea while sitting here at my desk while wondering what kind of underwear a particular blonde Naval Corpsman upstairs was wearing and how I could impress her.  Haiku Contest!  Yeah!  I want to do a haiku contest on my blog, mainly because I know a lot of my readers (all 12 of them) are a bunch of silly geese and could probably come up with some pretty good shit.  So if anyone is so inclined to participate, send me your best haiku to my email address posted in my profile.  Remember the rules of haiku.  First line 5 syllables, second line 7 syllables, last line 5 syllables again.  However I do have one catch:  They all have to be of one theme, which will make it much easier to judge them.  I will post the one I deem best on a future posting.  Now for the haiku theme.......   Breakfast Cereals     I look forward to reading your submissions, and I'm sure I'll get a few because you are all slackers just like me who have better things to do than work.  Good Luck!  

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I think that Curves place has the right idea. No mirrors. The YMCA I went to last night had them everywhere except the ceiling. They really give me the opportunity to see how much of a sweaty mess I am after 30 minutes of cardio work. Sure they're good for looking like a retard and doing a little meathead flexing after some weight reps, but I do that plenty when I'm by myself naked in the safe solitude of my apartment. One thing I noticed yesterday were the abnormal sweat patterns I was producing, particular underneath my meaty man-tits. I've included a diagram.   I've circled the areas that brought me the most shame. Yeah, real easy to impress the ladies when you look like you're lactating out of your lower pectoralis, not to mention sweating enough that you look like Ozzy Osbourne after he's just doused himself with water on stage to cover the fact that he's urinated himself.    

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Coming back to work after taking time off is truly one of the most miserable experiences I believe you can have. Technically I was in last Friday, but I can't really in good conscience call that a "work" day, as spent two hours a pig roast and about five hours spacing out and smoking cigarettes. Today I have to spend the day catching up on things and generally figure out what the hell is going on, what's due when, who's pissed off at who, etc., etc. Sadly I'm having one of my weekly, "what the hell am I doing working at this place" moods. Seriously, sometimes I come in here and start to shiver and pee my pants thinking about just how long I'm going to be working here, dealing with the same mundane crap day in and day out. I'll be looking at other jobs online, and I honestly believe that this place has actually made me less qualified for other jobs than before I started. I think getting into IT was my biggest mistake to begin with. It's so monotonous, and I don't feel at all as if I'm helping people, in a sense that I am enriching there lives or making there days better. Not even close. I "service" people, not help. I've learned there is a difference. I was watching the news one day, and saw a story how some city planners were renovating these old basketball courts/crack park to be a new childrens playground, complete with a scale model of the Thurbers Ave curb for the kids to learn about traffic safety. It hit me that I'd much rather be doing something like that than staring at a block of SQL code trying to figure out why my Business Objects reports aren't running, while someone on the phone is bitching that their printer is printing their patient encounter forms out of alignment. I hate to whine like about the 70% of all other job holders in America, but sometimes this place feels like the most unmotivating place in the universe.  Weekend wasn't so bad. Friday night, after a rather drab ordinary night at the Star Bar (except for the fact that Callahan went roid-rage at some guys we were playing a friendly game of pool with over nothing). We were all gathered outside the exit after last call, when a couple of ladies walk by and invite us up to there place for a party. Me being the most horniest and in desperate need of physical contact, immediately started following them. So everyone I'm with is asking where the hell I'm going, because the plan was to go back to Callahan's dad's house and do nothing until 3 am. Hmmmm....what should I do? Go with the two beautiful women who just randomly invited us over there place....or Jim's dad's place. If you guessed Jim's dad's place, then you are homosexual. So I dart off with the ladies, and Leon and Schneller follow. We're led into this three story apartment that this chick, Beth owns. Beth was a masseuse, and this place was really nice and I can't imagine her owning it on just a masseuses salary, so I'm thinking, "sugar daddy". I could be wrong though. She's also got a couple of friends over, Lolita and Rosalie, who it turns out are gymnasts and (no word of a lie) former New England Patriots Cheerleaders. I took there word for it when they started to doing flips, splits, and other contortionist shenanigans all over the living room floor. I took a bunch of pictures that I could save for my stalker memoirs scrap book, and will post them on this at another time. They were generally some nice ladies though, set us up with drinks, made us feel quite at home. Not the sharpest tacks though. Schneller convinced one that I was quite the volleyball player, and she honestly thought I was going to meet her the next day for a tournament. I don't know what gave the idea that my pudgy little frame had anymore that a 6 inch vertical leap, but I humored her. Everything was going quite fun until about 2:30 when a short bus-load of dudes showed up. Dudes, always ruining things. So we left around 3:00, a memorable night but unforfilled. The most action I saw at these girls' place was when I was looking at the pictures I took on my camera, and Lolita came over to look over my shoulder to see the pics. One of her goddess like breasts pressed against my left shoulder for a few moments, at which point I instantly spilled semen in my lap. Score! After I got home at 3:20, I decided to reconnect with an old friend. Online pornography.  "Oh when I look back now, That summer seemed to last forever. And if I had the choice, Ya - I'd always wanna be there. Those were the best days of my life."  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have such a love/hate relationship with the city of Newport.  I mean, I did grow up here for one thing.  It's nice going out around here in the fall/winter/spring.  No matter where you go there's just a nice comfortable vibe coming from everywhere, and you can always find friends of yours wherever you go.  Summertime....forget about it.  The city is plagued with meatheads and.....meatheads.  And many pretty, pretty ladies who don't wear much clothing.   Errrr...I'm complaining???  Oh, wait I remember, I really hate the crowds,  and the repugnant level of testosterone waifing throught the city.  I was listening to this song by Johnny Cash today, "When The Man Comes Around".  It's a hip tune off of his final album.  It more or less concerns judgement day and the Apocalyps.  I had this vision while listening to it, of the general after hours crew of dipshits and drunks that gather around Via Via pizza on lower Thames St.  And then what the looks on everyones faces would be when all of the sudden The End comes and the Four Horsemen just start raining fire, brimstone, and chaos all over everyone....with Johnny Cash playing in the backround.  I just don't think you could dream a better ground zero and setting for the end of the world.  Just totally fuck up everyone's summer, right!  I need to buy a fucking Howitzer.  OK, I'm shitfaced and need to go to bed.  

						
</post>


</Blog>