<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We played a show on Tuesday, and it went pretty well... most of our songs were played a lot better than last time... with each passing show we're getting tighter and tighter with our music! My friends Frank and Darren, along with my cousin Garnet, sat together and watched the rest of the show... all the bands there were quite kick ass, especially the second one... "A murder left of crows" or something like that... they were from Vancouver, and i would have to say they were the best band of the night, along with Don't Jump, who played a few sweet covers! I love being at the shows, cause you can talk with other bands and stuff, so it's all cool   Moving on, our stage presence wasn't all that great....at all... many people said i moved around most and had the most energy, which is pretty sad since im sitting down the whole time... I was on another planet when I was on stage... all the other bands had mosh pits going and had full energy jumping around and stuff getting the crowd going wild... why is it that my band can never do that? Something needs to be changed...   Rock on   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry for the long wait, but i've been quite busy during the past few days, with work, being tired and getting no sleep, etc etc... so yesterday was band practice, and that went alright... we have our set&nbsp; list for tuesday's show, which is: 1) What's Wrong With Them 2) Snobby 3) What Is the World Coming To 4) Trying to Make It  ^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^ Those are probably our 4 best songs, the songs we're really tight on anyways... we played some more covers, although not all the way through (Mark needs to learn em) but Andrew and I went through Try Honesty by Billy Talent... first time through and we got it perfect! Yet another song we should cover!  So it's the weekend now, and i get to sleep... muahahahaha  Rock on 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, my aunt from switzerland and my cousin (her son, whom i haven't seen in over 13 years) came to visit. Was pretty cool, we had dinner, she showed us pictures of her house and switzerland and all that stuff, talked about some things etc. My cousin and i were talking about cars and his motorcycles and different things he's done and that... he's coming back here on august 11th and he's going to come&nbsp;and get me and we're gonna go out to his friend's house not to far from here, who has a lot of old cars that have been built up, such as the '69 chevelle ss with a 454, '71 nova ss, etc, and we're gonna go down to the track, and it's gonna be sweeeeeeet :) hopefully i get a bunch of pictures of this whole thing and all the cars.  Today i was off work again because my dad is still injured from his side, and he still seems that way, not sure how work's gonna go tomorrow... but it has been a rather slow and boring day, not very eventful, and i'll leave it at that  Rock on 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So i can't get to sleep after trying for about an hour, which is normal i guess, and i'm really tired.... and i gotta go to work in like 6 hours, so maybe i should try sleeping! So after my rant, i will continue on with my day. I woke up at around 10 feeling tired as hell, talked to dorian for a bit, then she let me go back to sleep, awwwwww what a sweetie &nbsp; THen i went and played basketball with Leah, she just got a basketball net for her birthday, it's cool. We got to try out the brand new bbq today, so we fired it up and bbq'd some nice expensive rib steaks... best. steak. ever! After that i came onto my computer, dorian came home and i talked on the phone with her for a bit, and watched tv. That's basically it. &nbsp; I've e-mailed a few bassists, so hopefully I get a response soon. &nbsp; Rock on 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today i went to my aunt's house where about 75 people were for my aunt and uncle's 25th anniversary. Went pretty well, there was tons of food, (which was probably the best part) not to mention i got to see a bunch of people that i haven't seen for a very long time. I spent most of the day with Kyle, my&nbsp;cousin's boyfriend who has a band called Miso ( urlLink www.miso.ca ) and i jammed with them once. I think i had too much food... i feel like crap. So that went pretty well.  &nbsp;  In other news, Dorian is&nbsp;at her dad's&nbsp;until&nbsp;Sunday, so i can't talk to her at&nbsp;all :( she'll be&nbsp;pre-occupied doing things, which is good for her  &nbsp;  As for the band, my dad may have a deal for us, where he can get the t-shirts for us so much cheaper than how we're already buying them, so we can sell all those and have our damn CD out. Speaking of our cd, it'll only cost us $450 to do the whole thing (new producer) and Jordan said he'll lend the $450 but that means we can't kick him out of the band... we'll have to do what's best... he's making absolutely no progression at all and it's getting on my nerves  &nbsp;  Sorry if&nbsp;some of&nbsp;this doesn't make sense, i'm really tired from all the energy it took from my hands&nbsp;placing food in my mouth&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Rock on   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, i decided to start up one of these things... i had the spare time  &nbsp;  So yesterday we had a band practice (you can go to our site at  urlLink www.eternal-instinct.com ) and it went alright. We changed 3 songs, and they're all sounding pretty good, but we just need to work on it a bit longer. We only practiced for about like... 2 and a half hours, which was shorter than usual. There wasn't much participation from Jordan, the damn lazy bastard fell asleep on the floor and didn't practice much (he's our bassist.) Other than that, Andrew pulled out a pretty crazy improv solo for what is the world coming to. Mark and I then started to play a few Blink182 and Sum 41 covers... which wouldn't be a bad idea for our shows, as long as we don't butcher the songs. Then Mark and I went for our daily bike ride, and the rest of the night was just blah.  &nbsp;  Today I went to the town centre to get a few things, and i saw Dorian with her mom... at least she didn't give me a crazy look, so i was happy about that. The rest of the day is ahead of me and i'm gonna do something... i just don't know yet  &nbsp; Rock on!  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SUCKED!  We were in a really really high class bar in Mississauga called Second Floor lounge, it was a great place... but there were only 3 bands (us included) and there was no crowd! To top it up, they only gave US 30 minutes of set time and the other 2 bands got 50 mins-1 hr set times... faggots. Anyways i just found out yesterday that we'll be playing at the El Mocambo on Halloween for the "Halloween Kicks ass Bash" with 2 great bands we've played with before - Manic and Still Life, and much more bands. This show is through Cupids Kiss, the same company that gave us our show at the Reverb on June 27th. Gotta work for the next 2 days, so i'll hit the hay now.  Rock on 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So the guy said we would get paid for it... minimum of $45... great, that would give us enough money to buy our t-shirts... wrong  We end up getting 2 friggin dollars  What the hell am i gonna do with 2 dollars? That doesn't even buy me a small sundae at dairy queen... i woulda rather played for free then get 2 bucks...okay my rant is over  Rock on 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep... so like i stated beolow, we'll be playing Johnny's in Richmond Hill (14 Oxford Street),  along with the other bands Xeno's Paradox and Manic (we've played with them before, they're amazing) Each band has to bring something - we'll be bringing the drums and cymbals, cause our PA system sucks and our amps aren't all powerful; but, they get the job done in our band practices. This will probably be one of our best shows this year, i lost a lot of sleep just thinking about it last night, lol. I should be back at around 1 or 2am after the whole show is over... then i can sleep!  Rock on 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So our show last night was our best one ever! They just get better and better each time, and that rules. We ended up playing those 4 songs, at around 10:30pm... had a huge crowd, they were moshing, all was good. I was sweating like a mofo though... but i dumped a water bottle on myself and that solved my problem. Bands there that i liked was the first band (don't know what they were called) and they played a cover of Pearl Jam's Even Flow, which kicked ass. I also liked All Signs Point to Know; they played punk music, me and the drummer talked a lot and hung out for a while. Also, 9D Quick played, and i think they won the band wars for that night.. Congrats to them!  We had band practice today, and that went quite well... we figured out the 14 songs we'll be playing in richmond hill, including 3 covers - All The Small things, The Hell Song, and Try Honesty... it's gonna be real kick ass!  Rock on  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, we have a show tonight at Club Rockit, it's on 120 church street and it's through supernova. (www.supernova.com)  The Rockit has a pretty neat set up, even though our stage isn't that big, and there's a pit right in front of the stage, and there's a level above us, and then there's a bar right at the back. Oh, and there's a sound guy who actually knows what he's doing. The song list for tonight's show will be:  What's Wrong with Them Snobby Trying to Make it I Wish  IMO, those are our 4 best songs... reason why we're only playing 4 is because we didn't sell many tickets, thus our set time is small. My friends Frank and Darren along with another person is coming to the show again tonight, I love them (not in that way.) So, I'll be back later tonight with the results!  Rock on 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>