<Blog>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             "Dear diary what a day it's been, Dear diary i't been just like a dream. Woke up too late wasn't where I should of been for goodness sake what's happening to me.".....Just some good Ray Thomas lyrics to set the mood.         Well to make a long story short.I have a busy week. I started out today by filling out an application for the fulltime spot in my Department. I am praying that I get it :). I have to start out this week by begging my best friend to please stay on the clean side of life. I am scared because I already know the outcome of this senereo. Please God save her, I love her too much.        This is a busy week.then the rest of the week consist of work and taking my dog to the groomer ,food shopping,Bed delivery,Final Days before Matt's Grandmother's house is sold. And his Parent's  are moving. I am looking forward to Fall.                                              So I need some sleep so I am going to bed early.   Byr Bye
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                      Today was ok. I spent most of the day with a really bad headace and stomach problems. It is really rainy. I feel good because my husband and I bought a new bed. A king size!!!!! I am looking forward to it alot because I will have room to sleep. Now I just have to make room for it. To get a picture of this We now sleep in a full size.Now there will be room for all of us Me, Matt and our Dog Lucy.                  I am excited because Fable is coming out in September.I am gald I pre-ordered it.Today I listened to Syd Barrett's Opel. It brought back some good memories. I started listening to Syd when I was around 10, thanks to my brother.Rainy Days Make me think of his music. Time to make dinner so until next time..........Bye Bye
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             Today had a great start.As soon as I walked into work today I got a great greeting by my boss telling me that I got a 100% on my secret shopper. It made me feel really good because I have been at this place for 10 months and just now they have seen that I am good with customers. Just because I am good with customers does not mean that I like them. I am just good to the nice ones. there are alot of assholes out there. I am almost sick of it. As for my job  I do really like it but I have come to a fork in the road. Do I stay at part time or do I go full time.It is a choice but I need to sleep on it. there are a few things in my life now I am worried about.         My best friend since I was 3 is a recovering addict. She is married with two beautiful children.I am afraid because she might make a mistake that will ruin her life forever. I love her so much and I fear for what she might do.I have been praying alot about alot of things but this one is on the top of my list.     i am also feeling bad because I said a few things to my husband last night that I wish I didn't say, I guess I should speak for myself sometimes. I love him more than anything in this world.He is the perfect man for me and I guess I don't tell him often enough.        I didn't watch any movies today but this week I watched Eurotrip,Club Dread,Bubba Ho-tep, Triplets of Beville. I also Watched Dune and the Matrix. the reson I watched the Matrix yesterday is because I wanted to sit down and Imagine Brandon Lee in the role as Neo.I also Watched Dune to re-discover why I had a crush on Kyle Machlaughin when I was 10. I think my next purchase will be Twin Peaks. He was really cute in that.        Right now I am waiting for Matt and His Brother Mike to bring the las of the things we stored at his grandmother's house. I am glad I don't have to be there but I had to be here to make room in our garage and to bring the grill out front. Fun!!!!!! Well I must go for now. I think I might watch Rockula today.     Bye Bye 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I don't feel like cooking tonight so we ordered out. I am getting A chicken salad. I also  have to be in bed by 9:45pm So I can wake up at 5:30.In the morning i am Going to a Meeting at work. Then after that I am going to finish moving stuff out of Matt's Grandmother's house into our house. (yay! more stuff)Matt's Grandmother recently passed away and for the last three months we have been cleaning it out. it has been painful but the afterwards have been painful.Soon it will be over and we can go on with our lives Well the food is here and the simpsons will be on soon. so until next time. Bye Bye
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello all you boys and girls.I'd like to take you to the inside world. It is such an irregular place to be but never a fear your safe with me.....   I am Jojopely. I hail from Southeast Pa. I am a Fanatic when it comes to Movies, music and video game. I guess that is why it is proper that I should work in the Media section at Best Buy. I  got so much to tell the world but for now I will fill out my profile.  Bye bye
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well it has been three weeks since I filled out for that fulltime spot. And after being almost 100% sure I was going to get it I now feel it has slipped away from me and I feel very sad about this because this would of been a great confidence booster. On top of that I can feel the pain of my monthly visitor setting in  so it is apparent to me that my other plans will fall through.On top of not improving my job ,I am not pregnant either.So I just have to start all over again. I know I can keep a sane head about everything but it is still vary heart breaking. Sometimes God can make things odvious. So I can see that he does not want me to have a baby and he does not want me to make more money and when the holiday season comes around I will have worked my ass off for nothing. Just so I can buy stupid presents for my dysfunctional family. I get everyone great gifts every year and I feel that it is pointless. No one cares , No one understands.(My job is more important in the winter time)    I have not had a decent convertation with my sister in a long time.I think maybe I am the one with the problem at this point.    I see myself as a failure.If you knew me you would understand.I do have great things in my live at this point for example My husband Matt ,and My Dog Lucy, And my Best friend Kim and her husband and children. I do love my job. I work with some great people.Mike, Steve,John, Vaughn, Darlene, Maureen, Jason. I am glade for all of these people. I wish My family could improve but I still love them.     There are so many people I don't talk to anymore. I miss all my old friends.        Well today is going to be very busy I got lots to do. So nothing is going to get done infront of this evil thing. So good bye Jojopely
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My husband was on vacation and we where kind of busy. Well we lucked out tremendously, Two different areas in my town where flooded out beyond belief. But I was unharmed and so was my precious basement.     I am feeling kind of embarrassed inlaws stopped by this morning and they wanted to see our new bed and I forgot I left a book next to my bed about pregnancy. This would not be a problem if I was anyone else. It just feels to me that anything Matt and I want to do with our lives has to be ran by them first and readied for approval.Well lately they have backed off a bit due to the fact that they are so busy with there lives but the last time it was brought up we got a lot of shit from them. So in fact Matt and I have decided on our own terms to start having children. We basically told everyone in the world except for his parents. Well I forgot about my book sitting there in plane view entitled"Pregnancy Book".. uhgggggg... Well that is all I need is my inlaws getting on our ass about this when all along it is a decition that is only ours to make. Hell I am not even pregnant yet. At least I don't think I am. I need to wait a few weeks , Like I said Matt and I where busy.  Well all in all it had put me in a bad mood. Not that I like being in a bad mood but it is just one of them things you regret after you think about it. Nothing really happened in my life this week. I found out someone I was friends with ten years ago died about six months ago. Her name was Jolene. We where best friend for a while but we went our separate ways. Just thinking about it depresses me.I do remember in the end that she was really mean to me so I decided to get new friends. The last time I saw her was 4 years ago and she gave me a big smile. I regret not saying something to her. All I did was smile back. Now that image is forever burnt into my head. Here's to you Jolene.  (Moment of silence).................................................................................................................................  As for What I am doing this week who knows. I found I have a new obsession with Orson Welles. We he is intriguing me so I bought his biography So I will be reading that as well as my "Pregnancy Book" And hopefully my inlaws are blind and they didn't see my book. And hopefully I get that fulltime spot at work. And hopefully I am pregnant. But I just need to wait and see.    As far as being pregnant is concerned I would just like the readers to know that for that last 2 and a half years I have been getting ready to have a baby.  I stopped smoking and drinking. I don't even drink coffee. I am on a limited diet now of just the four food groups and I am drinking a ton of water a day and practice yoga. Funny when you consider that about three years ago I was Smoking two packs a day and Smoking pot and drinking every weekend. I really changed. I have no urge to do any of these things. All I want to happen is for me and Matt to become parents.I pray all the time for it to happen.   good bye for now   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>