<Blog>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The rips lead to alternate universes. The rips lead directly from A-B, the  universe a rip links to does not change once a rip has formed.  Every rip into a new universe causes that universe to begin to decay also.  Other universes touching against that reality also have rips formed to them,  and in turn begin to decay. Once all the universes are infected the  omniverse will be a free-flowing torrent of ideas and possibilities, shared  tested and experienced in on instant, the ultimate Chaos and the ultimate  Order simultaneously.  Until then, naturally, all the inhabitants of each world are naturally a  little concerned.  There is a way to repair the fabric, but this technique takes a day to close  one rip (during which time every infected universe will have created  another).  There may be a way to slow, or stop, the decay, but this has not yet been  discovered. (hint: It will be. May involve other universes or magic. not  decided.)      
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have you ever seen a laptop screen, where the image is only perfect at a certain angle to the user's eyes? The windows are like that, only more so. There are no imperfections, the image is either perfect, or non-existant. Windows will appear anywhere, they may be extra unusual items on the mantle-piece up to entire sides of buildings changing into a rolling green pasture. Those on the other side of a window (if any) will not be able to see into the CW universe, and neither side can travel between universes with the windows.    
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The world will be an imperfect parallel universe next to our own. The  majority of history is the same, but details are slightly blurred between  the universes.  In the Collected World (CW) universe, a scientist working with sub-atomic  particles has accidentally created a minute tear in the fabric of  space-time. From this tear, the entire fabric of the CW universe will begin  to unravel. The majority of the story will follow inhabitants of CW as they  drop through into other universes, or universes show through the holes.  The world at large was unaware that the universe was destabilising, in  fact the scientist who caused it didn't know. The evidence only becomes  clear when the president of the united states drops into another dimension  during a political broadcast, aides on either side and cameras rolling.  Once the world begins to wake up to the fact their reality is leaving  them, there will be mass riots. Children will, with their limited grasp of  reality, be the first to spot a new hole or window. Windows will be oddly  placed items that disappear when not looked at from the right angle, holes  can appear anywhere and may alter the existing reality around themselves.       
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The holes can be anything, and can appear anywhere (including inside other  objects). They may appear at any angle, and can be viewed from one side  only. The opposite side shows a distorted version of what should be there,  the front shows a completely alternate universe (These may not be  distinguishable). Holes warp the reality surrounding them, but not always to  a noticable degree. Sometimes they can create impossible rooms within the CW  reality that any passer-by would be hard pushed to miss. EG: A sports hall  that fades to black four meters from the entrance, and is twice as tall/wide  as it should be, with a rip near the center of the resulting room.  Falling through a rip is not an everyday occurance, however there is  normally at least one 'visitor' from another dimension that slipped through  the holes. There are no 'special effects', the faller just appears to pass  through an infinitley-thin hole, dropping out onto the other side (or not,  as the case may be. Holes need not be precicely at ground level)      
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The first phase of creating a story is to define a world for it to take place in.  For&nbsp;the remainder of this month,&nbsp;I'll be planning the vanilla Collected World (and mentioning any bolt-on worlds I might use later).         
      
</post>


</Blog>