<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just saw a Michael Moore film, which I had been meaning to see since its release entitled "Bowling for Columbine" This documentary tries to find out why Americans are so...well....such assholes who kill each other. It all comes down to, nobody knows why....The Media keeps everyone in fear, and that doesn't help much,  I REALLY suggest you see this film, Absolutely amazing. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I bought a new hat today....It's pink....so what? A picture to come, but I'm telling you....Pink hats > You.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, This list will be updated as I see fit, This is a list of movies you are required as a human being to watch.  * indicates that males are the only gender REQUIRED to see this film   Bowling for Columbine Casablanca Pulp Fiction Reservior Dogs Die Hard* The Matrix* Swordfish Punch Drunk Love Schindler's list Nightmare Before Christmas The Last Samurai Philadelphia The Green Mile Top Gun* Rainman Mission Impossible* Vanilla Sky When Harry met Sally 12 Monkies Bullet Proof Monk* Con Air* Alice in Wonderland (NOTE: This film has a much deeper meaning, Alice in Wonderland |the book at least| can be seen as a young girl who is using LSD or Acid. Wonderland in entirely in her head....She is on an acid trip) The Wizard of Oz    This list is subject to being updated whenever the fuck I feel like it. If you have not seen these movies...you are in danger of being made fun of by me. ESPECIALLY if your a guy who hasn't seen Die Hard....thats just gay....TOTALLY GAY
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No updates recently...life drags on and on, as boring as ever. I bought Painkiller, it is fucking great, I don't get the FPS i want, but whenever I get my new videocard it should be good. Saw some girl at a store today with pink hair, made me miss MY pink hair :P BUT Taco Bell tends to frown upon pink hair.... I still need like 4 things before I can get that job, but I've pretty much got it...I hope. I reformatted my computer, so it runs better, but I lost all of my music :( I feel like I've done a good deed, I introduced someone to Atreyus wonderful music :) Hah, wow this is a boring boring boring post.....boring....WOAH WHAT A COOL DOG! be back later, I have to chase a dog down the street! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      :) Well, at 3 I am going to Taco Bell for an interview. Sadly I have to get a job :-\ Hopefully it goes well. My french Fries are burnt :( My oven sucks. And I forgot salt...
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Grrrrr, it's me.....the Vampire from the Dungeons and Dragons Monster Manual GRRRRRR!!!!!!!! Seriously though...isn't that dude cool as hell?&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me as Gordan Freeman from half-life. Clifford "BuZzSaW" Rose sent it to me as a joke.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A great desktop Background given to me by a friend of mine from the UK by the name of Kurt, or "KeneticKangaroo" Check out his Condition Zero team Played the game.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Not sure where this picture came from, but thought it was worth a mention. See ladies, I'm sensitive :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The "Nurse" Project after I was finished :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A Photoshop Coloring project I did.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Samurai Kittens.....trust me...it is worth mentioning....&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A Banner a made that I am pretty proud of. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me with my uber cool pink hair and pwning with my deagle at CS :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me again, caught off guard by my sister and her camera, I was walking home from school, the medical mask is something I did at school, running around screaming things, was pretty funny.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is a bad photo of me :-\ But its one I just found. my sister took it as I came out of my room, this was before I moved out. In the background the the picture frame is me as a baby :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am watching southpark and eating cashews and M&Ms, and being the person I am, decided to mix the 2 in my hand and down them at the same time. I was interested to find how it would taste, and might I say, Cashew M&Ms would be lovely.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I started my radio empire :) HaveN Radio with HaveN (Bryden) Ghostkodiak (Chavez) and RoninAfro (Jacob) can be heard every Friday via shoutcast. more to come, weeee.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is KIKIKIKIKIKI! I am kikikikikiki prenounced key-key-key-key-key-key (ALWAYS SAID 6 TIMES AND NO MORE!) I often add teh kikikikikiki onto my name in various things. IE. fL ^ HaveN teh kikikikikiki or sSquezz [!] hvn teh kikikikikiki kikikikikiki comes from lol, i made kik mean the came thing as lol, because they are directly to the left of the keys  lol, thus kik was born, rather than lololololololol i said kikikikikiki and I kept the word. :) THUS is the history of kikikikikiki&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    WHAT KIKIKIKIKIKI IS! For the first time EVER I will annouce WTF KIKIKIKIKIKI is!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    WTF IS KIKIKIKIKIKI? GRRR!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    WTF IS KIKIKIKIKIKI?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    No it is not.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>