<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm no fan of Tom DeLay; never have been.&nbsp; But today he went onto my "I Really Hate This Guy" list.  DeLay spent his time yesterday criticizing a promotion being run in Germany by Subway, in which trayliners at the company's local franchises feature the promotional slide for "Super Size Me", an independent film (played in Europe recently) in which the filmmaker eats nothing but McDonald's food for 50 days, and gains 25 pounds as a result.&nbsp; The point of the film is to discuss why Americans are commonly overweight, blaming the fast food industry for much of the problem.&nbsp; Part of the tray liner is a figure of the Statue of Liberty, in parody: holding aloft an order of french fries and being quite overweight.&nbsp;   I'm not sure whether or not the Statue parody is part of the movie's materials; it may be.&nbsp; DeLay found all this offensive, and also criticized Subway for allowing the promotion to go on.&nbsp; Clearly DeLay hasn't a clue that multinational brands such as Subway do not dictate local promotions and have no say in the matter at all.&nbsp; DeLay, being a lockstep republican in tune with the White House, likes taking instructions, and probably assumed that the Subway HQ in Connecticut must have approved the promotion, whereas the rest of us in the business world knows that they probably hadn't even heard of it until DeLay opened his mouth.&nbsp; But DeLay has no problem denouncing Subway as a whole for the promotion.&nbsp;   DeLay further displays his idiocy when he included Michael Moore for criticism; a quote from Moore is featured on the trayliner, but it is a quote referring only to McDonald's.&nbsp; The quote is not represented in the article I read, but is purported to be an anti-McDonald's quote from the movie itself.&nbsp; Why would DeLay go out of his way to criticize this aspect of the promo?&nbsp; Perhaps because since Moore made an anti-Bush film, he must be anti-American?&nbsp; Perhaps because as Bush's most outspoken and famous critic, DeLay sought to gain favor with the President by denouncing Moore?&nbsp;   DeLay's sanctimonious attitude really came out in this statement: "For Subway to thumb its nose at its American customers and promote Michael Moore's blame-America-first conspiracy in a foreign country is very concerning".&nbsp; Let's analyze this.&nbsp;   As already discussed, Subway corporate had nothing to do with the campaign; it is a local franchisee doing the promotion.&nbsp; No doubt the worldwide Subway headquarters never even heard of the promo - nor should they be expected to.&nbsp; And since the promo targets local German customers in Germany, how is Subway therefore "thumbing its nose at its American customers"?&nbsp; If anything, Subway is thumbing its nose at American customers of McDonald's, not Subway.&nbsp; And how does one thumb its nose at American customers when the trayliners are in Germany?   But here we go with the clearly "See Mr. President, I Stuck Up For You" ass-kissing of which DeLay is most guilty.&nbsp; He claims that the promotion promotes Michael Moore's "blame-America-first conspiracy".&nbsp; How?&nbsp; How does Moore's comment about McDonald's in a movie that targets a serious problem in America, translate to an anti-American crusade?&nbsp; Where the hell doesDeLay get this stuff?&nbsp; Neither Moore, nor film director Morgan Spurlock, are the first to criticize McDonald's, and blaming an American problem on an American corporation does not strike me as being anti-American.&nbsp; If anything, it strikes me as being an attempt to solve a problem that concerns many Americans, something that DeLay should try doing some time.  So rather than spending his time trying to solve the real problems in America, DeLay chooses to make fatuous speeches about what a marketing specialist in Germany does to promote his products.&nbsp; So the trayliners can be thoughtof as being somewhat anti-American; but so what?&nbsp; Germany is a free country, a democratic state, and thus its people are entitled to express themselves as they so choose.&nbsp; And even then, I don't see the trayliners as anti-American; they may say that Americans are disproportionately fat, but is this not a proven fact?&nbsp; Has McDonald's not tacitly acknowledged some culpability by introducing salads and other healthier fare to their menus?&nbsp; To his credit, DeLay does point out the use of the word "Amis" on the trayliner, which is a low-grade derogatory reference to an American, much as we use "Krauts" to describe the Germans, or "Frogs" to the French.&nbsp; But there are far more offensive words that could be used, and if DeLay is so thin-skinned, how did he get to be the House Majority Leader?  It is clear that DeLay's speech is meant to pander to the "I'm So Patriotic"crowd in an election year.&nbsp; I doubt that he has any personal vendetta against Subway, but he certainly won't endear himself to them after these largely baseless remarks.&nbsp; And since when would this be his call, anyway?&nbsp; Since he is no defender of free speech in this country, one certainly wouldn't expect him to defend it in another country.&nbsp; But you would expect a public official to realize that poking fun at another country is not nearly the same as attacking it.&nbsp; DeLay and his party have long displayed a lack of sense of humor, and this reaction demonstrates that perhaps they just lack sense, period. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I don't really have any completed thoughts to share - mostly because late this afternoon I was stricken by a migraine, and thus not at my best philospohically.&nbsp; I get migraines on an occasional basis, and this one for a very specific reason which I will share when I'm able to.&nbsp; But I have gotten them periodically since I was 10, so I've learned to deal.&nbsp; Neurologists refer to me as having "classic, textbook migraine".&nbsp; But enough about me.  Yesterday, the Democratic National Convention opened, and former president Bill Clinton gave what I thought was a very fair and balanced speech and assessment of the current administration.&nbsp; And unlike what the republican party no doubt has cooking, the former president avoided any personal attacks on Mr. Bush.&nbsp; Indeed, he acknowledged that they were acting in what they believed in, which shows a respect for their abilities while disagreeing with what it is they did.&nbsp; This is the high road; would you have expected this man who was so maligned by the republicans for eight years, who was impeached on the flimsiest of grounds, would you have expected him to show such grace and class in a speech that could have simply excoriated the current administration?&nbsp; Well, yes, you could - if you had been paying attention to Bill Clinton, you would know that this is his style.  And maybe that's what the republicans hate about him; instead of employing the scare tactics that the republicans have been using since 1988, Clinton uses his talents to deliver his message, not simply sling mud on&nbsp;his opponents.&nbsp; If you've ever been to see Clinton speak (I had the pleasure of seeing him in the last weekend of the 1996 campaign), you know how well he gets his points across.&nbsp; His method of communication is much closer to Ronald Reagan than anyone named Bush has ever been.&nbsp; Yet the republicans hate his guts - is it jealousy?&nbsp; Jealousy that such an intelligent man can display wit, charm, and humor, and take the middle of the political spectrum away from the right wing?&nbsp; I don't understand it.&nbsp; Thousands of republicans benefitted from the Clinton economic policies, which were in part steered by the lifelong republican Alan Greenspan; millions of people benefitted from the welfare reform that saved the country money and put poeple to work; millions of people have benefitted mentally from the Family Medical Leave Act, allowing new parents to share the first weeks of their child's life together instead of dad having to run off and go to work right away.&nbsp; Why do the republicans hate that?  I thought Clinton's speech was terrific, as most of his speeches are; and amazingly, this one was noteable for its brevity, not something ordinarily associated with a Clinton speech!&nbsp; His statistics were not manufactured lies; he did not make fire-and-brimstone predictions about what would happen if you vote for the other party, he indeed pointed out that if you agree with the way they are running the country, then by all means vote for them.&nbsp; And this is exactly what public discourse should be like.&nbsp; No screaming or crying about what might happen if so-and-so gets into office, no "the terrorists win if John Kerry wins"-type scare tactics.&nbsp; But will it win over votes?  I don't think it will.&nbsp; As much as I enjoyed what Clinton said, and I'm sure many intelligent people did, let's face the fact: the average American is not all that bright.&nbsp; This is proved time and again by the volume of talk show callers who have no independant ideas about the world, able only to regurgitate what they heard on Rush Limbaugh's show.&nbsp; In today's New Haven Register, I was appalled by the number of comments sent in to the daily question regarding the Convention.&nbsp; Many readers clearly had no intention of giving the Democrats any ear, preferring instead to wallow in their own prejudices.&nbsp; And that will only lead to Bush' re-election.&nbsp;   Bush communicates well with the underinformed; unaware of facts, his voters believe what he says, that scowl being so convincing.&nbsp; Don't get me wrong; I do not adhere to the conventional wisdom that Bush is an idiot.&nbsp; Quite the contrary; I think he knows exactly what he's doing, and that he's much smarter than the democrats give him credit for being.&nbsp; I've read articles by people who knew him in his early days as governor of Texas, and they report being wowed by his fluid speeches and grasp of issues.&nbsp; That can't have vanished; it's being held back.&nbsp; I do believe that Bush believes that what he's doing is right; too far to the right, for my tastes.&nbsp; And I even credited him for his speech at the RNC in 2000, the "It won't be long now" speech.&nbsp; I thought it was very well delievered, and I remember that&nbsp;upon hearing it I turned to a friend and said, "There is no way Al Gore can win this election."  Bush has even improved in the foreign policy arena.&nbsp; I think he is handling the Chinese quite well, by not giving in to everything they want but not agitating them either, thus keeping Taiwan from becoming a dangerous situation.&nbsp; I don't think anyone really knows what to do about North Korea; short of assassination of Kim Jong Il, there is no real solution obvious.&nbsp; I do not like what he is doing with the Europeans, and I think his reluctance to help much in the Israel-Palestine conflict is problematic, but the first two issues I mentioned are an improvement.&nbsp; I give him credit there.  But with Iraq, I feel insulted.&nbsp; There was every reason to want to remove Saddam Hussein from power: in addition to his violation of UN sanctions (reason enough to go in), Hussein had for years been torturing and murdering his people.&nbsp; As the only force on the planet strong enough to save the common man, America could have gone to Iraq on principle along.&nbsp; But Bush decided instead that the only was to get popular support for his war was to lie to them and tell them they're threated.&nbsp; Sounds like typical republican party policy, actually.&nbsp; But as am American citizen, I find this insulting.&nbsp; Why more Americans don't feel this way is beyond me - and why so few of them seem to be willing to call him to account for it is even worse.&nbsp; Tell me if this is hypocritical: the republicans thought it was worth while to impeach president Clinton for lying about an affair that could have cost him his marriage, but no lives, but it's acceptable for Bush to lie about our reasons for going into a war that has cost thousands of Americans the lives of their sons and daughters?&nbsp; I don't get it.  The only answer is that the country has become so incredibly divided that one side can't see the other's views.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; Only three years ago, we were so united together; the attacks on the World Trade Center (I lived in New York City at the time) brought us together as a nation like no time since the second World War.&nbsp; How did the fabric fall apart so quickly?&nbsp; Why can we not find any common ground these days?&nbsp; Every issue is so polarized that there's no chance of finding middle ground.&nbsp; And yet, many of these issues are not so black and white.&nbsp; But no one is willing to make concessions.&nbsp; Part of the blame for this goes to the Bush administration for governing so far to the right when the election made it clear that the country is evenly split.&nbsp; Who else is to blame?&nbsp; Well, democrats like Nancy Pelosi would be serving their country better if they weren't diametrically opposed to everything the administration does.&nbsp; Though I can't name any Bush domestic policy that I am 100% in agreement with, there's no way that every measure out of the White House has been totally unacceptable.&nbsp; However, this is just a guess.&nbsp;   When he campaigned for president in 2000, Bush promised to be a "uniter, not a divider".&nbsp; He has certainly united the republican party, but he has not united America.&nbsp; He promised to "change the tone in Washington"; he has, but only for the worse.&nbsp; He was a"compassionate conservative"; well, conservative, certainly, but compassionate only if you earn over $250,000 a year.&nbsp; He has reneged on all three of these principles.&nbsp; I hear many republicans say that democrate will say anything to get elected; take a look at yourselves, republicans.&nbsp; To elect Saxby Chambliss in Georgia in 2002, the republicans said that Max Cleland was not in favor of a stronger America.&nbsp; For those of you who don't know Max, he lost both legs in Vietnam fighting to make America stronger.&nbsp; How the voters in Georgia fell for that vicious ploy is beyond my comprehension, but it's the republicans who said it in order to get elected; Bush made his aforementioned statements in order to get elected; and they will say whatever they need to say about John Kerry and John Edwards to get themselves elected.&nbsp; As long as the American voters buys it, they will sell it to them.  I will not be buying their invectives.&nbsp; I hope you'll join me in that regard.&nbsp; Because it's time for America to be together again.  &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The big news today was about the 9/11 report that just came out, claiming that the intelligence agencies knew enough about the plans to attack the World Trade Center in advance and didn't do anything about it.&nbsp; The report stopped short of blaming presidents Clinton and Bush, but did blame Congress and the FBI and CIA.&nbsp;   My first reaction is that yes, Congress must take some of the blame: In 1987, as a result of the Iran-Contra scandal (that's the one with Oliver North), Congress began to scale back the amount of money allocated to covert operations.&nbsp; I also recall the CIA getting lambasted in the press for its role in espionage, and the public in general found spying to be rather distasteful.&nbsp; That was followed by a number of spy scandals, involving FBI and CIA agents who were caught being double agents either for Israel or Russia.&nbsp; Covert operations became considered dangerous and a waste of taxpayer money; and Congress rode that tide all the way through.  The CIA had been handcuffed, and the FBI along with it.&nbsp; The press and Congress followed that by making President Clinton's second term hellish after the attacks on the USS Cole.&nbsp; When Clinton ordered two cruise missile attacks as retaliation against Osama bin Laden's terrorist training camps, the press and Republicans in Congress pronounced the efforts to be an attempt to divert attention from the Monica Lewinsky scandal.&nbsp; At this point, Congress is 0 for 2.  Decimated by cutbacks, the CIA and FBI began competing for the little resources that became available.&nbsp; A strong anti-CIA atmosphere&nbsp;in the age of political correctness on college campuses left the agencies with fewer and fewer potential recruits.&nbsp; With the private sector paying so handsomely, how could these federal agencies expect to get the top qualified candidates coming out of our universities?&nbsp; Impossible, given the funding they had to work with.&nbsp; Who controls those purse strings?&nbsp; Congress - now 0 for 3.  The fact is, Congress has too much power over our international policies, and it's a shame.&nbsp; Congress has never shown itself to be particularly proficient on forgein affairs, save for a few of the past members of the foreign relations committees.&nbsp; The Senate has failed to ratify several legitimate treaties in the past, including the League of Nations and the Kyoto Protocol.&nbsp; And why should they be expected to?&nbsp; A member of Congress has a constituency that is but a small part of America; why should they be expected to know anything about international relations?&nbsp; I say leave it all up to the executive branch, even this corrupt and misguided one currently in charge of Foggy Bottom.  Secondly, though, I have issue with the report's claim that the attacks on the WTC could have been stopped.&nbsp; I disagree that we could have done anything about them.&nbsp; Terrorists are a different kind of people than Americans; rather than value the lives of others, they see the world as a battle between themselves and their oppressors.&nbsp; Even while visiting America and enjoying the benfits of our relatively open society, the terrorists came to hate it.&nbsp; Hate breeds a certain type of cleverness that fanaticism only exacerbates.&nbsp;  The Koran teaches that when Moslems are attacked, they should fight back to defend themselves and Allah.&nbsp; Fundamentalist Imams have twisted that teaching around to make their followers believe that America is always attacking them, and thus they must fight back in the name of Allah.&nbsp; The Israel-Palestine conflict has a certain amount of this aspect of Islam in its fervor as well.  What does that fervor do? It leads to some quite creative plans.&nbsp; When you step back from the attacks of 9/11 and their utter inhumanity, you see a brilliantly-conceived plot.&nbsp; The report says that we didn't have the imagination to foresee the attacks; well, of course not.&nbsp; We're not radical murderous zealots.&nbsp; And not only that, but what would the CIA have done if they did have an inkling that the attacks were going to occur?&nbsp; As an unprecedented event, who would have taken the CIA seriously?&nbsp; Americans were not at all prepared to believe that the Arab world had grown so hateful of the USA as to sacrifice 19 of their own people to perform the attacks; now we think of it as common knowledge, but if you think back to September 10, who would have believed that?  The fact is, terrorists will find a way.&nbsp; When the shoe-bomber was caught, our pitiful security minds decided that the best way to stop that from happening again would be to make every traveller take off their shoes.&nbsp; This is the stupidest policy to ever come from the FAA, or whoever it came from.&nbsp;&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; Because it's no longer a surprise.&nbsp;&nbsp; Terror's primary weapon is surprise; once that element is gone, a plot loses its effectiveness.&nbsp; The Palestinian suicide bombings have decreased in part because a suicide bomber is no longer a surprise, but also because they are not terrorists in the same vein - an entirely different essay for another time.  Metal detectors were first installed at airports to prevent terrorists from bringing guns aboard in order to hijack planes.&nbsp; So hijackings stopped.&nbsp; The 9/11 terrorists used box cutters and other small metal devices to hijack the plane.&nbsp; So, there are no metal utensils on the airlines, and we take away a nail scissors.&nbsp; What's next?&nbsp; Maybe a hijacker comes on with a sharp piece of wood.&nbsp; In any case, it's like a kindergarten teacher disciplining a student: Abuse the metal utensils and I'll take them away.&nbsp;   Whatever measures we impose at the airports, there will come a time when a terrorist hatches a plot that no authority will be able to foresee or prevent.&nbsp; The attack will come out, and people will scream about why we didn't see it coming.&nbsp; Whatever the guy did will become the focus of security measures and investigations.&nbsp; And while we waste all that energy on implementing the new rules, another terrorist will be working on another plot that we again won't see coming.&nbsp; Because that's how it works; and there's nothing you can do about it.&nbsp; Implementing measures after an attack only prevents copycats from doing the same thing; useful, certainly.&nbsp; But for the amount of time and money invested in these measures, it's a waste.&nbsp; Who really thinks that searching every businessman or every passengers' shoes is going to prevent a terrorist attack?  Because the plot,&nbsp;the chief weapon, and the will to execute a plan, are invisible.&nbsp; They are contained in the mind of the terrorist; and until we invent a device that can read that mind accurately, we will not be able to prevent another terrorist attack on the United States.&nbsp; Until then, we have a choice; be scared shitless, which seems to be the current government's preference, or live your life the way you always have, and enjoy our freedom for what it is.&nbsp; I clearly am choosing the latter, and I hope more people will join me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Howard Stern this morning brought up a very good point about obscenity, and I think it deserves some further comment.&nbsp; First off, I am not a regular listener in the sense that I spend four hours every day with the radio tuned to him; rather, he happens to be on the station that wakes me up for work every morning at around 7 am.&nbsp; So I listen for 30 seconds to two minutes every day, and that's it.&nbsp; Not that I don't like what he says, but I just don't have the time to listen.   Today, that minute happened to be when he discussed the fact that NBC aired the f-word (how infantile to say it that way!) during a NASCAR race, and was betting that Michael Powell of the FCC will  not  fine the network under its zero-tolerance obscenity laws, which have cost Stern well over half a million dollars now, and may cost him his show on broadcast radio.&nbsp;&nbsp; He is expecting the FCC to be hypocritical, by fining Stern's show (because it criticizes the Bush administration) and not NASCAR (because down-home boys support Bush).   My guess is that he's right.&nbsp; And as one of his colleagues pointed out (I don't recall which one), you can't control what will be picked up on a microphone at a live sports event.&nbsp; Stern called for NBC to be forced to use a three- or ten-second delay.&nbsp; I call for everyone to get over themselves.   For years, we as Americans have debated what the effect of obscenity will be on us.&nbsp; And as a result, we have the most puritanical society on the planet, with the exception of some of the&nbsp;Moslem world.&nbsp; In the 80s, the PMRC, led by Tipper Gore (whose husband at the time was the senator from Tennessee) responded to Wal-Mart's voluntary ban on certain record covers by inventing the ubiquitous "Parental Warning" labels that are now affixed to almost every CD you buy today for its sexual content, its violence, its language, whatever.&nbsp; The debate then was that children were listening to this music that talked about various unsavory topics, and parents should know that.   This was at about the same time that the porno industry came under fire, as feminist groups tried to ban many magazines and videos as being degrading to women (funny, no one ever talks about men being degraded by porn).&nbsp; The effect would be that women would be further victimized by society and that children would grow up with the "wrong impression" of how they should treat women.   And you know what?&nbsp; None of these things happened.&nbsp; The music industry today is far more misogenist than the porno industry, at least in the hip hop field.&nbsp; No parent really wants to expose their children to either, but it happens, and it's been happening for many years.&nbsp; And as much as society has continued to decline in intelligence (take a look at some of the other blogs available here and you'll see a startling lack of critical thought), it's still orderly enough to survive well, and there are plenty of other areas to pin the blame for its decline.&nbsp;   When Janet Jackson's breast got exposed in the Super Bowl halftime show, I missed it.&nbsp; I was in a bar and talking to some people, rather than studying a screen with two fluff pop stars.&nbsp; But from the replays, yes it looks like they meant to do it, but so what?&nbsp; In the rest of the world, this wouldn't cause a ruckus.&nbsp; Several countries' TV stations&nbsp;regularly show women in various states of undress, and even in Mexico an accidental breast comes onto TV every so often, with no concomitant uproar from parental groups.&nbsp; Why here?   We're ostensibly a country that cherishes freedom, cherishes the seperation of church and state, and cherishes our free press.&nbsp; Yet when something comes onto TV that a minority group feels is obscene, all three of those principles go out the window: are these people so oversensitive that they will be scarred for life by seeing on TV what they see in the mirror every day?&nbsp; Here's another example that women point out to me all the time: In American movies, you never see a man's penis.&nbsp; You can see breasts, you can see a woman's pubic hair, but you never see a man's penis, with the possible exception of The Crying Game, and that was in context.&nbsp; In foreign movies, there is no such prohibition.&nbsp; What are filmmakers in the US afraid of?&nbsp; The government, probably.   And that's the problem.&nbsp; We're not supposed to be afraid of the government.&nbsp; The government is of the people.&nbsp; Are we afraid of ourselves?&nbsp; Is the obscenity debate really a debate over what we're afraid we have become, or what we're becoming?&nbsp; And if it is, should we be paralyzing ourselves with this fear?&nbsp; Society doesn't move forward when it's afraid to: the south was afraid of integration for many years and consequently had to be forced into it, and now there's no reason to fear it.&nbsp; But look at what the cost was; how many people had to give their lives, just to be as free as everyone else.&nbsp; Howard Stern may lose his show on the radio as a cost in the debate over obscenity, because we as a society are too afraid to find out what happens when you make the airwaves reflect what society really is: sex-obsessed, potty-mouthed, and titillated by what we're not "supposed' to see on TV.   &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's not going to happen in this election, because neither party saw this coming; and as much as it's been talked about for 2008, I don't see it quite happening there yet.&nbsp; But it's the truth, and we need to come to grips with this reality: the time has come for a woman to be President.  The first question that comes to mind for me is, Why not?&nbsp; Why SHOULDN'T it be time?&nbsp; After all, Margaret Thatcher led England through the cold war; Indira Ghandi was Prime Minister of India, the world's largest democracy.&nbsp; Benzair Bhutto was twice president of Pakistan.&nbsp; Corazon Aquino.&nbsp; Evita Peron.&nbsp; Mary Robinson.&nbsp; Violeta Chamorra.&nbsp; The list of women who have been the leader of their country is getting longer, as is the list of women who lead their states: Jodi Rell has just been inaugurated as Connecticut's governor - its SECOND woman governor.&nbsp; And it's time to make one President.  So then, Why?&nbsp; Well, let's face this fact: America peaked in the 1990s insofar as society is concerned.&nbsp; Low crime, expanding economy, decreased welfare rolls, increases in women in the businessplace, the election of numerous women for office (California in 1992 elected TWO women to the Senate), and basically an affirmation that women can handle the job of high leadership.&nbsp; Instead of it being odd, it's now commonplace; I have worked for at least three companies in my life that were owned or managed by women.&nbsp; Thus there is no longer any  question that a woman could handle the office.  Indeed, what extra consideration would go into sending our troops overseas?&nbsp; When George W Bush came into office in 2001, he pledged that our troops would no longer be used for nation building, ostensibly because the human risk was too much.&nbsp; But as soon as he found an excuse to send them into Iraq, he did it.&nbsp; I would imagine a woman would be more likely to consider the human cost of war before sending troops anywhere, but that is not to say that I think she wouldn't send them at all: when the situation would require us to act, she would do it.  And let's face it, politics in this country is an area of our society that could use a little feminization.&nbsp; As I discussed in my last post, the tenor of debate in this country has gotten worse and worse, and with the exception of Ann Coulter's misguided invectives, women have become the symbol of reasoned discussion - witness Paula Zahn (I like witnessing her!), for example, as she handles a panel of discussion as opposed to, say, Bill O' Reilly.&nbsp; The contrast in tone is remarkable, and while I'm not saying that women have a monopoly on being calm and reasonable, it's harder to find a woman on TV who screams at her opponent (except on the court shows and Maury - but let's stay focused here) than it is easy to find a man who does.  What is there to be afraid of, anyway?&nbsp; I remember when I was young, one macho way of opposing women in the White House was to say, What if there's a crisis and Madam President is on her period?&nbsp; Will she make rash decisions?&nbsp; This neanderthal way of thinking has, I expect, gone the way of the plaid leisure suit, and there shouldn't be any reason to believe that a woman would make any more a rash decision than men have in the Oval Office over time.&nbsp;   So what's missing?&nbsp; Right now, it's a lack of qualified women candidates.&nbsp; Hillary Clinton has been an exceptional Senator; were it not for the stigma attached to her last name (and her husband's presidency, so popular among the right wing), she would be a perfect candidate.&nbsp; It would not be unprecedented in world politics for a woman to lead her country after her husband had; indeed, up until two weeks ago, Mexico seemed to be headed in that direction until Vicente Fox's wife publically declined that she would run in 2006.&nbsp;   But aside from Hillary, only Dianne Feinstein of California (unpopular among conservatives) and perhaps Jennifer Granholm of Michigan have the type of personality that people would vote for in a presidential election.&nbsp; But Granholm was born in Canada, and thus ineligible; and Feinstein has made it clear that she does not seek the office.&nbsp; Christine Todd Whitman, former governor of New Jersey and EPA administrator, would be a perfect candidate but for her giggling while frisking a suspect on camera during a police raid, and resigning from the Bush cabinet cannot have made her popular in her party.  Barbara Boxer?&nbsp; Too far left.&nbsp; Maxine Waters?&nbsp; Equally radical.&nbsp; Olympia Snowe?&nbsp; Too liberal as a republican.&nbsp; Madeline Albright?&nbsp; Never run&nbsp;in an election.&nbsp; Ditto for Condoleezza Rice.&nbsp; Who does that leave us with?&nbsp; Well, there's Elizabeth Dole, who HAS won&nbsp;her own election, and IS popular, and although she's a little to the right, would probably&nbsp;make&nbsp;for a viable candidate but&nbsp;for one thing, and that's the fact that she's getting older and probably wouldn't want to take the job at this point (she'll be 72 in 2008).&nbsp;  That leaves a Hillary Clinton campaigning on her own&nbsp;merits&nbsp;rather than her husband's.&nbsp; She did this successfully in New&nbsp;York in 2000, and many believe her to be the Democratic front-runner for 2008,&nbsp;unless John Kerry wins this November.&nbsp; With her Senate seat up in&nbsp;2006, she would have the opportunity to run in 2008 without risking her&nbsp;current office.&nbsp;&nbsp;But I still don't know if she could win, and not because of the male vote: I've spoken with plenty of women who are mad at her for putting up with Bill's indiscretions.&nbsp; We're taught to forgive, but for some people this lesson doesn't apply to politicians.  So where does that leave us?&nbsp; With a leadership gap.&nbsp;&nbsp;A gap that could be closed with an out-of-nowhere candidate that comes from another sector: the private sector, perhaps?&nbsp; Or it is possible that our first woman president could come from the entertainment field, much like Ronald Reagan himself?&nbsp;&nbsp;It's a trend: Jesse Ventura, Arnold Schwarzenegger, and to a lesser extent Jon Corzine, all came from the private sector where their names were known for their NON-political lives.&nbsp; Could a woman enter the national arena on that same basis?  It will have to do for now.&nbsp; Because it's time for a woman&nbsp;to be president.  &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Two things today: &nbsp; First off, the cartoon This Land by JibJab is hilarious; great fun!&nbsp; And whoever they got to do George Bush's voice is a dead-on ringer for it.&nbsp; Awesome! &nbsp; Second, I saw a sign today that made me cringe.&nbsp; I was driving back from Boston on the Mass Pike, and in the right lane a guy had taped a sign to the back of his SUV: "Combat veteran will pay cash for Michael Moore's dead lifeless body".&nbsp; At first I was offended by its vulgarity, but then I became upset by the driver's clear lack of historical perspective.&nbsp; When I passed the guy I saw he couldn't have been over 25, and once again my favorite phrase came to mind:&nbsp;They don't teach kids anything in school these days. &nbsp; See, it's clear that the driver was offended by Michael Moore's recent film Farenheit 9/11.&nbsp; Since this kid was only old enough to have fought in either Afghanistan or Iraq, the Moore implication is intuitive, but I think it's a solid guess.&nbsp; So the question is, What would make this kid so furious at Moore?&nbsp;  &nbsp; I haven't seen the movie, but from what I've heard from&nbsp;qualified friends who have, it doesn't seem as if Moore was critical of the soldiers themselves, but rather of the Bush administration.&nbsp; So why is this driver pissed?&nbsp; The only conclusion I can reach is that he doesn't like Moore's criticism of President Bush.&nbsp; And the sign makes it clear that this not just a liminal feeling; it's a deep hatred. &nbsp; So here's the question I would pose to our ex-Marine (judging from the haircut).&nbsp; As a combat veteran, you fought for what is generally called Our Freedom.&nbsp; What is this freedom?&nbsp; It is the freedom of individual rights guaranteed by the Constitution, and most generally in the first Amendment.&nbsp; For those not familiar, allow me to quote: &nbsp; "Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof; or abridging the freedom of speech, or of the press; or the right of the people peaceably to assemble, and to petition the government for a redress of grievances." &nbsp; In other words, Moore's exercise of two of these rights (speech and redress) is exactly what you as a combat veteran fought for.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I have no problem with the guy's disagreement of Moore's opinion, but to call for his head shows an intolerance of debate, and this is where I really want to go with this essay.&nbsp; Since the mid 90s, informed debate has been dead in this country.&nbsp; Take a look at shows like Crossfire and any of the right-wing tirades on Fox News; do you see any debate there?&nbsp; Does The O'Reilly Factor ever look at any view other&nbsp;than the conservative view?&nbsp; No.&nbsp; Does Rush Limbaugh consider alternate opinions to have any validity?&nbsp; No.&nbsp;  &nbsp; With the exception of some of the sunday morning network shows (Tim Russert's Meet The Press being the most significant of them), I can't watch any of these ostensible "debate" programs.&nbsp; Indeed, Russert strikes me as being the only one of these hosts who truly takes a neutral-side opinion, although he only lobbed softball questions when he had Bush on earlier this year - probably something that the White House forced him into, if I had to guess.&nbsp; No surprise - indeed at the start of this administration, a number of White House Press Corps writers lost their credentials because the administration didn't like what they wrote about Bush.&nbsp; It's not illegal, but it is disingenious to swear to "preserve, protect, and defend the Constitution" and then cleverly stomp on the first amendment. &nbsp; And getting back to the ex-Marine, what's he so up in arms for about criticizing the president?&nbsp; After all, if there's one clear lesson we learned from Vietnam, it is that you don't blame the soldiers fighting the war for the mistakes made by the White House.&nbsp; No one is upset with our soldiers; unlike the Vietnam vets who got pelted with rotten fruit when they returned home, the Iraq soldiers are being hailed as heroes.&nbsp; It's a lesson well-learned. &nbsp; But that doesn't mean that we should reserve criticism from the President.&nbsp; In Vietnam, both Johnson and Nixon took plenty of heat for the war; why shouldn't Bush feel such heat?&nbsp; FDR had plenty of critics in WWII, for domestic policy steps that people didn't like; why should Bush be exempt from that?&nbsp;&nbsp; In America, criticizing the President is a right, although I grant that in times of crisis it is better to back him up - however, this is no time of crisis.&nbsp; September 11 was almost three years ago, and I was in NYC for much of those two years.&nbsp; There is no crisis in NY, nor in Iraq; a war on foreign soil is not a crisis, especially one that we started. &nbsp; For years, we have been proud of the fact that we can publically declare our disdain for the man in the White House; why all of a sudden is it "unpatriotic" to do so?&nbsp; In Russia such a declaration would get you arrested; in Zimbabwe, it would get you killed.&nbsp; If we are to call ourselves the leaders of the free world, we need to recognize that all this criticism is a part of freedom.&nbsp; Otherwise we risk descending into the pit of despair that the people of Italy and Germany felt in the fascist regimes of the 1940s, or that the Soviet citizens felt in the Stalinish 1950s, or that black South Africans felt in the apartheid 1970s, or.....well, the list goes on.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Without a knowledge of history, we are doomed to repeat its mistakes.&nbsp; To the ex-Marine I saw today, I say: Open a book.&nbsp; I'll even let you borrow some of mine. &nbsp; &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I almost forgot to mention that I saw two foreign movies last night.&nbsp; The first one, Todo Sobre Mi Madre, I actually found somewhat disappointing.&nbsp; Great acting, to be sure, but the plot just didn't put me on the edge of my seat the way I expected it to.&nbsp; Beautifully done, of course, Almodovar being who he is.&nbsp; But disappointing as a story. &nbsp; Amores Perros, on the other hand, was riveting.&nbsp; I have liked Gael Garcia Bernal's acting since I first saw him in Y Tu Mama Tambien, and here he did not disappoint, and actually no one did.&nbsp; Quentin Tarantino fans will tell me that this is just like any Tarantino movie, but I didn't watch those; I watched this.&nbsp; Though the second segment in Amores Perros got a little long and dry, the remainder of the movie was captivating.&nbsp; My favorite recently-viewed foreign movie continues to be Sex and Lucia, but this is certainly a close second place. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Actually, I had a lot of them today.&nbsp; I was reading an article in Newsweek about the rise in female infidelity, and it got me thinking about why this is happening.&nbsp; The first thing that comes to mind, of course, is that after thousands of years of sexual repression, women are finally able to do what they want for themselves, an ability men have had forever.&nbsp; But it also made me think, Marriage isn't natural.&nbsp; Why do we treat it as such? &nbsp; After all, there could not have been marriage before the invention of religion; I would guess that cavemen and cavewomen simply kept together because they liked each other, and when the arrangement failed to work any more, someone took off.&nbsp; Children were probably raised in a tribal setting, much like elephants do today.&nbsp; Village elders probably acted as dads for a whole tribe.&nbsp;  &nbsp; For a few thousand years now, we've tried to make marriage work.&nbsp; It has to some degree, but it's not the paradigm for life that western society has made it.&nbsp; I certainly don't plan on getting married; if I feel the situation is right, I'll do it, but I'm certainly not forcing myself into it, nor do I have a timeline (which is another way of forcing it).&nbsp; My grandmother once told me, "Robert, don't bother getting married,&nbsp; just go have fun with all the women you can."&nbsp; Sage advice. &nbsp; We are probably unaware of witnessing a major change in social history.&nbsp; For the last hundred years, it has become possible to not join a church and remain alive; no crusades or inquisitions exist now to weed out non-believers.&nbsp; Thus secularism has flourished, and regular church-going was the first casualty.&nbsp; Marriage is next; what's the use of continuing an outdated mode of living in a world that has changed so much in just 60 years?&nbsp; I see no point to it.&nbsp;  &nbsp; When humans were an agrarian species, women were the dominant sex; they had, after all, brought up all the children, so theirs were the stronger figures.&nbsp; Without any way to tell whose dad was whose, one's identity would be entirely wrapped around one's mother (hence the Jewish identity coming through the mother's side).&nbsp; Marriage was forced upon men (ironically enough, BY men writing the rules once religion was invented) to keep them with their women and children , allowing for an identity to be handed down on the man's side: thus the practice of keeping the male's last name when a couple becomes married.&nbsp; What better way to keep men from going out and impregnating the entire tribe by themselves, which biologically we can do. &nbsp; So perhaps this is the first step back: back to the time when women dominated society, when they were the ones who set the rules and raised the children.&nbsp; Another recent article outlines the phenomenon of "marrying up" and how the result becomes undereducated males being unable to marry.&nbsp; Social Darwinism, to be sure: just as the survival of the fittest works in physical strength, so too does it work in reproductive strength when the women of a society are granted (or usurp) the right to select their mates.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Gosh, I thought a lot today. &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Since Formula One racing isn't very popular in this country, this post will probably go ignored by many. But I have to put my comments down somewhere, so why not here?  For those who don't know, this has been a very interesting season in F1, mostly because of the absolute dominance of Ferrari. Michael Schumacher has won all but one of this year's races so far (we're coming up on race number 13), and teammate Rubens Barrichello is the only driver to finish every race this season. Between the two of them they have already won Ferrari the constructor's championship. It is perhaps the most dominating season ever witnessed in Formula One, and Schumacher has cemented his place as one of the all-time great drivers with this amazing domination.  So what's so interesting? Well, it's rare that any sports witnesses such abject domination by any one individual. Think the NBA during Michael Jordan's peak years, or the NHL when Wayne Gretzky was shattering all the single-season scoring records. That's still not quite the level of domination that Schumacher has displayed this year. It's really that incredible. That's not the sort of performance we see all that often in sport, and it's important to recognize it when it's happening.  But what has been truly interesting this year is the shift in the balance of power below Ferrari. Traditionally, the runners-up of late have been McLaren and Williams; but this year, neither of those teams are in the running for even third-place honors. Instead, Renault has turned in its second consecutive fine season (led by Spanish superstar Fernando Alonso), and BAR-Honda has emerged as a power with popular British and Japanese drivers Jenson Button and Takuma Sato. Indeed, until last week's race in Hungary, Button was the only non-Ferrari driver with a shot at winning the season title.  Button's emergence has been stunning. Until this year, few put much stock in him, though he has shown such promise as a youth racer. He didn't seem totally immersed in his driving, and didn't get many results. All of a sudden, this year, he's focused, and although he hasn't won a race yet, he's been on more podiums than any other non-Ferrari driver. Where Alonso was last year's surprise (along with Kimi Raikkonen, who has had a dismal year) , Button has been this season's new kid to watch.  Also interesting have been the drivers fading into the past. Olivier Panis will almost certainly retire after this year; David Coulthard has been almost invisible this season, and Ralf Schumacher is out for the remainder of the season after a crash in Indianapolis, his second consecutive season with a major incident. Juan Pablo Montoya is clearly disinterested with his final season at Williams, and Mark Webber's year at Jaguar is a major step down from 2003.  Felipe Massa has failed to live up to expectations; Cristiano da Matta, after a great rookie season last year, has so disappointed Toyota that he won't be asked back next year. Kimi Raikkonen is fortunate that he's only 24 years old; he's proven that he knows how to race, and the blame for his underperformance sits squarely with Mercedes, whose engines this year have been totally unreliable, exploding at least three times on the Finn and conking out on several others.  In short, this season has been nothing like what was expected, with the sole exception of Renault's performance. Ferrari is performing beyond expectation, along with BAR-Honda. Sauber and Renault are probably the only two teams that are just where they would be expected. Everyone else is having a dismal season. That's a lot of unhappy team principals!  The only driver to win a race this year who is not named Michael Schumacher is Renault's Jarno Trulli, and even his win is a little tainted; although Michael said after the Monaco race that he didn't think he would catch Trulli anyway, fans will always wonder if Schumacher might have had a perfect season in Montoya hadn't crashed into him in the tunnel...         
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Last week I had the opportunity to see the exchange between Bill O'Reilly and Michael Moore, which was taped during the Democratic National Convention.  I can't sit through The O'Reilly Factor for a number of reasons, not the least of which being that it causes me to reach for the Rolaids.  But for this special occasion I thought it was worth viewing, and as a friend of mine had it on her TiVo, I had the fortunate opportunity to watch.  My initial response at the end of it was that Michael Moore made a poor impression.  He didn't adequately outline his viewpoints, and I was dissatisfied with his rebuttals to O'Reilly's contention that Bush hadn't lied to the American people because he was actually just misinformed.  Moore insisted that since the President hadn't told the truth, he lied, regardless of whatever the reason for the misinformation.  O'Reilly defended the president by saying that since his sources told him he was telling the truth, and several other sources did, too, then he wasn't lying.  Both men were wrong.  Moore did make a halfhearted attempt to state the real problem behind the president's raison de guerre, that being the desire of the Bush administration to pin the 9/11 attacks on Saddam Hussein.  But he let the subject drop quickly, preferring instead to ask O'Reilly he question of what to tell the parents of soldiers who have died in Iraq for a false reason.  O'Reilly's answer wasn't bad, but it did come across as somewhat coldhearted.   However, that's not what I wanted to discuss here.  Let me state for the record that I supported the effort to remove Saddam Hussein from power.  My reasons, however, differ from those given by the White House.  See, I lived in the Bay Ridge area of Brooklyn for much of the the past three years; in that area, we have a heavy Middle-Eastern population, and I got to meet a few expatriot Iraqis.  One of them had a particularly poignant story to tell me that led me to believe that the Hussein regime had to go.  To the best of my recollection, here is his story:  Being from the south of Iraq, this particular Iraqi lived with his wife and children - all of them fairly young - in a modest home, in a small neighborhood.  One day, he went to work, doing whatever it was he did, and while he was away, the local militia called out the neighbors for noontime prayers.  Naturally, his family went with the rest of the neighborhood to the mosque, whereupon the doors were locked and the militia opened fire on everyone inside.  His family was massacred.  The few survivors told him when he got home that the militia said that they knew there were spies in the neighborhood and that the killings were a message from Saddam.  He immediately fled to Saudi Arabia, familyless, and the US State Department succeeded in relocating him in New York.  I asked him if he had other such stories.  "There are hundreds of them in Iraq today.  Saddam is a brutal tyrant," was his reply.   That, coupled with Hussein's attacks on the Kurds, his attacks on the people of Basra, and his refusal for so many years to allow UN weapons inspection teams into the country - and his inability to account for all the weapons that we already knew he had - were, in my opinion, justification enough for his removal.  Is he the only dictator we should remove?  No, there are others as well.  But we have no better documentation and history of a brutal regime than that of Saddam Hussein.  There lies the reason we should have invaded Iraq; not because of intelligence reports that were skewed from the beginning.  And why didn't Bush just come out and say that the reasons I mentioned were justification enough for an invasion?  Because, in my opinion, the Administration didn't think they would get the support of the American people for simply making it a humanitarian mission.  After all, this is a president who swore in his election campaign that he would not be party to "nation-building" the way the Clinton administration had been.  This is a president who realized his greatest approval ratings immediately after 9/11, proving to him beyond a doubt that when people get scared, they get behind him - and that's exactly where he wanted them on the Iraq question.  Saddam Hussein is coming to destroy you; get behind me and I'll save you (as soon as you pass another tax cut).   Bush had every reason to tell the Iraq story that he wanted to tell, knowing it would be effective.  Why rely upon high-minded human rights activists to convince the American people that Iraq is evil when you can scare them into supporting you by announcing the presence of nuclear weapons pointed at the United States, even though they wouldn't be capable of firing upon us for several years?  Why waste time with the United Nations security council when we're going to provide most of the cover anyway, and who needs that silly intellectual debate that the Europeans enjoy so much?  We're big and powerful and strong; we can have our way because we so will it.  Iraq is coming to get you; get behind me and we can WIN!  Cheerleader Bush was exactly right, and the Iraq invasion was off and running.  Now, we know that Saddam didn't have weapons of mass destruction (a term I loathe, just so you know) lying around waiting to be detonated; we know that his Republican Guard was, as usual, greatly inferior to our military forces.  We know that if he DID have WMD being constructed, there wasn't so much of it in production that it couldn't be hidden quickly.  But we also know that the Bush administration greatly misestimated the guile of the Iraqi people, and that they had no clear solution for what to do with Iraq once their military work was done.  Granted it is not easy to predict the reaction of any conquered peoples, but might it not have been somewhat easier to convince them that we were liberators if we had gone in for the right reasons?  And more to the point, might it have been more convincing if it wasn't just the English-speaking countries that invaded?   The deplorable situation at Abu Ghraib may have been an unintended but logical consequence of an occupation; war brings out the best in people and the worst in people.  But allowing the Secretary of Defense, Donald Rumsfeld, to escape unpunished makes a laughingstock of our entire government and media process.  Here is a man who is famous for his handling of organizations, and whose authority goes unchallenged at the Department of Defense.   While an isolated incident in the Iraq prisons could have been chalked up to renegade soldiers awash in war rage, the number of incidents leads one to believe that there's more to it than a bunch of undereducated rednecks having a fun afternoon at the torture chamber.  That the president has failed to publically reprimand the secretary is a disgrace, but the fact that the media backed off so quickly from its criticism of the administration is an abomination.  Such behavior from the so-called leader of the free world is not going to win us points in the countries we wish to influence, either those in the Greater Middle East Initiative states or in the emerging democracies of Latin America and Africa.  The Iraq war has been a success in two areas: One, it removed one of the world's primary despots from power, freeing many from his tyrrany.  Two, it proved that American military might is just as strong as ever, and as administered by the Marines who have done their jobs properly, this force has been the knight in shining armor it was intended to be.   But there are numerous failures as well: One, the president has failed to show the rest of the world why they should trust him.  Two, he has made it clear that he doesn't care what the rest of the world thinks.  Three, we have been unable to stamp our democratic ideals on a people who are not as comfortable with them as we are - and why should they be?  Just because we know what's best for us doesn't mean we know what's best for the rest of the world.  Four, we have bred cynicism in the people whose loyalty we need in order to pursue the war on terrorism, that is, the underpriviliged of the Arab states.  Five, we have failed to capture Osama bin Laden, a far more dangerous figure than Saddam Hussein ever was.  Proof?  Saddam never dreamed he could attack the USA on its own soil - he was waiting for a long-range missile with nuclear capabilities to do the job.  Osama bin Laden inspires radical muslims to sacrifice themselves by flying jets into big buildings - in America.  Which of the two men is more dangerous to you?  Bill O'Reilly concluded his interview with Michael Moore by stating that the Bush-haters are so blinded by their dislike of the president that they won't admit that there are times when he is right.  My problem with O'Reilly is that he is so blinded by his neocon agenda that he won't admit to any of the president's mistakes.  Iraq is such a mistake; not because we shouldn't be there, but because we should have been there for the right reasons, with the right allies, with the right agenda, and at the right time.  By executing the plan the way we have, we have failed to meet any of those criteria.    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Business-section readers may have noticed recently that something interesting has happened within the past week.  Cox Communications, a multi-tiered media giant, has announced that they plan to buy all of their outstanding shares of stock, which effectively returns them to their once-held status as a private company.  No longer subject to the whims of Wall Street accountants, they will no longer have the need to fudge their earnings for the sake of the shareholders.  So what?  So plenty.  Media companies over the past decade have fallen onto hard times.  Since 2001, the advertising market that drives these companies' earnings has been pretty lacklustre.  Accounting scandals both in financial areas and in the circulation figures have scarred several large companies, including some widely respected ones.  Pressure to continue growth, which is used to encourage higher stock price, has caused many media companies to put unrealistic expectations on their employees, and to cut necessary costs in lieu of this growth.  The result is that the advertising industry has become a miserable place to work, after so long being one of the great jobs in the United States.  All because of Wall Street.  Not only that: with the continued unreliability of the media-mesuring systems (Nielsen and Arbitron), which relies upon the average citizen to write down all their days' TV viewing or radio listening, stations are forced to rely upon flimsy numbers to set their ad prices in a time where Joe Viewer isn't sure if he watched Seinfeld on the local TV affiliate or on TBS; and Nielsen doesn't credit either channel if the viewer fails to get the call letters wrong, or if he gets the time wrong.  Much viewing goes uncredited by Neilsen because of these mistakes, which are not surprising given the average person's intelligence.  What Cox Communications is doing by pulling out of the stock market game is allowing their business to act naturally.  There will not be any pressure to fudge numbers; a bad year can be a bad year, and they can recover - instead of panicking and firing executives because of a sagging ad economy, they can remain innovative while keeping their jobs.  Expenses - an essential part of the business world - can return to reasonable levels, instead of the piddling that many companies have today.  And the company can turn the excess cash into a profit-sharing plan for its employees, allowing the people who work at the company to make the money, instead of it going to a bunch of accountants at an investment firm.  In all, a great move.  Some other media giants have announced stock buybacks, although they have not announced their intention to make the buyback complete.  Technically, once a company owns 55% of its stock, they can pretty much dictate what they want to do, since the shareholders won't have enough votes to override them.  But a complete buyback is much safer, for then you can eliminate the shares entirely.  Perhaps this will mark a return to the concept of a "responsible corporation", something we have not seen in some time.  Death to Enron; may Cox Communications succeed!  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Since Islamic radicalism has been in the news lately (under the headings "The War On Terrorism" and such), I thought I'd reflect upon some facts and history concerning this religion and try to add some sensibility to what is often a fiery debate.  That having been said, I still sincerely believe that anyone under 40 years old today will at some point in their lifetime witness a major war between Islamic states and the West, possibly involving a nuclear exchange.  And it's really a shame. In its purest form, Islam is a benign religion; subservience to Allah (Jehovah and Elohim are two other names He uses, depending on the follower) and belief that He alone is the all-powerful, all-knowing, and ever merciful is the cornerstone of the religion. Prayers five times a day are required to fulfill one's abject subservience to Allah, and indeed the world "Islam" can be translated both as "Peace" and "Surrender", with the connotation being that with surrender to God one finds peace. So why has this religion become synonymous with violence and random killing?  Basically, it's because Islam has been hijacked by extremists over the past century, most likely as a reaction to colonialism.  In his book "In The Shadow Of The Prophet", Milton Viorst counts time after time where extremists have murdered their more-moderate (and thus more modern) counterparts in the name of strict adherence to the Koran - to an extremist, any interpretation of the Koran other than the literal interpretation is blasphemous; and blasphemy is punishable by death.  The logic is that since the Koran is the word of Allah Himself, and Mohammed was the last prophet, then we are to believe that this is our final chance to do right.  Indeed the Koran is full of admonitions: over and over, Allah asks mankind to recall how the Jews forsook Him in worshipping idols, how the Christians mistook Jesus for being His son, and how the Arabs at the time of Mohammed were once again worshipping idols (the desert Jinn).  It is easy to make the inference that the Koran is our last chance.  But there is much more to the Koran than this.  The Koran is a guide to living; in it, Allah sets out rules for the treatment of women (which in Arabia was abysmal prior to the Koran), for divorce, for charity, and many other areas of everyday life.  But like the Bible (heavily referenced in the Koran), the Koran cannot possibly cover everything in a modern society, and thus must be interpreted somewhat liberally to be germane to our lives today.  Here is where the extremists differ from the modernists: Modern interpretation says to use the Koran as a general guide, much as Christianity today takes the New Testament and applies its lessons to present-day life.  Extremist interpretation does not believe that Allah meant for us to interpret the Koran with any liberality; if Allah had so willed, he would have said so to Mohammed.  But the extremists' greatest Koranic weapon has to do with war.  According to the Koran, it is acceptable in Allah's eyes to kill non-believers if they are attacking you.  If they are benign to your presence, however, then you should reciprocate with benevolence as well.  It is the liberal interpretation of  this  particular principle that has given rise to militant Islam; for the militants believe that any encroachment of Western culture is an attack, and this justifies the kinds of attacks on the West that have been perpetrated by Al Qaeda, and the bombings by the Al-Aqsa Martyrs Brigade on the Israelis during the second Intifadeh.  While the latter would somewhat justify itself even under strict interpretation of the Koran, the former would not.  Hence the power of the mullahs: if an imam or mullah so chose, he could preach that the west is benign and we shouldn't attack them.  But with the American military presence in the Muslim world, more and more mullahs are seeing this as an actual attack upon their society, and thus their actions are justified in their eyes and the eyes of Allah.  Osama bin Laden's primary issue with the United States is, after all, our military presence on the Moslem Holy Land.  While our bases are not located in the Rub' al Khali or anywhere near Mecca or Medina, the fact is that we are present in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, keepers of the Holy Shines, and therefore infidels to the Koran.  His interpretation is that it is Allah's will, according to the Koran, that they attack the USA so long as we are present on their land.  Ostensibly, once we are out of Saudi Arabia, the attacks will cease.  But of course, now we are in Iraq and Afghanistan, which while not Holy lands, they are nonetheless Islamic nations, and no doubt he has extended his fatwa to include these nations as well.  Is it truly an Islamic principle?  Maybe.  As Americans, we don't really know what happens on a day to day basis in the Moslem world.  We don't know what it's like to wake up in Nablus in the morning, or in Baghdad, or in Kabul.  But we have an opportunity to see what it was like to live in Kabul during the Taliban regime: a recent film out of Afghanistan that won a number of respected awards, called "Osama", shows the terror that the Taliban regime inflicted on their own people, and what life was like on a daily basis for women under this tremendous oppression.  It's based on a true story, but the story isn't as instructive as the cinematography of what Taliban Afghanistan was like - brutal, tremendously misogynist, and phenomenally stricken with poverty.  Islam is behind Christianity in terms of age by about 600 years.  So as a religion, Islam is in its 1400s right now - in the history of Catholicism, that puts it at the end of the Middle Ages, prior to the Renaissance and about 150 years before the advent of Protestantism.  Could Islam be headed for the kind of reformation that the Church experienced, which led eventually to the modernization of society?  Continuing with the parallel, it puts Isalm about 300 years before the time of Cardinal Richielieu, which marked the beginning of the modern state - in which the focus of the state's energy was the state itself, and not on its adherence to the church.  Is Islam heading in that direction?  Certainly nations such as Turkey and Egypt, both modern and somewhat liberal in their interpretation of Islam, have shown that extremism is not necessarily the future.  Algeria, caught in a brutal civil war between extremists and moderates for many years, has recently seen its extremist movement lose popularity and the country is returning to normalcy - and modernity.  Indonesia seems to be headed in this direction as well.  Thus it is difficult to say whether Islam is on any clear parallel path with Christianity.  In any case, the next hundred years or so will be tough as Islam struggles to decide its future.  States such as Iran and Afghanistan have used brutal methods to keep their population in check, and it is only a matter of time before the people revolt.  In Iran, the country has been edging away from the extremism that was started by Ayatollah Khomenei, and since his death several years ago the youth of the country have expressed more of a tendency toward Westernizing.  Politically Iran's theocracy is proving inadequate; earlier this year, mass resignations in Parliament reflected the distrust that the secular politicians have with regard to the ruling Mullahs.  Should Iran's theocratic state collapse, it would possibly signal the beginning of the end of extremist interpretation.  What kind of implications would that have on the west?  For one thing, the west would recoup the ability to send their positive messages into the Moslem world.  Right now, Wahabbi sects dominate the information paths in Saudi Arabia, and the imams in Iran control those paths.  Between those two nations are found the great majority of the extremists who threaten the US.  With the ability to once again project a positive image of the West, which was happening in the early 1980s, perhaps the terrorist threat would subside.  But there is a very important factor that has not gone well-discussed here with regard to its impact on terrorist motivation, and that is the Israeli-Palestinian crisis.   So long as the West (read: United States) supports Israel in the conflict, the Moslem world will continue to rally around the Palestinians and against the US.  Bill Clinton's efforts to bring peace to the area did not go unnoticed in the Moslem world, but that did not prevent attacks on the US for other transgressions (the USS Cole bombing was probably more a reaction to US military presence on the Arabian peninsula than for the support of Israel).  However, George W. Bush's failure to engage either side of the Palestinian conflict may well have been a contributing motivation to the attackers of the World Trade Center and the Pentagon.  Indeed, I personally have interviewed several people from Islamic nations who verified this hypothesis.  Of course, none of us really know what their full motivation was; but to hear several Pakistani men suggest that the attacks would not have been carried out against a Clinton administration was certainly food for thought.  A modernized Islam would be a welcome addition to the world.   The golden age of Islam, best characterized by Moorish Spain, was a time of scientific learning, beautiful cities, and peace.  In many ways, today's extremism is the exact opposite of what Islam can be, and as such it's a shame that the West views Islam with such contempt - but given its recent history, Islam has earned this title for itself.  When seen objectively, Islam is a very interesting religion, and its history colorful.  Some have claimed Mohammed to be the most influential person in human history, surpassing even Jesus (who, by the way, Muslims regard as a great prophet but no more than that).  As it is claiming more adherents every day, the world's fastest-growing religion is in a position to shape the course of history for the next several hundred years.  With luck, that history will not include the widely-predicted clash of civilizations that could lead to a true third world war.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is really just a minor entry meant to fill in some time; I haven't had much of that lately, so I thought I'd tag something in here before people thought I'd vanished.  I have not.  The Democratic convention is over, the troops are fired up...and I still don't think they can win.  Which really sucks, because I can't stand the Bush administration.  I don't like neo-con foreign policy, and I don't like evangelicals running domestic policy.  How does a country as nominally moderate as the United States let itself be run by right-wing fanatics, who are pushing the country into fascism?  Bush's slogan at the 2000 RNC was "It won't be long now" - and no, it won't be, but what will it not be long before?  It won't be long before the corporations of this country have a 100% free ride from the government.  It won't be long before the internet is taxed.  It won't be long before the government allows itself to spy on citizens for whatever reason they deem necessary.  The time has already come when the police can arrest someone for wearing an anti-Bush t shirt (Charleston WV this past May); the press has already succumbed to the White house's demands for favorable coverage of all and every thing they do.  And yet, I don't see the Democrats winning in November.  For one thing, they spent too much time by using the economy as an issue.  As any economist will tell you, the economy goes in cycles.  If it falls, it will come back.  If it soars, it will have to come back down to earth eventually.  Making criticism of the economy over the past year has been a mistake for the Democrats.  Had they criticized Bush's economic philosphies, however, that would be different.  After all, by giving out a tax cut to the richest Americans while a war was on, causing the surplus to evaporate, the President took an expected downturn in the economy and made it much worse and much longer-lasting than it needed to be.  But the democrats haven't specified that this is the area of contention.  Just saying "the economy sucks" doesn't explain why you could do anything better.  That was really all I had to say tonight.  I hope I'm wrong about Bush getting reelected, but I just don't see him losing.  The Republican party is very good at winning elections they shouldn't win.  This will be one of them, and unless the democrats can coax James Carville out of retirement, I don't see this election going the way I hope it will.  I am preparing for the final descent of the USA into the fascist state that the Bushies are hoping to make it for the next four years.  This sucks.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>