<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What a day ive had.   My Uncle and cousin came up to visit us folks today, and in order to keep my 2 year old cuz amused we took him to an animal centre *joy*.   I had a 'great' time feeding chickens and tiny fluff balls that you might call rabbits, and the dreaded goats.   When you visit one of these places you dont expect to be nearly killed by a wild rampaging goat after a bag of strangly coloured animal food.   I could have died!I could have been eaten!My life was in danger!      And there seemed to be a plague of these wasp looking things called hoover flies.   Is this Bin Ladens next attemp to cause chaos ?   Lol.      I'd better go before my mind starts working overtime.      Goodbyb!             Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com       
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well my dear fwend, bitch and hugga luva Dazu is off to sunny Spain today where the rain falls mainly on the plain.     Have a guten time dearie .    *coughs* bitch, i want to go on holiday!          See you when you come back           Byebye          Adios to the rest of you.                   Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hewwo and welcome to another dose of my blogg.     Just as addictive as drugs but with only half the side effects!     My feet really hurt today, but you cant blame the poor ickle things as they were walking round Lincoln yesterday for 8 hours.Thats alot of shopping.And alot of hours to spend with your muther....     Im suprised i returned alive.     &nbsp;   The rest of the week doesnt seem too bad.Get to see my ickle cousin Gabriele (the male name...not the female one) on Thursday,Friday and Saturday, as him and my Uncle are coming up to visit us folks.     Still havent his baby sister yet (Isabella) whos sommit like 3 months old now..........oh dear.       &nbsp;   Well im going to send some emails now, so for now:     Goodbyb!             Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Once upon a time there was a weekend.And that weekend was full of crappitty excitment.     Saturday was full of jobs&nbsp;to earn some well earned cash, and Sunday was rather light with the 'joy' of going to see Thunderbirds....       &nbsp;   Ok, im going to stop talking like that now, its really starting to annoy me.     &nbsp;   So as you can see that was my weekend.Not too bad, but not great for someone whos starting to climb walls ( i really dont know what i mean by that, but i will include it anyway).     Got dragged along to see 'Thunderbirds', where the cinema was FULL of screaming little brats, one of them i had to put up with kicking the back of my chair through-out the ENTIRE film.I really did have to resist the urge to turn round and have a go at the little gremling.     I think i deserve a medal of some sort.     In my opinion the film was badly acted and the storyline was extremly poor.It was a slow start but near the end it got more interesting (if you could say that).     It was crap but watchable.       &nbsp;   Also whilst in Lincoln my parents descided to buy my birfday prezzie.You must understand that they brought it in front of me, the bloke in the shop let me look at it...and then it was taken off me, not to be seen again for 16 days.     I think it was rather cruel.     But when we got home, they put it in the kitchen....and so i sneaked in there to have a look.     And while i had a quick look, i transfered my numbers from my old fone to my new one.And also picked my ringtone, and message tone....and wallpaper.....and skin.....and played one of the games called 'Go!Hamster'.....and set the clock and date.      So really it wasnt a quick look...............Hmmm.          &nbsp;    So to my ickle fwendies (if your reading this), my fone is 'out of order' until the 6th of August because im keeping my old number and its being transfered.       But i wont get any messages (not like anybody txt's me...but you must on my birfday) unti the 11th :D.        &nbsp;   Wow ive really gone on.     So Goodbyb!       &nbsp;    p.s- Dazu have a guten holiday! :D              Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Yay!Its nearly the weekend, but i dunno why im so happy about that,because nothings going to happen!     Maybe i will have to buy myself a social life next time i venture into town.....     Finally some of that summer sun that everybody loves, but doesn't hardly know because its never there.     I would go and get a tan, but due to my unfortunate pale-ness,i go from red back to white again and never go even slightly brown.     Dam you skin....u win this time!     I really am looking forward to my birthday now.Probably because i saw my mums little book where she works out the bill's and shite.She really shouldnt write down what she has got planned for me and leave the thing lying around.     Well....it wasnt actually lying around, but in the cupboard in the kitchen on the top shelf.......           &nbsp;   So for now     Goodbyb     XxXxXx             Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Your bored right, and so you make a trip into town.     If i was bored before i travelled in, then that boredom was only doubled by the time i had a look around.     There is absolute crap in town.The only half decent womens clothes shops are:     New Look     Dorothy Perks     Select     Etam     Next       &nbsp;   But all of them are either full of crap,cheap looking or expensive.Arghhhhhhhh.The council really should get a move on to get some other shops moving into the area.     I was trying to look for something really purdy for 'Lauras' sweet 16th prom style party, but i found nowt.     Instead i came home with some fairy wings and some milk free biccies which taste like powered crap.     But then what do you expect really..............       &nbsp;   So for now     Byebye             Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Why is is that one minute your perfectly happy and talking to your mates, and then the next you find yourself getting angry and starting to feel really pissed off.        &nbsp;    I mean, i havent fallen out with the un-named person *coughs* peewee, its just that he really started to piss me off, and spoke to me as if it was all my fault.  &nbsp;     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   [edit]&nbsp;Ok, ive realised what i put is wrong,&nbsp;cos it was a spur of the moment kinda thing which i didnt&nbsp;mean.     So all ive got to say to you peewee dearie is:     Im sorry,     Im sorry,     Im sorry,     Im sorry.......and loads more of that (but i just cant be bothered to type it)     XxXx     &nbsp;    [edit] im feeling happier now that i have calmed down.All is well again.          urlLink      Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I'd like to say something interesting today.But im not as there isnt anything interesting to say except:     Im bored,     Im bored,     Im bored,     Im bored     and IM BORED.       &nbsp;   Enough said, as i know you already feel sorry for 'Moi'.     OOOOOh....there is something interesting to say!     Its 22 days to my birthday and counting.      *yum* i cant almost smell that cake (which would be evil as its still 3 and so weeks away)          &nbsp;   Adios Amigos      xXx        &nbsp;     &nbsp; &nbsp;             Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com      
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well its officially the start of the week and what a day its been.     You'd think a shopping trip to Lincoln would be easy, but trust me it isnt.     An early start followed by the sight of  'Rizzie' , dripping from head to toe with moistness (and by that i mean fresh out of the shower).     Next thing that happened is that our dear friend and twin of  'Fin' ,didnt know that we&nbsp;     were&nbsp;still going to Lincoln.But a quick phone call to her mother ( Mrs Wendy)  soon sorted that out, and  'Row'  was soon woken up from her deep deep sleep from beyond.       &nbsp;    What seemed like hours later that poor excuse of a train greeted our eyes and we where soon on our merry merry way!      Our VIP seats aboard the train where extremly comfortable and our journey was made that little more brighter with our friendly and really rather groovy ticket meister.... Mr Dave  (we did find out that his real name was actually  Mark ...but we prefered  Dave ).       &nbsp;   As soon as we stepped foot on Lincoln soil, we made our way to ye olde Odeon to feast our eyes on 'Shrek 2'.Oh how we laughed (!), and  'Rizzie'  did an excellent impression of someone trying to dance, which im sure made several young children cry.       &nbsp;   After&nbsp; hours of rib tickling laughter, we made our way to 'poundland', where we spent the rest of the afternoon prancing around dressed as fairies.       &nbsp;   As the day was drawing to a close,  me  and  'Row'  went to water our taste buds with a light and refreshing beverage, and descided to meet the others back at the station.     Soon enough the train had arrived, but there was no sign of the other faries.As the train was ready to leave, my eyes spotted the other fairies and&nbsp; mad ones running as fast as their little legs could take them to try and catch the train.     The likes of  'Hannah','Emily'  and  'Marshall'  managed to jump aboard..but Woe behold, the others didnt make it and had to endure 8 minutes until another carriage came to take them home.       &nbsp;    I must say it was an extremly eventfull day, full of quirky suprises and a gimp looking like a bug (or sum random whos name i have forgotten and was wearing a hat over there face).          &nbsp;   So for now my chums...     Goodbyb     XxXxXx               Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Another day, another long and depressing Sunday.      I really dont see the point in Sundays.I know its like the 'day of worship', but it shouldnt mean that most shops are shut, and that theres absolute crap on tv.I mean, who really wants to watch the likes of 'antiques roadshow',and 'songs of praise'?.      I suppose it shows you how little there is to do in life.      Enough of me drowning on, lets think *happy thoughts*.      Well i'd like to say that the sun is shinning, and the birds are singing, but due to the unformidable British weather...its not.Instead, the sky is grey and i think the birds must be oversleeping  (either that or they have all mysteriously died).       Strange really...      So for now my little chums,Goodbyb.      XxXx    &nbsp;      urlLink      Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                Wahoo!Well this is my first entry ever,so first i am going to welcome myself to the world of blogg.*welcome*.Next i am going to welcome anybody else (people i know or even newcomers who have just happened to accidently find themselves here and dont know how to get out again)*welcome*.       Now thats over with....       Its the start of the summer holidays, and you would think that i would be glad, but no.7 weeks of pure boredom doesnt really seem appealing, even if it does allow me to escape from the likes of 'Treadders' (Becca would call him pretty, i would call him my slightly cheesy Blodge teacher), and also long,depressing hours of endless coursework.But i suppose theres a bright side to the situation, even if i havent found it yet,Oh well.       So to my mates 'Hewwo and enjoy me raving on for as many days as i can be bothered to fill this darn thing in!'       To you lot 'Just hewwo!'.        &nbsp;
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hewwo again there dearies, A much clearer head today but still very muddled.......    I had a erm... 'fab' day with my grandparents as it was my dear old nana's birthday. We took the them to Ye Olde York where there where street performers trying to get out of straight jackets....which tells you alot about the state of peoples minds. After hours of nothing except walking we finally came home.      Should be a better day tomorrow as i see my two bitches, 'twin of Fin' Roisin and Peewee. And hopefully Trina..but bless her...she's not aloud out often.Poor lass.    Ive had Maroon 5 songs stuck in my head allllllllll day!Argh.    Anyhoo: When i got back home i completed a quiz that tells you which video character you would be. It said i would be Mario, but then underneath it said 'if you are not Mario then you would be Mr Do...'. Who the hell is Mr Do? Which bloomin character am i? I will let you choose;          urlLink   I am  Mario .   I like to jump around, and would lead a fairly serene and aimless existence if it weren't for my friends always getting into trouble. I love to help out, even when it puts me at risk. I seem to make friends with people who just can't stay out of trouble.  urlLink What Video Game Character Are You?               urlLink   I am  Mr Do .   I am sedentary by nature, enjoying passive entertainment, eating when the mood takes me, and playing with my food. I try to avoid conflict, but when I'm angered, I can be a devil - if you force me to fight, I will crush you. With apples.  urlLink What Video Game Character Are You?           Hmmmmmmmm.Interesting.      For now, Goodbyb!             Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com      
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Yet ANOTHER boring and terrible Sunday.     I really really really HATE Sundays!     Arghhhhhh im shoo....i dunno...bored.     Today feels like a huge great weight  .      I think my brains gone all weird because im shoo bored.So whatever i write next will probably make no sense at all and bla bla bla......     Wouldnt it be really cool if you lived in like a fairytale type land place?And you where a princess...and there were dragons?And everything in the land of make believe was perfect and everything you wanted you got?     Also wouldnt it be really freaky if your dreams and nightmares came to life....how scary would that be...expesh if you dream about a giant chasing you because you have his medal...and you run away from him...and he finds you and he starts crying....and then you leave the island on a raft and drift off into the sunset with the giant crying and waving goodbye?      *Shivers*      I'd like to know why i said that.strange really.Well i got a kinda of idea.Hmmmmm.        Well im going to leave you with that weird-ness of a blogg.     I hope my mind gets better soon.          Goodbyb!        [Edit]Dazu....my hugga lober...your great.You give the best advise and your a great mate and ...yesh.Lobe you dearie!     [Edit 2] I lobe all my mates...your all great, some more than others..lmmao!         urlLink     Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hewwo there my lovely's,     The sun is out (*gasps*...yesh its shocking) and what a splendid day to attend the gym.     I saw my two divine bitches and endured many hours of cardio and weights.     After we descided to visit our dear friend 'twin of fin' Roisin....who seems to have grown a sorta semi afro type thing......     After a session of talking on hot tarmac,we did what every sane person does.....goes and sits in the middle of a round-about.     If that aint normal then what is?     Old men on bikes really shouldnt be allowed to ride such things on the road....its a health hazard!     Anyhoo,     After several hours of random chit chat, we dragged ourselves home.        Sounds fun doesnt it?        Goodbyb!          [edit] Welcome back 'Peewee' dearie...                Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Finally!     My bitches are back!     Back from the doom!          I will be able to see people again!     I wont be bored!          I lobe my bitches!          I want all my ickle fwendies to be back and then it will be like...*YAY!*.               Im shoo happy!          Goodbyb!              Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        WAHOO!      urlLink      Its my birthday!Im finally 15!I dunno why im so happy about that fact because it doesnt feel different and only means im getting older....but yay!     Ive finally got my beautiful new phone!Its shoo gut!     I got loads of lovely money to spend at Meadow hall too!     I got £200 .     I had a great day shopping (as any girl would) and i brought:       A bear from the bear factory and thats it...cos i didnt see anything else i liked.      (i did get some fab school schools and trousers but i didnt buy them so it doesnt count).     urlLink      I had a great brekkie of pancakes, followed by a days shopping and then went to TGIF's, which have the best cocktails and ice-creams (which i could only look at and not eat).          Im just looking forward to my next birthday now. Holiday,Birthday and a laptop! *yay!*          Im on a high and thought i'd write a quick blogg!     So for now my lovely ickle dearies     Goodbyb!         urlLink                Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Nothing much to report except:     Tomorrows my birthday,     Tomorrows my birthday,     Tomorrows my birthday,     Tomorrows my birthday,     Tomorrows my birthday!          I will have much more to say on that matter tomorrow.     So until then,        Goodbyb!             Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com       
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well as you can see from the title of todays post, it has nothing to do with dancing, or a disco.     Which is a shame really, but hey what you gonna do about it?     Its been a week since i last posted and to be honest, nothings happened.And by that i mean nothing exciting.     I did however manage to speak to my two bitches on MSN the other day which was quite marvy.     Ones in Spain (where rain falls mainly on the plain) and the other is in Frog-a-go-go-land.     They are coming back soon which will be a guten thing....even if it is after my birthday.        Another dear fwendie of mine has also gone away now....to merry old Newquay (or Newquey?).     So as i have wished both my bitches farewell, it seems only fair that i wish 'Peewee' (whos name isnt really that, but nicknamed that in order of our code...which is breakable...and also abit pointless when people know who your talking about).     So to you dearie...Au Revoir (thats french by the way) and have a guten time!     (p.s i did say i would mention you again..mwhaha!lmmao)        Only TWO days till my birthday now .* yay*.I was about to say that i wont be the baby anymore as it seems that im the only one who hasnt turned 15 yet....but then most people will be turning 16 and it makes me the ickle younger one again.     It really is annoying that 'twin of Fin' Roisin isnt at school on her birthday .    We had great plans for assembly.........        I hate the weather.Yesterday it was boiling hot and probably about 30C, and today its rainy gloomy, with a slight hint of muggy-ness.     I think its about time i stopped moaning now.        Tune in again for another helping of 'moi's' lovely blogg.     So for now     Goodbyb          [edit] crap, im gonna have to pay full price at the Odeon now.Dam you!You win this time!          urlLink     Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com     
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hewwo there my dears.     Today was quite a good day full of shopping and spending other peoples money (which is always a good thing in my book).     The only down side to the day was that i had to get up early to be dressed and ready to walk down to the station to get the train.     I nearly fainted though which was quite scary.Im not sure why.     It was just shopping for school stuff, but it was something different, and i now know what i want to get my ickle fwendies for crimbo.It might only have turned August but it doesnt hurt to get some ideas.Lol.     In the...um.. square bit in Nottingham with the big fountain and stuff there was this bloke.     Im not sure what you would call him.Weirdo,Preacher....insane loony.....but he was shouting at the top of his voice 'You have ten minutes to live!'.     I suppose this was his idea of causing panic....     But it does make you wonder, what would you do if you had only ten minutes left on this crappy little planet of ours?        4 hours or more of shopping later we headed back to get the train (and by 'we' i mean moi and my muther who seemed quite generous today).     Now my French is really terrible and most people should know that.My teachers obviously didnt as they kept me in top class and then gave me a rubbish report last year, which i think is rather rude .    'Lauren will not achieve a GCSE in French if her attitude remains unfocused' (or something along those lines).Why the hell put me in that class then!God dam them........     Anyhoo, on the train there was this group of Frenchies and i managed to work out what they were saying...which is quite an achievment for moi.     Well at least i think they were talking about a long....house........something about a...erm....dog maybe.....ummmm     Maybe not.     Nevermind.        Blimey, if i carry on writing i will have myself a novel.     I'd better go and rest my weary feet now.          Goodbyb.             Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com      
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Why oh why did they invent that god dam store!?     Why did that stupid swede go and make a shop called IKEA!?     Why is it full of cheap-ness!?     Why is there always a sale!?     Why is it full of screaming kids, who like me, really dont want to be there!?     Why is there cafe full of meatballs and Lingonberries!?     What the hell is a Lingonberry?!        Oh why oh why?!        Goodbyb.             Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com      
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Pinch Punch,First Day Of The Month!     Wahoo!Its August, which means four more weeks of boredom before the end of the holidays (I think thats good, but maybe it isnt when your venturing into your GCSE year at school ), more of that lovely summer sun, and also my birfday!     *Yay*          Gouranga!          Goodbyb!              Image by  urlLink FlamingText.com      
     

    
</post>


</Blog>