<Blog>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The only way to get rid of temptation is to yield to it... I can resist everything but temptation.  urlLink Oscar Wilde     So I called him.&nbsp; We talked for quite a long time, just like we always did.&nbsp; I love talking to him on the phone.&nbsp; We used to talk for hours.&nbsp; He always cracked me up, and frankly I find him fascinating, and I'm not just saying that because he rocks my world.&nbsp; In fact, if we're not having sex, I much prefer&nbsp;talking to him on the phone than actually hanging out with him.&nbsp; He is  quirky . &nbsp;We discussed all the reasons why I quit him.&nbsp; He said we used to have fun and we could again if I could get out of my head.&nbsp; He says I overthink things (he's right.)&nbsp; We DID have fun and it was the perfect situation until I started trying to figure it out.&nbsp; I started trying to figure it out because I started wanting to be with him all the time.&nbsp; My body  craved  him...and that just pissed me off.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   So then I started power dating in the hopes that I'd meet someone who could possibly distract me from that craving.&nbsp; There was Dentistman (who was actually kinda fun,) Brokerman (no chemistry but such a nice guy,) surferman (oh my, still seeing him,) writerboy (smart, smart, awesome to talk to, but soo young,) and mostly out of town claims-adjusterman (a blast to hang with.)&nbsp;&nbsp; The only thing all the dating did was distract me from my  life  to the point that my friends nearly held an intervention...and on thinking about it, rightly so.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   I don't know how men manage to juggle dating several women at the same time.&nbsp; It was extremely difficult to juggle dating several men, and men don't even call that often!&nbsp; If I was man trying to juggle 3 women who all called every other day I'd go crazy.&nbsp; Have I just stumbled on the reason why men&nbsp;ARE crazy?..lol.&nbsp;&nbsp; Surely that is part of why they are so terrible about calling back.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   And really, the thing is, I don't want a relationship, don't have time to&nbsp;feed and care for&nbsp;a relationship, ...I don't have any particular  longing  to be part of a couple.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   What I  would like  is to have someone whose company I really enjoy, with whom I could have really fun sex, and who might be willing to go do stuff now and then, and if this situation was able to exist for a good while, so much the better.&nbsp;  That  would be a perfect situation.&nbsp; Ironically, that was exactly the situation I was already in!&nbsp; And I resigned from it!&nbsp; Good grief. To be fair though, it was starting to feel relationship-y, and in my more rational moments I recognized that and was concerned by it.&nbsp; And I sort of was starting to fall for him, (&nbsp;concerning also, because I was fully aware that even if it WERE reciprocated, given his considerable quirks, it would never work, I couldn't love him that way.)  &nbsp;Certainly he noticed it too and I suspect that is why he put the brakes on.&nbsp; I'm glad he did.     &nbsp;   So I visited him and it was really really good to see him. It was his birthday.&nbsp;He kissed me...I've never been kissed by anyone who kisses better.&nbsp;He is&nbsp;exquisite. &nbsp;He rocked my world until I begged him to stop, only he didn't stop...lol.&nbsp; I'm glad that we are friends again and I told him so.&nbsp; He&nbsp;reminded me to stay mindful that we are  friends.&nbsp;&nbsp; I feel like I will.&nbsp; But I'm&nbsp;confident that he'll put the brakes on again if I start to get loopy.&nbsp; At that point I'll either re-focus or quit for good.&nbsp;&nbsp;    I'm even more confident that I'm going to keep trying to figure out where my mind derailed from my brain and why I started acting so possessive (and even jealous?)     &nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I called Mr. Rock-my-world today.&nbsp; Oh Lord am I ever dumbass.&nbsp;&nbsp; I don't waaaaaaant a relationship with him.&nbsp; I just want to have sex with him!!!&nbsp; Now!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When I log on to the computer now I get a message from Mr. Rockmyworld saying "Hi....it's Mr. Crack, have you met a new dealer yet?"&nbsp; Pfft.&nbsp; Jackass.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I can't tell if he's busting my chops or really bothered?&nbsp;&nbsp; Do I care? NO( yes )!!!&nbsp;&nbsp; Hopefully soon he will become so annoying that he becomes loathesome.&nbsp;&nbsp;I estimate that&nbsp;to be&nbsp;about 4 days out if he continues on like this.   I had dinner last night with a&nbsp;man (date #2)&nbsp;who is so positive and happy.&nbsp; He's totally buff because he lives in the gym.&nbsp; He's funny, educated, sort of interesting, and&nbsp;verrrry interested in me.&nbsp; I  was  looking pretty hot&nbsp;which I'm sure that turned the interest in me up a notch.&nbsp; I have lost about 40 lbs since I invited&nbsp;my future ex-husband (who I affectionately refer to as my baby' daddy) to leave.&nbsp; But I digress.&nbsp;&nbsp;Mr. C'mon-get-happy invited me to his place.&nbsp; I declined.&nbsp; I'm not feeling the chemistry even though I can tell he is.&nbsp; I hate that.&nbsp; I  want  to want a guy who won't toy with me. What is  wrong  with me?&nbsp; &nbsp;  My house is trashed. Ugh.   Gotta get ready for work.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am newly single, therefore I date.&nbsp;&nbsp; I work full-time, therefore I have personal ads on internet dating sites.&nbsp;&nbsp; How is that going?&nbsp; It's going surprisingly well.&nbsp; Of course, it doesn't hurt that there are about 4 men for every woman on the internet sites.&nbsp; That allows even someone like me to be selective.&nbsp;&nbsp;I have emailed and met men who I would not have otherwise had an opportunity to meet. I have met an engineer, a dentist, several business owners, a chef, several financial planners (it might be coincidence, but financial planners seem to be WAY over-represented on online dating sites), a lawyer and a part-time magician.&nbsp;&nbsp; For the most part they were all very normal seeming, really cool guys.&nbsp; I dated several for a while.&nbsp; I've even been having sex!&nbsp; Who knew it was still so much fun?&nbsp;   One man  trifled  with my affections.&nbsp; I knew I was a flavor of the month, but I was ok with it because OMG, he was so gorgeous and funny and interesting&nbsp;on lots of different levels&nbsp;and made my body to respond in ways I didn't even know were possible.&nbsp; And anyway, I was just looking for a good time and I accepted his evasiveness and&nbsp;trifling ways&nbsp;as part of his package deal.&nbsp; Guess who I fell for?&nbsp;&nbsp;Oh yes, you know who it was.&nbsp;&nbsp; It wasn't like an in-love kind of falling for him, rather I just couldn't get enough of him.&nbsp; I  craved him. &nbsp;&nbsp;When he moved on to the next flavor of the month I thought I would go crazy.&nbsp;&nbsp; I told him that being with him was like smoking crack, to which he took great offense.&nbsp; Pffft. Could I just drop it then?&nbsp; Oh no.&nbsp; I was on my period and was overcome with this need to  explain  myself, in a realllly long email no less. &nbsp;Good grief.&nbsp; Like THAT helped anything.&nbsp;&nbsp;   So now, several weeks later, I'm over it/him (mostly.)&nbsp; I still get the craving.....but I'm dating others who are doing a fair job of distracting me from it.&nbsp; That's how men date, no?&nbsp;&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I called in sick today and wasn't really sick...totally faked it.&nbsp; I just didn't want to go in.&nbsp; It was rainy this morning when I woke up and I just wanted to lay on the couch.&nbsp; Did I?&nbsp; Oh no, I surfed the internet all day!&nbsp; I should've just gone to work.&nbsp; Now I'm going to have a million emails that all need something and a stack of paperwork on my desk.&nbsp; Oh!&nbsp; As if that weren't bad enough, future ex-husband (who was rained out at work and came and took daughter for the day since I had to "  work") called because he couldn't reach me at work.&nbsp; So I lied and said I came home early because I had a touch of food poisoning.&nbsp; I must've been very convincing because he said I sounded terrible.&nbsp;&nbsp; O what a tangled web we weave....    &nbsp;  Two more weeks until school starts for the kids.&nbsp; Thank God.&nbsp; Whoever invented summer vacation was clearly not a FT working single mother.&nbsp; In the next two weeks I have to be school supplies and uniforms for daughter.&nbsp;&nbsp; I told daughter that there were only two weeks left of summer and she just looked stunned!!&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;  She is 8.&nbsp; I'm crazy about her.&nbsp; She doesn't care much for me though.&nbsp; She's a daddy's girl through and through.&nbsp; I have to keep reminding myself that I didn't sign up to be liked by her.&nbsp;&nbsp; I'm sure she'll figure out lots more ways to break my heart before it's all said and one.&nbsp; The best I can hope for is that she'll come out mature, smart, and purposeful when she comes out the other end!  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>