<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Ok are they trying to deprive us of every bit of indivuduality that we own??? I mean if i make fun of someone, it's not for their clothes!   I mean even peeps with the hottest out fit ever get made fun of! So, a little note to those peeps who gave us uniforms, It didn't help the bullying problem, and never will! This what this letter says about the school uniforms!:        "At Abell Junior High School we strive to establish a dress code that teaches grooming and hygiene, instills self discipline, prevents disruption, avoids safety hazards,  (uh thats a little weird if you ask me)  and teaches respect for authority."  Ok i don't see how wearing geek clothes makes you "learn" anything!!!            N  KATIE   N      
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Ok Avril Lavigne and Hilary Duff hate eachother?? Why?? Nobody knows. Oh wait! I DO!!!     Well first Avril Lavigne told her crazed fans to get a life. Then Hilary Duff, being the goody goody she is told Avril to respect her fans who just want to be like her. Avril didn't take that little peice of advice and told Hilary to "Go screw herself"and called her a *gasp* "Mommy's girl".    
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        For those who don't know, The Assistant is a show where Andy Dick lets 12 people live in his house and choses one of them to be the assistant. Some might think it would be like The Apprentice, but it's not. Andy Dick makes them do weirdo-things (training his cat, finding the lense to his glasses at the bottom of his pool etc.). Andy Dick is hilarious, but the way he choses to send someone packing is really unfair. If you haven't seen it yet, he sends home two people who tried their hardest cooking a meal for Andy, rather than a guy who cheated to get a first-place trophy in a marathon. but besides that the show is hilarious! I luv it this  YYY  much.    &nbsp;      Y KATIE  Y      
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        This was one of those movies where one funny thing happens, and you're laffing for ten minutes! If you love the show "Family Guy", then this is the perfect movie for you. Who would've known that this movie would inspire people to make adult dodgeball teams?? If you ask me, thats a little creepy. Well any way I luv it this   YYYY  &nbsp;much        &nbsp;       Y KATIE  Y       
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           The Punk In Pink                 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        For those of you who don't know, the 4400 is a show about these peeps who get abducted by aliens and then come back and try to ajust to life on earth. Well some of the situations are kinda cheesy, some things are kinda interesting. I don't think you'd like it very much if you're younger than 7, because you might get bored with it. But besides that it's a pretty good show! How much do I love it? I give it three  YYY  's          Y KATIE  Y      
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey this is my blog!!! So reply to alot of stuff and I'll be a very happy Katie!!   
      
</post>


</Blog>