<Blog>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have You Ever Noticed That Every Couple Of Years Of So, You Notice You Really Never Cared&nbsp;About Something. For Me, The First Thing Was The Friends Televisoin Show On The WB.&nbsp; I Know It Sounds Funny, But I Almost Felt As Though&nbsp;I Was Growing Too Old Too Quickly.&nbsp;I Still Feel The&nbsp;Same Way. When I Was Younger, It Was Completly Different.&nbsp; I Wished I Could&nbsp;Gett Magically Older, Or Taller&nbsp;So I Could Do The Things That The Older Kids Got To Do.&nbsp; Now I Think About&nbsp;It, It Was&nbsp;Never Really That big Of A Deal Like I Made It Out To Be.&nbsp;    I'm Soo Not Ready For Highschool.&nbsp; Everyone Else, It Seems, Are All Excitd, But I'm Scared. I Don't Even Know Why, Really, It's Not That I'm Afraid I'll "Get My Ass Kicked," As My Sister Says, I Think It's More About After Highschool.&nbsp; I'm Afraid My Friends And I Will Sort Of Go Our Seperate Ways After Highschool.&nbsp; I Mean, Shit, I Have More Trouble Just Trying To Get A Hold Of&nbsp;Some Of My Friends&nbsp;Now...... &nbsp; &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm. I'm Really Not Sure If I'm Ready For Highschool. Not That I Have A Choice. I'm Sort Of Forced Into It. I'm Actually More Afraid Of My Grades Than Anything Else. I Mean, They're Not That Important, Right? They Just Control The Rest Of Your Life, Like Wether You Become A Scientist, A Doctor, A Drug Dealer, A Bum, Or Even Worse, Someone Who Works At Mc. Donalds. I Think The Only Way I'm Going To Last All Four Years Is Not Taking Crap From Teachers, Not Getting Beat Up, Taking EVERY Non-Athletic Extra-Curricular Activity They Offer, Bury Myself In Schoolwork And My Wiccan Duties, And Not Leave Myself Any Time To Get Upset About How Screwed Up My Life Is. I Hope My Friends Will Be Reliable Through My Highschool Years, Unlike Current Times, And Help Me Say, "HEY LIFE, YEAH, I'M TALKING TO YOU! FUCK YOU! YOU HEAR ME? FUCK YOU!Recently It Just Seems Like Everyone And Everything Is Out To Piss Me Off. The People Who I Like Are Impossible To Get A Hold Of, As I Have No Means Of Contact, And I'm Getting Scared About Everyone Around Me Doing Drugs And Drinking, And Talking About Nothing More Than Sex, And If Not Sex, Than Suicide. Talk About A Trade-Up. Oh Yeah, Something Good Happened Yesterday. I Won 3 Fish At The Fouth Of July Carnival (on the 2 of july) 
    
</post>


</Blog>