<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hi! I am back after a few days.Anyway i will write some extremely important things about my past, like my deepest & darkest secrets or desires! My first crush was on a Indian[tamil]-muslim guy who is one year older than me.His name is Hameedul Ansar.He is a south indian,tamilian to tbe precise.He is a muslim too. What can i say about him? Hameedul is very tall, slim,dark,intelligent,studious,diligent,responsible,energetic and very very good-looking!!He was in my primary school Ahmad Ibrahim Primary School. He is one year older than me, but he is extremely mature and responsible for his age. All the teachers in my school were extremely fond of him. He is also an football maniac! He is not only very good in his studies but also in  sports most importantly in his character! Girls were completely mad about him but he was very modest and stayed away fom such distractions.You wont believe this but my best friend  HONEY CRYSTEL S. APALE also had her first and major crush on him too just like me!Anyway i always kept this as a secret and nobody got to know aout this , even now other than god and me!  I had a major crush on him for 2 whole years from the age of 10 to the age of 11.I was totally mad about him. I even remember myself praying to god everyday so that i can win his heart !!!!I met him almost everyday at school and whenever  he was absent , i used to get very upset. He was my school heart-throb!!Every day after school the two of us used to take the same route to home but we never talked to each other as i never dared to and he didnt even know me well! And then  he got promoted to a secondary 1 in a completely new school, Victoria secondary school, which is a pretty good school it is only for boys. He is in secondary 3 this year. After moving to his new secondary school i never saw him again that was the end of my 1st major crush- HAMEEDUL ANSAR.  After 1 year, i had this much deeper and my second crush on this bengali guy from my bangla school bus.I will write more tomorrow as my pathetic dad is irritating me, i dont understand whats his problem.He keeps on disturbing as well as lecturing me on what to do and what not to do. He is a complete idiot and a total fool! Bye,see ya later!!!            
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Yo! Whaz up? u won't believe this, i have been chosen as the vice captain of Spring house instead of Raina!I mean honestly,raina is much better as a vice captain than me. I was just so damn suprised that Swati mam with Somia mam, rekha mam chose me instead of raina! Its totally unbelievable! I am still in shock!!!!Raina is much better than me in studies, dancing and taking responsibilities! I mean what the heck were&nbsp; the house teachers thinking at that time! May be they are all mentally retarded just like my pathetic and annoying classmate Shivali, who according to me looks like a well........dog!Anyway i will write more later my idiotic dad is scolding me and giving me lectures! Bye!   
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hi! I am Priyanka Ghosh. I am born on the 12th of september 1990.My sun sign is Virgo and according to the chinese astrology, i am born on the year of the horse. I am 5 feet 5 inches tall, my weight is 55kg. I&nbsp; am slim,very tall for my age, i have short hair, i wear specs my skin complexion is tanned and i have very sharp &amp; attractive features! As a person i am very friendly,humorous,kind,understanding,reliable,artistic,sincere and logical or down to earth! My worst qualities are my dishonesty and my lazyness, these qualities have created loads of problems,misunderstandings in my life and also has created a very bad impression of me. I mean sometimes previously i did not even know half of the time what i was saying!!!!!! Just because of my utter stupidity and dis honesty, my classmates and friends in my school dont trust me and have a bad impression of me.But today i am proud to say that, i have changed a lot, i have stopped making stupid,idiotic tales , i have stopped critizing people, i seldom lie and i always think twice before doing anything!!! Due to god's grace, i have changed a lot for the better, have become a honest person now!Anyway i am studying in std 8 this year at Delhi Public School International Singapore.&nbsp;My school&nbsp;&nbsp;started&nbsp;  few months ago this year, 19th of april to be precise! School 's cool! I like all my classmates except some of course! Most of my teachers are o.k, pretty&nbsp;&nbsp;tolerable, even though some are absolutely weird, all teachers teach really well, clearing all the doubts, they sure know how to teach well even though they are totally nuts!!God, i have loads of homework to complete and there is so much to study , that i dont know where to start and wher to end, life sure is weird!! I will write more tomorrow bye !!   
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        H I  ! I am back again!!I am in a much better mood now!I did'nt finish any homework at all because i am feeling very sick as well as complicated about what to buy for Janhvi on her suprise party this thursday.I mean there is only 1 more day left & i don't even know what to buy her as a gift!How annoying!Anyway,nowdays i have been noticing something very disturbing indeed,guess what?Arjun, our class pandit, keeps on staring at me all the time!Eeeeeeeeuuuuhhh!!!!!!!I mean i have been noticing this for the past 1 and a half months!!I don't understand his problem at all. Whenever i am answering or talking to any of the teachers or my dear friends , Arjun keeps on staring at me continuosly!!! This is becoming weirder day by day!Both arpita&amp; shivali are driving me completely nuts! I think both of them should seriously consult a pshyciatrist for their mental illness!!!!!!!!!They are becoming more & more pathetic and intolerable day by day!Anyway, i can hardly wait for jaanu darling's party and our school trip to science centre.I am just so thrilled!!I think i will buy jaanu darling a bracelet for her birthday as i cant think of anything nice and fancy yet.Raina cant stop telling me  ''give me a 3'' or ''give me a 7'' or ''give me a 1''!!God! Raina is totally insane but maybe that's why i like her very much!!!And on the other hand so many things from our class has been stolen recently.6 of my pilot pens & my chemistry notebook dissappeared into thin air!Can u believe it?Something is very fishy!Ipsita lost her expensive handphone yesterday at class &amp; she also lost her biology notebook and maths worksheet as well.Raina dear also lost 3 of her hindi notebooks in the class!I don't get a thing.All our things just start getting lost in the class!!Very,very, very weird!The thing which i absolutely don't understand is that why in the world would anyone want to steal my chem notebook cause whatever i wrote in it was crap and it hardly makes any sense!!Oh yeah!Now i know why i have so many pimples in my face. Wanna know? It is because my beloved friend Ipsita,keeps on coughing & sneezing into my face directly all the time!!Seriously what the heck is her problem? What is so special about my stupid and ugly face?Ipsita Basu-she is extremely humorous,intelligent, friendly,crazy &amp; interesting as a person.But trust me , sometimes she can become really weird like today all of a sudden she started to sing this really weird song to me into my ear just after English lesson, I was so damn shocked!!!But despite of her craziness, ipsita is actually a very,very nice,understanding & helpful girl. She is filled with joy &amp; laughter , bringing smiles to all the people's faces arond her.Raina SWEETHEART-She is extremely talented,responsible,whacky,reliable,friendly & kind!!Raina is the best dancer in our whole school!Her dancing abilities are absolutely awesome!!!The best thing i like about raina sweetheart is that she is very modest,inspiring &amp; cheerful! You can always go to her for help!Raina is our very own dancing queen. Both Ipsita & Raina darling are truly a blessing to my life!!!Even Janhvi is vey nice, friendly &amp; helpful but her biggest backdraw is that she talks way too much of nonesense & she kind of likes to boast a lot.Other than that, there is nothing wrong with jaanu darling!Ramu is becoming nicer day by day, thankfully she has finally come to her senses at last!Except for arpita &amp; shivali who are becoming worse day by day! Anyways, my pathetic dad is again lecturing me on not to waste my time on the computer. I just dont understand my parents problems, why cant they just leave me alone in peace?Why must they always boss &amp; lecture me around all the time? Don't i have a mind of my own or what?! Nobody understands me!!!Nobody!Gotta go, see ya later! BYE.    
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      God! Why does Ms.Michelle keep on stereotyping us all the time? I mean what's her damn problem!What does she have against us? I mean she is just so unpredictable!Sometimes she is very nice and understanding then sometimes she acts like a bitch!I dont understand any of the teachers, i mean they are all pretty nice but sometimes they can turn out to be really freaky!!!Example:Ms.Zaki,Ms Elizabeth,Ms.Rekha & Ms.Michelle!I think they suffer from serious mental illness!Anyway, Shivali cant stop staring at me during lessons  and acts like a complete idiot! I mean everybody knows she is pathetic but does she always have to prove us so? Another reason why i cant stand Shivali, She goes around complaining about every tinywiny thing we say to all the teachers !!!!I mean doesnt she have a brain or what? But unfortunately most of the teachers believe her stupid& senseless complaints and we always get into trouble unnecessariliy!Now you understand why i hate shivali &amp; have grudges against most of the teachers in my school!They are all so bloody damn sickening!!You cant even talk in peace! Goodness sake!And shivali's parents also complaint about me ipsita,raina,janhvi,meghna&amp;priyanka from 9 standard!!
      
</post>


</Blog>