<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
              A little known fact of Greek life is the perception of everyday conversations by non Greek speaking people. To the untrained ear, most social discourse sounds at best like an exchange of orders and at worst like a blazing row. For example, when sending an email, it is virtually impossible to use lower case characters since the default is automatically to upper case, SO YOU CAN SHOUT AT THE TOP OF YOUR F'KIN VOICE!. This said, however, once one finds the more dulcet, "little" letters it is as a lull in the storm . . . .  Most are aware that Greece is the cradle of civilization, many of the world's great thinkers solved the mysteries of mankind here whilst the rest of us were living in caves and there are many areas that have been developed here for thousands of years, greatly surpassing the efforts of" newer" nations who have far to go in their evolution of certain concepts.  One such area is Traffic Jams. There are very few places on the face of the globe that can offer more frustrating vehicular transport then the roads between Athens and Pireaus which are a virtual melange of pot holes, construction sites, heat, dust, opportunistic drivers and road rage. Somebody untrained in the navigation of this road would be more than foolhardy to attempt to actually drive it themselves as it is certain that the end result would be to be splattered against the rear of a truck or at the very least to have three scooter riders embedded in the passenger door.  To compensate for this, Greek Taxis are numerous, reasonably priced and a source of some of the best entertainment one can wish for. My travels today took me to the little know town of Kastri, from the time it takes to get there one would assume that it is situated somewhere in Bulgaria wheras in fact it is a northern suburb of Athens.  The adventure of returning from this place to the bosom of Pireaus is one of the most entertaining couple of hours I have spent in a long time. My business completed, my host informed me that it was very easy to hail a taxi outside his office.  Clearly, this is not an activity he undertakes regularly since after some forty minutes beside an extremely busy highway, the only things i had "hailed" was about half a kilo of dust to stick to the pint and three quarters of sweat that had run out of me on to the pavement. Then, lady luck smiled upon me with the entrance over the horizon of Nikos and his much loved (and certainly much used) Seat taxi.  Nikos appeared to offer an unusual variant on the taxi theme, the "local" service. When he stopped next to the grease puddle that i was transforming rapidly into, there were already two elderly ladies in the back seat of the car. Having determined my eventual destination I got into the front seat. It was at this point that I realized that Nikos considered one leg to be a sufficient proportion of a passenger to be actually in the vehicle and that it was time to move away at as high a velocity as could be achieved.  Fortunately, I was swift in my reactions and managed to get my bum through the door several milliseconds before we passed the first parked car. Nikos is a cheery man, he spoke little English but this was far greater than my Greek which is limited to phrases like "malacca" and "yasu nafti".  He explained that the ladies were going to points on our route which was fine with me since being close to fainting (both from the heat and the dramatic embarkation) I was prepared to be agreeable to pretty much anything. One of the ladies left us fairly early, to be replaced by a mother and child en route to Athens to go shopping. Nikos is not a person you would readily give a TV remote to, he kept one finger on the radio tuning button at all times flipping between stations every few seconds. A large wear mark on the dial stood in evidence of many years of this practice.  We happened upon a news station; during a twenty or thirty second report I recognized one word. "Australis" which I presumed to be Australia. I regretted my lack of linguistic ability since Nikos roared with laughter at the end of the piece and endeavoured to explain the joke.  Apparently, a man in Australia (I was right!) had been driving his wife and mother in law somewhere when he had run out of petrol. He went to a station to get a can but found that he had no money on him. The owner was reticent to give him any gas without security so it was agreed that the wife and the mother in law would remain whilst the man refilled his car, went to the bank and returned with payment.  Apparently the man seized his opportunity and never returned!! Nikos opined that he may well try that himself and whilst he did not know the word "harridan" he made it abundantly clear that his life contained at least two! The lady with the child left us and shortly afterwards the other lady and we replaced them with a very attractive young woman and a man who,from his odour, probably worked in the goat industry.  We were now a little over an hour into our journey and the discussion had turned to my background in the maritime industry. Nikos was not a fan of shipowners, his opinion was that they make vast fortunes and then spend them in foreign lands, I wondered where he got that impression . . . The goatherd was the next to leave us and we found another gentleman to fill the vacant seat. I am not certain he really wanted to go anywhere but was clearly keen to sit next to the young lady in the back seat who he engaged in flirtatious conversation (flirting sounds the same in any language) She was not receptive and left us shortly afterwards.  When she was gone, the man and Nikos exchanged a few words which I took to mean either "She must be a lesbian", "She had big ears anyway" or "Nice tits". All too soon, the voyage was completed and I was back in the more familiar streets of Piraeus. I bade Nikos farewell as he set off to find more lost souls to fill his taxi.  
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Thank goodness the people in Athens aren't listening to the criticism they are receiving from the international media for lagging on Olympic construction projects.&nbsp; They're too busy putting their collective soul into the rebirth of their ancient capital as I witnessed with wonder on a recent visit and many are quite positive: "I quarantee everything will be done on time", one Athenian told me. "This is the Greek way. We are last minute people."  Being a chronic procrastinator myself, I was relaxed by their optimism. Let's face it, complaining about the way Athens stages the Olympics is like criticizing the way Chinese brew tea: Greece invented the Olympics thousands of years ago and then shared their divine ritual with the world. And what have we done with it? Added money scandals; political manipulations; steroid use in the name of victory; and terrorist threats.
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         There is more money being spent on breast implants and Viagra than on Alzheimer's research. This means that by 2030, there should be a large elderly population with perky boobs and huge erections and absolutely no recollection of what to do with them. 
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        All ladies and gentlemen of good social standing or disrepute are once again called to order.  &nbsp;  Notice is herby given of the next meeting of the NAPU society (Naval Architects Professional Union). Due to the poor organisational skills of most naval architects, the event will once more be organised by a marine engineer and a very nice one at that.  &nbsp;  As the NAPU society has now been formally recognised as a professional body by the Inst. of Licensed Victuallers (“I.Lic” for short) it is felt that on this occasion we should base the day mainly around drinking, curry and free sight tests.  &nbsp;  The more observant among us may well say that there is nothing new about that, others will clearly be looking forward to the completely new format (mainly the naval architects).  &nbsp;  Never the less, there is a slight twist to the plot, in that we propose (courtesy of Helen) to meet at the Dickens Inn in St. Katherine’s Dock (by Tower Bridge for those not well travelled). This is still within easy striking distance of Brick Lane and the opticians in Bethnel Green, and will give us the chance to drink outside if the weather is nice. Good suggestion Helen.  &nbsp;  Unfortunately no “match report” was made after the last event as no “exclusives” were given by any of the participants and the general standard of behaviour was far too orderly. Another small issue was that I couldn’t remember going to bed or indeed what happened leading up to that. However, with my new electronic organiser I am now able to take notes during the event as well as full colour photographs (sorry Fred not you – I’ve already seen your bum in the golf club showers).  &nbsp;  Please let me know if this date is OK, alternatively we could make it the following Thursday at the Yacht Show in Monaco, where I can recommend venues for the beer and curry but not for the opticians.  &nbsp;  End of sermon – now strike a line through Thursday 16th September in your diary!
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The Export-Import Bank of China has either come across a whole new ship type or displayed some serious ignorance.&nbsp; 
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.naftemporiki.gr/news/static/04/07/21/934968.htm         It seems that Euro 2004 success of Greece has given a lot of inspiration to the shipping world as well.&nbsp; I guess the next big hit will be to see a cargo ship named: B/C Zagorakis   Cool...     
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    I suppose this picture may be the basis for any future info published through here.  Moreover, it depicts the average weather conditions of this lovely city to a great extent... &nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello World...... &nbsp; My first post, and there will be more to come....&nbsp; &nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I am always getting really impressed when Engineers and Architects get on together to use their inspiration and knowledge and create the new jewels of the seas. This is also the case for the new Car Carrier 'Utopia Ace' delivered by Mitsubishi Heavy Industries. The Utopia Ace features advanced technologies such as a double-hulled fuel tank that reduces the risk of oil spills and a hull design that significantly reduces wind resistance – the same technology used in the Courageous Ace, which was named the Ship of the Year for 2003.     Under the water line, the ship features a hyper-slim energy-saving design that reduces resistance by 8% compared to a conventionally designed vessel. The ship has an aerodynamically rounded design not only on the bow but also on the sides to further reduce wind resistance. Additionally, the ventilation covers on the shipside decks feature aerodynamically rounded sides. These energy saving features will reduce the ship's CO2 emissions by about 14%, compared to current vessels. The Utopia Ace has a double-hulled fuel tank to reduce the risk of spills in case of a grounding or collision. 
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A new kind of power source is being developed at the University of Houston that is so small yet so efficient it could make traditional power plants obsolete while greatly reducing the cost of electricity.   The source is a so-called ‘cool’ fuel cell, officially known as thin film solid oxide fuel cell, or SOFC, which originated from research at UH's Texas Center for Superconductivity and Materials. The SOFC uses superconductivity and semiconductor concepts developed at UH and, by applying them to the fuel cell, UH researchers were able to significantly reduce operating temperatures which are a drawback to other fuel cells.   A traditional fuel cell can take up an entire room, while the thin film SOFCs are 1 micron thick and UH claims that a unit about the size of four sugar cubes would produce 80 watts of power, more than enough to operate a laptop computer, while one the size of two beer cans could power a house. This revolutionary technology has applications for residential, business and industrial consumers of electricity including ships. It is anticipated that the fuel cells will be ready for the testing phase of development within the next six months. That will be done through the Houston Advanced Research Center's Center for Fuel Cell Research and Applications.         
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A storm seems to be more than enough able to turn the largest part of central London into 'chaos'.  Houses and tube stations were flooded, streets were packed with frazzled commuters that decided unanimously to abandon their shopping spree and get home at the same time and a huge traffic jam spread over dozens of miles on all major streets while people started getting off the cabs and buses to walk home as that was apparently faster.   I was one of them, too. It was one of these days that you consider to leave the office 'on time' and get home 'on time' and by the minute you leave the building door behind you the whole universe seems to be your worst enemy.   " You are going to regret that...sucker!"....seemed as the exact translation of all the lightning strikes and thunders dropping all around; and I did.   Well, at some point this was funny because you watch a demonstration of Murphy's laws, one by one. Therefore, I got off to get the rest couple of miles on foot smiling when it started raining again and really laughing when the bus started to move again faster. Why not having some exercise and the shower at the same time? And afterall my suit needed to get to the dry cleaners, already. There is always a bright side in everything...isn't it??        
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If you are thinking of upping sticks and moving to France, beware! You may not only have to fight the massive red tape but, it seems, French maritime foklore.  When a family decided to move from Manchester to Normandy, it booked the ferry trip, but forgot to mention the children's two pet rabbits, 'Bugs' and 'Nibbles'. They checked to see if this was alright only shortly before the departure date.   "Non", said Brittany Ferries- rabbits are banned on board.  Although French-owned BF accept cats, dogs, parrots and even snakes, it won't abide bunnies, not even a lucky-charm rabbit's paw! Apparently there is a 400 year old superstition among French seafarers that rabbits bring bad luck. It dates from the 17th century when, legend says, a rabbit being carried for food gnawed through the hold of a warship which sank with the loss of hundreds of lives.  A Sunday paper quoted a naval attache' at the French Embassy in London as saying: "The superstition remains very strong among the older generation of French sailors. Even the word 'rabbit' is banned on board ship; you have to say "the animal with the long ears"...  Well the family finally was refunded by BF around £1,000 and eventually sailed to France with rabbits on a P&O ferry..    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>