<Blog>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It mind seem unorthodox that I will begin this tale not at the beginning but at what I have come to view as the middle, but I am in such a manner compelled to write this, that I have no choice but to follow my heart... and since my heart beats for one man and one man alone, it seems important that my tale begins with him. My husband...  My George...      &nbsp;   I met George in a dream and though you might laugh when you realize I mean this in its literal sense, just bear with me and it will all make sense later on...     &nbsp;   I was 12 at the time and I had a crush on a 22 year old young man by the name of Alex, who of course could never return my "affection". I had dreams of marrying him in the way lots of young girls do and they were filled with flowers and frills and white doves... Of course the young man (who was Australian by the way) didn't even know I existed at least no more than "Gee she has a heartbeat" level... Oh, he also knew my name!!     &nbsp;   One night, I can't recall if it was spring or winter, I dreamt that I was getting married. There I was in this white long dress, my daddy at my side and this tall man, with a slightly too long neck and very short cropped dark hair... But it wasn't my Alex...  I felt a deep disappointment at this... the sleeping 12 year old's heart wept because somehow I knew this dream was of some importance... but the adult me in the dream was beaming with joy. She was really, truly in love with this man with the long neck and the short dark hair. That gave the sleeping 12 year old some comfort to the fact that when she did get married to his man, she would be ok, because she would truly, deeply love him... and though I never did see his whole face, the  sense  of him stayed with me ever since...     &nbsp;   I was 15 when I got my first modem and connected to the web... that was 1993... March.    I found a BBS and started chatting on a regular basis with the guys there. To my knowledge I was one of 4 women and the youngest member yet.    That's where I met George... In a conversation he challenged me saying I was not a girl but a guy playing tricks on-line, a common practice at the time. So we agreed to meet at a gathering of the BBS users.     &nbsp;   He saw me before I saw him and he later told me he felt a connection to me immediately. I believe him because he was 22 at the time, 7 years older than me, with a career and I was a mere bedraggled teenager, the unfortunate victim of hormones that were winning the war at the time... I couldn't possibly imagine what he saw in me but I definitely saw something in him...     &nbsp;   The tall, dark haired handsome man felt like an "old shoe", worn to perfect comfort&nbsp;and one that fits perfectly as a result.    It was like I somehow  knew  him of old though we had never met prior to the day.  Though I can only say this in retrospect, I could see my future in his eyes even though it would take him another 4 years to see his future in mine. Because, lets face it, its far easier for a 15 year old girl to fall in love with an older, handsome man, than for this older, handsome man to fall in love with a bedraggled 15 year old girl, that still&nbsp;wore Doc Martens and torn jeans...    &nbsp;   However we soon became friends though I think he saw me more like a kitten in need of a caregiver or perhaps a younger sister... and me of course at the age of 15, just discovering boys, had no idea of the needs a man his age would have and of course I would be in no position to meet them had he decided to take advantage of my infatuation...    At the time I thought I wanted nothing more except him but now I am glad he didn't make a move because if he had, we probably wouldn't be together now...     &nbsp;   George remained a silent presence in my life and I contained my love for him and dated, got my heart broken, dated again and had my heart broken... again and again and again while he was there most times to pick me up.    In all these years I had  never  seen him with a girl... he kept his personal life private from all of us which made me happy because I could maintain hope...  George became the hero in my stories, the knight in my RPG scenarios but not my fantasy. It was really odd because as a child, my imaginary husband (all little girls must have one, right?) was this tall, dark haired man that wore a uniform... and George seemed to fit that description. He is 6" tall, has raven dark hair and chocolate colored eyes and he is an officer in the Navy.    He also happens to be a Pisces, my favorite star sign... my dad is also a Pisces and I guess I am living proof that little girls do&nbsp;marry their daddies when they grow up...     &nbsp;   It wasn't until after I had celebrated my 19th birthday, long after I thought torn jeans and Doc Martens were out and that shaving the back of your head while you had long hair otherwise, was  not  cool, that George took an interest in me...  I was in my second year of studying when we became a couple... and though I was certainly  not  as innocent as I was at 15, I still was as&nbsp;dumb as a doorknob when it came to relationships. Thus I again failed to accommodate all his "needs"...    I had openly admitted my love for him; after all what good is a feeling if you can't share it, and I think in the emotional department he was covered... though I am sure he did not love me (nor had he ever said he did) at the time&nbsp;I assumed that he did...    I suppose George felt a gap in the physical department...    Me at 19 was perfectly happy with kissing and holding hands and going to the movies... and though I was not raised in a family who abolished pre-marital sex, I had never felt the desire for my partner and was quite content with just kissing.    I now understand that when you are a 25 year old man... well things are not exactly the same...     &nbsp;   It was no great surprise that after 3 months of dating, George decided that his gap needed filling and a beautiful brunette took my place at his side...    I still remember that evening when he told me "he was seeing someone else" like it was yesterday though it was more than 7 years ago...  Up until that fateful night, I had still believed that nothing was wrong... but when I came down to meet George, he didn't hug me or kiss me... his hair fell unruly on his forehead and he wouldn't meet my eyes. I wore my hair short at the time and I had chosen for the evening a light blue button up shirt and a boot cut pair of black pants. I wore just the right amount of make-up and my heart was beating like crazy in my breast...    We walked in a wary silence... his shoulders heavy with what he had to tell me, my shoulders heavy with wondering why wasn't he holding my hand... somehow I was not going to try and&nbsp;make the first step... besides he was the one who for the past 3 months was absent from the relationship...     We walked a few blocks from my house and sat at a cafe' called Dolce (Sweet in Italian).    We ordered beers... We sat in silence for a while... not the kind of peaceful silence you get in a secluded forest but the heavy kind, the kind that is filled with unspoken words and is&nbsp;ladden with unexpressed emotions... When he finally spoke, I was shocked to hear about his new girlfriend. I was so surprised that I said nothing. I honestly had no clue... I think that at the time,&nbsp; I would have found it more believable if he had told me he was abducted by aliens...  I sat there as he added "But lets stay friends". I remember&nbsp;starring at the floor and thinking "No... this is the last night you will ever see me".    I opened my purse and put some money on the table to pay for my beer which I hadn't touched... I got up, looked him straight in the eye, patted him on the back and said "Take care..." and I left him standing there, making sure I kept my head held high and that I didn't let it get dragged down by my heart on which I felt I stepped on with every step I took away from him...     I locked myself in my room and made a long distance call to my friend Helen back in Glasgow... I don't believe Helen understood me through my wails but she sure tried to calm me down... and she sure stood by me when I returned to Glasgow after my spring break... and for that she will be my friend forever...     &nbsp;   * * *     &nbsp;   That must have been one of the lowest point in my life mostly because it was so unexpected!!  I had truly, honestly  never  thought this could happen. He just didn't seem the type... I think the one thought replaying in my head at the time was "My sweet, gentle George"... and what he had just done to me certainly didn't fit my "sweet, gentle George" profile.    I remember sitting long hours, rocking back and forth in the dark, chanting like a mantra... "My sweet, gentle George"... And then I remember getting up every morning and breathing in and out until blessed sleep took me... day in, day out until all days merged but blessed oblivion would not come...     &nbsp;   It appears that all great changes are brought home to me with a great big BANG!!  This was no exception... Those 3 months I spend thinking about my "sweet, gentle George" (who grew less sweet and gentle as time went by), were the only 3 months that I smoked and behaved nasty in my whole life. I have never touched a cigarette ever since...    But out of this smoking and nasty cocoon I had locked myself into, emerged a new Me. A wiser Me. A Me that put things into perspective... A Me who picked her heart off the floor, put it back where it was supposed to be and commanded it to stop thinking, assigning this new task to&nbsp;her brain instead...     &nbsp;   Yes I loved George and yes he had "betrayed" me... but was it really that big of a shock to me? He had "needs" I was unable to meet and I will never know if those were only physical or emotional too, since George was and is, the type who won't open up to you... I have to assume now it was a combination of both... Besides, I reasoned, hadn't I broken a few male hearts myself?    I found comfort in the thought and slowly left my cocoon. But somewhere inside I swore I would let no man do this to me ever again. No man would have so much power over me ever again... or so I vowed at the time.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   I kept no contact with George as I was never one to believe in "lets stay friends". The word "friend" to me has a deep meaning, one that he could never fill again, so I steered away from him. I erased his phone from my mobile's memory. I gave away the big stuffed bear he gave me for Christmas, I deleted all his photos from my PC and threw away all memories we had created together...    I met another young man who looked nothing like George... And for a time I truly felt I was ok.  Nick, my new partner, was the first one to notice that George had never left my system.    After a while and as&nbsp;we grew closer, he developed this "irrational" fear that someone from my past would steal me away from him (He did not know about George so he could not put a name to his fear).    This sounded completely crazy to me and I tried my best to chase the fear from his heart but it only grew and grew in such proportion that he became insanely jealous and possessive.    Some rather unpleasant events took place that stemmed from his jealousy (which also made me swear that I would  never  date a Taurus ever again, even if he was the last man on Earth!).     &nbsp;   It was 6 months after I left George sitting alone in that cafe' that I got a message from him on my name day. At first I didn't recognize the phone number that appeared on my mobile phone screen, but as I read the typical "Happy Name day message" my heart started missing beats because even though my brain hadn't recognized the number, my heart had never forgotten it.    In the message he said he would have called but he was out of town... Thankfully he hadn't because if I judge from the rush I got from a text message, I might as well have gotten a stroke if I had heard his voice again that day...     &nbsp;   From that day onwards I was "tainted". My brain would scream for my heart to stop thinking about George and my heart would promptly ignore my brain and would scream louder.    I would walk down the street hand in hand with Nick and I would think "I am ok now George...come see how happy I am with Nick..."    But I wasn't. I realized soon after that wherever I went, I would be looking for George in the crowd. I desperately needed him to see how well I was doing without him... But having been hurt I didn't want to hurt Nick, who seemed smitten with me... I stayed with him and really tried to banish George from my thoughts... I might have done a better job trying to stop an avalanche with bare hands...     &nbsp;   * * *     &nbsp;   Months went by and messages from George became a frequent occurrence. I always replied in a measured and polite but rather cold and typical way. There was no mention of his new girlfriend but he did ask me out for a coffee.    I refused that proposal for over 5 months, when one day he dropped out of the blue and landed feet first right on top of my recently put together heart...    It was Good Friday, a year and 5 days since I walked out of his life and I was having coffee with a mutual male friend who had an interest in me. I had broken up with Nick the minute he had found a new girl to take my place. I felt it was the merciful thing to do and I was sure he would be less hurt now he had a new girlfriend...     &nbsp;   It is impossible to describe what I felt when I saw George again that day.    The physical symptoms I can describe but the turmoil in my soul is impossible to put into words... I remember my spine tingling and the hair at the back of my neck standing up... but I could never make out the chatter my heart and brain provided...    Somehow my mouth managed to smile and my hands did not shake... Somehow I made polite conversation to both the men that were with me. Apparently the part of your brain that controls these things is a totally independent part from the one that controls your emotions, because it was certainly surreal for me to be there with these two men, one I was in love with but didn't want me and one that I was not in love with but who certainly wanted me...     &nbsp;   George pretty much fled shortly after we finished our coffees, but not before&nbsp;I caught the furious glance exchanging between him and my date. Apparently my date won because George retired for the day with I am now sure was a made-up excuse of some business he had to attend to.    An hour in his presence was enough to make me forget every single promise I had made to myself and my brain was no longer able to hush my heart's desire...    However it did have enough power to stop her from rushing headlong into George's arms... so for the next 3 months I gave him a run for his money...     &nbsp;   If he wanted me back, he would have to not only win me back but also say it clearly this time...    I won't bore you with the details but eventually I was convinced and I found myself once again in his arms... though I was certainly prepared for the worst every single day. But somehow instead of him leaving me again, he loved me...    I don't know if it was the fact that I was now 21 and more mature .. or as I liked to think of it, that he had missed me. I was certainly the  only  woman he ever came back to...    Later on he told me that he realized he loved me that summer... And for the first time in his life he said "I love you" and that was meant for me...     &nbsp;   We had a few more bumps on the road mostly stemming from my distrust but we bonded slowly and steadily, checking and re-checking everything before moving on to the next step. Maybe we did a good job and build a strong relationship that will last a life time... I certainly hope it will. Only time will tell... but I can tell you this with certainty: I can see my unborn children in his eyes and if I am to grow old with one person... there is no other person in the world I want to grow old with.     &nbsp;   Do I love my husband? Madly...    Will I forever be with him? Only time will tell... but if love  is  the greatest force in the universe, then I think the odds are in our favor...    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just minutes ago I was pretty sure of what I wanted to say.    All these thoughts and emotions flowed through me, eager to be released, eager to manipulate my fingers so they would convey themselves into comprehensible&nbsp;words...  T  hat was minutes ago.       I stood starring at the monitor, the words leaving me, the emotions ebbing away slowly. I was not sure anymore... what  did  I want to write about? Was it a story? Was it a sort of journal?    Did I want to write about anything at all?!     &nbsp;   I took a deep breath and closed my eyes, tapping lightly on the source of all my thoughts and like scared butterflies, my thoughts spread their translucent wings and flew away.    Truth is I didn't know where to start... and without a start, you cannot begin to tell your tale.     &nbsp;   There are days that all this&nbsp;seems so complex and I drift in awe and fear, in this endless sea, a relic left to the mercy of the waves and the winds.    Then there are days that I feel I am the captain of this mighty ship called My Life and that I turn the wheel to follow in the direction I want to go. I feel strong and competent on days like these and my fear is nothing more than the frail whisper of the wind as my ship, My Life, rides the waves undaunted...     &nbsp;   I was this brave captain up until I got married, basically because I had to be; I was all alone before and I was held accountable for my self only.    Little did I know of the magnitude of change my life would undergo as I softly said "I do" looking lovingly into a pair of dark eyes on that Friday morning in the City Hall.    A crummy looking, fat man with a stained shirt performed the ceremony. His skin was brownish and sickly looking, his graying hair tousled, his eyes yellowish and his big belly overflowing over his belt. If I didn't know better I would think he was a garbage collector and not the deputy Mayor of Philadelphia.    I had no notion of what this day would be like; in fact I hadn't even thought to invite our parents up until the last minute. All the mystery and fun was taken out of this thing called "The Wedding Day";  MY  wedding day...    Maybe it was because George, my husband, had made it seem like a trivial thing. All this paperwork and the lack of a romantic proposal put me in a frame of mind that was certainly  not  romantic. However I did get my hair done and I did buy a new suit for the occasion. He didn't even wear a tie...     &nbsp;   We didn't live together immediately after we got married... I still had roughly 7 months left on my apartment lease and our new apartment was not ready yet. It now seems like so long ago but at the time to me it seemed like those 7 months would never end...    However time has this tendency to indeed pass and there I was all of a sudden, 23 years old, married,  somebody's wife,  responsible for someone else, responsible for a whole household, with no particular knowledge and suddenly... with a  family  that seemed to want to be this huge part of life, to know everything I did daily and of course always eager to give me advise about how to best care for their firstborn who now was my husband... &nbsp;   &nbsp;   Don't get me wrong, both my parents are alive and I have two younger siblings so technically I do have a family. But its the kind of family that you see on formal occasions. The kind of family that would swear they want to see you more often but whose busy lives don't offer that opportunity often. I was raised with a time limit "You must be grown by age 18 because after that you are on your own". By age 18 I was ready to be on my own... I  wanted  to be on my own.    My parents, though divorced of course, gave me everything I could possibly need so that by age 18 I would be ready to be on my own.    I went to the finest schools, took piano lessons, guitar lessons, did my ballet, did my sports, got my degrees and diplomas and by age 18 I was sent off to University to study.     &nbsp;   But as my family would soon prove to be, that attempt of mine to study was taken to be "frivolous" and when the chance came, my family would come to the conclusion that a Bachelor's in anything wasn't a "must have" and I would be pulled off Uni in order to get a job. I was after all 21 at the time, certainly I was able to fend for myself so why would they have to pay for me to study??      However I did get a diploma in Pre-School education and I got a job as a kindergarten teacher.    The salary sucked and the hours were long, the work arduous and filled with responsibility, but I loved the children! The children made every second worth my troubles and their smiles filled my heart... I cried at the end of each school year knowing I would not see my children again as they left me to go to elementary school. I wondered if they would remember me, but I don't remember my teachers from the age of 3 or 4 so I suppose they won't remember me either...       &nbsp;   I got an apartment on my own acting under the impression that George would move in with me, but it soon became evident he wouldn't. The rent was more than half my salary and suddenly I felt betrayed. I was stuck with a two year lease on an apartment I could not afford, all by myself and a boyfriend who seemed totally "out there". Thankfully he intervened and I got a better paying job as a Developer in a big computer company. My passion for computers indeed helped me out for once...    George was "with it" and "out of it" at the same time. I cannot possibly judge him because God knows how he must view me. I am sure a lot of my personality traits bother him to no end like some of his bother me. But I am not the manipulating type; I would never try and change him in his basic form and function. I take most things as they are, in a way respecting that they are the way they are for a reason... but the more I stayed with George the less brave I became.  He had a cunning power over me, this need of his to be on top and in control. This need to double check me just in case I did anything wrong and of course every argument would end up in a fight; a fight he would always win. He had an inate need to convince me that I was no longer alone, that I could count on other people and as time went by I started to believe him thus letting go of my strength... I would not need it anyway now that I had other people to rely on.. right?    Sometimes I think the only reason he stayed with me is because I was the only one with low enough self-esteem to nod and say "yes sir" every time and let him get away with everything.  He has a mean temper... and complete and utter terror seizes him every time he feels he might loose control. He has an obsession with money; he seems to think that as long as you have money, you are fine... so in turn he works all day long.  Basically I think that I can commit murder and tell him and as long as he won't have to pay, he will nod and say "ok". But if something threatens his status in any way, there will be Hell to pay.    Its been two years since we moved in together... and here I am, alone in this apartment, waiting for a husband who works from 7am to 9pm, to walk through the door, eat and sleep and sometimes watch a movie with me and I wonder... is this really the life I dreamed of? Is this the life all couples of this era live? Am I the only one who feels there is something seriously missing from my life? Or am I just plain crazy and I have watched too many love films over the years, enough to have a clouded version of what a married life is?    I used to believe I was waiting for something to happen... that all that happened before were just preparing me for this one moment when my life would  really  start... and I look back now and I realize it  has  really began. However he seems to think that he is still in preparation. He seems to say very often "We still have this or that to do and then we can relax"... there never seems to be a right moment for him. Things have never&nbsp; really  started for him, he is still building infrastructure.  It seems we are on different pages... or is it simply that  this  is life and all this time I was just living in a dream world? Were all my dreams and fantasies about the future just that? Fantasies? Is this the real life? Is real life nothing more but hard work, a husband who moves further and further apart from you but provides you with a good living... a house that needs constant caring but is also your golden cage? Where is the balance in all this and how can I find it?    Up until 2 years ago I was sure I was the captain of my ship... now my main sail is broken and hangs loose and my rudder won't always obey my hand... I feel less and less strong and confident... I started caring more and more about appearances and what the people would say... I started laughing less and less... and I wonder:    Does this happen to all new couples? Or is it an omen? A sign? And will love really be enough?    The universe is calling me... and I don't know how to answer...     
     

    
</post>


</Blog>