<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmmm i received an email yesterday about this hang out place in KL called Rush (at Eastin Hotel)... for the benefit of those of you who havent gooten a copy of it, lemme copy and paste it here for you to read.     Subject: FW: Aware of the RUSH club washroom Ladies      To every ladies out there,       Please be aware that there is a new club which used to be called Viva located in Eastin hotel called RUSH Club. Inside the ladies washroom there is a blue water flowing glass with a mirror next to it, it's a see through mirror from the guys washroom. So ladies be aware because we can't see the guys from the opposite but the guys can watch every single move and things that we are doing int he washroom except when u're in the cubicle. I've been to the club and my bf told me about it. He said he sees every gal in the washroom clearly and the other guys are like watching a show in their washroom. Please pass this message to all of ur gal frens to aware them about this humiliating action that is going on at RUSH Club.       The One Who Cares       &nbsp;  what i want to say is that... heyyyy people out there who hasnt been to Rush.. or to all the guys, ah peks, ham sap lous, werewolfs, vampires and kind&nbsp;who are probably&nbsp;Rush-ing there just to get into the little boysroom.. to oogle at the poor unfortunate girls who are somehow unaware of you looking at them while they check on thier make up, adjust their bras... pick their nose.. drying their wet arm pits or hope to see some cleavage of some&nbsp;drunk chick&nbsp;puking her guts out at the washroom bla bla and bla...     before you get so excited.... this email is only partially  true ...  ohhh yes yes , there is a blue water flowing glass&nbsp;complete with bubbles rushing upwards&nbsp;in the ladies toilet at the place where you wash your hands...    this was my own expreience ok... whilst washing my hands and trying to look for my own reflection (like any normal girl would do when faced with a mirror)&nbsp;on that so called mirror with those little bubbles and all... at first thought i was too drunk till i cant even recognise my own face or what the hell.. who is that fat reflection looking at me!!   actually there was this other guy who was also washing his hands after a pee.. and that drunken&nbsp;idiot was mimicking what i was doing.... ohhh god... its not a really clear image though with those bubbles and Chivas swimming in my blood system.. and i was like going nearer and nearer to the&nbsp;'mirror' squinting to see a very vague figure or a guy on the opposite side... quite good looking hunk though waving back at me... while i showed him the universal sign~~&nbsp;my middle finger!   then it was like a game of guess what i'm trying to say session ~~ somewhat similar to a win lose or draw session.. just that this was a silent type.. and everything was blue in colour :Þ we had fun in the toilet though hahaha.... and tadaaaaa&nbsp;i made a new friend   so what, if they can see you while you wash your hands.. you can also see what is going on in the guy's toilet from the girls toilet... its entirely up to your own judgement what you want to do while you are in there...like the chinese saying, in every threat there is always an opportunity.. for my case it was this cute looking guy with a great sense of humour  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometime this march or was it february, I started this internet dating thingy, the very first guy I dated was everything I had never dated before..&nbsp;older but&nbsp;rich, matured and good-looking.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; Being in full romantic mode or out of total boredom, we did all the usual msn chat and stuff... email till you are crazy or until mailbox exploded... chat till Celcom&nbsp;had to send me a&nbsp;message saying that i have exceeded my credit limit~ all those lovey dovey stuff.... so my friends that&nbsp;was&nbsp;the beginning of&nbsp;my fairy tale... complete with the peter pan and whats&nbsp;that little fairy like girl throwing golden dust everywhere?  crazily hangin on to my email, msn,&nbsp;my phone, great thrill and excitement i tell you :Þ  after a few weeks of&nbsp;meetings and dinners and movies... and&nbsp;walking about midvalley, klcc... practically all the malls available in kl... the thrill somehow&nbsp;died.. i really mean DIED... and by then we were not really getting along that well.. cos&nbsp;handsome guy suddently appeared as this rich fool with not much sense of humour and he was this control freak who makes you feel like you are some dumb ass with toufoo for brains and your breast as his playground... and he had this bloody male ego thing that could piss off any sane minded girl in the radious of 2&nbsp;km!! sooooo i concluded that its time to say good bye.. you bastard..&nbsp;and i did&nbsp;it in the most&nbsp;tech savvy way.. via my new toy "msn&nbsp;messenger" 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      eheheh... this is like backdated entry.. but anyway.. this is my page and i can write whatever and comment whatever i want&nbsp; :-D   last weekend was a crazy and super packed weekend.. with the mood switching from sombre to hyper... back to solemn... cos my uncle passed away, so we were like at the wake of my uncle damn sad occasion... but its like a final release for him as he has been suffering like hell for the past 2 years... but it was such an event i dont think i will ever forget.. quite a unique occasion actually.. cos on sunday (his funeral day) my cousin's, aunties, uncles.. his dancing students.. everyone of us took out our dancing shoes and started ballroom dancing before the service.. and my uncles also took the occasion to play a song for him and there was also a karaoke session.. wah lao chaotic and damn bloody noisy.. even the pastor was shocked!! this type of thing you can only expect from the "Ong" family.. hahaha   saturday night was great.. my parents and me, we drove up to Genting to watch Richard Clayderman Concert, tickets that we have bought like 2 months ago, and waited like hell for the day to come.. so Genting we went... actually feel bad also didnt go for my uncles final wake night... but well the concert was really great!! totally enjoyed the whole session...   was suposed to come back to kl, to meet up my friends&nbsp;who were partying at Rush... *this is for Kevin, complete with apologetic wink&nbsp;~ i'm so sorry*... but have to ffk last minute cos, i was busy with "Uncle Lim" hahaha... made RM100 that night...   ohh for those who dont know Kevin... he is this handsome childhood friend of mine whom i used to have this BIG time crush on him when i was much younger... used to run about palm trees.. rolling on the grass... splashing water at each other... like indian movie huh? actual truth is that we learn to play tennis together under the same coach, my bowling mate, we go for stamina building swimming sessions together... what else? cant remember.. but well quite a hunk... maybe i should go and meet him that night.. heard that he is single again muahahaha.....    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow.. i finally went and get myself registered at a blog site! hahaha....  &nbsp;  loads of thanks to a friend who told me about this site :) so much less hassle to blog here...  &nbsp;  didnt go to work today... managed to sleep till about 9.30am till Sujata called me for lunch.... too bad susan couldnt make it.. so we ffk sujata hahaha.... hmm i cant wait for our all girls get away next week.. i think its going to be really fun.. the 3 of us driving to our holiday destination...  &nbsp;  ok i think i will continue with more tomorrow....  &nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;    
    
</post>


</Blog>