<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So many things happened in July this year. I must admit that I was kinda distracted by few thoughts and events which took place in my life, and one can understand what really happens when they call themselves back? How would i like to rate it? Well, I dont know. There were good things as well as the bad things, but then again, bad things had more time then the good things during this july. I survived in a terrible car crash, the worst of its kind in my whole life. Thanks to Allah, he gave me a new life. Then had few relatives deaths in the family, few were of course terrible, as the person was either too young or too innocent to die but I guess thats life. We are just so unaware of the next moment. By the way, I want to apologize for the last time, I left the whole talk in the middle without putting an end to it. I hope I will be able to complete that someday. Wishing you all a happy August and hoping to keep the best amongst us. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever felt what it is like to lose someone? I have....! might not have&nbsp;lost her&nbsp;completely but YES..!!!! I DO MISS HER. We are good friends. Yes.!! after that incident, we are still good friends. We talk, we discuss things, we share whenever we need things to be but there are jut so many complications or should I say misunderstandings, which are making me unsure with each passing day. Not that I need a sympathy or something, its just..............I couldnt keep this any longer&nbsp;deep in my heart. I msut confess something here, i cried the first day when i realized that I might lose her if i dont let her know about my feelings for her. Its really embarressing for a guy actualy to cry, bcoz we are not suppose to cry out our worries or things that bother us&nbsp;but we are also human beings, with a beating heart. I remember that day was a terrible one, i docked off at Claisebrook station, took a walk towards my home&nbsp;while she was in my mind. Im sorry i cant complete it at this time but I will come back with a second part of this pretty soon. Hopefully with lots more concentration. Thanks for being with me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      August 1998, that was the time when i started working as a cleaner in the Parliament House of New South Wales. My job was of two hours daily in the morning, and i had to clean up the entire floor of ministers and cabinets included, which was a big task seemd at first but then i got used to it. It was my 3rd day in the House, when i was in one of the offices, dusting off the tables, i felt a cold touch on my shoulders. It ran through whole my body. I was wondering what that could be, bcoz the windows and doors were closed and there was no room for cold breeze to step in. I looked back but found nothing. To mention here, that there was one cleaner on each floor and so was I on the first floor, doing my job. Well&nbsp;I shook my head off and got back to work, finished the day as usuall, drove back home, had breakfast and left to university as usuall. The next day, i went to House, took my gear and headed off to clean the bunch, when i was the same room as the previous day, bz dusting off the tables and chairs, singing to myself...i felt the same cold touch of a hand on my shoulder, i left it all, and started looking what was that, but there was nothing, i checked behind the curtains, under the table, looked everywhere...but what could be there? it was just me, standing there with my cleaning gear,amazed what might have touched me? i was kinda surprised as well as shocked bcoz the touch was of a human hand and i felt that on my shoulder, now that was the second day in turn, i tried but couldnt get it off my mind, so i decided to get back to work, singing in high tunes then before, thought that might help. After finishing off, i came down and signed the leave register, i told my Incharge lady about what has happened and what i felt, but she smiled and advised me not to watch too many movies. So i drove back to my place as used to and followed my daily schedule. Next day, i started workin in my routine again, bearing in my mind that if something happens today then im gonna find it out for sure whats that about? Keeping myself calm, i entered the room and started cleaning, five minutes went very well, nothing happened and i was thinking to myself that it must be my imagination or something else which kept me bothered for the past 2 days. But wait a minute, the next moment i heard a voice, asking me to quiet down as i was singing really loud...geez!! that really broke the shackles if you know what i mean, i opened the door and look right and left in the long coridor, but there was no one, and why should be? it was I who suppose to work on that floor...so i came back in the room, and looked all over carefully, sat on a chair. nod my head, try to forget it but it was just so real bcoz i heard the voice myself. I was really worried, so i started talking to myself that its not real. As i get up saying, "i cant see you but i know you're there". she talked to me again, saying that i have disturbed her by singing that loud. It really made me crazy and I sat back in the chair, whirling my eyes on the roof and around. I couldnt see her but she introduced herself as Ms.Cowan, an Ex-minister of the House. I ran back down staries, telling all this to my incharge, she made me calm down. Then she told me that this is the spirit of Ms.Cowan, who was a minister of the parliament house, and she still lives there but she doesnt disturb anyone unless the person disturbs her. She told me that the cleaners who worked there before me, left the job after finding this out. Thats why she didnt tell me about this in the first place. So I decided to make friends with Ms.Cowan. After that whenever i step in that room, i say, Good Morning Ms.cowan, im afraid i have to clean this up but I promise I wont disturb you." That was just one the incident happened with me in Australia. There are lots more and I will be sharing those with you in days to come.  &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      day took off as usuall.....was wid few family peeps last night, had fun, after a long, felt good..its always good to be wid peeps who lov u, esp fer me, been away almost all my life so far, now gettin back seems good, they say it runs both ways, so i believ it, seen it happenin, wat more it takes?? i'll be back wid few more lines ti share wid u, had a good day, will let u know bout it 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had fun today. Summer in this part of world is cruel but still a lively corner of the world. Its about getting my guitar back. You think i lend to someone.Nooo.!! i broke it few months ago against a wall, i guess i was angry at something. Anyways, its not the right time to discuss that. I went to Lahore just before the long weekend here, visited Hasan, a childhood friend of mine and a good colleague aswell. We roam around in the bustling city and ended up buying myself a guitar. I am a gutar freak, you see. I have been playing guitar for twelve years now, started it off when i could hardly get it in my hands, but that was fun. I have always been inspired by Santana and then there was Bryan Adams. The one i got now is a Semi-Accoustic one, like the one you can mix softies on. It does support hard but softies sounds marvelous on it, and i love to play softies when im down....Ooopsss..!! thats a secret..!! LOL Gosh...if you peeps know what time is here, will definately kill me, LOL..!! but i aint sleepy, told you i cant put off before 4, but its past 4 already. I dont know what should i do? hmmmmm, like i better play some tunes but then all the other peeps are sleeping sound in their rooms, yeah and i dont want them to bust me in the morning or like as we speak. I better get outta here or else do some posts to my mates. i havent done that like in 5 days now. I think should be nice to others, LOL...!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its Friday the 13th here, wood u believe this? nothing like the frankinstein stuff or else, its the August 13th here, and tomorrow is Pakistan's Independence Day. Yep..!! we are gonna crack some fires, rush up or do something like that. I am not really used to this, been doing that in my boyhood, but then there was the age of maturity or rather must say, didnt have much time to waste as used to. It'll be the same fireworks sight on independence day, like we witness on Australia Day, January the 26th. Fire rocking in the capital, over the parliament house here in Islamabad, a spectacular sight to see every year..lots of people around and it gets hard to drive by on the raods, you know what I mean? Last night was hell boring. Nothing was in favor, i got my pc fixed, then i checked with the internet and it didnt work, someone took the cable off the switcxhes and as the switches were tightly secured, i was unable to get my fingers in there to get the cables back in place,, so me and my brother, we spend the whole night playing video games, eventaully ended up one which was quiet boring. Its been with me for the past 7 years now that I cant sleep before 3 o clock in the morning. i got this bad habit from Australia where i used to work late and then end up reaching home late hours in the night and leave home early next morning for work again. That was quiet fun too and as well as painful sometimes, as i felt like not doing anything. Weather is really lagging here now a days. Had rains few days back and now again the same old Humidity prevails...Gosh, when we gonna get over it? I know its gonna stick with us till end of October but I'm aint in a position to wait that long. I always hated summer, it always brings so many things with it I hate to do. For instance, taking shower like countless times in a day,sweat, smell, yuck..!! forgive me what am I talking here.?? I decided to go out and see a pal whom i long visited, and i was told at the gates that I cant do that just now because mom wanna take me somewhere with her. Hmmm, hows it gonna be, Im just wondering..... Aite, heres the call..i gotta run now peeps...Oi, stick around me mates...i wanted to share few things with u guys, and will do that later when i return. you know I'll always return.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I meant to write it sooner and in a more delightful manner but I guess it wasnt suppose to happen. Life is really weird, dont you think? Especially mine, so many troubles and problems poping up everyday. You know, every morning I wake up with a hope that this day might bring some light, it might do some thunders, but it hardly happens, you see..!! Its nothing like that Im disappointed or something. Its just one's patience has its limit, yeah...!! The night before, i badly needed to talk to someone, and to my luck, there was no one i could speak to. So i signed in on internet and looked there, had few peeps but they were either in good mood or were busy in something important of their own, so I left it unsaid. I spend the whole night staring my roof, wondering what it is made of? Frankly, I have no idea what i am putting down here coz its just so aweful. Leave no comments here ok? 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me and Fred were just talking on msn messenger when he had a look at my blogs, relating towards my profile, telling me that I was born in the Year of a Horse. Now would you believe this? Horse and me, we both have nothing in common. Horse is an animal and well..!! what can I say about myself, you guys know me better, dont you peeps? Fred was just so high up with it that i decided to put some lines about it here so when he returns, he'll have something to read about. So here its for u Fred. I think that the idea of putting a theme of "born in the year of...." in the profile of a blogger here is quiet aweful. The guy must have been from Mars or some place near about, or maybe in the last hood, he/she was an animal, LOL... Not quiet so mad about being born in the year of horse, some people here were born in the year of Cows, Buffalows, Sheeps, Gerrafs and so on. But onething is for certain that Fred was born in the year of Godzilla, LOL. No offence my friend but you see, sometimes things are more than they appear. So have a laugh about it and keep it cool bcoz after all SIZE DOES MATTER. auright, i hafta write few lines to my mates back in Sydney, they have been complaining about not getting their replies in order. See ye all around and yea, keep your Jag off the corner, Fred..!! Have a nice day. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AHH..!!! I couldnt believe Renee called me up today. Its been like three years now since me and Renee last spoke to eachother. I remember the last time i saw her was in the Willeton Galleria, she was doing some shopping while i was catching up my coffee there. I saw Renee with a heavy load, confused as always so I decided to offer her some of my help. We have alot of good memories together. She was the first person in university to show me the student's office and from there on in, we became good friends. She told me today that she has finally got her dream guy and they have decided to get married in December this year. Congrats to her as it was hell tough for Renee to find a "suitable person" as she used to say. I dont know renee that i'd be able to participate in your wedding but as I promised to you on the phone, I'll do my best. After all we are the best buddies. She has a mysterious personality among our clique, the one of its kind whose eyes always roam around when we were either at cinema or dodging glances on a train. It was fun being with her. quiet amusing I must say. Aurihgt fellows, time for me to catch up with some drink now. But you know that you guys hafta come back to see if there's any update, eh? You bet there will be. Take care ye all and see ye all back in sydney. Wish me well
     

    
</post>


</Blog>