<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;I went to watch a pratice at the high school today. I missed it while I was there. I miss performing and all that stuff but when I in my normal life I dont miss it. Do I want to do winterguard? Is this me just having a moment of craziness. Shouldnt I just focus on school my first year and get settled before I get all crazy and have myself divided in a million pieces again. I just finished with colorguard. Do I really want to start the whole thing all over again?? What do you think? 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bfast: coffee 0               lunch: publix sub.. i know what you are thinking, i went all crazy, but i did good... for a publix sub.  You KNOW how good those are!  turkey on wheat, mustard, lettuce, tomato, bl. olives (a couple),  vinegar.  I am going to count that as 8.      snack-banana bar -3    dinner- 2 fat free eggo waffles with brummel butter 2+1 and syrup 2=5  hmmm... that means i can have some ice cream!  :)  i think i will.    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hi everyone!   &nbsp;  This is my first blog...ever!!&nbsp; I'm not quite sure how I would like to utilize this experience though.&nbsp; Most of the people that know me&nbsp;would probably attest to the fact that I am the "keep it inside and work things out internally" type of person.&nbsp; I am sometimes envious of the people who can just get it out there and talk about shit.&nbsp; It takes some coaxing with me I guess...I have had 23 years of practice being internal, but I've been trying for a while to&nbsp;create new communication practices.&nbsp; When I was younger I tried to keep diaries and journals.&nbsp; Yeah...those never lasted.&nbsp; I&nbsp;tried recently&nbsp;to keep up with a journal of sorts, but I&nbsp;could never to commit to it.&nbsp; I'll try hard to keep up with this blog...I really love the idea of it.&nbsp; I love to hear peoples stories and maybe I'll post some of my own.&nbsp; For now I think I'll stick with random thoughts, freak-outs about my body, my lethargic attitudes towards exercise, some favorite poems and maybe some of my own.  &nbsp;  Until next time...take care  Jenna   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I cannot wait until my Sundays are filled with fun things.  I long to be part of the culture that goes out to restaurants rather than serving those that go out to restaurants.  What, I ask you, is better than a 'free agent' Sunday?  I would say that lipgloss, pillow top mattresses, bubble baths, and beer and wings would be on the same place on my list as a 'free agent' Sunday.  I will tell you what does not top my list.  Early evening menus and bitter participants of the eating out community, that's what!  So supermodels, now is the time to schedule your Sunday time with me.  I know you are thinking to yourself, Jan, it is five months away until 'free agent' Sundays even begin.  Why do I need to book now?  I'll tell you why.  Because my mind is furiously thinking up ways to spend those very days...and I know that you want to be included in the fantastic world of fun I am planning for myself.  So don't hesitate.  Act now!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I ate my granola bar for breakfast - along with my caffeine filled Diet Dr. Pepper.  But then - that's when it went wrong - I ate 4 chips ahoy cookies.  Why?  I was not hungry - I just wanted them.  They are wrong - and chips are wrong - and dog gone it - ahoy is wrong in some way too.  I need to do better - or my "big" pants that now are large due to dieting will fill up with "ahoy" and I will no longer be on the path of dieting.  Ahoy fat - ahoy....
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bf- coffee  lunch- turkey sadwich on wheat 40cal bread.  2 points         grapes 1 cup- 2 points         3 pumpkin oatmeal WW cookies (with craisins) 3 points  dinner- Applebees- side salad 0                     that fish and rice dish 7                     choc raspberry dessert- 3 (and I DIDNT share!  lol soo good) and as if that wasn't enough sweets for the day I also had:  skinny cow cookies and cream ice cream (double serving) with cut up bananas and strawberry sauce- 7 points.  total- 24 (not sure exactly how many i am permitted, but i try to say around 21-23... last night it was worth every single bite.  that ice cream is good!  water-5 soda-none  Xersize- i moved half of my classroom and my whole body hurts today.  so that counts for something!  scale 8.5
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was really close to going to work out today.  but i didn't.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got this off my other message board.  FUN!  :)   A- What is your Age? ~28 B- What is your favorite Book? ~Tuesday's with Morrie. (read it right away if you haven't!) C- What is your favorite Color? ~Purple D- Dessert or not? Favorite kind? ~yes. bananas foster cheesecake from red losbster. E- Are you Employed? Where? ~ Yes, special ed teacher-elementary F- Do you have a favorite Flower? ~no, i just like color comboniations of flowers G- What Games did you play as a child? Hungry Hippo, candy land.. the usual. "as a kid" we stillplay games now. no kids, and we play cards etc regularly H- What are your Hobbies? DIY home decoration/improvement. beads, scrapbooking etc. ** new, knitting. I- Do you suck or chew Ice? neither J- Junk collector or neat freak? both extremes. K- Kids, do you want any more, and if so, how many? lets just start with one and see how it goes :) probably 2 total L- Which Loved one have you lost or are losing? gma and stp mother. M- What is your favorite Memory? The look on my husbands face while looking at me on our wedding day N- Where is your favorite spot in the Nation? ~anywhere that is concidered "vaction" O- Own or rent? Own P- Any Pet Peeves? shoes on the counter/table.. really anywhere but the floor.. Q- Favorite Quote? If you always do what you've always done, you'll always get what you've always got R- Favorite Restaurant? i'm not picky.. but i do prefer steak and potatoes S- Why did you choose your Screen name? It is my last name, and my sp. ed kids call me "Peters" not Mrs. Peters, just Peters. You shold have seentheir faces when I introduced them to my husband Mr. Peters. They couldn't believe we had the same name!! :) Peters-like Madonna or Cher :)lol T- Tea, coffee, or soda ~soda was my fav until the dentist said NO MORE! so, coffee. U- University degree, have one or could care less? Yes-couldn't teach without it. V- Where and when was your last Vacation? New years vacation house with our friends. we rent a huge house and all stay a week. W- Weight, happy with it or want to gain or lose? i am a diet expert~ Sweet potato queen. (read that book if you havent.. hillarious!!) X- Xtra salt or none? None Y- Yummy or Yucky- Pickles? Yummy Z- Zoo, Sea World, or Disney? Nah... I live in Florida. Too much hype. I hate the crowds. Can't wait to go to the zoo when i have a little one. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      here is why i should be proud of myself but need help feeling that through my hurt right now...  i told him that i loved him, that i had fallen in love with him through all of this and that i didn't expect him to make any choices, that i was deciding that i needed to say goodbye...  he cried   i was crying the whole time...duh...and he said he felt frustrated...that he really liked our connection but understood why i needed to do this...  if i had not said how i felt and distanced myself from this emotionally explosive situation, i would have slowly eroded away, and hoped and waited for him to change his mind....  but i did say and i did choose...and it's supposed to be liberating and good feeling and this sucks instead...i hate that i had to say goodbye  i hate that he said he did have these feelings for me too but had to be on his own, to live life on his own for awhile to gain a clearer picture of who he is...  i'm angry because i'm not able to manage my feelings into better places where they don't mess up my head and make me cry all the time  i wanted him to say come back to me in 6 months and then i will say "i love you now" but just for now i need to be only friends..  i wanted to be enough....................  i'm not though, and i feel very bad through a place when i'm supposed to be proud that i stood up for suzy  i can't  beat this feeling that something wonderfully special just left my life  so i'm proud... right
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok...  I've been fooling around with our blog and have done some html coding to make our comment areas easier to read and deal with.  I've transferred old comments to the new places and some that were too big, i made them their own post.  Hint...sometime when you click on the new comment link, it's lazy...so refresh your webpage and try again kids...it will work.  Any comments on the newest change...i'm learning all kinds of neat things that we can do to our new blog home.  Suggestions are welcome...I AM THE DIRECTOR!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Phenomenal Woman -Maya Angelou  Pretty women wonder,  where my secret lies I'm not cute  or built to suit a fashion model's size But when I start to them them They think I'm telling lies.  I say It's in the reach of my arms the span of my hips the stride in my step the curl of my lips I'm a woman phenomenally Phenomenal Woman That's me.  I walk into a room Just as cool as you please and to a man  the fellows stand or fall down to their knees Then they swarm around me A hive of honey bees.  I say It's the fire in my eyes and the flash of my teeth the swing of my waist and the joy in my feet I'm a woman phenomenally Phenomenal Woman That's me.  Men themselves have wondered what they see in me they try so much  but they cant touch  my inner mystery when I try to show them they say they STILL can't see.  I say It's the arch of my back the sun of my smile the ride of my breasts the grace of my style I'm a woman phenomenally Phenomenal Woman That's me.  Now you understands just why my head's not bowed. I don't should or jump about or have to talk real loud. When you see my passing it ought to make you proud.  I say It's in the click of my heels the bend of my hair the palm of my hand the need for my car. I am a Woman Phenomenally Phenomenal Woman That's me.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is such a selfish, spoiled life we all live. I get so wrapped up in daily happenings and stresses and what I believe to be "tramas" of my life. It is all so insignificant.  Living on cement, a bane of my existance... and then to read of a woman who lived in a room smaller than a bedroom with eleven people, on bunkbeds three tiers high, with no heat... listening to mice eat within an earshot away.... Going on a diet, trying to feel more attractive within myself, when they had nothing but moldy bread and water that caused such disease... starving to death with clothes just draping over them...   Family surrounding me, living near me, that I do not spend hardly enough time with... when these people were ripped apart from their husbands and children...  Feeling "cheated" out of a fair income as a teacher, when these people were robbed of their every possession. Paying money to be put on a "special list" that they believed would save their lives, and in the end it did not.  Drawing a line of what I will and won't do for kids, as in staying after and volunteering my time to complete things that I make wait.. feeling that the more time I volunteer, the more I am saying, i will give without expectations for reinbursement... when she worked her every breathe to give friends, family and total strangers more comfort...worked until she passed out from fatigue...  It is amazing the spoiled lives we live in... and only want more for ourselves in such a selfish way.. feeling we deserve more. what more can we deserve? when we are healthy, surrounded by loved ones, fed, clothed, and free?  It is such an inspiring story... putting much needed perspective ... that somehow gets lost after time of living in such a materialistic society where things come first... and "no I in team" is a cliche to motivate people to do what is not already self motivated within...   Where free people feel grand enough as to martyr themselves in their daily CHOICES. The nerve to think that all that they possess in riches is not enough... it is disgusting. and i am guilty of it as much as the next person...  my manic behavior during thanksgiving... feeling that I have done enough, and unappreciated. it is crap. we all have our moments of ugliness and weakness of character, and there is no fault in having your turn.. but it boggles the mind.   Everytime I think "___________ is not enough. I want more" I am going to have to go back and reflect my thoughts of today. How blessed I am. How much more I can give to the world. Where my wealthy truely lies.  It is strange the clarity you feel after dragging yourself through an emotional pit. How much you yearn to reflect.. now much you hope your new ideas stick.. and stay with you.. and have a permanent impact on your life, and not just a fleeting thought.  The best thing I can give to myself is improving my outlook... to become a more positive thinking, and beliver. How much easier day to day functions become when you are believing yourself blessed. The increased patience, and understanding... compassion...  I think that is all I care to write for right now. I may come back to this later. Thanks for listening, if you made it this far. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bf- coffee 0     banana 2 lunch- salad w/ turkey, fetta and bacon bits 6  dinner- turkey meat taco salad with baked chips, ff cheese, salsa, lettuce, tomato, lowfat sour cream, mexican rice a rf beans- 10-12 pts    water-4 boo  soda- 0  xrsize-zip  (maybe I'll just write when i do instead of when i dont.. if you dont see anything, assume i sat on my ass all day lol)  pts 20 rating- 7
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's good to be back home. I have been such a pig the past 2 weeks.  You don't even want to know what I have put into my body lately. So bad for you but damn GOOD! My goal is to start some type of diet tomorrow! Hope this helps.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just finished as much as I could stomach to read of diaries and letters by Etty Hillesum.  As closely as I can describe her, she was the Anne Frank of the 20 somethings.  The book titled her name is two books put together.  The first is her diary leading up to her going to Westerbork.  (Westerbork is the place where Anne Frank and her family were also sent... along with most Dutch jews and many German jews as well.  It was a camp that housed tens of thousands of jews waiting for the trains to Poland.  The train left weekly on a Tuesday.  She was a member of the Jewish Council.  This council were the "leaders" of the camp and have varied jobs of sorts.  Etty died at 20.  She was a lawer and had a doctorate degree of some sort.  Her family was very scholarly and her brother Mischa was a musical prodigy.    Her letters and her life's writing were consumed with humanity and beauty.  She found all things beautiful even in unthinkable situations.  situations that we have no understanding of.  so incomprehansible.  She would write these letters outside, sitting on a grassy spot and discuss teh beaty of the world, and the goodness in everyone, including thos soldiers who mastered over her andher family.    Her words are eloquent and strike the chord that connects your heart to your gut.    she never stopped giving to others, giving of herself, her food, her belingings for the comfort of others, and also her family when the eventually joined her in Westerbork.  she  saw to the needs of the orphans and sick...  she worked until passing out or fainting when exaustion consumed her.  She never once complains in her letters.  Never once breaks down into the "why's" that I can only imagine myself being absorbed with.    During her time in Westerbork she grew quite ill and while on release in amsterdam stayed wit friends for five months until she was well wnough to return.  During the time she was sick, she wrote to her friends in the camp expressing how badly she yearned to return to them and their company.  She was approached many times by people who were a part of the resistance movement, who  wanted to get her out, and although many survived the war, she declined the offer.  The council was disolved in 43 and during that time 60 of the 120 members were permitted to return to Amsterdam, and life.  Because her family was now at the camp, she declined to leave, because of the relationships she had built, and she believed that her influence may still have an effect on the lives of her faimly and her brother.    On more than  one occassion, it did.  But in the end, it didn't.    Her last letter was written on a post card from the freight train taking them to Poland.  she scribbled it down and threw it fromt he train.  It was found and mailed by some farmers.  It read:  Christine, Opening the Bible at random I find this: "The Lord is my high tower."  I am sitting on my rucksack in the middle of a full freight car.  Father, Mother, and Mischa are a few cars away.  In the end, the departure came without warning.  On sudden special orders from The Hague.  We left the camp singing, Father and Mother firmly and calmly, Mischa too.  We sahll be travelling for three days.  Thank you for all your kindness and care.  Friends left behind will still be writing to Amsterdam; perhaps you will hear something from them.  Or from my last letter from camp.                          Good-bye for now from the four of us.                           Etty   I don't know why I felt that I should share this, except that it had such an impact on my and my thinking, I thought to share it in writing.  Trying to speak of it getts jammed up in a knot in my throat where it doesn't seem to come out in words.  Only tears.    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was tough for me. As most of you know Craig and I are trying to get pregnant.  I was supposed to start my period yesterday... but there is no telling what my cycle will be like off the pill.  (this is the first month off). I took a test this morning and it came back negative.  Now before you give me the whole, it is just the first month, don't worry, you will get pregnant, keep your hopes up speech... please know that I know all of these things.  I can tell myself that.  But, it didnt help the disappointment I felt.  I cried most of the morning...  I guess I just this one thing to go easily for me.  no big rigamarole.. no hoops, ovulation kits, etc.  such is life for me.  I am feeling better now and much more on top of my emotions. s but it was a tough first half of the day.  I spent most of it painting and thinking... so, that out of the way.  here is the food report: bf- coffee (splenda) 0     pickle  0  (craig had to go to the stsore.. there was nothing low point ot eat.. so a pickle was it.      bowl of cereal with ff milk.  5      cup of grapes 1 (slept in... so, no lunch) dinner- chicken nuggests and french fries.  chicken nuggets are a shit ton of points... but i stayed within reason...  had ff ketsup and ff barbeque sauce.  total points 23  water=5  soda=none xrsize= does crying count.. guess not.  (good try though, right?)  overall day (must change my rating scale so that 10 is the highest=oprah.. 1 begin fatty fatty booblatty=goodyear blimp)  8  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YES!!!!!!  I weighed in today and I lost 4 pounds this week. It definatly gives me incentive to wake up tomorrow morning and exercise even if I do it by myself.   Food Report: English muffin-2 peanut butter-2 banana-1 popcorn-2 some sort of a bread thingy that was probably boocuu points- 10ish mabey not sure tea-2  Exercise:   35 min got my butt kicked  Scale- 8.5 (shouldnt have easten the bread thingy but was hungry)  Cindy- I would love to do the walk/run/skate thing with you give me more info when you know count me in!!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah! I made it on here!  Who is Big T?   This will be a more of a "how i'm doing on my weightloss" than a what I ate today (I already so this somewhere else, I guess I could copy and paste!)  Anyone interested in Joining me on the Walk for the Cure in October to end Breast Cancer?  I'll be R U N N I N G (as much as I can) in the 5k, but you can walk/rollerblade/electric slide with me!  Fun group activity that raises awareness for a scary disease!  I'm here! C
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I was proud of my self today I did good and I didnt cheat. I went to walgreens and walked down the candy isle to the book section and i could have grabbed my FAVORITE candys but i didnt. Yeah me!! Food report: Morning: banana-2pts          Thomas Everything bagel-3pts          Peanut butter-6 pts(dont care i LOVE peanut butter) Afternoon- none (big lunch) Dinner- orange-1 pt         wrap(2)- 2 pts         cheese-2pts         turkey-2pts         sour cream- 1pt  19 total not to shabby 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Breakfast- Coffee- 3pts (switching back to splenda tomorrow) Yogart (not good points wise, as I still have to clear out non diet friendly items) 5 points.  (frickin FIVE!!) Kashi granola in said yogart 1 point (some things still remain from last round of WW)  Snacky-lunch type item (because i got up late.. ahhh summer) plum 2 points  Dinner- Hamburger Helper (see non WW food above) round up to ten.   Salad-free  water 6 glasses  Xrsize- zippo.  painting and chatting up Suz all day :)  Soda-none  :)  Ciggs-2 BOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!  One things comes and the other goes.  No nagging, it will all end soon.  Total points-21  Rating for the day-2.5  :)  perfect day for me would be: within point range, no soda, no ciggs, all water drunk, + Xrsize.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have decided that this Blog thing is too good to know about - especially at work.  It sounds like I am typing a memo to the general cubicle populous.  It looks like I am hard at work - pondering the net operating income or some dumb crap.  It also is fun - and I love that it is slacking off.  I wrote about foods - but somehow now I need to come up with witty, meaningful blog topics.  I will think this weekend on some topics...such as "The Perfect Jean - How to Acquire It" .....
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here it is...as discussed last night while watching tv.....the new lists of foods that have no reason to exist (no good reason, that is...)  Spam Clamato (juice...for those not in the know.  And yes, it is clam and tomato)  New addition: Head Cheese
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I could paint you in the dark Cause I’ve studied you with hunger like a work of art These are very secret days I collect my information then I stowe it all away  Call me when you breeze through to your appointments The work you do Call me, I’m collecting you  The pleading prayer and hairshirt sting My hair-trigger love and faulty spring Motivation smokes a name, but I don’t like that smell applied to me so Blindly just the same   call me When you breeze through to your appointments the work you do Call me I’m collecting you Turning up my collar to an unseasonal chill you ask a favor, you know I will The rain comes a surprise we fly across the railroad ties I feel the danger the foolish thrill oh yes I will  What it will or won’t be then The shutter pre development the ink full in the pen Mind the mind’s eye’s trickery You might picture killer beautiful much more than it might be  Call me tell me what you’re up to what you’ll do Call me I’m collecting you  I would be foolish to think that I could turn it off and stay alive The way I live when you switch on hand on the dimmer, give me just a glimmer Give me just a shadow hope around the edges, agony and rapture forever uncaptured  Take these secrets to your grave Drug across your landscape and buried in your cave You’re piling up and out of sight But trying to add it up just feels like counting shades of light  Call me when you breeze through to your appointments what you must do Call me I’m collecting you  Hang it in my window let it complicate my view The separation the glass of you But I can paint this picture any way that I see fit The art of pain the subject sits unmoved  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok…I’m sitting here doing my best to combat this yucky feeling in the pit of my stomach. Nothing much is working so I’m going to go with the flow of what I’m feeling  I think wow I shouldn’t have come last weekend because right before that I was definitely at the place of return…I mean I could have been ok and not hit the place of actual physical emotion. I mean I’m glad I came because it was wonderful…every moment wonderful…I can recall how each moment shifted into the next in a easy cool good way.  I like having friends…good friends…ones you can trust and spend seriously joyous time with…before this weekend you could have hung on to your standing position as my friend…now it’s too late…  oh man, that little envelope on my crappy phone that shows up when I have a text message is nice…so nice because I know it’s from you, and it makes me smile every time…not just a hmm smile…but the kind of smile that starts with my toes and warms my body.  You get me  There aren’t many people that get me, though I don’t hide much  I love that you think my hair is cool, and tell me always when I look extra pretty…because you always make me feel the normal amount of pretty  I love that we sing together in the car to music that everyone else I know would laugh at me for knowing the words and that you cry and I cry and it’s good and I was watching you singing and all I could think about was that I have no idea how we got to this point, but I wished the song would never end. And then all I could think was that I want to know what the side of your neck smells like and I really couldn’t even hear the music anymore, let alone remember the words.  I love that most of the time I wear no makeup and don’t do my hair, and I do fun things like hiking, and swimming in the ocean and laughing on swings.  I love that you baked bread and taught me how to ‘have tea’ and don’t think I’m weird because I cleaned your shower  I’m trying to figure this out, why I’m falling for you and I know I’m not supposed too and I know that you won’t love me back but I have no answer and it just keeps happening  And I love that you want to share with me important moments in your life, and tales of interesting people and your lists and pizza from the box in the car  And I love the good day star and everything that that day was about and how on the drive home those stars were so lovely but not nearly as lovely as you and wanting grab your hand and how you thought Jill Scott was groovy too And how laying on the beach I wanted to curl up with you and have a bit of a snuggle and how I secretly thought people might think we were the couple with the sweetest dog  And how it seems that you pop into my head more times than I can count and I spend times when I should be doing other silly things thinking about what nice way I can make you feel good  I just don’t know how I’ll combat this one, remember you told me I had nothing to be scared of…I knew then you were wrong and I should have run far away…I knew that weekend that I would fall in love with you…and I guess I believed as usual that it was possible for you to fall in love with me back…that you would see how wonderful I am and that you would be unable to be without me and now I’m way past that and I’m hurting because I know I’m not the one you’ll pick flowers for or make neato gifts for no reason for…no matter how long I hang around and the present moments feel good…the rest is shitty and I feel abandoned  I know there are a million reasons for you to be alone…I know why they are important and essential… …but it’s just that I’m hoping you might have one reason to say “yes.”  so with that…after I hear the ‘no’…not now, not in a month or a year…I’ll say to you…thanks…you’re so wonderful and I must say goodbye…this friendship is too much for me and it’s tough being this emotionally available and intimate with a friend that needs to stay a friend…my heart doesn’t feel the difference…  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I ate a whole lotta shit yesterday.  Coffee-   3 pts  Granola bar for bfast-  3 pts  4 turkeyslices and a piece of cheese-  3 pts  Granola bar snack-   3 pts  Cheese dip and flat bread for dinner (ugh... how terrible when it is in writing)-  LOTS of points.   Water= 2 glasses   BOO  :(  That is it.  I drank Crystal light raspberry lemonade all  day... free points.  Soda=  None ... hooray for me.  (dentist said no more soda... so i'll report that too)  Excersize:   none  unless you count painting.  my calves are killing me, and I sweat my ass off.. but I wouldnt really call it cardio.  1-10 scale of the day  (1 being super dieter- oprah, and 10 being  fatty fatty boobalatty- goodyear blimp) about a   6.5 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What program are you on?   I am doing not a whole lotta anything right now.. hense this web community.   What do you want from coming here?  I would like to try and be better motivated.. and be held accountable. It really helps me to be motivated...   What works? How has it worked?  Weight Watchers works for me (when I am being good). I am not fully in it right now, but want to be.  Okay... that is it for introductions.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       … that make the whole world sing. What statement could be truer when speaking of the legendary composer – Barry Manilow? Don’t scoff. Don’t scowl. No one person can deny the powerful stylings of Manilow. True – I am biased – I am a “Fanilow”. Some may claim to hate him, some may claim to despise. I challenge all of you non-Barry-believers to listen the Copa Cabana and not (in some way) groove a bit in your chair. You will sing along – oh yes – to Lola and her feathers. You cannot resist. Such is the power of Manilow.  Read the lyrics below to the most famous (and lovely) “Can’t Smile Without You”.  You know I can't smile without you I can't smile without you I can't laugh and I can't sing I'm finding it hard to do anything you see I feel sad when you're sad I feel glad when you're glad if you only knew what I'm going through I just can't smile without you you came along just like a song and brighten my day who would of believed that you where part of a dream now it all seems light years away and now you know I can't smile without you I can't smile without you I can't laugh and I can't sing I'm finding it hard to do anything you see I feel sad when your sad I feel glad when you're glad if you only knew what I'm going through I just can't smile now some people say happiness takes so very long to find well, I'm finding it hard leaving your love behind me and you see I can't smile without you I can't smile without you I can't laugh and I can't sing I'm finding it hard to do anything you see I feel glad when you're glad I feel sad when you're sad if you only knew what I'm going through I just can't smile without you  It really is a medley for life – the highs and lows of life can be enhanced with the lyrics to his songs. Barry has been there. Barry knows. Barry cares.
</post>


</Blog>