<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Oh my god, you are teh sux, can you believe it? I'm afraid of the girl sitting next to me. She's a druggy to the first degree. It's amazingm, don't you think? Webdings rock. They do. Very much. They will need to be translated, however. I'm This is the most powerful blog in the world! I! To translate this, you must translate, before I can translate you rmind into my computer, using your cerebral cortex as a central processor. Why must you be human? Where am ? I'm strange. Leave me ALONE! Can you believe me buttum?    &nbsp; Translation unavailable.  

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hear-ye, hear-ye! Adelphia is teh sux! I give you pain, and what do you give me? EVIL!  That's right. Anyways, I need seventy-two able-bodied males to take up their swords, axes, and firearms to help me march on the Adelphia control center, take it over, and provide free internet connections for ALL! ... Though I don't know why people would want an&nbsp;Adelphia connection.  Anyways, I called Adelphia the other day about my internet connection being down. They were helpful, perhaps, but they won't be able to send a technician over until thursday, which really puts a damper on all of my plans to GET BACK ONLINE and SPEAK TO PEOPLE. Lazy arses. What am I talking about? I'm a lazy arse.  Ooh, Daedric Crescent! All I'm doing, while my connection is down, is playing Morrowind. Not that I mind. I'm a GOD, in that game. My character can slaughter all things living, and most things unliving. He's like:     Venicus  (My character): "OMG WTF!"  Almalexia  (Goddess): "WTF BIZNOTCH!" She fires a massive&nbsp;blast of magical energy.  High   Ordinators  (Goddess' Protectorate): "U R TEH DED!~" They charge in, slashing with their powerful&nbsp;magical blades.  Venicus : "LOLz" The blast of magical energy reflects off his spell-shield and back at Almalexia as he begins to cast a spell.  Almalexia : "OMG! U R TEH SUX!" She screams as she is hit by a massive explosion of every sort of damaging&nbsp;energy known to man.  High Ordinators : "TIHS IS NOT TEH R0X0R!" They are eviscerated by the blast of energy.  Venicus : "HAHAHAHA I AM TEH R0X0R! UR TEH SUX0R" He gloats.  Almalexia : "OMG I GEV UP UR TEH MAST0R" She kneels before Venicus and kisses his feet.  (This has been an extreme dramatization. They all died in a single casting of Venicus' Final Word spell, which deals one hundred points of Acid, Fire, Shock, Frost, and Health damage, each.)   So, yes, I have been having fun. Have a nice day!  

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My father will be calling Adelphia soon. I hate Adelphia. I want it to die. Die, Adelphia! Die!   I am soone to returne to the online worlde. Alle haile the Benevolente Overlorde!  (Translated into Old English for your simplified perusal.)    

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My connection, at home, is down. I can't do anything from my own home. I'm forced offline by terrible circumstances. Wahahaha... Nothing to report.  

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hello, hello. This is being written from SUMMARR SKOOL. Yes, I'm in SUMMARR SKOOL, at this very moment. I just finished an assignment on Animal Interests. It wasn't in the least bit interesting, but it was informative. Very informative. I'm on the fence, in terms of animal rights. Cruelty directed at animals is wrong, yes. But we cannot reason with animals. In all this "animal rights propaganda", where are the lions chewing on the necks of people they have just slain? Where are the constrictors wrapped tightly around the bloated, bruised, and lifeless bodies of small children? You cannot stop animals from killing you for sustinance; so there is nothing wrong with utilizing animals for the same purpose, or for production purposes, so long as it is done in an ethical, painless way. In essence, animals have no rights, as they are&nbsp;incapable of comprehending&nbsp;their own existence, their impending death. They will kill, as every living thing is a murderer. Humans evolved the gift of production, and that is how we survive. Animals do not need to produce. So then why are their needs worth any more than ours? They aren't. We're all alive. We're all murderers. The best humans can hope to achieve is the painless processing of animals, not cruel in the slightest. Cruelty in one respect incites cruelty in others.   

						
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ARGH! ARGH! ARGH! flop ARGH! I got up, thinking to go to class; got everything ready, headed out the door... Wouldn't you know, it was quarter to seven... I go at quarter to eight. Needless to say, when I realized my mistake, I burst out into tears. I can't get back to sleep, it's too late for sleep, so I'm here, writing, and crying, and dancing with tears in my eyes, and so on.  Early Morning Phonecall? Why does that sound familiar? Is it a song? Oh well... Where are my parents? They're gone for a week, sure, but they didn't call last night. They probably forgot. Oh well. I miss them.  

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ah, this is my new blog. But, instead of only journal entries, I'll be writing stories, and hoping for some feedback on them. Yes, a new blog for Russell. &nbsp; So, my depression has finally fled. I can function, once again. There's nothing I can't accomplish. I'll be dropping out of school, to go on to community college, and then, probably, some university. Those who think people can't succeed without highschool are sorely misinformed. In fact, college is over-rated, as well. College provides an individual with steady income, yes, but some of&nbsp;those&nbsp;vocations tend to&nbsp;end in&nbsp;glass ceilings. You can only earn so much in a profession provided by college. One can only achieve so much without being an entrepenieur. I'm going to laugh a lot when I throw my success back in the faces of those who thought I couldn't succeed. Bwahaha!  

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Actually, boring, and good. Amazing, eh? Boring, good, they don't tend to coincide. But, here, in this place and time, they do! It's as if I've been sucked into a temporal stasis field, then covered in temporal resin, made immortal, thrown back out into space, and shot by something painless, yet lethal, put back together, revived... Rinse and repeat.  Such is what little I have to tell you about what's going.  

						
</post>


</Blog>