<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Listening to NPR this morning, I couldn't help but think that many of the responses to the 9/11 commission report have missed the point.&nbsp; Richard Falkenrath, former Deputy Homeland Security Advisor, commented that much of what the commission recommended had already been done, and that the commission further failed to discuss the difficult decisions that needed to made.   Chief among these difficult decisions is whether or not to push the CAPS 2 airplane passenger data collection service, despite its unpopularity due to privacy concerns.&nbsp; Attention therefore needed to be paid to what fields are required for passenger information, and how best to collect it.&nbsp; This further emphasized the point made by deputy commission chair Lee Hamilton, who noted that what was&nbsp;needed&nbsp;"heightened standards of identification for those entering or exiting the country."   But will tighter standards really help anyone if governments and industries aren't prepared to support and implement them?&nbsp; This seems to be the underlying, and unspoken, question.&nbsp; Steven Flynn, of the Council for Foreign Relations, commented that both private industry and governmental bodies weren't prepared to spend the money on critical infrastructure improvements.   It should also be noted that no one is talking about what these infrastructures are.&nbsp; It's long seemed to me that airport security is one of the most crucial, and most ineptly managed, of those groups.&nbsp; When I say ineptly managed, I don't mean that the staff aren't diligent or that management aren't sincere in their desire to mess around with foreigners.&nbsp; I mean that the systematic erosion of working conditions and pay for those people checking bags and scanning passengers has left airports fundamentally underresourced.&nbsp; It's further clear that the staff at many American airports haven't been given the training necessary to adequately complete thier jobs.&nbsp; After all, closer scrutiny  STILL  didn't convince anyone at Dulles Airport that box-cutters on a commercial flight are a bad idea.   The professionalization of airport security would no doubt help to create the sort of workforces needed in international airports.&nbsp; Of course, this would mean providing real training and a real wage - something most businesses in America seem opposed to.&nbsp; It would also mean convincing industry and government that people matter more than profits, and we all know that is bad for business.&nbsp;&nbsp;Of course, I can't help noting&nbsp;that it is precisely the same groups that proclaim daily their commitment to beating terror.   So instead we'll look at racial profiling or, better yet, inspect people's last names, and determine from there whether or not they are with us or against us.&nbsp; But the reality is that we never could tell what evil lies in the hearts of men just by looking at them, and we never will.&nbsp; What is needed right now is more pragmatic risk assessment systems in airports (such as the "no boxcutters" principle), and better paid staff to implement them.&nbsp; Without paying attention to the way in which particular conservative workplace practices backfire at home, Richard Clarke's assessment - that America is less safe now than it was before 9/11 - maybe the only one to really hit the mark.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So this arrived in my inbox today and I couldn't resist putting it up here.&nbsp; It's things like this that remind why it is I like Americans, despite the decisions their illustrious leaders make.&nbsp;   urlLink http://www.personal.psu.edu/users/s/a/sas437/bagtag.gif   This is a clothing label from a small American company that sells their product in France. Here's the translation of the French part of the label.   Wash with warm water. Use mild soap. Dry flat. Do not use bleach. Do not dry in the dryer. Do not iron. We are sorry that Our President is an idiot. We did not vote for him.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I'm still not sure that I have anything terribly interesting to say, but after looking at other people's blogs I guess I'm feeling a little inadequate.&nbsp; Given that my days consist for the most part of reading for comprehensive exams, teaching technical writing and sitting in front of a computer, I shouldn't really be surprised.&nbsp; Still, if you want something interesting, you should probably spend your time at  urlLink www.howstuffworks.com , and not on this sorry site.   I figure I should probably let family and friends know that I have a blog, as it&nbsp;no doubt defeats the purpose to have one that no-one knows about.&nbsp; But then again, I'm spending my time getting ready to write books and articles that nobody will read either, so this might be good practice.&nbsp; At the very least this gets me writing for a half-hour a day.   Oh well, more tomorrow (and maybe more interesting then, too)...   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I finally decided to take a leap into the blog-o-sphere.&nbsp; Actually, I unwittingly signed up for this site while visiting  urlLink www.johnhowardlies.com , and decided that a blog might be a more profitable way to spend my mornings in the office than planning for class or doing research. &nbsp; I'm not sure who exactly is going to want to read the tawdry ramblings of an Australian living in America, or what those people actually expect to get from such reading, but I'll put them up here nonetheless.&nbsp; If you've got some response you feel you absolutely have to leave, feel free to respond... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>