<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I woke up this morning and heard the birds singing. Lots of them. Some that I've never heard before. I didn't hear any cars, trucks or motorcycles. It gave me the distinct impression that my house had somehow been teleported into the woods....or the country....some sort of open space.  Of course that didn't last long for I soon heard cars from the highway, dogs barking (that were not my own) and the neighbors yeslling at their kids. *sigh* Oh well. It was nice while it lasted. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK, so I had my interview. I was nervous before I got there....then I got more nervous when I saw this school. Mind you, it is one of 2 Jr. Highs in Merrillville. I pulled up.....looked ahead of me and saw one of the biggest schools I'd ever seen. I was later informed that over 1100 seventh and eigth grade students attend there. Wow! That's a lot of hormones running around! Then....to make my nervousness worse, when I walked in, there were not 1, not 2, not 3, but 4 people there to drill me. Great! They were very nice though. I really hope that I get the job. I will know early next week. *fingers crossed* They even asked me to sing for them! Cool!   Signing off.....  Current mood = nervous? excited? I'm not sure!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK....so today's the day. I really want this job. My interview is at 5 pm. I'm a little nervous, but I think I'll do well. Man, I hope I get it. It would help Chris and I out sooo much. Please think of my and pray for me today. I'll definitely be posting about how it went.  Signing off.  Current Mood......nervous....anxious 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I have a lot in my head right now.  So much that I can't put into words.  My house is a mess and I have lessons tomorrow. Guess it'll be a 6am wake up with lots of cleaning in 4 hours.   I don't ask for compliments, just interaction.....and really, I don't  ask  for that. Just have an internal craving.   I miss my friends in Grand Rapids. A lot. I miss hanging out in the Music Building. Just seeing friendly faces. I miss hanging out in the Student Union. Sitting by the fireplace with a coffee (made by one of the Whitman's). Ahhh....those were the days.  These are the days of lots of bills, house payments, feeding the dog, walking him too. Trying to get a job. Sometimes just crying myself to sleep because there is too much to think about.   Crying is a great outlet. It gets all my frustrations out without having to complain to anyone else about them. Thank heavens that God always listens. He's never giving me only part of His attention. Always all of it. God is awesome, is He not?  Why do good people get sick? Why does my uncle have cancer that will never heal? Why do some people that are bad live so long? I think somewhere in the Bible it mentions that people who live past 80 have led a righteous life (or something to that extent....I need to read my Bible more). I know people that have lived long healthy lives and are the most self absorbed people I've ever heard of. *sigh* All part of this living hell we call life.  Why don't men (most men) pick up after themselves? Why do they leave dishes lying around? How come when they miss the toilet (for whatever reason) they don't mop it up? They have had years to learn how to piss  inside  the toilet, but still seem to miss 10% of the time.  I was cleaning the church bathrooms today and the men's room always smells like pee....no matter how much Lysol, bleach and ammonia I use. The women's room smells nice. Maybe it's the potpourri....or maybe it's because we know how to get our urine in the toilet instead of on the floor. Well, that's my gripe of the day.   This sure has been a misture of thoughts.....just random things I'm thinking about.   I'm going to keep going....sorry.  Why do babies die? I don't understand that one at all. And how can anyone believe that God would send a baby to hell? I know several people that believe that a person is destined (at conception) to be saved by grace or not. If a person hasn't even had the chance to breathe on their own in the few days that it lives, why would they go to Hell? I for one don't believe that our God is like that. True, God is  not  a big teddy bear, He is a God who is angered by sin. But would He really send a child to hell?  It must make it much harder for a couple to cope with the death of a child when their pastor tells them that there is a chance that the baby went to Hell. Cold. Just cold.  I like movies. They let us escape from the reality of our world. It's nice to watch a ficticious character's life for a while and forget about our own. I especiall like movies when they have Edward Norton in them. *drool* I have a small (ok, small in comparison to the galaxy) crush. Hee hee.  That's all for now. More random thoughts of a Deedle Bug later. Take care and thanks for listening.  Current mood.....confused 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You know, writing in this thing is a whole lot more fun when people leave comments, isn't it? 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well folks, my floor joists are supporting 2.4 pounds less than they were last week at this time! Woo hoo for another 2.4 pounds lost this week. I gotta tell you, I feel great and I'm starting to look better too! I'm fitting into those size 14 jeans again (bye bye size 16 and 18).   I have a couple of motivational sayings relating to weight loss today:  "Never give up what you want most (to be thin) for what you want at the moment (that huge piece of chocolate cake, perhaps?)."  "Being thin feels better than  (insert name of fattening food that you're craving here)  tastes."  Remember, if I can do it, so can you! So get out there, exercise, eat right, and feel better! 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just wanted to let y'all know that I had a job lined up for this coming school year. I was taking a maternity leave position (full year) for an elementary music teacher in the Portage school system near my house. Unfortunately the teacher carried to term and delivered a still-born infant. The teacher now wants her job abck for this year (understandably). This leaves me displaced for this year.  Fortunately (for me), I have the school superintendant on my side and she has been calling around to the other area schools to try and place me in a permanant job setting. Today I was informed that I have an interview on thursday the 29th of July at 5 pm for a choir director position at Merrillville Schools (Jr. High). Hopefully this will lead to a full time position. Please pray for me with this interview.  I also need to finish a correspondance course and get my Indiana Teaching Certificate in one month. This is going to be a real stretch for me, but I think I can do it. Pray for me as I will be very stressed out trying to get all my papers and tests finished by this time.   I know that God is leading me into something wonderful here. Perhaps because there is a child in this school that needs my guidance. This sounds like a wonderful opportunity and I'm hoping and praying that I get the position.  Signing off.  Current mood: Hopful  Current Music: Third Day 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think people fill up too much of their time. In the Bible we read about the characters meditating, watching their sheep, creating music, creating psalms....and the list goes on. Why do we fill up our whole days??????   If we get bored, why do we turn on the Television? What is the harm in just sitting....Maybe meditating on God or something else? Why do we only pray before meals or when it's time to go to bed? Of course, not everyone is guilty of this. I find myself, quite often, just sitting and praying for, sometimes, hours at a time. Who else in the world would give you His undivided attention for that long and just let you talk, or even ramble about the days happenings? Who else in the world would listen and be sympathetic???   The question may be raised here...."Is God sympathetic?" My answer to this would be, yes, I believe so. Jesus walked this earth and struggled though&nbsp;everything that any other man struggled with. Just because he was perfect does not mean that he was not tempted, right? So God (Jesus) does know what we are going though. He sympathizes and empathizes with us. Wow.....a God who not only listens and hears our prayers, but also understands our struggles???? Mind numbing.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here are some reasons that I think humidity sucks:  5)&nbsp; Makes it hard to breathe (huff puff).  4)&nbsp; You don't want to drive with your windows down, because the air conditioning feels oh so good (ahhhhh).  3)&nbsp; You can't take the dog anywhere with you because if you leave him in the car, he'll suffocate (dead dog....awwwww).  2)&nbsp; You don't want to go outside to get yardwork done because you'll be drenched with sweat when you come back in and have to take yet another shower (eeew gross).  AND THE NUMBER ONE REASON THAT HUMIDITY SUCKS.......  1)&nbsp; You might end up with hair like this: &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  urlLink http://chnm.gmu.edu/lostmuseum/images/circ.gif   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok....Some of you already know that I recently joined Weight Watchers. Let me just tell you. I love it! So many people say....."All diets are the same". True. I'd agree with you there. And all diets are hard. However, Weight Watchers is not a diet! It's a lifestyle change. And you know what else? Changing your lifestyle is even harder than a diet, but it's long lasting, unlike most diets.   I have been on this diet for 4 weeks. I have lost 10 lbs. I know, you can loose more on the Atkins diet in a short period of time. But the question is, "Can you stay away from carbs for the rest of your life?" I would have to answer that with a no. Will it do your body any good to eat lots of fatty foods for years to come. I doubt it. Atkins is a good "quick fix" for those times when you want to lose a quick 6 lbs. I wouldn't recommend it for more than that though.   With Weight Watchers, you eat 5 servings of fruit and veggies per day, 6 eight ounce glasses of water, and 2-3 servings of milk. You also eat foods that are low in calories, low in fat and high in fiber.&nbsp; However, you may eat foods that are high in fat and calories, but they take up more of your allotted daily points. You can also earn points by exercising. Gee, sounds like being healthy, doesn't it?   I just wanted to say here that if you are one of us in the world who is overweight, don't be! You can do it! Group meetings are wonderful. You go once a week for under $10. You get weighted in and rewarded for lbs that you have lost. You get encouragement and tips from other Weight Watchers. The website is also a great place to go.  urlLink http://www.weightwatchers.com    If I can do it, so can you! I will be posting some low point foods, recipes and tips for weightwatchers on here in the future, so keep your eyes open!   Signing off.....   Current Mood: Enthused   Current Music: Mix of 80s music (oh yeah!)   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Eating.....something that we do every day. Here's my break down since monday of things I have eaten and their points values:  Monday: Points Target: 24 Flex Points Remaining: 35 Subway Turkey Breast w/ White American Cheese = 6 points Baked Lays Chips (1 1/8 oz) = 2 points Diet Coke = 0 points Pizza with low fat cheese and tomatoes (4 small slices) = 12 points Skim Milk (16 oz) = 4 points  Total points consumed = 24 (0 flex) Activity Points Earned = 2  Tuesday: Points Target = 24 Flex Points Remaining = 35 Skim Milk (16 oz) = 4 points Granola Bar = 2 points Stuffing w/ fresh veggies = 2 points Applebees Sizzling Chicken Skillet = 7 points Peanut Butter Power Bar = 3 points Tortillas stuffed with cheese and veggies = 5 points Light Microwave Popcorn(3 cups popped) = 1 point  Total Points Consumed = 24 (0 flex) Activity Points Earned = 1  Wednesday: Points Target = 24 Flex Points Remaining = 35 Chicken Pita at Redamak's = 3 points Sour Cream (1 Tablespoon) = 1 point Chips = 4 points Swiss Cheese = 2 points Pudding (zero fat) = 2 points Diet Soda = 0 points Sugar Free Candies (2 pieces) = 0 points Peanut Buster Parfait from DQ = 17 points  Total Points Consumed = 29 Activity Points Earned = 2 Flex Points Used = 3  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      OK, so I don't post the most intelligent things on here, but I'm using it as more of an outlet. Things that are bothering me....Maybe things that are interesting to me. That's what I'm posting here.   I was at the store yesterday and in front of me were a mother and her 2 children (I'd say one was about 5 months and the other was about 3 years). First of all, the three year old was on a leash. (It's NOT a dog!!!!!) It always bothers me to see kids on a leash. Maybe it's a good idea, I don't know. But personally, I think that if you can't take care of your kids and you can't make them mind you and stay nearby where you can always see them, what business do you have being a mother?!?!? Secondly, the dog-child wanted a candy-bar. Mom said no and the child whined. "But mommy, I need it." So what does the mother do? She turns around, get the candy-bar and pays for it. All because her child whined once. Sheesh!!!!! I pray to God that there are at least SOME decent mothers left in the world. If I ever would have run away from my mom in the store, she would have smacked my butt so hard that I didn't' know what hit me!   Let me address the issue of time-outs. Now. For some kids, time-outs work wonders. For me, for instance. I never ever wanted to disappoint mom and dad. When I was told, "God sit in that chair and think about what you have done for 10 minutes.", I did. I thought about it. I cried. I wept. I told my parents I was sorry. Sometimes, I did things that just required a spanking though. Haha.   Now, for some kids, time-outs just don't work. Let's take my husband for example. Nothing worked on him. I remember tell of a story from his childhood. He was sitting in the living room watching TV and his mom told him to turn the TV off, that he'd had enough TV for one day (yea for parents that don't sit their kids in front of the TV all day). He said he wouldn't turn it off. So My husband's mom, Debbie, comes in and says, "Chris, it's time to turn the TV off." And she reaches down and turns the TV off for him. She leaves the room, Chris turns it on again. Debbie comes back, turns it off and gives Chris a spanking. Debbie leaves, Chris turns on the TV again. This went on (with a spanking each time) over 30 times!!!! Chris was fighting back tears from the spankings and Debbie was fighting back tears for not knowing what to do about her non-compliant son. Nothing ever worked for Chris(God help me when I have children).   One more mother that I want to rant and rave about before I sign off here. My neighbor has 2 children. One is 7 and the other is 13. The 13 year old girl is constantly whining about her brother. And when I say whining, I mean whining. They live across the street and I can hear them from inside my house. Pathetic. The 7 year old is always talking down to his mother. I was standing in the yard talking to her one day and her son came up to her and started yelling at her for not ever taking him any where (the park, Boy's and Girl's Club, etc). She just says, "Shut up. I do take you places." At this point I said to the child, "Why don't you ask your mom nice? Maybe she'll take you places if you don't yell at her." I would have never corrected someone else's kid, but I know my neighbors very well, and they didn't mind.   Now, I know that there are wonderful parents out there still,&nbsp;but I leave you with this question.....What is wrong with parents today? Are they lazy? Do they have better things to do than raise kids? Do they give up too easy? What is the problem????   Signing off.   Current mood: Tired, but excited to start the day.   Current Music: Rachmaninoff   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Did you ever wonder if things in your life could pile up so high that you can't take care of them? I've been wondering that lately. It just seems like there is not enough time in the day to take care of everything that needs taken care of.     &nbsp;  The grass needs cut (it's a jungle out there), the bills need payed (ugh), the house needs cleaned (yuck!), need to call the bank (no money there anyway), need to sleep (that's an important one), the dog needs walked (I could use the exercise myself), and the list goes on.   &nbsp; However, God promises to take care of His children....and I'm one of those rowdy little kids, right? Right.  &nbsp; Oh well, I guess it will all get done eventually. Signing off. &nbsp; Current mood: Depressed &nbsp; Current music: Jars of Clay &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow my good friend from Michigan, Kristy, is coming to visit me. She was in Chicago this weekend and drove seperate from her friends so that she could stop by on her way home! Yippee! It's been so long since I got to hang out with her. She was at my wedding, but I didn't get to spend much time with her. Can't wait to see her!  I have to be at church early again tomorrow. I thought I was supposed to get at least one sunday per month off of the music schedule. Not so much. Ah, well. No biggie. I enjoy playing, singing, doing whatever they have me doing. The problem is, I'm supposed to be in the nursery tomorrow night as well as at the piano for worship. Hmm....if only I could split myself in half. That would be nice. My mom said she'll switch schedules with me for the nursery though. Thanks mom!!!  I just got done using a whole Mr. Clean Eraser on my kitchen floor. Wow! I've used them before, but never thought about doing my whole floor with it! My floor is old in the kitchen (and getting redone soon!) so it is very badly stained but it looks 100% better now. Woo hoo!!!!  Well, I'm tired, so I guess I'll head to bed.  Current mood...kinda spacey......just out there, man. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm participating in a Walk-a-thon on September 18th. It's for a local shelter/clinic. They offer:   Free Pregnancy tests  Free Ultrasounds to women considering abortion  Free Post-abortion Bible Study and Counseling  Free Abstinence Education  Free Pregnancy Counseling (24/7)  Free Medical Services to Pregnant Women  Free Parenting Classes   Thing is, I need sponsers. You can pledge as much or as little as you like and it's tax-deductible. Payment is due when you recieve a bill. This way, you know it's not a scam. The bill comes from The Women's Center of NW Indiana in Merrillville, IN.   Please consider this. I'm trying to raise $500. If the total of all walkers reaches $30,000, the shelter will be able to purchase their own Ultrasound Machine and will not have the hospital expense. This would be a great blessing and the machine saves tons of unprotected lives. Once 99% of women have an ultrasound, hear the heartbeat and see their unborn child, they decide to have the baby and either keep it or give it up for adoption.  If you're interested in sponsering me, either reply to my post or shoot me an email at  urlLink Gual8199@yahoo.com . I'll let you know what info I need from you.   Thanks! 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so we've got PPP (prayer pet peeve) #1 covered. On to #2.  It bugs me when people use the many holy names of God as filler (instead of saying ummm...or errr....they say God, Father, Lord....etc). Here is what I mean:  Oh Father, please help us, Jesus, to know you God, better Lord.  For crying out loud! Are you trying to get His attention (you've already got it, duh!) or can you just not think of anything else to say? Maybe you're just trying to be more holy by calling God the many names that he has??? I dunno!!!  Does this bother anyone else?  Signing off.....  Current mood......extremely tired. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I'm headed to the Buckeye State. That's right, folks. Ohio here I come!!! I'm going to visit Kimra (as I had said in an earlier post). We're going to have fun without men! Woo hoo! (And don't you go thinking those dirty thoughts, either. Not that kind of fun. Haha.  Well, I'll be gone for a couple days, but when I return, I'm sure I'll have lots to say.  Signing off.....  CUrrent Mood......Excited to see an old friend! 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nobody likes me Everybody hates me Guess I'll eat some worms..........  How come Pfitz is the only one who signed my guesbook???? Don't the rest of you like me? Or maybe Pfitz is the only one who reads my posts....aha! lol  For real though...sign the thing!  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I teach piano lessons. It is a job.  It is not just "something that I do on the side". It's a freakin source of income, for cryin out loud!!!!  You see, I have a student (name with-held). She comes once a week for an hour lesson in between two other students. Last week, her parents failed to bring her. I called, left a message on their answering machine, and alas, no reply.  I saw them earlier this week and they said nothing to me. They did talk to my husband, but not to me. Hmm.....strange.  Today, she was to have another lesson. Guess what? Her parents failed to bring her again. Still no phone call. I called their house 15 minutes after our lesson was to start and left a message. Still no reply as of yet. What is goiong on, I ask????  Another problem with this family is that they are constantly bringing their daughter to lessons late (usually anywhere from 10-30 minutes late (yes, that's half of her lesson and yes, they are required to pay for the whole hour). Why would you do that???? It just doesn't make any sense. And when I ask if they need a different time slot for lessons they make up some lame excuse about traffic being bad or a Dr. appointment that ran late. I'm so tired of it. *sigh*  And it's a shame, too. Because their daughter is very sweet and talented.  Oh one more thing....I had bought 2 new books for this student and was expecting pay for them last week. Still no pay....because they don't show UP!!!!!! I'm now out $30 for the lessons they have missed and $10 for the books. Yeah.....they will be paying me. One way or another. I don't want to sound harsh, but c'mon people! At least give the curtousy of a phone call to let me know that you won't be here. My introductory letter stats that "if sufficient notice is not given for cancelling a lesson, the weekly fee will still be issued".  Well, I guess I'll go do something useful.  Signing off.....  Current mood = motivated 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have several pet peeves when it comes to prayer. The first is this:  Someone is praying and informs God of things that are going on. Example:  "Dear Jesus, Mr. Jones is in the hospital with a fractured knee cap after getting in a very bad car accident. He's in a lot of pain. I know how much pain he must be in, so would you help him feel better, please?"  Like God doesn't know all of that already???? I know that prayer can be simply "talking" to God, but it just annoys me that some people have to pray as if they are informing God of what's going on down here on Earth.  More prayer pet peeves to come later on.......  Signing off.....  Current mood = ticked off. You may ask why....well,  see my next entry...... 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's official. I'm now a Junior High Choir Teacher. I'm also officially crazy now. lol. Thought y'all would like to know!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I go back for a second interview today. The vice principal called yesterday and wants me to come in and meet the principal. They want to "see if I'm the right candidate for their school". Hopefully all goes well.  Current mood....tired. I just got up *yawn* 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have been asked by some (and know that most of the rest of you are wondering) "what is a Deedle Bug?".  Let me tell you a nice little story. I grew up on a little dead end road in a quaint little town in Indiana. Down the street from me were my Aunt, Uncle and Cousin. I was an only child and so was my cousin, so we were like brother and sister. But that's beside the point. :)  My whole family always called me Dee Dee (my real name is Deanna, for those of you that don't know me). So, my Uncle gave me a nickname. That nickname was none other than "Deedle Bug".  So now you know that a Deedle Bug is really a nice person named Deanna who grew up down the street from her aunt and uncle. *big grin*  Signing off......  Current Mood......silly. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so the phone rings this morning. I answer it (hello?). Beth, the vice principal from the school I had an interview at) is on the other end. (my heart pounding) She says, I wanted to call and tell you (did I get it, did I get it????) that you are one of our top canidates for the job. (sheesh!) She called me to tell me that?????????? She said whe was going to make some calls to references and then let me know tonight or tomorrow if I got the job. Grrrr....just makes me worry more.  On a happier note, I lost more weight. almost 15 lbs. now that I've lost. I'm so excited. Did I mention that I don't have to shop in the plus sizes anymore??? Cool, huh?  Signing off.....  Current mood.....tired 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I'm having more random thoughts this morning. Here they are:  I hope I get this job. I should know today or tomorrow. *yikes*  Sharp rocks located at the beach suck. My foot is cut up bad. :(  I love sleeping under an air conditioner (window unit). It makes sounds go away and keeps me cool. Ahhhh.  I don't want to weigh in this morning at Weight Watchers. The last thing I need is bad news....although, good news could make my day better....hmmm......  I have a lot of reading to do. Would anyone really notice if I read a couple chapters and then wrote my papers? After all, the papers are only 2-3 pages per book. I mean, sheesh, that's not a lot of space!  I'm going to the Buckeye State to visit my roommate from college on friday. I can't wait. We're going wedding dress shopping (for her, not me). I've already gone through that hell. I definitely don't want to do it again. Oh, and her blog is located at:  urlLink http://www.opendiary.com/entrylist.asp?authorcode=D269709  It's mostly about her and her fiance and how much she misses him, but it's a great story. You see, her fiance is in Iraq fighting for the US right now. I hope he comes home soon.  My house is a bloody mess.....that's bloody in the British use of the term...not as in, blood and guts splattered all over my house. That would be gross and I wouldn't be sitting here on my computer writing to tell you about it. I'd be cleaning it up.  I really want to go back to Hawaii. It was so beautiful. So peaceful (well, Maui was....honolulu was another story). I can't wait to go back sometime.  I also want to go to Alaska. I've been wanting to take an Alaska cruise for a while now. I think that may be the first big vacation that my husband and I take. You can check out alaska cruises and travel at:  urlLink http://www.alaskatravel.com   Well, I guess I should get to drying my wet hair and go to weight watchers. I'll let y'all know how it goes...and if I hear anything from my job.  Signing off....  Current Mood.....crazy 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Following suit here....please sign my guestbook!!!! It's over there --------->>> under my friends' blogs. 
     

    
</post>



</Blog>