<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today was the best!!! I beat the living shit out of Michelle Yorker! And to my suprise when I was on top of her as soon as I saw blood I hesitated...Wow it was crazy! But I know if I had half the adrenilen I usually have I wouldnt have stopped..Eh oh well she still got fucked up!I'm happy!    &nbsp;  But anyways...I going to Cali for two weeks on saterday..I kinda dont want to go I dont want to miss anything down here!But It'll still be fun!    &nbsp;  Hanging my a thread...A&W    &nbsp;  P.S. the new taking back sunday (where you want to be)is the shit!  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       God I'm so hypacritical...I'm always telling other girls not to fall for guys cuz they are just going to loose thier trust and get used...And what do I do I go for A.   &nbsp;   I told him at the very start that I wasnt gonna go off and trust him right away cuz I new what he did to past G.F.'s&nbsp; and he promised he wouldnt. And after a while I didnt think he was everything was dandy...But then ppl where saying me and A fucked and I found out it was comming from one of his best friends I wonder who told him that...When I asked him about it he just denied ever saying anything...So...Then when I started asking about shit I heard we stared fighting and whatever else...And today I came to the conclusion that he was just using me the whole time..    &nbsp;  And now I bet everyone thinks I'm a loser cuz all my friends said this was going to happen and I dissed all of them and still went with trusting A..I feel so dumb...The worst part is I'm auctully gonna miss him and its gonna be hard to get over him..But I called my dad today and I'm gonna go visit him and if I like it I'm moving...    &nbsp;  Hanging by a thread...A&amp;W  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         FUCKING A I'M SO PISSED....I'M ON THE PHONE WITH T AND SHE JUST ENLIGHTEND ME THAT PPL ARE SAYING THAT A'S SAYING SHIT ABOUT ME...BUT SHE WONT TELL ME WHAT HES SAYING...BUT I KNOW THAT HE DOESNT REALLY LIKE ME AND HES PROBABLY USING ME...AND I WISH I COULD SAY FUCK HIM AND I DONT CARE BUT I DO....ITS FUNNY HOW I ALWAYS GET FUCKED OVER!I'M SERIOUSLY GONNA TALK TO MY DAD TODAY AND SEEING IF I CAN GO SEE HIM AND GET AWAY FROM ALL THIS SHIT!!! I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE WHETHER TO GET OVER HIM CUZ&nbsp; HE APARENTLY NEVER EVEN LIKED ME....I FUCKING HATE LIFE! HEH....SO MUCH FOR MY HAPPY ENDING!!!!           &nbsp;     FALLING TO HER PLUMITING DEATH....A&amp;W      
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well there is not much to write about today since I no longer have a life cuz&nbsp; C left me!!!But soon she will be back and all will be good, we can go back to the normal!To bad A hasnt called me or I would probably be going on in a entertaing rant...But he is out do god knows who or god knows what...       &nbsp;   I dont even know why I'm putting up with him cuz I let him do whatever with out gettin jelious since we are together but we are not going out...But If I even talk to a guy he flips out and says I dont care for him.Well uh hes a weird one but arent we all!I'm kinda pissed cuz he says he 'd never "cheat" on me but I think he has something going with A.P. cuz at practice one day she was saying something about him...But its kinda funny you would think he would be a little bit smarter than that and relize that we play soccer together.But I really have no room to talk about anything cuz I'm the one that doesnt have balls enought to comfront him about it or anything else...       &nbsp;   Oh well I still like him a lot reasons why are unknown...       &nbsp;   Hanging&nbsp; by a thread...A&amp;W   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         My moms a smart lady...I believe she knows I'm like the average teenager&nbsp;and have my good and bad times...And Ibelieve she isnt naive about stuff.    &nbsp;     K a long time ago my love interest thing came over while I was sleeping to say good bye before I went of vacation...Well when I woke up I talked to him for a couple minutes and of course I had to help myself to a make out session lol..But I&nbsp;told him to leave right after...           &nbsp;     Well then my mom comes home and&nbsp;I told her that A came over but I was sleeping and she was fine with it...Up untill she noticed a cartin of cigarettes where missing. Then she accused A of doing it because of his past (he had been in Hawthorne once before).Even though he didnt do it..A doesnt have a car so he got a ride over he invited who ever was with him in to sit in the living room while we talked and I believe one of them took it..Either that or my mom missplaced them and found them after she blamed it on A and just didnt bother to tell&nbsp; me cuz&nbsp;to&nbsp;her it would be killing to birds with one stone. Me replacing her cigs and me not being able to she A again.           &nbsp;     So she go's on in a rant A gets parinoid that my mom was gonna say something to his P.O. and runs away..He then get arrested&nbsp; for being out past kerfiew and running away and something else I dont remember. So he ends up going to Hawthorne again...So for a while my moms plan had worked he was mad at me cuz he thought I told my mom he did it...           &nbsp;     But then he comes back and we got everything straitend out..and go back to being together. Then my mom finds out hes back and says I'm never going to see him and so I thought ya ok whatever..Just reciently she decides that shes planning to get a restraining order put on us so we really cant see each other!!!        &nbsp;        Shes such a bitch! Maybe instead of judging him she sould talk to him for once and she'd relize he didnt take them and that hes not that bad...But no she had to be a judgemental bitch and just automatically say no more A!!!!           &nbsp;     Well what she doesnt know is that if she does get the restraining order I'm going to move in with my dad in Cali...So I'm just counting down the days...Shes already aware that I hate her with a passion and if it wasnt for A I wouldnt be&nbsp; here..           &nbsp;     Its funny cuz she blames my having Bipolar Disorder on her...When really it isnt if she had the slightest traces of a brain she would know why!!!!!!           &nbsp;     FUCK HER!!!Its sad cuz I lot of kids wish bad things on thier parents and dont really mean it but I do...And when I say I hate&nbsp; her I truely mean it..WONDER WHY as if I cant screw up my so called life enough she has to take away the only things I really care about...!      
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         K I    really really hate Avril Lavigne     but I've come to really like this song.But It's one cuz it reminds me of my so called love interest...         &nbsp;   Let's talk this over It's not like we're dead Was it something I did? Was it something You said? Don't leave me hanging In a city so dead Held up so high On such a breakable thread You were all the things I thought I knew And I thought we could be CHORUS: You were everything, everything that I wanted We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it All of the memories, so close to me, just fade away All this time you were pretending So much for my happy ending You've got your dumb friends I know what they say They tell you I'm difficult But so are they But they don't know me Do they even know you? All the things you hide from me All the shit that you do You were all the things I thought I knew And I thought we could be [CHORUS] It's nice to know that you were there Thanks for acting like you cared And making me feel like I was the only one It's nice to know we had it all Thanks for watching as I fall And letting me know we were done He was everything, everything that I wanted We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it All of the memories, so close to me, just fade away All this time you were pretending So much for my happy ending You were everything, everything that I wanted We were meant to be, supposed to be, but we lost it All of the memories, so close to me, just fade away All this time you were pretending So much for my happy ending &nbsp;&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Grrr....As if life cant get any worse but no our so called &nbsp;     GOD    had to place these faggots I call males            &nbsp;          on the earth especially A!!!! Yeah today was good up untill he called!!! So we start talking and              &nbsp;      everythings fine but then he starts accusing me of likeing and fucking other guys which is funny cuz              &nbsp;        I'M A MORALISTIC VIRGIN  ! What the fuck should he care about me doing anything with&nbsp;       &nbsp;      anyone else! We arent even going out, oh yeah wait we are but only when it convinient for him! Well&nbsp;             &nbsp;      guess what he can go   FUCK HIMSELF  ! I should just really move to Cali to get over his  LOSER                    &nbsp;   &nbsp; ASS       !!!So          he calles&nbsp;me back cuz he grew a brain and relized I was mad hes like I'm going to C.K.'s                  and I'll call&nbsp;you when I get there and I'm sry baby..Uh well   DONT CALL ME BABY YOU         &nbsp;&nbsp;        FAG!!! GO&nbsp;FIND ONE OF YOUR OTHER WHORES LIKE FUCKING AIDS                   &nbsp;       INFESTED KIM  !!!! &nbsp;     &nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;       Well now that I'm done venting....  I HATE GUYS!!!!           
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         *Incurable*        The day was cold but so was my heart        I knew someday it would all fall apart        I was the most outgoing who would have guessed        But when it comes to hiding things I'm the best        I had tons of friends and a lot of great stuff        But I&nbsp;don't know what's going on and I've had enough        I cant wait to go home the reasons unknown        Just to sit in my room in the dark to be &nbsp;alone        Today was a waste along with the rest of them        Maybe its just me I must be condemned        I wish I would have fixed this in the past        The time is passing&nbsp; and its going by fast        The pain is&nbsp;eating away at me&nbsp;how long is&nbsp;this&nbsp;going to last        Mom and dad found me cold and barely there        that's how I've always been they just didn't care        The doctor announced I overdosed and that I was slipping        I now could feel the medicine it was unbearable and my heart was skipping        Then it&nbsp; was done it happened so fast        The doctor then said I'm sorry but she's past           &nbsp;        &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, I can tell you one thing I'm dissapointed they dont have pink for an option (fave color) so I have to use red.Anyways I dont really know what to say but I can tell you I will so be ranting on about back-stabbing friends, my crazy mom, and shitty stuff in general later on.But I'm just starting to get a hang of this things so boring posts untill then.. Enjoi   &nbsp;   Hanging by a thread...A&amp;W  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah so..I'm auctally getting kinda home sick so I'm looking forward to Sunday (when I go home)!Anyways yeah I cant wait to get home and chill with all my buddies...Most of all I cant wait to hang with H and C its gonna be a awesome time!   But yeah hmm I havent talked to A in the last couple days but eh ya know him well lol well no you dont know him but I do hes always out drinking and all that so ya know..How it is..But yeah hes gettin a cell phone I cant wait lol then I'll have a bell around his neck jk lol but at leaste I'll be able to talk to  him more so I'm excited!!!Anyways about K I'm so confused between the both of them...Cuz A is finally starting to trust me and talk to me and I dont want to be fucked up and just say oh I dont like u n e more cuz he already thinks that I'm gonna go off and screw K but then K is such a sweetie and I know he would never be an assfuck like A and I know he would be awesome so I dunno what to do?LoL I hate shit like this..  Anywho I just got contacts and ordered my glasses so I'm excited to get them both!!! I really cant wait to get my glasses cuz they look almost exactly like my old nerd glasses I got from hot topic that I lost and was really depressed about..So these will be nerd glasses #2 and they will auctally be perscribed lol...So I'll officially be a nerd!!  Well imma gonna go  Hanging by a thread....A&W
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hmm so yeah I've been upto a lot since the last blogg..But yeah I'm in Cali I've been here for like a week and a half..But yeah I went to a Dodgers game and just been hanging out its fun!!!But yeah I cant wait to go home on sun!!!      Anyways about A...Well I just reciently found out he tried to get with my friends C and A but I cant really get mad or blame him..Cuz thats our agreement since we arent together and cuz I did it to him..But  yeah we had a really good talk and we settled a lot of stuff..        But yeah I'm currently confused on who like cuz I like A but I like K too and they both have good qualitlies  ...But I guess I'll just depend..But yeah I'm kinda tired so I'm out..   Hanging by a thread..A&amp;W  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>