<Blog>


<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      POST #1! *Not much happened.&nbsp; A Rod hit two homers against Detroit, the Mets beat the Phillies in 11 innings, and Shawn Green hit a game winning grand slam in the top of the 8th to beat the D-Backs 4-3. *Giants vs. Rockies:&nbsp; Jerome Williams had a rocky (no pun intended) first inning when he gave up two runs, but then settled down&nbsp;and the Giants got the lead 3-2 until a JT Snow error to make it 4-3 Rockies.&nbsp; However, Shawn Chacon got rocked in the ninth, the Giants scored 4, and won 7-5 despite Scott Eyre having to bail out Matt Herges *Now, I'm off to the A's-White Sox game.&nbsp; Fireworks night is always fun! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Minnesota Twins 4, Kansas City Royals 1   WP: Santana (8-6) LP: Gobble (5-7) SV: Nathan (24)  Highlights:: Santana-- 8.0IP 1H 0ER 4BB 9SO   ------------------------  St. Louis Cardinals 5, Cincinatti Reds 7   WP: Jones (8-2)LP: Tavarez (2-3)SV: Graves (34)  Highlights:: Pujols blasts homerun (24) off Todd Jones  --------------------------  Philedaphia Philles 8, New York Mets 2   WP: Wolf (4-5)LP: Glavine (7-8)  Highlights:: Jim Thome hit 30th Homerun of the Season   ------------------------  San Diego Padres 7, Houston Astros 4   WP: Wells (5-5)LP: Oswalt (8-8)SV: Hoffman (24)  Highlights:: Jeff Bagwell hit first homerun in 29 games!   ------------------------  Chicago White Sox 5, Oakland Athletics 2   WP: Garcia (7-8)LP: Redman (6-7)  Highlights:: Garcia--6.2IP 2H 1 ER 2BB 6 SO&nbsp;   ------------------------  Milwaukee Brewers 0, Chicago Cubs 5   WP: Maddux (8-7)LP: Sheets (9-6)   Highlights:: Greg Maddux 3 wins away from 300!   ------------------------  Baltimore Orioles 3, Tampa Bay Devil Rays 2   WP: Lopez (7-6)LP: Brazelton (2-3)SV: Julio (14)  Highlights:: Huff hit 15th Homerun of the season!   ------------------------  New York Yankees 5, Detroit Tigers 3   WP: Hernandez (2-0)LP: Knotts (5-4)SV: Rivera (33)  Highlights:: Sheffield--3/5 3 RBI 1R 1BB   ------------------------  Flordia Marlins 2, Pittsburgh Pirates 4   WP: Torres (5-3)LP: Benitez (2-1)SV: Mesa (24)  Highlights:: Benitez-- 3rd Blown Save of Season   ------------------------  Montreal Expos 2, Atlanta Braves 6   WP: Ortiz (11-6)LP: Bentz (0-3)SV: Smoltz (17)  Highlights:: Drew hits homerun 22 of the season!   ------------------------   Toronto Blue Jays 0, Texas Rangers 4   WP: Rodriguez (3-0) LP: Lilly (7-7)  Highlights:: Teixeira-- 1/3 3 RBI 1HR;&nbsp;  ------------------------  San Francisco Giants 4, Colorado Rockies 0   WP: Schmidt (12-2) LP: Cook (4-4)  Highlights:: Schmidt-- 12 Straight Wins   ------------------------  Los Angeles Dodgers 7, Arizona Diamondbacks 6    WP: Mota (7-3)LP: Bruney (2-3)SV: Gagne (25)   Highlights:: Ventura hits game winning homerun!  ------------------------  Cleveland Indians 6, Seattle Mariners 5   WP: Sabathia (6-4) LP: Franklin (3-8) SV: Riske (5)  Highlights:: Jacobsen hit his&nbsp;1st Career Homerun  ------------------------  Boston Red Sox 3, Anaheim Angels 8    WP: Colon (7-8)LP: Wakefield (5-6)  Highlights:: Guerrero blasts&nbsp;homerun in 3rd inning  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Cubs Superfan will be the Cubs writer 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am a new writer and will be the Cardinals beat writer   yes bill will be the cardinals beat writer  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        With one of the best starts in St.louis Cardinals history people wondered if they could keep it up thru the second half. Along with Scott Rolen and his 82 RBI's, The Cardinals pitchign led by Chris Carpenter and Jason Marquis have avoidign Losses and Injuries. Many people will continue to rank the Cardinals behind the Cubs and even the astros. But in the end matt morris of the Cardinals said that "the fact that they are underdogs drives&nbsp;us toward winning and proving everyone wrong".     &nbsp;   So after one half of the season passed by the Cardinals hoped that the all-star break did not cool them off. As people can see it did not the Cardinals won the first two games of th second comign back in both, thanks to Jim Edmonds and Marlon Anderson.     &nbsp;   On saturday the Cardinals luck ran out. After Jason Marquis gave up 4 runs in 6 innings the Cardinals then got 3 in the seventh and 1 in the eighth. it was&nbsp;4-4 goign to the bottom of the 8th and int he bottom half Adam&nbsp;Dunn smacked a 3 run homer off of Steve&nbsp;Kline.&nbsp;They could only get one run in the 9th and loss 7-5 . In the end the Cardinals still are in first by 7 games and are 9-2 in there last 11.&nbsp;        
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       American League Midseason MVP Hank Blalock:   Maybe not the most obvious choice, but Blalock has lead the charge with Soriano to take a team projected to end in dead last to first pace in the tough AL west. After losing two future hall of famers i n Alex Rodriguez and Rafael Palmeiro, Blalock has led this young team with his .303 average and 23 homers.   National League Midseason MVP Barry Bonds:   It's nearly impossible to consider anyone else, Bonds is by far more important to his Giants then anyone is to any team. Bonds along with Schmidt carrying the Giants with  maybe another batting title, and he  set the single season record for intentional walks only half way through. He is hands down the best player in baseball, and arguably the best hitter in baseball history.   American League Midseason CY Young Mark Mulder:   He doesn't have the best stuff or fastest fastball, but Mulder has been consistently the best SP in baseball. His team is 13-1 in his last 14 starts, with Zito slacking Mulder as kept his injury full team in the race. Mulder has been more dependable then any other AL sp this season with his 12-2 record and 3.21 ERA.   National League Midseason CY Young Jason Schmidt:    Might seem like i'm favoring the Giants players, but Bonds and Schmidt are clearly the best two platyers in baseball. Schmidt 12-2 with a 2.38 ERA is just amazing. Bonds might be the only run support he has, and to see a 12-2 record is very impressive.     
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Abe will be the Yankees writer, and Steve will write occasional MLB analysis, and Aaron will post the MLB update, Lou will do the Mets and Bill will do the Cardinals    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Orlando Hernandez keeps winning thanks to a three run blast by Gary Sheffield. While Brown and Mussina are on the disabled list Hernandez comes through with another win. Detroit who tied last years win total Friday lost due to a three run homer by Sheffield in the fifth. A-Rod with a good game as well going three for five with one RBI. The Yankee relief almost automatic with the two all-stars Tom Gordon and Mariano Rivera who closed it out with his 33rd save. Even though a good start with the two run shot from Eric Munson in the second they couldn't hold on. Starter Gary Knotts dropped to 1-3 in his last five starts bringing his ERA to 5.15.         
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink click here for more  .&nbsp; Once again, Redman loses by giving up the long ball.&nbsp; All&nbsp;4 of the 5&nbsp;runs by the White Sox were scored on homers by Paul Konerko, Carlos Lee, and Aaron Rowand.&nbsp;&nbsp; Freddy Garcia(7-8) gets the win, giving up 2 runs (1 unearned on the error by Jose Valentine) in 7.2 innings with 2 hits and 6 Ks.&nbsp; Redman (6-7)&nbsp;gets the loss&nbsp;after giving up 5 runs on 6 hits and three walks in 7 innings, &nbsp;&nbsp;striking out three.    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Unhittable, as usual, Schmidt 8 shutout innings, striking out 8 and giving up&nbsp;2 walks and 4 hits.&nbsp; Giants went ahead 1-0 in the top of the fourth, when Michael Tucker hit a line drive double to score Ray Durham.&nbsp;&nbsp; That was all they needed, but the Giants expanded their lead when JT Snow doubled in Tucker in the 6th, making it two nothing.&nbsp; The Giants also struck in the eighth, when Barry Bonds hit a double to drive in Tucker and Snow.&nbsp; Bonds went 1 for 2 with a double, 2 (intentional walks), and 2 RBIs.&nbsp;&nbsp; Schmidt gets&nbsp;his 12th consecutive&nbsp;win (12-2),&nbsp; Aaron Cook gets the loss (4-4).  No doubt about it, Jason Schmidt is the best pitcher in baseball.&nbsp;&nbsp; He pitched a shutout at Coors Field.&nbsp; That&nbsp;is unheard of.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gostros! will be the astros writer   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *I decided&nbsp;not to go to the A's game yesterday.&nbsp; I was too tired so I went to bed early.&nbsp;&nbsp; The A's won 5-1, and nothing much happened, so I didn't miss anything. So I went today instead.&nbsp; Just got back, they lost 5-2, but the highlight was before the game when they had a 1974 team reunion.&nbsp; It was&nbsp;much better than when they had the 1989 last month when only two (TWO!) players showed up (Dave Henderson and Carney Lansford).&nbsp; Most of the other players showed up. As I write this, the Giants lead 1-0 in the middle of the fifth.&nbsp; Jason Schmidt's pitching for the Giants,&nbsp; Aaron Cook for Colorado, bonds is 0-1 with a walk  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       YESTERDAY'S MLB REVIEW:  There were quite a few blowouts, a couple shutouts, nothing interesting happened.&nbsp; Mike Maroth one hit the Yankees, that's pretty impressive though.&nbsp; The Giants lost 7-1 and only scored 1 run in eight innings off of Shawn Estes.&nbsp; How the hell do you only score one against Estes?&nbsp; We've scored 1 runs in 13 innings the entire year against one of the biggest headcases in baseball.&nbsp;&nbsp; Bonds went 1 for 4 with no walks, Kirk "Woody" Rueter&nbsp;got the loss, giving up 5 runs in 6 innings.    &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What I am planning to do is have someone do a log of every team, I will continue to do the Giants and MLB, and will do the A's as well until we find an A's fan to do this.We are looking for other members, so please comment on this board or PM me on AIM, my screenname is JDK93085I already have one person doing this, Zachary, and he will be doing the Angels.  I am looking for:  1 person for each team to write a frequent review and analysis of how and what the team's doing.  A few people to write an occasional analysis on the world of baseball.      
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Getting his first start since the end of the all-star break, Greg Maddux pitched brilliantly receiving a six hit complete game shutout. Sammy Sosa Teed off in the first inning off Brewers best pitcher,Ben Sheets,&nbsp;today sinking him from the beginning. Also going yard for the cubs was Moises Alou and Corey Patterson  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Cubs Superfan will be the writer for the Cubs   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Minnesota Twins 3, Kansas City Royals 4    WP: Reyes (3-4)LP: Balfour (3-1)&nbsp;     __________________________ St. Louis Cardinals 10, Cincinatti Reds 4    WP: Suppan (9-5)LP: Acevedo (4-8)&nbsp; __________________________     Philedaphia Phillies 1, New York Mets 6    WP: Leiter (6-3)LP: Myers&nbsp; (5-7)SV: Looper (19)&nbsp; &nbsp;__________________________    San Diego Padres 3, Houston Astros 5    WP: Clemens&nbsp; (11-3)LP: Lawrence (10-7)SV: Lidge (8)     __________________________ Chicago White Sox 3, Oakland Athletics 5    WP: Mulder (13-2)LP: Loaiza (8-5)SV: Dotel (19)     __________________________ &nbsp;  Milwaukee Brewers 4, Chicago Cubs 2    WP: Capuano (4-5)LP: Beltran (2-2)SV: Kolb (28)     __________________________ Baltimore Orioles 2, Tampa Bay Devil Rays 7    WP: Hendrickson (7-7)LP: Borkowski (1-1)     __________________________ New York Yankees 2, Detroit Tigers 4    WP: Robertson (9-4)LP: Lieber (7-6)SV: Urbina (15)     __________________________ Flordia Marlins 2, Pittsburgh Pirates 4    WP: Torres (6-3)LP: Koch (1-3)SV: Mesa (25)     __________________________ Montreal Expos 5, Atlanta Braves 16    WP: Thomson (7-7)LP: Downs (1-4)     __________________________ Toronto Blue Jays 5, Texas Rangers 7    &nbsp;WP: Brocail (1-1)LP: Chulk (0-1)Sv: Cordero (28)     __________________________ San Francisco Giants 9, Colorado Rockies 10    WP: Harikkala (4-1)LP: Herges (4-4)     __________________________ &nbsp;  Los Angeles Dodgers 10, Arizona Diamondbacks 3     WP: Lima (9-3)LP: Dessens (1-6)     __________________________ Cleveland Indians 5, Seattle Mariners 7    WP: Hasegawa (3-3)LP: Miller&nbsp;&nbsp; (2-1)SV: Guardado (17)     __________________________ &nbsp;  Boston Red Sox 6, Anaheim Angels 2    WP: Schilling (12-4)LP: Lackey (7-9)&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       What's there to say?&nbsp;&nbsp; Giants were up 5-1, Rockies tied it 5-5 in the fifth.&nbsp; Giants went up 6-5, Rockies tied it 6-6 in the seventh.&nbsp; Giants score 1 in the 8th,&nbsp; 2 in the 9th, and then Matt Herges gives up 4 runs in the bottom of the ninths to blow the game.&nbsp; Tim Hirikkala gets the win (4-1), Herges the loss, homers by Todd Helton (18), Jeremy Burnitz (19), Preston Wilson (3), Durham (8), Cruz (2), Tucker (8), and Bonds (24).   A tough pill to swallow for sure.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Cardinals knock off Reds With 5 run inning      The Cardinals were coming into Sunday wanting to win the 4 games series with the Reds. With a win and a Cubs loss the Cardinals would get there 8 game lead over the second place Cubs back.     &nbsp;   The Cardinals won 10-4 in convincing fashion. Down 2-1 heading into the 3rd inning, Reds pitcher Jose Acevedo didn't know what was coming. Edgar Renteria led the inning off with a solo homer and after that Acevedo unraveled. The Cardinals ended up knocking Acevedo out of the game after 2-2/3 innings with scoring 5 runs in the 3rd to take a commanding 6-2 lead that they would not surrender. After the 3rd the Cards were a bit quiet until the Reggie (reggae) Sanders led the 5th off with a solo shot of his own off the Batters eye club 430 Ft away from home plate in dead CF. Then in the top of the 6th Renteria walked, Pujols beat out a single and the Cards RBI machine Scott Rolen drove them both in. In the end the Reds only got two more runs in thanks to Jim Edmonds who once again threw someone out at the plate. Simply the Best.&nbsp;    W--Jeff Suppan&nbsp;(9-5)    L-- Jose Acevedo (4-8)    Now 57-34 the Cards are 23 games over .500 and 8 games up in the Central and now go to the North Side of Chicago to face the Cubs in a 2 game series    NL Central .GB    1-  Cardinals  --    2-Cubs 8.0    3-  Reds  9.5    4- Brewers 10.5    5-  Astros  12    6-   Pirates   14     
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       White Sox recieve:   OF Carl Everett (39 G, 127 AB, 8 R, 32 H, 10 2B, 2 HR, 8 BB, 19 K, .252 BA, .319 OBP, .378 SLG)  Cash     Expos recieve:   RHP Jon Rauch-AAA (6-3, 3.11 ERA, 14 G, 72.1 IP, 57 H, 27 R, 25 ER, 25 BB, 61 K)  RHP Gary Majewski-AAA (3-3, 3.19 ERA, 35 G, 14 S, 42.1 IP, 30 H, 16 R, 15 ER, 16 BB, 41 K)    The White Sox make a trade during the season for Carl Everett for the 2nd year in a row. With Frank Thomas out for at least 8 weeks (potentially the season) and Magglio Ordonez not 100% yet, the deal was made. If Carl can hit like he did in 2003 and stay healthy for the rest of the season it will be a great pickup for the White Sox. Rauch was a top prospect in 2001 but since then his stock has fallen, especially with White Sox management. He should get a chance with the Expos and could develop into a quality starter. Gary Majewski is a decent relief prospect and will probably see time in the Majors with the Expos this season.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       While Giambi and Posada took the day off the yankees couldn't score enough runs, besides the two run shot in the 4th by Ruben Sierra they didn't give Lieber what he needed. The real story today is Nate Robertson winning his 9th game brining his ERA down to 3.98. Robertson may be the future ace the Tigers have so desperately needed showing very good signs for the future of the Tigers. Robertson going eight innings striking out three all on Gary Sheffield who was hitless in todays game. Robertson did have a great start, but the most impressive thing is the depth the Tigers lineup is showing with Pudge hitless the bottom three hitters in the lineup all getting rbi's. Most of the damage was done just leaving it to Ugueth Urbina to close it out getting his 15th save of the season.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Montreal Expos have traded outfielder Carl Everett and Cash Consideration to the White Sox for minor league starting pitcher Jon Rauch and reliever Gary Majewski. This is Everett's second stint with the White Sox. The Expos signed Everett last December to a two-year, $7.5 million contract, plus an option year. Everett can opt out of the contract after this season. The club option is worth $5 million, but the Expos could have bought him out for $500,000.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       American League  East: Team&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Record&nbsp;&nbsp; Games Back New York Yankees&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 57-33&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;----- Boston Red Sox&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 49-40&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;7.5 Tampa Bay D'Rays&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 43-47&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 14.0 Baltimore Orioles&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 39-49&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 17.0 Toronto Blue Jays&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;39-51&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 18.0 &nbsp; Central: Chicago White Sox&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 47-40&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ----- Minnesota Twins&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 48-42&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 0.5 Cleveland Indians&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 44-46&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 4.5 Detroit Tigers&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 44-47&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 5.0 Kansas City Royals&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 33-55&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;14.5 &nbsp; West: Texas Rangers&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;51-37&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ----- Oakland Athletics&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;49-40&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 2.5 Anaheim Angels&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 49-41&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 3.0 Seattle Mariners&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 33-56&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 18.5 &nbsp; &nbsp;  National League &nbsp; &nbsp; East: Philadephia Phillies&nbsp;&nbsp; 48-42&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ----- Atlanta Braves&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 47-43&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 1.0 Florida&nbsp;Marlins&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 45-45&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 3.0 New York Mets&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 45-45&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 3.0 Montreal Expos&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 32-58&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;16.0 &nbsp; Central: St. Louis Cardinals&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 56-34&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ------ Chicago Cubs&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 49-41&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 7.0 Cincinnati Reds&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 48-43&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 8.5 Milwaukee Brewers&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 46-43&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 9.5 Houston Astros&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 44-46&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;12.0 Pittsburgh Pirates&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 41-47&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 14.0 &nbsp; West: Los Angeles Dodgers&nbsp;&nbsp; 51-38&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ----- San Francisco Giants&nbsp; 51-41&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 1.5 San Diego Padres&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 49-41&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 2.5 Colorado Rockies&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 37-53&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;14.5 Arizona D'Backs&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 31-61&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 21.5 &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       National League Leaders (top 2)::&nbsp;  Hitting::  Hits:&nbsp;  Jack Wilson PIT&nbsp;(120)&nbsp;  Mark Loretta SD&nbsp;(116)  &nbsp;  Doubles:  Lyle Overbay MIL&nbsp;(37)&nbsp;  Derek Lee CHC&nbsp;(30) 
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       American League Leaders (top 2)::  &nbsp;
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The New York Mets came into todays game just 2 games behind the Phillies. With Tom Glavine starting today you would think the Mets would cut the lead to 1 but no it was A different story. After pitching a scoreless 1-2-3 inning in the 1st. Glavine came out to pitch the 2nd. Thome led of with a double. Then 2 batters later Tomas Perez comes up with A 2 out single. Thome scores. Then they intentionally walk Doug Glanville and then Wolf hits a grounder to 3rd but and error by Wigginton allows the inning to continue. Jimmy Rollins comes up and hits a 2 out 2 run doubles to give the Phillies a 3-0 lead.&nbsp; Then in the top of the 3rd with one out Thome hits a single. Burrell then flys out to right. 2 outs Lieberthal up he hits a deep fly ball to left you would think end of inning but no Mike Cameron couldnt make the catch and Jim Thome comes around to score to extend the lead to 4-0. We got to the bottom of the 4th when the Mets will finally get on the board. Hidalgo walks and with 2 outs Wigginton hits a single. Cameron comes up and hits A 2 out RBI Single to score Hidalgo. Mets cut the lead to 4-1. We got to the bottom of the 6th when the Mets could of put themselves right back into the game. With the bases loaded 1 out Catcher Jason Phillips comes up and Wolf throws 2 balls then Bowa goes to Cormier. Cormier got the count to 3-1 the next pitch Phillips grounded into a inning ending double play. Mets couldnt put a run across the board.&nbsp; Bottom of the 8th 4-1 score Mike Piazza leads off to hit A solo bomb cuts the lead to 2. But thats all they would get for the day. But the scoring aint done for the Phillies in the Top of the 9th 2 on 1 out Jim Thome hits his major league leading 30th homerun of the season to give the Phillies a 7-2 lead. 2 Outs Lieberthal walks and Perez doubles. Doug Glanville&nbsp;up hits&nbsp;a sharpe grounder to Kaz but he couldnt come up with it. Charged with and error Lieberthal&nbsp;scores. Phillies goes on to win 8-2. They now have a 3 Game lead on the New York Mets. Mets ruin another chance to cut the lead.    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If you are anyone else is willing to help post updates, analysis, or something else, please IM me @ jdk93085 (aim) 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Bonds sat out the game because he had a root canal earlier that day, but the Giants scored 6 runs and won anyways.&nbsp; This was probably because it was against the Diamondbacks and Steve Sparks.&nbsp; The Giants struck for four runs in the second, and 1 in the 6th and 7th.&nbsp; The Diamondbacks scored their only run on a Luis Gonzalez homer.&nbsp; BRet Tomko (5-5, 4.71) gets the win, Steve Sparks (3-6, 5.94) gets the loss.    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Two minor deals went down today:     Mets recieve:   RHP Mike DeJean (0-5, 0 SV, 6.13 ERA, 37 G, 39.2 IP, 49 H, 29 R, 27 ER, 28 BB, 36 K)     Orioles recieve:   OF Karim Garcia (62 G, 192 AB, 24 R, 45 H, 7 2B, 2 3B, 7 HR, 22 RBI, 10 BB, 35 K, 3 SB, .234 BA, .272 OBP, .401 SLG)    Both teams exchange players who have been disapointments this season. DeJean has been one of the worst relievers in the Majors this season, not helping the cause on the awful Oriole pitching staff. Karim Garcia has had a bad season and was useless after the Mets traded for RF Richard Hidalgo. DeJean should not be used in any close game for the Mets, who would be better suited calling somebody up from the minors. Garcia may see some time at DH with Jay Gibbons and David Segui out.           Padres get:   SS Rich Aurilia (73 G, 261 AB, 27 R, 63 H, 13 2B, 4 HR, 28 RBI, 22 BB, 43 K, 1 SB, .241 BA, .304 OBP, .337 SLG)     Mariners get:   Cash or a PTBNL    And to think, the Mariners gave away All-Star SS Carlos Guillen to sign Aurilia this offseason. Wow. The Mariners had to trade or release him after designating Aurilia for assignment on July 10th so they gave him to San Diego where he will back up rookie Khalil Greene and Mark Loretta.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Photo courtesy of mlb.com      Tuesday, July 20, 2004: In front of 34,154 fans at Minute Maid Park, Dodger Blue overpowers the Astros.  After six innings of work for Dodgers starting pitcher Jeff Weaver, he leaves the game with a chance at acquiring his tenth loss. Weaver's teammates believed otherwise, and would change the outcome in their next at-bats.  The seventh-inning rally begins with a Grabowski double, followed by Dave Roberts getting hit by a pitch. After an error by Houston, All-Star Paul LoDuca comes out with a timely single to knock in the two on base. With LoDuca on, the surprise of the season, Adrian Beltre, comes up big with his 25th homerun to leftfield to take the come-from-behind lead of 5-4 off of the Astros' embarrassed&nbsp;reliever David Weathers. His blown save was the cause, and the boos from the Houston crowd were evidently&nbsp;the dramatic effect.  You'd think the rally would stop there, but Shawn Green walks on six pitches after Milton Bradley reaches first base on a surprise bunt single. Alex Cora then feeds off of his teammates and drops in a single to load the bases before Olmedo Saenz ends the inning on a pop-up to Jeff Bagwell.  In relief of Guillermo Mota, the dominating presence of Dodgers closer Eric Gagne made&nbsp;its way to the mound in the 8th inning after the Blue offense brings home two more, followed by another Astro run, earned by Mota.  Three of the four outs made by Gagne were recorded as strike outs, and he takes with him his 27th save of the season.     Dodgers (54-38) remain in first place of the National League West, two and a half games ahead of the Giants (53-42).  
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The writers list and what they're covering: Abe: Yankees Aaron: MLB Brad: Indians Cubs Superfan: Cubs JoseGrapinino: A's Erisa: Dodgers Lou: Mets The Baseball Man: Giants musicman: Braves Vasanthi: Orioles GoStros!: Astros Steve: MLB Bill: Cardinals Zachary: Angels
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Travis Hafner is seeing the ball well these days. The DH for the Indians crushed 3 of the 6 Home Runs the Indians hit at Angels Field in Anaheim Tuesday Afternoon. Hafner now has 17 homers and 75 RBIs on the season. His 11 RBIs over two games tied the Indians' franchise record set by Earl Averill in a doubleheader against the Washington Senators on Sept. 17, 1930. It also was the second time in a week that an Indian has hit three home runs in a game -- Victor Martinez did it against Seattle on Friday. Jake Westbrook got the win pitching 7 1/3 innings limiting the Angels offense.The Indians are only 4 games back of Minnesota in the American League Central Division and play a critical 2 game&nbsp; series against the Chicago Whitesox at the Jake beginning Wednesday Night.     .
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      JoseGrapinino will be the A's writer, Erisa will be the Dodgers writer, and Brad will be the Indians writer.     
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Jerome Williams faced off against Randy Johnson for the third time this year,&nbsp;and once again it was Williams who looked like&nbsp;the 5 time Cy Young Winner and future hall of famer.&nbsp;&nbsp; Williams (9-6, 4.41) pitched 7 innings, gave up just four hits and one run, which was an&nbsp;unearned one in the eighth.&nbsp; All the Giants runs were scored in the first two innings off of JOhnson (10-8, 2.83)&nbsp;.    But the big scare came in the ninth.&nbsp; Matt Herges, two days removed&nbsp;from his Coors field blow up, &nbsp; came in to try to close the ninth.&nbsp; Once again, he failed his job.&nbsp;&nbsp; He gave up a double to Alex Cintron,&nbsp;and a single the Chad Tracy, moving Cintron to third.&nbsp; Tracy was then bunted over to second by Juan Brito, and Quinton McCracken, pinch hitting for pitcher&nbsp;Greg Aquino, drew a walk to load the bases.&nbsp; Jason Christiansen came to the rescue, and forced Roberto Alomar to ground into a game ending double play.    It was Christiansen's first save in four seasons with the Giants.    Tommorrow, Rich Aurilia returns to the city he played in for nine seasons, this time playing for division rival San Diego Padres      . 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      musicman and vasanthi will do the Braves and Orioles respectively   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The orioles offense has finally shown signs of waking up and producing like most people thought they would be able to, even though it was just 2 games against the royals.&nbsp; Yesterday, Sidney Ponson pitched a shaky game, allowing far too many base runners and pitches in the middle of the plate, yet he managed to pull out the victory and end his 9 game losing streak.&nbsp; This game brings hope of a better 2nd half for Ponson, who was one of the biggest disappointments in the first half, as far as free agent signings are concerned.   This afternoon, the orioles jumped all over Royals starter Zack Grenike, tagging him for 8 runs, including 4 home runs.&nbsp; He was unable to record an out in the 3rd inning. This game was a major turn around from the last time he faced the Orioles, when he was able to change speeds much more effectively and pitched deep into the game.&nbsp; The newly acquired Karim Garcia (from the Mets for Mike DeJean) contributed with 2 home runs and 5 RBI.&nbsp; Daniel Cabrera, labored through 5 innings, but only allowed 2 earned runs.   The Orioles head to Boston where they will play 3 games in two days.&nbsp; The pitching matchup for tomorrow features Erik Bedard vs Pedro Martinez.&nbsp; For Thursday's double header, Rodrigo Lopez will pitch one of the games, and either Dave Borkowski will pitch the other game on short rest, or a minor leaguer will be called up.          
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Minnesota Twins 3, Detroit Tigers 1     W-Terry Mulholland (2-3) L-Jason Johnson (7-8) S-Joe Nathan (25)  HR: None  Highlights: PH single from Offerman puts Twins ahead       New York Yankees 7, Tampa Bay Devil Rays 9     W-Lance Carter (3-2) L-Tanyon Sturtze (3-2) S-Danys Baez (19)  HR: Ruben Sierra (NYY) 11  Highlights:  Alex Graman (1/3 IP, 5 H, 5 R, 5 ER, 0 BB, 0 K)       Chicago White Sox 12, Texas Rangers 6     W-Scott Schoeneweis (6-7) L-Joaquin Benoit (3-5)  HR: Carl Everett (CHW) 1; Carlos Lee (CHW) 13; Gary Matthews Jr. (TEX) 6; Mark Teixeira (TEX) 22; Hank Blalock (TEX) 24  Highlights: Teixeira homers in 5th straight game       Baltimore Orioles 7, Kansas City Royals 4     W-Sidney Ponson (4-12) L-Brian Anderson (1-9)  HR: Miguel Tejada (BAL) 16; Ken Harvey (KC) 11; John Buck (KC) 1  Highlights: Ponson ends personal 9 game losing streak       Cleveland Indians 8, Anaheim Angels 5     W-David Riske (5-2) L-Troy Percival (2-2) S-Matt Miller (1)  HR: Casey Blake (CLE) 16; Travis Hafner (CLE) 13, 14  Highlights: Travis Hafner (4 AB, 2 R, 3 H, 2 HR, 5 RBI, 2 BB)       Toronto Blue Jays 5, Oakland Athletics 3     W-Josh Towers (4-3) L-Kirk Saarloos (1-1) S-Jason Frasor (10)  HR: Carlos Delgado (TOR) 11; Vernon Wells (TOR) 10; Erubiel Durazo (OAK) 12  Highlights: Josh Towers (7 1/3 IP, 7 H, 2 R, 2 ER, 0 BB, 5 K)       Boston Red Sox 4, Seattle Mariners 8       W-Mike Myers (4-1) L-Curtis Leskanic (1-5)  HR: Jason Varitek (BOS) 11; Edgar Martinez (SEA) 7; Bret Boone (SEA) 12; Miguel Olivo (SEA) 8  Highlights: Bret Boone hits walkoff grand slam in 11th         Montreal Expos 6, Pittsburgh Pirates 2       W-Joe Horgan (3-0) L-John Grabow (0-4)  HR: Craig Wilson (PIT) 18  Highlights: Termel Sledge (4 AB, 2 R, 1 H, 2 RBI, 1 BB)       Milwaukee Brewers 4, Cincinnati Reds 8     W-Aaron Harang (6-2) L-Ben Hendrickson (0-2)  HR: Geoff Jenkins (MIL) 14, Jason LaRue (CIN) 10, Wily Mo Pena (CIN) 13  Highlights: Wily Mo Pena (4 AB, 1 R, 3 H, 2B, HR, 3 RBI, 1 K)       Florida Marlins 6, New York Mets 5     W-Josias Manzanillo (2-2)  L-Braden Looper (2-2) S-Armando Benitez (31)  HR: Shane Spencer (NYM) 4  Highlights: PH Lenny Harris drives in go-ahead run in 9th for Marlins       Philadelphia Philles 2, Atlanta Braves 4     W-Mike Hampton (5-8) L-Paul Abbott (0-4) S-John Smoltz (18)  HR: Jim Thome (PHI) 31  Highlights: Braves pull back into 1st place in NL East       St. Louis Cardinals 5, Chicago Cubs 4     W-Chris Carpenter (10-4) L-Carlos Zambrano (9-5) S-Jason Isringhausen (23)  HR: Jim Edmonds (STL) 22; Edgar Renteria (STL) 8;  Scott Rolen (STL) 20; Moises Alou (CHC) 21  Highlights: Scott Rolen delivers with 8th inning 2-run homer       Los Angeles Dodgers 7, Houston Astros 6     W-Giovanni Carrara (2-0) L-Dan Miceli (3-5) S-Eric Gagne (26)  HR: Shawn Green (LA) 12; Adrian Beltre (LA) 24; Milton Bradley (LA) 10; Morgan Ensberg (HOU) 4  Highlights: Red hot Dodgers push Houston back further       San Diego Padres 13, Colorado Rockies 6     W-Ismael Valdez (9-5) L-Denny Stark (0-5)  HR: Terrence Long (SD) 4; Larry Walker (COL) 5; Jeromy Burnitz (COL) 20, 21  Highlights: Denny Stark (3 IP, 10 H, 8 R, 8 ER, 2 BB, 2 K)       San Francisco Giants 6, Arizona Diamondbacks 1     W-Brett Tomko (5-5) L-Steve Sparks (3-6)  HR: Luis Gonzalez (ARI) 16  Highlights: Brett Tomko (7 1/3 IP, 9 H, 1 R, 1 ER, 2 BB, 2 K)      
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        At 10:30 on June&nbsp;19th no one except&nbsp;Cardinal country thought that the Cardinals could be up 9 games in the NL Central.&nbsp;A win&nbsp;would have the Cards 9&nbsp;games up tonight. And yes a win was in the Cards As they hit 4 homers to seal a 5-4 victory over the Cubs. In the first Edmonds got hit by Zambrano, then next time up Edmonds first pitch, put it over Waveland Ave. On the way to the dugout Zambrano yelled " Why dont run like scott rolen around the bases", After that in the bottom of the 4th Sosa stood about two feet away from the plate during his at bat and then after grounding out, carpenter said " You can step into the batters box next time, i am not going to hit you, i dont play like that". So then tempers calmed. In the top of the fifth Edgar Renteria hit a solo job&nbsp;and made it 3-0. Then with a collection of hits the Cubs tied the game at 3-3. The fued between Edmonds and Zambrano continued and in the 8th Carlos got his wish about Rolen running the bases as Rolen hit a 2 run homer to&nbsp;give the Cards&nbsp;a 5-3 lead. Next up was Edmonds ,who got plunked&nbsp;after that it was &nbsp;so long for carlos as he was ejected. The game finished at a score of 5-4 and now the Cardinals- Cubs will play there last game against each-other for the Reg. season tomorrow.       Carpenter Earned his 10th win tonight and 4th this year against the cubs          &nbsp;   W- Chris Carpenter ( 10-4) 
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After the first 3 innings, Pedro Martienez looked to be having another very solid outing.&nbsp; He struck out 6 of the 10 batters he faced and appeared to have cooled down the Orioles' bats.&nbsp; However, in the 4th inning, David Newhan and Melvin Mora reached base, and Miguel Tejada drove them both in with an RBI triple.&nbsp; The Orioles scored 1 more in the inning to take a 3 run lead, only to have the Red Sox come right back and tie in the bottom half of the inning with a 3 run home run by Gabe Kapler.&nbsp; Then, in the 6th inning, the Orioles took the lead for good.&nbsp; Brian Roberts, Newhan and Mora all singled and were driven in by an RBI single by Tejada and a sacrifice fly by Javy Lopez.&nbsp; Tejada finished with 5 RBI.&nbsp; Newhan continuted his hot hitting with 4 hits, including an inside the park home run.&nbsp; Erik Bedard pitched 6 innings for the win. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      1. St. Louis  2. NY Yankees&nbsp;  3. Los Angeles  4. Texas  5. San Francisco  6. Boston  7. Oakland  8. San Diego&nbsp;  9. Chicago Cubs  10. Anaheim  11. Minnesota  12. Chicago Sox  13. Cincinnati  14. Milwaukee  15. Houston  16. Pittsburgh  17. Philadelphia  18. Atlanta  19. Tampa Bay  20. Baltimore  21. Cleveland  22. Florida  23. Toronto  24. NY Mets  25. Detroit  26. Colorado  27. Seattle  28. Kansas City  29. Montreal  30. Arizona   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Baltimore Orioles 12, Kansas City Royals 3     W-Daniel Cabrera (8-3) L-Zack Greinke (2-7)  HR: Karim Garcia (BAL) 1, 2; Robert Machado (BAL) 1; Miguel Tejada (BAL) 17; Larry Bigbie (BAL) 9  Highlights: Garcia's 2 homers power O's to victory       New York Yankees 4, Tampa Bay Devil Rays 2     W-Jose Contreras (8-3) L-Victor Zambrano (9-6) S-Mariano Rivera (34)  HR: Gary Sheffield (NYY) 18  Highlights: Sheffield 6th inning homer puts Yanks on top       Toronto Blue Jays 0, Oakland Athletics 1 (14 innings)     W-Justin Lehr (1-1) L-Justin Speier (2-6)  HR: None  Highlights: David Bush takes no-hitter thru 8th       Cleveland Indians 14, Anaheim Angels 5     W-Jake Westbrook (7-5) L-Jarrod Washburn (10-5)  HR: John McDonald (CLE) 1; Travis Hafner (CLE) 15, 16, 17; Victor Martinez (CLE) 17; Coco Crisp (CLE) 6; Jeff DaVanon (ANA) 5  Highlights: Hafner 3-homer game just days after Victor Martinez's       Boston Red Sox 9, Seattle Mariners 7     W-Derek Lowe (8-9) L-Joel Pineiro (5-11) S-Keith Foulke (15)  HR: Manny Ramirez (BOS) 27; David Ortiz (BOS) 26  Highlights: Back-to-back homers from Manny and Ortiz put Sox ahead       Minnesota Twins 5, Detroit Tigers 4 (10 innings)     W-Grant Balfour (4-1) L-Ugueth Urbina (3-4) S-Joe Nathan (26)  HR: Jacque Jones (MIN) 15; Justin Morneau (MIN) 4; Craig Monroe (DET) 4  Highlights: Lew Ford's hustle puts Twins ahead in extra frames       Chicago White Sox 4, Texas Rangers 6     W-Carlos Almanzar (7-1) L-Damaso Marte (3-3) S-Francisco Cordero (29)  HR: Jose Valentin (CHW) 20; Paul Konerko (CHW) 24; Carlos Lee (CHW) 14; Gary Matthews Jr. (TEX) 7  Highlights: Barajas double puts Rangers ahead in 8th       Milwaukee Brewers 2, Cincinnati Reds 6     W-Brandon Claussen (1-0) L-Doug Davis (9-8)  HR: Bill Hall (MIL) 6; Jason Romano (CIN) 1  Highlights: Claussen (7 IP, 5 H, 2 R, 2 ER, 2 BB, 4 K)       St. Louis Cardinals 11, Chicago Cubs 8     W-Ray King (3-0) L-LaTroy Hawkins (2-2) S-Jason Isringhausen (24)  HR: Reggie Sanders (STL) 16; Albert Pujols (STL) 25, 26, 27; So Taguchi (STL) 2; Derrek Lee (CHC) 15; Aramis Ramirez (CHC) 16; Michael Barrett (CHC) 11  Highlights: Pujols (5 AB, 4 R, 5 H, 2B, 3 HR, 5 RBI)       Montreal Expos 1, Pittsburgh Pirates 2     W-Sean Burnett (4-2) L-Livan Hernandez (6-10) S-Jose Mesa (26)  HR: Rob Mackowiak (PIT) 14  Highlights: Burnett (7 IP, 8 H, 1 R, 1 ER, 3 BB, 1 K, W)       Florida Marlins 9, New York Mets 7     W-Ben Howard (1-1) L-John Franco (2-6) S-Armando Benitez (32)  HR: Alex Gonzalez (FLA) 13; Miguel Cabrera (FLA) 21; Mike Cameron (NYM) 16; Richard Hidalgo (NYM) 13  Highlights: Piazza leaves game with sprained wrist       Philadelphia Phillies 4, Atlanta Braves 3 (1o innings)     W-Tim Worrell (3-3) L-Antonio Alfonseca (5-4) S-Billy Wagner (15)  HR: Andruw Jones (ATL) 16; Marcus Giles (ATL) 5  Highlights: Philly rallies late to tie then win the game       Los Angeles Dodgers 7, Houston Astros 5     W-Jeff Weaver (7-9) L-Dave Weathers (6-5) S-Eric Gagne (27)  HR: Adrian Beltre (LA) 25; Jeff Bagwell (HOU) 13; Morgan Ensberg (HOU) 4  Highlights: Beltre (4 AB, 1 R, 3 H, HR, 3 RBI, BB)       San Diego Padres 9, Colorado Rockies 7     W-Adam Eaton (5-8) L-Jason Jennings (8-8) S-Trevor Hoffman (25)  HR: Ryan Klesko (SD) 4; Khalil Greene (SD) 5; Jeromy Burnitz (COL) 22  Highlights: Klesko and Greene lead offensive attack with 5 RBIs       San Francisco Giants 3, Arizona Diamondbacks 1     W-Jerome Williams (9-6) L-Randy Johnson (10-8) S-Jason Christiansen (1)  HR: None  Highlights: Big Unit loses despite good outing  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Braves lost a heartbreaker to the Phillies in 10 innings.&nbsp; The Braves were up 3-1 going into the 8th, but a costly error by Furcal allowed the tying run to reach base.&nbsp; Then in the 10th, an error by Eddie Perez and a base hit by Jim Thome sealed the Braves fate.      Final score:&nbsp; 4-3    My daily rant:&nbsp; When will Bobby Cox realize that Chris Reitsma is not major league material.&nbsp; When Reitsma came in the game in the 8th, my first thought was "Well there goes the game."&nbsp; He's allowed seven runs (five earned) in his past four appearances, and has now blown leads in three games that Jaret Wright should have earned a victory.&nbsp; Both of Philadelphia's victories in its past five games against Atlanta have come in extra-inning games, where Reitsma has struggled in the eighth inning. It's&nbsp;appears Reitsma doesn't really bare down and pitch decently until he's blown the Braves' lead or made the opponents' lead greater.&nbsp;     
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Despite Crosby's efforts the A's drop their 2nd game in as many days to division rival Seattle. The good news is that Texas and Anaheim have taken a game each from their 2 game stint, and now the A's get to host the Rangers in Oakland for three games with Texas coming off a loss to Anaheim at home.  Redman got the start, and despite a rough begining and end, he managed to stay out of harms way most of the game. In the first inning he allowed Ichiro a lead off single followed by a Winn single placing runners on first and second. There would be a calm before the storm though, when Redman got Boone to pop up for an infield fly rule, but lightening would strike when a passed ball would get behind Catcher Adam Melhuse, advancing the runners to 2nd and 3rd. Thunder would clash on a Edgar Martinez single to left scoring both Ichiro and Winn. Unfortunately, for Martinez the storm didn't descriminate as Eric Byrnes got the ball into McLemore at 2nd in time to rain on his parade. The damage had been done though as the Mariners took a 2-0 lead after the 1st.  Seattle would go down 1-2-3 in the 2nd, but wouldn't go down quite as easily in the third, loading the bases with&nbsp;a two out rally before Ibanez would ground out to McLemore.  Offensively, the A's didn't start out very well either.&nbsp;&nbsp;In the first&nbsp;lead off man, Kotsay popped up to Boone at 2nd, followed by a McLemore walk, but don't get excited he was stranded after two strike outs.   In the 2nd inning the A's&nbsp;managed to&nbsp;load the bases, Crosby and Durazo both singled, and Kielty would reach on an error.&nbsp;The next 2 batters&nbsp;proceded to record 3 consecutive outs before they were able to bring in any runs. Byrnes would go down looking, and Melhuse would ground into a inning ending double play.  In the third, fourth, and fifth innings only&nbsp;4 men would reach base. Chavez would be stranded in the 3rd after a single. In the&nbsp;fourth inning Crosby&nbsp;hit a single followed by a HBP for Byrnes despite raising their OBP both would be stranded as would McLemore who singled in the fifth.   The A's came alive a little in the 6th, well at least Bobby Crosby did blasting a two run homer to left scoring himself and Scott Hatteberg whom led the inning off with a single. Out of the following four batters only Kielty would reach base on a walk.  Franklin would come out after 6 innings of work, but Seattle reliever Sherrill would hold the A's to just a walk in the seventh. Then in the 8th he'd record two outs before issuing a walk to Kielty, and then Sherrill was replaced by Hasegawa who would strike out Byrnes, the first and only batter he would see.  In the bottom of the 8th, Boone would hit a homer out to centerfield, scoring himself and Winn who previously reached on an error. The next two batters would fly out to end the inning.  Going into the 9th as the visiting team the A's would face a tough spot against closer Eddie Guardado. Seattle would make a few defensive adjustments, bringing in Jolbert Cabrera to play third switching Spiezio to first. Damien Miller would pinch hit for Melhuse, reaching base on a single to centerfield. That'd be the end of the line though as Guardado would get the next three to fly out and pop out for final three outs.  Redman would take the loss, going 8 innings with 4 earned runs on 7 hits and 4 base on balls.  Hasegawa would be credited with the win, and Guardado would pick up his 18th save on the year.   Final Score:  Seattle 4, Oakland 2 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Anaheim Angels:   Designated IF Shane Halter for assignment; recalled RHP Matt Hensley from AAA-Salt Lake.     Baltimore Orioles:   Purchased the contract of RHP Todd Williams from AAA-Ottawa; optioned OF Tim Raines Jr. to Ottawa.     Boston Red Sox:   Optioned RHP Joe Nelson to AAA-Pawtucket; recalled 3B Kevin Youkilis and LHP Mark Malaska from Pawtucket; acquired IF Ricky Gutierrez from the Cubs for a PTBNL or cash; place IF Pokey Reese on the 15-day DL with a strained rib cage muscle.     Chicago Cubs:   Recalled RHP Jon Leicester from AAA-Ottawa; optioned RHP Francis Beltran to Ottawa.     Cleveland Indians:   Recalled OF Grady Sizemore from AAA-Buffalo; designated OF Mark Little for assignment.     Detroit Tigers:   Placed OF Craig Monroe on the 15-day DL with a strained left hamsting; recalled OF Nook Logan from AAA-Toledo.     Kansas City Royals:   Recalled RHP Shawn Camp from AAA-Omaha.     New York Mets:   Optioned RHP Dan Wheeler to AAA-Norfolk; recalled 3B David Wright from Norfolk.     San Diego Padres:   Optioned OF Brian Buchana to AAA-Portland; activated 1B Phil Nevin from the 15-day DL.     Seattle Mariners:   Designated OF Hiram Bocachica for assignment; recalled LHP Bobby Madritsch from AAA-Tacoma.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
              Photo courtesy of mlb.com      &nbsp;   Wednesday, July 21, 2004: Back to Dodger Stadium we go. In hopes of continuing their eight-game winning streak, the Dodgers return home to entertain their Los Angeles crowd. The table seemed to be set perfectly tonight: The 11-game winner Kaz Ishii takes the mound, homefield advantage is on their shoulders, and the team feeling as though everything has been going their way lately.  
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Rangers have come to Oak Town and they're hog tieing the A's. In game&nbsp; one&nbsp;of the&nbsp;three game stint, the Rangers took the first game of the series&nbsp;8-3. The Rangers victory handcuffs the A's dropping them to 4 1/2 games back.  Things stayed fairly even early on, both teams scoring&nbsp;two in the 3rd. Texas got two men in on an Eric Young double. Oakland answered right back in the bottom half with an Eric Byrnes 2 run homer to right-center.  The A's appeared to take charge in the 5th when byrnes would again do something with his bat, hitting a sac fly to center scoring Scutaro. That wouldn't last long as the Ranger would break out the sticks, and get&nbsp;five runs in the 6th. Michael Young would lead off with a single, Soriano would be sat down looking, Texiera would line out to Crosby and then the fun would really start. Brian Jordan would single to left moving Young to third, and then the first run would score after a Blalock single placing men at first and third. Gary Matthews would follow up with a single scoring Jordan from third and moving Blalock to second. Kevin Mench would&nbsp;cap the 6th inning parade with one of his own around the bases. Rod Barajas would double and Eric Young would walk, but shame shame on Michael Young for popping up to end the inning he started off with a lead off single.  Texas would add another run for insurance in the 8th inning, but it wasn't needed as the A's failed to put any of their own on the board for the remainder of the game.  Luckily for the A's its only the end of July and they've got two months to erase a 4 1/2 game gap. They just might want to start with their next two games. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      During Game 1 of Thursday's double header, the Orioles' hot hitting continued.&nbsp; Miguel Tejada crushed a home run in the 1st inning, helping the Orioles get off to a quick lead.&nbsp; After that, the Orioles never looked back.&nbsp; Mevin Mora had a big day, with 2 home runs.&nbsp; All this came against a AA pitcher, Abe Alverez, who was making his major league debut.&nbsp; The Orioles set aside their struggles against soft tossing left handers, and got the win for Rodrigo Lopez, who pitched six solid innings, giving up only 1 run.&nbsp; Then the bullpen took over, and surrendered a 2 run home run, but that came too late for the Red Sox.&nbsp; Final score: 8-3.  In the second game, the orioles offense came to an abrupt halt.&nbsp; Stymed by Tim wakefield's knuckleball, the Orioles only truly had 2 scoring opportunities.&nbsp; In the first inning, Brian Roberts and David Newhan had singles to put runners on the corners, but Melvin Mora lifted a fly ball to shallow left field, and Brian Roberts was thrown out trying to score on the play.&nbsp; In the 4th inning, Larry Bigbie and Robert Machado had singles, but the top of the order could not scratch out a run.&nbsp; The game was essentially decided in the bottom of the first inning, with Orioles starter Dave Borkowski issuing a walk to Johnny Damon, who advanced to second on a balk call. That balk rattled Borkowski who loaded the bases, could not field a slow bouncing ball back to the mound, and 3 runs scored.  Tonight, the orioles are facing the Minnesota Twins, and hightly touted pitching prospect, John Maine, is going to make his major league debut.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
             Photo courtesy of mlb.com     &nbsp;   Thursday, July 23, 2004: The Rockies prevented the Dodgers from coming from behind in last night's game, but today was not the case.  Odalis Perez was practically lights out, allowing one run in seven innings; although, Rockies' pitcher Aaron Cook managed to do the same. It all came down to the wire when Royce Clayton came up big with a sacrifice fly to allow Aaron Miles to tag up and score from third in the eigth inning. Colorado had the edge over the Dodgers by just one run.  In the bottom of the same inning, the Blue Crew created their own rally&nbsp;as they&nbsp;knocked in two runs to take the lead with Milton Bradley's homerun, and an insurance RBI by Jason Grabowski after Shawn Green singles to left.  "GAME OVER" is all the crowd&nbsp;could say as their All-Star closer Eric Gagne took the mound to wrap up the night. To make the victory even sweeter, Gagne struckout the side to tie in his 28th save of the year.     San Diego Padres (53-42)&nbsp;defeat the San Francisco Giants (53-44) as the Giants take one step back in the National League West standings, as the Los Angeles Dodgers (55-39) add on to their league lead. 
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Braves-Mets game was canceled due to rain.  It will be made up as part of a double-header on September 13th.    The Phillies 5-1 lose to the Cubs allowed the Braves to take a half a game lead in the East.      My daily rant:  none 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Photo courtesy of mlb.com      Friday, July 23, 2004: This was the series both Los Angeles and San Diego have been anxious about this week, and now it's finally here. With the Padres in town, the Dodgers are in the midst of either making or breaking their National League division lead. With the help of some friendly pitches and swingin' bats, tonight was worth the bitten nails.     Dodgers class-act Jose Lima took the mound, resting the mighty bullpen by pitching eight full innings and only giving up two runs. On the other hand, Padres pitcher Brian Lawrence pitched seven innings and silenced the Blue Crew to just one run.    To start the bottom of the eighth, Juan Encarnacion successfully drove the ball out to leftfield for a ground-rule double. Since one run was all they needed to tie the game, Alex Cora laid down a sacrifice bunt, fielded by pitcher Akinori Otsuka but thrown away as the ball sailed passed firstbaseman Mark Loretta. As Encarnacion scored from second, rightfielder Brian Giles committed an error as well on a bad throw towards second base on an attempt to keep Cora from advancing. Due to the off-line throw, Cora stood on the thirdbase bag with no outs, and the twisted arms of the Padres' defense were noticeably on LA's side. 
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Kansas City Royals 2, Cleveland Indians 10 (Game 1)   W-Chad Durbin (4-4) L-Chris George (1-2)  HR: Tony Graffanino (KC) 3     New York Yankees 10, Boston Red Sox 11   W-Ramiro Mendoza (1-0) L-Mariano Rivera (1-1)  HR: Ruben Sierra (NYY) 13; Bill Mueller (BOS) 8     Texas Rangers 2, Oakland Athletics 6   W-Kirk Saarloos (2-1) L-R.A. Dickey (5-7)  HR: Mark Teixeira (TEX) 23; Mark Kotsay (OAK) 6, 7; Eric Chavez (OAK) 15     Tampa Bay Devil Rays 2, Toronto Blue Jays 4   W-Josh Towers (5-3) L-Rob Bell (3-4) S-Jason Frasor (12)  HR: None     Minnesota Twins 2, Baltimore Orioles 4   W-Sidney Ponson (5-12) L-Joe Roa (2-2) S-Jorge Julio (15)  HR: Miguel Tejada (BAL) 19     Detroit Tigers 6, Chicago White Sox 7   W-Damaso Marte (4-3)  L-Ugueth Urbina (3-5)  HR: Carlos Guillen (DET) 14, 15; Brandon Inge (DET) 9; Marcus Thames (DET) 4; Jose Valentin (CHW) 22; Paul Konerko (CHW) 25; Joe Crede (CHW) 13     Kansas City Royals 3, Cleveland Indians 4 (Game 2)   W-Matt Miller (3-1) L-Scott Sullivan (3-3)  HR: None     Anaheim Angels 8, Seattle Mariners 4   W-Aaron Sele (6-0) L-Julio Mateo (1-1)  HR: Darin Erstad (ANA) 4; Josh Paul (ANA) 1; Robb Quinlan (ANA) 1     Chicago Cubs 3, Philadelphia Phillies 4   W-Paul Abbott (1-4) L-Carlos Zambrano (9-6) S-Tim Worrell (10)  HR: Sammy Sosa (CHC) 20; Derrek Lee (CHC) 18; Aramis Ramirez (CHC) 18     San Francisco Giants 5, St. Louis Cardinals 3   W-Felix Rodriguez (3-4) L-Ray King (3-1) S-Jason Christiansen (2)  HR: Marquis Grissom (SF) 15; Edgardo Alfonzo (SF) 7; Jim Edmonds (STL) 24     Milwaukee Brewers 3, Houston Astros 6   W-Tim Redding (4-6) L-Ben Hendrickson (0-3) S-Brad Lidge (10)  HR: Brady Clark (MIL) 5; Lyle Overbay (MIL) 11; Adam Everett (HOU) 6; Jason Lane (HOU) 3     Florida Marlins 2, Montreal Expos 6   W-Rocky Biddle (2-4) L-Dontrelle Willis (7-6)  HR: None     Cincinnati Reds 4, Pittsburgh Pirates 14   W-John Grabow (1-4) L-Aaron Harang (6-3)  HR: Barry Larkin (CIN) 6     Atlanta Braves 5, New York Mets 2   W-John Thomson (8-7) L-Mike Stanton (0-4) S-John Smoltz (19)  HR: None     Colorado Rockies 8, Arizona Diamondbacks 2   W-Jamey Wright (1-0) L-Lance Cormier (0-2)  HR: Larry Walker (COL) 6; Vinny Castilla (COL) 21; Todd Helton (COL) 18; Aaron Miles (COL) 4     San Diego Padres 2, Los Angeles Dodgers 12   W-Wilson Alvarez (5-3) L-Ismael Valdez (9-6)  HR: Shawn Green (LA) 14; Juan Encarnacion (LA) 13; Adrian Beltre (LA) 27  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Photo courtesy of mlb.com      Saturday, July 24, 2004: Power was surging through the Dodgers' bones tonight as they blew the Padres away, 12-1. Adrian Beltre, Shawn Green, and Juan Encarnacion all manage to hit the ball out of the park, producing nine of the twelve runs as a trio.    After the Dodgers' rookie starting pitcher Edwin Jackson goes down with an injury,&nbsp;Wilson Alvarez filled in the rotation and threw a gem by&nbsp;allowing one run in seven innings. He proudly&nbsp;earned his fifth win of the season with a 3.51 ERA, which is second best in the rotation behind Odalis Perez. Alvarez also helped out the offense by getting a basehit and scoring a run. 
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Orioles had been struggling; they lost 2 of three to the twins, when normally reliable Daniel Cabrera had one of his few bad outings against the twins to end that series.  Then they split a rain shortened series with the Red Sox who the orioles had handled all season.  Pedro was his usual strong self in game 1 but Javy Lopez almost singlehandedly beat Curt Schilling in the finale of the series.  Following that came a trip into Yankee Stadium.  Sidney Ponson began the series with an excellent outing- very rare for him.  Following that, the Orioles' offense stalled, stranding runners, not working the count.  The pitching chose the same time to go through a rough patch, not unusual for young starters in historic Yankee Stadium.  Becasue of this, the orioles lost the next 3 games.  However, then seattle came into town for 3 games in 2 days and the orioles woes were solved.  In game 1 of tuesday's doubleheader, Sidney Ponson reverted back to his usual self, but the offense bailed him out knocking Seattle's starter, Ron Villone, out of the game early.  The bullpen held the lead to seal the game.  In game 2, the orioles surprisingly managed to beat Jamie Moyer, who has been an Oriole Killer.  Wednesday's game was another all-around good game, with Daniel Cabrera giving up 3 runs in 5+ innings, but leaving with a no decision.  The bullpen came in and held the Mariners, while the Orioles offense came through with some rare clutch hitting.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>