<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This site is amazin! Run by th same ppl as quiz ur friends, all u hav 2 do is keep holdin a button down with the mouse.&nbsp; My record is 56 mins, but hav 2 admit 2 cheatin lol.&nbsp; Try it at  urlLink www.holdthebutton.com   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My pictures from Poland are here at last!&nbsp; They arrived in th post yesterday, n yesterday eve n this morn has bin devoted 2 publishing them 4&nbsp;UR benefit on th web.&nbsp; Ud betta b grateful! :P hehe.&nbsp; Sorry jenny, jus had 2 post that pic, check out th last pic at th Bohema restaurant guys :P.&nbsp; The pictures page is  urlLink here .&nbsp; Please sign the guestbook.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Iv emailed most of u, but those hu iv missed, plz  urlLink take my quiz  and then  urlLink check out the scoreboard! &nbsp;&nbsp;   Make ur own quiz at  urlLink www.quizyourfriends.com , its fun!   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       These pictures r taken by a friend, u can either get at them via   urlLink Her Blog  or direct from her page about our time in  urlLink Poland .&nbsp;  &nbsp;
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Guess the Dictator or Sit-Com Character  Check this site out guys - spooky!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         You believe in Santa Claus.    You don't believe in Santa Claus.    You are Santa Claus.     You look like Santa Claus.   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          How to shower like a woman            Take off clothing and place it in sectioned laundry basket according to whites and coloureds.       Walk to bathroom wearing long dressing gown.  
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     This picture was taken in the Wieliczka salt mines near Krakow, Poland. More pics of the trip will follow once theyre developed, but had 2 pay 10 zlotti 4 this 1, as it was taken by th mine staff. Th salt mine is very interestin. If ur eva in Krakow, giv it a visit, lol. &nbsp; urlLink   
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A great site with no end of hilariously funny video clips. Just refresh the page 4 more.    urlLink  http://www.supanet.com/funnies     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        hi peeps im new 2 this blogging business jus thought id giv it a try. 
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you remember  urlLink Frances the Firefly ? That cool lil cartoon th firemen gave out yrs ago? Theres a web page 4 it!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi ppl, sorry there havent been any updates 4 ages, iv been away for a week campin nr Whitby, North Yorks.  Was gd fun, tho far 2 wet 4 my likin lol.  Havent done any surfin since i got bak, so no fun links 4 u, sorry hehe.  Was away 4 my bday as well, was an experience.  Nothin like th sound of rain on a tent 2 wish u a happy bday lol.  Na was ok, it dried up l8r, n i had a gd day. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woo got back into CYO, was sure i wud, but u can neva b sure till th day.  Had a friend last yr hu got moved from CTO bak 2 CSO, didnt realise that that actually happened until it happened 2 him.  He was so pissed off he left lol.   Moan time.  3 things:  1) Y is my post so slow? Sum ppl got their results on Wednesday, n here i am waitin til friday!  2) Y dont they put where ur theyve placed u in the orchestra on th letter?  Even jus an indication of 1st or 2nd violins would help.  Wud make so much more sense than makin every1 crowd around 1 tiny notice on th 1st rehearsal, n also it wud allow ppl 2 deal wiv their dissappointment/elation in a private place instead of in front of everybody.  Stupid ppl.  3) Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo its Mr leech!  I knew it was gonna b, but was hopin my source was mistaken!  Evil man.  Jus hope he doesnt know about this page lol. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a really funny spoof on th  urlLink Windows  environment.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>