<Blog>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      print:&nbsp; hello world!&nbsp; *coughs*  Just decided to try out blogger and see if it's as popular and community-oriented as LJ.  I suppose that I'll start x-posting my new LJ posts here also, to give some insight on my life.&nbsp;  urlLink (http://www.livejournal.com/users/shannonizm &nbsp;if you're interested in reading previous material, poetry, rants, and life bullshit.)  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Forsyth County, N.C., Real-Estate Officials Eye Sites for Possible Dell Plant Winston-Salem Journal 07/08/2004   Briefly:&nbsp; Jul. 8--Two business parks in southeastern Forsyth County -- the Alliance Science and Technology Park and Union Cross Business Park -- are considered prime sites for a possible $190 million Dell Inc. plant, local real-estate officials said yesterday. The project, still under wraps, would consist of a 400,000-square-foot manufacturing plant on 100 acres, according to an application for job-training assistance with the Golden LEAF Foundation filed by Winston-Salem Business Inc., a city economic-development arm. The Union Cross and Alliance business parks, which are about three miles apart, would be the most likely sites for meeting the project's likely site specifications, said Michael Clapp of Michael S. Clapp & Associates Inc., a Winston-Salem real-estate appraisal company,  Jul. 8--Two business parks in southeastern Forsyth County -- the Alliance Science and Technology Park and Union Cross Business Park -- are considered prime sites for a possible $190 million Dell Inc. plant, local real-estate officials said yesterday. "If you do a filter map on Forsyth County, there are only a handful of places with potential," said Glenn Simmons, a city-county planner. The project, still under wraps, would consist of a 400,000-square-foot manufacturing plant on 100 acres, according to an application for job-training assistance with the Golden LEAF Foundation filed by Winston-Salem Business Inc., a city economic-development arm. It also involves plans by a separate, unidentified company to build a 250,000-square-foot logistics operation costing $6.2 million near Dell's proposed electronic-equipment plant. The Union Cross and Alliance business parks, which are about three miles apart, would be the most likely sites for meeting the project's likely site specifications, said Michael Clapp of Michael S. Clapp &amp; Associates Inc., a Winston-Salem real-estate appraisal company. More than $12 million combined has been spent on buying the land and developing the parks. Other Forsyth business parks that could accommodate the project are Smith Reynolds Business Park at Smith Reynolds Airport and Piedmont Triad Research Park in downtown Winston-Salem. Clapp said that the Alliance and Union Cross parks could offer lower land costs compared with sites closer to the proposed FedEx Corp. cargo hub at Piedmont Triad International Airport. The hub is set to open in mid-2009. Analysts said that its overnight delivery times are a primary reason why Dell is considering a plant here. "Winston-Salem Alliance put together this park together with this kind of project in mind," Clapp said. "Both parks are centrally located for access to labor and to the airport. I would think it would even be an advantage that Forsyth has two business parks that close together to accommodate the project being placed in one park and suppliers in the other." The Union Cross park was formed in 1997 and consists of 400 acres. It has eight tenants and is about one-third full, according to Bob Leak, the president of Winston-Salem Business. The Winston-Salem Alliance, a non-profit organization focused on economic development, formed the Alliance park in 2003. The City-County Utility Commission paid for nearly 200 acres for the park. The Alliance has plans negotiate for another 300 acres if demand for space increases, said Allen Joines, the mayor of Winston-Salem and the president of the alliance. "The key is to get the land assembled and hold it until it can be turned over to a developer," Joines said. He declined to comment about Dell's interest, if any, in the Alliance park or other city business parks. Dell, the world's largest maker of computers, has not disclosed its business plans, and other Triad counties and other states may be in the running for the project. Details of the plans, dubbed "Project Merlin" by Winston-Salem Business, are included in its application that seeks $41 million in job-training assistance from the foundation. The documents do not mention Dell by name or any potential park sites, but state and local officials said several weeks ago that an incentive package is being prepared in a bid to attract a Dell operation that could create up to 1,896 jobs. It's not clear how big a role a site will play in the project compared with incentives, job-training assistance and a trainable work force, said Greg Wilson, a senior vice president with Lincoln Harris, a development company and real-estate brokerage firm. "Because there is sufficient infrastructure and roadways in place, and a lower land cost, the parks should be an attractive tool in the overall package," Wilson said. Dell's first expansion outside its Round Rock, Texas, home was to Nashville in 1999 where it has manufacturing, distribution, technical support and sales operations. Dell's deal with Nashville included 149 acres with an option for 326 acres around Nashville International Airport that expires Dec. 31, reported the Tennessean, a daily newspaper in the city. Dell benefits from a property-tax abatement plan with the Metropolitan Government of Nashville and Davidson County. It won't pay any property tax through 2009 and then will pay at a reduced tax rate through 2039. "Project Merlin" in Forsyth County involves about 20 local volunteers, including business owners, business leaders, downtown boosters and local architects, who have studied several sites and drawn preliminary sketches of buildings.  By Victoria Cherrie and Richard Craver   ++++++++++ I sincerely hope this works out. If they decide to put a plant in NC, they'll more than likely put a tech support center there also. I'll commute if nothing better has come up by then, I'm qualified for any position with Dell, pretty much, from assembly to Tech Support. $35k a year would be a nice start. No it's not gonna buy me a mansion, but it's better than anything around here, and it's computers (grin).Yesterday everyone in the world was here and that kind of irritated me, but it wasn't as bad as it usually is. Tune, Brandon, Beverly, Jonathan, JJ, Jarrod, Vicki, Catie, Willie, Emily, Jonathan, Lee, Drew, Lil Ryan, Largen, and a few other people were here for most of the day. More tiring than anything, really. Brandon got drunk and stuck his head in the pool several times. My brother puked from drinking rum and Dr. Pepper, but then again, who wouldn't puke from that?Ian's been here several times in the past week, and he and Drew (his brother) got in a fight in my back yard a couple nights ago, and I sincerely have no doubt that if they wouldn't have been stopped, Drew would have killed Ian. Drew was beating him senseless. Drew does have a point though, Ian does talk about him terribly. Ian insists that Drew's gay, and I know for a fact that he is not gay. He might be bi, I don't know about that.... but I do know he's not totally into men. Even still, and I know how much of a pain brothers can be, is it necessary to broadcast your family's sexual preferences (true or not) to everyone they know and hang out with? Did he really think it would make us think less of Drew? Come on. Not necessary. Who really cares? Basically the only thing that Ian really mentions (other than to disrespect his brother) is his new Tool-esque band that has 2 1/2 songs now, and his plans to write a song about Andrew Abbott and how he wants to kill him.... Ian's adopted this holier-than-thou attitude towards a lot of people lately, and I don't think it was wise of him to say that he could beat Largen down, since Largen is now just waiting for an excuse to hit him. I mean really, what is it with all the fighting?   We've sworn off the Temple (or at least paying to go in) because we're too old for it. The place will probably end up shutting down, being as how no one wants to pay to get in, they all stand outside smoking cigarettes (since it's a non-smoking establishment) and trying to be cool in their ripped up fishnets and Goodwill clothes, and especially since they're so heavily monitored by the police now for "gang activity", drugs, etc. Nay, not everyone there is bad or stupid, there are a few people that go there that I actually know and like. The only thing that will pull me to the Temple again is Manly Firmness and the Semis, and hell, I can get them to play on my patio for free.Danville's "scene" as some people like to call it, is nothing. There are no real clubs around here. If they want a prosperous "scene", they need to make it 18 and older (and I'm not saying cut everything out for the teenagers, no, no, no. Obviously though, kids are unwilling to spend $5 to get into the Temple, when they can stand outside and spend said $5 on a nickel bag of oregano that some asshole has in his pocket) and serve alcohol, and of course, they can't fuck it all up by having punk nights and rock nights followed by DJ SleazyDork busting out the freshest top 40 around. Pick a genre and stick to it. Actually, I'm tired of the word "scene" being thrown around this town. We get an insert in the paper on Thursdays called Danville's Scene, which highlights the "exciting goings-on" in this dump. Most of the time, it includes pottery classes for retired people, beach bands and country singers playing at Carrington Pavillion, and day camps for kids. Some scene. People who say they're "so scene" and "into the Danville scene" are retarded and deserve to be kicked in the groin.*rolls eyes*Plus the Temple is right in front of the police station... you don't have to go far if you get arrested, they'll just walk you across the street and slap you with a contributing charge, not to mention HOW STUPID someone would have to be to paint anti-Bush propaganda anywhere in Danville, I'm sure if most of these kids' parents knew how they acted and how "politically motivated" they try to come off as, they would shit the bed. The kicker: none of them really know what the fuck they're talking about. I will continue to take my clubbing business to North Carolina to actual clubs that are able to serve alcohol, that I can light a cigarette in, that are air conditioned, clean, and minus 12-year-old skanks, places that will check ID at the door, with actual paid security and bouncers instead of some guy who walks in and voulinteers to "keep an eye on things". The Temple was fun for awhile, until it was overrun by loiterers and cops. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>