<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Attn: my dear silly .....   To me,people fall into 3  categories:  1st:The ones that are very intelligent, and truly know that themselves, 2nd:The ones that think are intelligent and are not and 3rd:The ones that are not intelligent and even don't know that.  The worst thing that I hate in my life is when someone thinks that he/she can easily lie to me and I won't understand. I had never suffered from this issue this much before I settle in U.A.E. I used to like someone who were and is quite kind and nice with me, but I started hating him when he thought that he can lie to me easily continously and threatening me about very stupid things. I am asking him: "My dear silly...,Don't you think that I easily understand it when you lie so obviuosly??!! Is it not important to you that how I may think about you when I figure out this??!! Do you know that then you will be the stupid one ,not me?! Don't you know that I'm already aware of anything you do and almost everything you are trying to hide from me?? I think you are too stupid to understand this, and you will only get to know your very big mistake once I leave you and never even talk to you, and it will be for sure a very good experience for you to care about your silly behaviour or you may decide not to deal with understanding people anymore, coz you don't deserve having such friends.  My very dear Friends;  Please know that if you really respect someone, even if you have no special relations with him/her you shouldn't lie at all! Unless you will lose them so easily.  Try to never discuss about anything which you don't want to give information about, coz if you initiate the issue, should be 100% honest!  At least this is the way I expect from any of my friends and almost all of them are 100% honest, but this silly.....     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi everybody:)First of all I should tell you that I'm glad to be here, and I thank my friend Somi for introducing me this bogspot!  Actually,I love reading and writing,and I can share manythings with you,but I rarely have time to do anything but work.  I've just signed up here today,we'll discuss about manythings,but please be patient and don't miss me:)):d  Best Regards  Armaghan 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God is knowledge, he is knowing, and he is being known. Since God has knowledge of his own essence, and since God is one, it follows that the essence of God is knowledge. And knowledge means that he knows himself, and is known by himself.  -Ibn Sina, "al-Risalat al-Arshiya" 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       عيونك شايفها وحاسس اني انا عارفها
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       وبينا معاد لو احنا بعاداكيد
</post>


</Blog>