<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Clare: You could do anything, couldn't you? I mean, is there anything you couldn't do?     Bobby: I couldn't be alone.        You've read the book, now see the movie!  I remember back when I first found out this was being made into a film. The most famous name attached to it was Robin Wright Penn and oh, there was that guy, Colin Something Or Another. One measly year passes along with The Recruit and Minority Report and suddenly this movie's got a new star. And his name is Colin Farrell, Irishman, drinker, smoker, ladiesman extraordinaire and don't any of you forget it or he might knock you down with his cursing prowess.     But all Russell Crowe-ishness aside, Colin Farrell can actually act. And by act, I don't mean playing the same role over and over again to perfection, but being enough of a strong character that while you watch him on screen, you forget that this is the same man who once made out with Britney Spears. Considering how he's looked in the media of late, Farrell does a pretty good job of burying his he-whore image. Yet still, watching Colin Farrell play Bobby, the shy, angelic, 24 year old virgin, does require some suspension of disbelief. You do wonder at times how innocent Bobby can be when he walks with that kind of swagger.  The movie as a whole is pretty much perfect in translating the book's tone. It's quiet, non-flashy, and gives equal screentime to all the characters and the relationships. My compliments to Dallas Roberts and Robin Wright Penn for playing their characters with enough depth, minus the DRAMA. The hardest character of the trio has to be Clare. She's the odd woman out and Wright Penn has to overcome stock kooky hair and matching persona that would normally set most people's teeth on edge.  The movie also has a soundtrack that conflictingly makes me want to rush out and buy it, while lying to the cashier that it's for "a friend."   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       So, I usually hate chick-lit.  It was okay when  Bridget Jones's Diary  was the only kind of chick-lit out there, but thanks to the combined power of greed and marketing, bookstores are crammed with novels about the down and out woman who strives to find love and maybe the perfect job while wearing Manolos. She'll fight off horrid bosses, suffer some humiliating moments around the man she fancies, but will ultimately find her true calling and a Forever Love in the end.  But despite my general ire for this genre, I picked up Caroline Hwang's book, telling myself it was research for my job.  The protagonist is a 27 year old Korean-American woman who quit her Ph.D track in English to work as the oldest, bottom-rung assistant at a fashion magazine. Generally, Ginger (the woman), is cynical, disaffected, directionless and has conflicting feelings of being overqualified for her job, but remains clueless as to what her goals should be. To add to her mental crisis, her mother shows up, determined to get Ginger a husband. The plot is peppered with the usual run-ins of bitchy bosses and co-workers, embarrassing moments of dating, outfits descriptions that would make any fashionista proud, and the predictable plot twists.  And god help me if I didn't love every moment of it.  A lot of my love for this book came from the protagonist. Minus the matchmaking mother and three years in age, Ginger is essentially me. I feel her pain. I feel her fear of having absolutely no future plans, other than maybe getting that package down to the messenger center for her boss.  All in all, I BELIEVED Ginger could be a real person, rather than just another neurotic chick-lit heroine. She is that as well in some ways, but Hwang stripping most of the romantics out of Ginger's life helped nudge this book closer to real-life, rather than the fantasy life where you end up with the man of your dreams in under 200 pages.  My guess would be that while one would read chick-lit to get away from reality, a judgemental cynic like me is pleased to see how lives of even chick-lit characters can continue to suck in someways after the The End.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Today seemed an appropriate  to review this book as the film version, directed by Michael Mayer is opening in New York.  I feel the need to state that I read this book about two years ago, back when the book jacket was a plain, gray photograph of a house, cast in the early light of dawn. It's an attractive cover that after you read the book you realize perfectly captures the tone, feel and message of the work. Now you'll be lucky if you don't trip over the copies with a new jacket prominently displaying Colin Farrell's visage.  Nothing saddens me more than when books get this kind of "face-lift." Logically, I realize that this ploy of the publishing house will mean more sales and therefore more royalties for the author=a good thing. And yet, I have to believe a book jacket designer out there dies a little inside when his or her cover, carefully and thoughtfully designed, is crushed so that the mug of the movie star in the film adaptation can be plastered all over it.  I personally love the current book jacket for  The Time Traveler's Wife  by Audrey Niffenegger. Now that Brad Pitt's production company has bought it, should I be preparing myself for bookshelves to be filled with copies of the book with his grinny face on the cover? Or even worse, copies with his BROODY face on the cover? Lord have some pity.  But back to the topic: A Home at the End of the World.  I already knew I'd be a sucker for this book, because it deals with a theme I hold rather near and dear: male relationships. The story starts with the lives of Bobby Morrow and Jonathan Glover, two boyhood friends who, despite wildly different personalities, form a unique and unbreakable bond. Jonathan eventually moves to New York where he meets and starts a platonic relationship (Jonathan discovers early on in his childhood that he's gay) with an older woman, Clare. Later, Bobby moves out to New York to join Jonathan and Clare in their East Village apartment.  The trio form an interesting group, made up of different pairings. There's Jonathan and Clare who hope to one day have a child together (at Clare's request), but that's eventually gets curtailed when Clare and Bobby fall in love. And in the midst of it, there's still the Jonathan and Bobby friendship that at times makes Clare feel like the odd person out.  Despite how the setup looks, nothing ever malicious happens between these characters. Despite some awkward moments of having to readjust, the three all love each other enough to weather any difficulties. Instead of getting a conflict within the relationships, they form a kind of support system for each other as events outside of their new family threaten to bring sad tidings.  Nothing about this book was sweeping or of epic-quality. The beauty of Cunningham's novel is that it never pulls any dramatic punches to try and make itself more dynamic and important. Instead it remains true to the idea that your life and the events of the world just happen: quietly and simply, which is profound in itself.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        "Once upon a time, there lived a boy and a girl. The boy was eighteen and the girl sixteen. He was not unusually handsome, and she was not especially beautiful. They were just an ordinary lonely boy and an ordinary lonely girl, like all the others. But they believed with their whole hearts that somewhere in the world there lived the 100% perfect boy and the 100% perfect girl for them."    -- "On Seeing the 100% Perfect Girl One Beautiful April Morning" from  The Elephant Vanishes      It's kind of interesting to me the ways in which people try to describe Murakami's writing to those who have never encountered it before. Usually, words like "mystical" and "bizarre" are tossed around. Sometimes the occasional "mindfuck" is thrown in. But most often than not, I see people giving up and telling Murakami virgins to just go ahead and read one of his novels.  I'll admit that I'm a coward when it comes to certain new authors. My fear of commitment leaks into my reading methods wherein I really don't want to consign to reading a whole novel if I'm not entirely sure about the author. Especially if the author is as iconic as Murakami. So if you're a reader like me,  The Elephant Vanishes  is a perfect way to start your discovery of this author as it is a collection of short stories.  As a whole,  The Elephant Vanishes  gives you a good idea of the kind of hazy, dreamy quality of Murakami's writing. You have characters who are either thrown into strange situations or who are prone to strange behavior and yet none of it ever feels convoluted.  Most of the stories deal with themes of isolation and the little deaths people feel when they sense how out of joint they are with the society and people around them. I love all the different ways Murakami can show this one theme in so many various characters. Who knew so many people of so many different situations and backgrounds could all experience this kind of crushing misery? For a pessimist like me, getting a glimpse into so many of these forlorn, unsatisfied lives was awesome.  I recently saw the stage adaptation of three of the stories from this collection. Quickly I'd say it was a good production with some wonderfully visual staging that captures the surreal quality of the writing. But like any book lover I'd tell you to read the book instead. Hey, it's cheaper too.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Contrary to popular belief, I'm not a big fan of clutter. Yes, my apartment looks like the place where books and scraps of paper go to procreate, but I firmly believe this has more to do with the fact that my apartment is the size of a luxury coffin. But I digress...  I'm not an advocate of clutter or excess. So why in this time of the Blogger Boom would I create a blog myself? Why would I add to the ever-growing mass of online journals? Who the hell am I? What sort of importance do my words hold? Answer: not that much.  I could go on about questioning and justifying my reasons for creating a blog, but like every other human on this planet, I'm just susceptible to adding to the cluster already out there. My little corner of the Internet is mainly for reviews of books with the occasional digressions that I am also susceptible to like so many others.  So hello and welcome.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       This is a grossly delayed farewell. It's been delayed mainly because I wanted this blog to be a place for reviewing books and occasionally films, not a place of eulogies. But I was sitting at a restaurant yesterday, talking about photography when my dinner mate brought up Bresson. By the time she had finished describing one of his photos, I strangely felt the need to cry. In lieu of that, I'm writing this.  About two weeks ago, Henri Cartier Bresson passed away. For those of you who don't know who he is, he's a photographer whose work I can guarantee you have seen, whether you knew it was by him or not. Bresson's photos are the kinds of art pieces that inspires an emotion that I'd equate as beauty. They say that photographers should work to capture a moment, but Bresson managed to do more than that. He captured the ineffable grandeur of the world. You can look at his photographs and sense the dynamic energy in front of you. But they also make you imagine and remember all the other fantastic events that make life so wonderfully liveable. I realize I'm breathing when I see Bresson's photographs and remind me of all the potential of the world still out there to be experienced.  When I heard that he had died, I was curious what the last photograph he ever took. As unlikely as it might be, I feel like it would give me an insight onto how a dying man saw the world just before he passed away from it. I wonder if he still saw all the beauty around him as reflected in his earlier works? I hope he did.   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        "...I wanted to feel happy today."               And believe me, I wanted to feel happy too after I finished this book.       People complain about having to wait at a doctor's office. I personally have never complained about having to wait hours at my doctor's office as I always go there equipped with a book and a fear of medicine that has me happily content that my time in the small examination room has been detained for an extra few hours. But last week, all I wanted was for the nurse to come out, call my name and relieve me from the hypnotic hold  The Interpreter  had over me.        The Interpreter  is the first novel by Korean-American journalist, Suki Kim. The protagonist is Suzy Park. She's a 29 year old New Yorker, who has never held down a job for more than a few months. Currently, she works as an interpreter for court cases around various parts of New York. When we meet Suzy, she is stuck in a perpetual haze caused by the death of her parents who were shot in their grocery store. The police claimed that the shooting was random. A new case of Suzy's, however, reveals that there was more to shooting then she thought.       There's an intricate mystery throughout this book. I certainly couldn't guess what happened to Suzy's parents or what it was exactly that drove such a horrible wedge between Suzy and her older sister, Grace. On this one level,  The Interpreter  is an intriguing novel that would probably hold your attention to the last page, even if you weren't as affected by its other aspect.       The other aspect I speak of here is Kim's writing. I'm impressed to find out that English is not her first language because it is rare for a writer to be so incredibly precise and accurate in conveying the kind of pain her characters feel. Never and I do mean never, did a book make me so seriously contemplate the utter hopelessness of life in general. Yeah, I'm prone to fits of depression, but the kind of depression that Kim writes about goes beyond simple cynicism. Her characters are the kind of people who have never felt happy. Ever. They might have gotten glimpses of it, but they have never felt it first hand.    The novel is drenched in prose that is infused with malaise and a sense of defeat that makes the reading of it one seriously depressing experience. That's not to say that Suki Kim's isn't a brilliant writer. On the contrary, the fact that she makes me want to crawl under the covers and never come out is a testament to how amazingly affecting and poignant her writing is. But I think one should be in a terrific frame of mind to read this novel. If you're already feeling down about something or another in your life, this book is NOT a pick-me-up.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I just got a new computer today at work. Along with a new hard drive and flat screen, I get a new keyboard and mouse. Everything is black, sleek and is virtually silent. Gone is the roaring, croaking, wheezing sounds of my old hard drive. Extinct is the odd *clackclack* sound my mouse made when I merely scrolled. Even the keyboard is so quiet that I can no longer hear neighboring cubicle prisoners typing away furiously, ala CIA control room style.  It's pretty great. I'm already thinking of names to give my new co-worker. And in celebration of its arrival, I've decided to do a joint review of two authors.  There are some couples out there who are the embodiment of cute. You know the types. They look right together, they do that thing where they finish each others sentences and they like to swap bites of each others dinners. Personally, stuff like that makes me retch. But what we have in Sebold and Gold is a cute couple of the writerly kind. They've been interviewed together. They've dedicated their first books to each other. Their books were even twined together on Amazon.com at one point. It's just so damn cute. And since it's bookish cuteness, I can probably stomach it. So let's begin:    The Lovely Bones by Alice Sebold         If you're a  New York Times  bestseller list whore or just susceptible to human suggestion (ie. pretty much everyone), you've already heard and most likely have read this book. Sebold's debut novel hit the bestsellers list and stayed there for a record amount of weeks. I think it might have taken  The Da Vinci Code  to throw this thing of its bestseller throne. A long lasting bestseller is not too unusual, but what amazes me is just how ordinary this book is. I got around to reading it when I received it as a going away gift from my first boss ever in the publishing world. I still have the copy for sentimental reasons because if it were just any copy, it'd be going right back to the Strand for resale.    The plot, (for those who have been living under a rock) is about a 14 year old girl who is raped and murdered at the beginning of the novel. The rest of the book is told from her point of view in heaven as she looks down at her family and how they slowly learn to move on with their lives. The most powerful moments happens when the narrator is still alive. Her rape and murder at the hands of a complete stranger is heartbreaking to read. And taking into account   urlLink  Sebold's follow up    to  The Lovely Bones,  it's not surprising that this section of the book holds the most amount of honest, raw emotion. Everything after it, feels like material leftover from an After School special or an episode of "Touched by an Angel."  I'm not one to shy away from fantasy, but the fantastical elements used here are just eye-rollingly bad, feeling like a last ditch-effort to get the reader's heart strings tugged. I mean, the narrator is the victim of a heinous crime and her family is left in shattered pieces. I don't need anything more to convince me to feel bad for these people. At yet the saccharine continues to be poured on as if more justification is needed as to why readers should feel for this family. It also becomes painfully apparent at one point that this book is being written for the movies. The writing falls down to something just barely above stage direction and there are enough perfectly tied off endings that my suspension of disbelief came to a crash landing.  I can't quite understand how this book maintained it's bestseller status or where it got its rave reviews. Every person I've talked to who read this book pretty much reiterated what I just wrote above. So where did all the praise come from? Who are these readers? WHERE are these readers??  Okay, moving on....  Much like his wife, Glen David Gold hit it big with his first novel. The I know that Gold has in his camp one of most demanding, hard-hitting literary agent, so I can only imagine how fierce the bidding war was on this novel. And was it worth it? Maybe....    Carter Beats the Devil by Glen David Gold         This one's a historical novel, based around a real-life magician, Charles Carter. At the book's opening, Carter has just performed a somewhat disturbing trick using President Warren Harding as a volunteer. Shortly after that night, Harding has a heart attack and dies. Suspicions arise about whether or not Carter had a part to play in this sudden death and the magician soon flees the country....or so we think.    The book jumps around the timeline a little as we see Carter as a child, his first outings as a professional magician and the friends, lovers, and rivals he makes along the way. I'm a fan of historical novels and it was a treat to see Gold throw in some references and real historical characters. What I wasn't a fan of was that like Sebold, Gold fell a little into the "for the screen!" trap toward the end of the book. After a pretty rewarding read of misdirection, mystery, angst and recovery, it was a let down that the final scenes should be dedicated to a scenario straight out of an old silent film with the damsel in distress and the mustached villain.  But other than the last few pages, I was a fan of Gold's first outing. His writing style is clean and flows neatly without any ornamentations. Like Carter's tricks, Gold's language is simple and lulls the reader into such a comfortable pattern that sudden twists come as a real surprise.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Reviewing works by Neil Gaiman is always tricky for me. I need to pick a time when I'm not completely obsessed with his writing and can critique objectively. It's embarrassing to admit, but if I were to try and review one of his books during an obsession period, it'd be filled with nothing but "!!!!!!!!!!" and googly :)'s, no matter how crap the material. While I don't dress like a goth (as per a large portion of Mr. Gaiman's fandom), I do have a rather large collection of his work and hope to continue building on it, damn the costs. His writing is the kind I turn to when I need something to cheer up my day and he is one of the few authors out there that I would describe as "erudite." He's got a scary about of random knowledge in his mind and from what I can tell, reads a scary number of books and manages to retain just about everything he reads on any given topic. Such talents make me giggle like a daft schoolgirl.  But luckily I'm currently in a state of mind where my admiration for Mr. Gaiman is at normal levels. And so I am able to review his first, full-length urban fantasy novel with a discerning eye.     American Gods  is the story of an ex-con named Shadow. At the beginning of the novel, he's awaiting the last few days of his sentence, after which he'll be able to return to his loving wife and keep himself out of trouble for good. 24 hours before he's due to be released, however, Shadow receives news that his wife was killed in a car accident....while cheating on him with his best friend. A free man, but with little direction in life, Shadow boards to plane to head back home when he runs into a strange man named Mr. Wednesday, who offers him a job. Wednesday is taking a trip around the country and he would like Shadow to be his bodyguard.  For those of you who are remotely Norse mythology savvy, you know Mr. Wednesday's true identity. He's traveling through America to recruit other old Gods to prepare for a mystical war that is about to be unleashed on US grounds. Gaiman's key concept is rather brilliant. His novel supposes that when people immigrant to America, they bring with them their deities. But as time passes, their faith and devotion are transferred to things like the Internet and television, the staples of American luxury. When this happens, the old Gods are left stranded in America with nowhere to go. To make matters worse for these poor deities, new Gods are being created with human adoration toward computers and technology and these new Gods think it's time for the old ones to take a hike. Hence, a battle is coming.  A short segway into a bit of history: Neil Gaiman became a cult sensation after he penned a graphic novel series called "The Sandman." Beloved by many, "The Sandman" catapulted Gaiman from just another British writer to being the man who has been credited with changing the face of the graphic novel medium. If you've never read the Sandman series, I suggest you keep it that way and read  American Gods  first. This is not because I think the graphic novels are of lesser quality (I think they're actually quite brilliant), but you'll enjoy  American Gods  a whole lot more if you go into it being a Sandman virgin.  Gaiman knows when he has a good concept going. And he's not above recycling a good idea over and over again. Shakespeare did the same during his day. Why not Gaiman? It's all fine and good, but if you've already read the Sandman series, it's hard not to see  American Gods  as being derivative. But if you're completely unaware of the events that occur in the Sandman series,  American Gods  will feel like a rollicking, solid fantasy. As a transplanted Brit, Gaiman went through a lot of painstaking research before writing about the great American landscape and his efforts are well deserving of praise. And when you're done with the novel, you can happily move onto the comic books that made Gaiman so famous in the first place. And trust me, going to Sandman after  American Gods  is a real treat.  The most recent word is that Gaiman is working on his next novel, which can be best described as a spin-off of  American Gods . Again, if Shakespeare recycled ideas, why not Gaiman?   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       No, this is not a book. Well, it could have been. But thanks to Mr. Shyamalan's desire to keep his script under lock and key, under a boulder, under an ocean, a novelization was never done. Let's wipe our brows in relief that this is the case.  I'm sort of kidding myself that I can write a review about this movie when A.O Scott of the  New York Times  has written THE perfect review. Really, why are you even here? You should go over there and read his brilliantly scathing take on Shyamalan's latest "masterpiece."  But in case you've stuck around, I'll give you my two cents.  I've never liked a single film by this director. I know most of the world was blown away by "The Sixth Sense," but I seriously chalk that up to mass insanity. Kind of like this  Da Vinci Code  phenomenon we're seeing. But like a glutton for punishment, I continued to watch every film he made. Each subsequent film of Shyamalan's has been less and less offensive to watch. And now we have "The Village," which at best leaves you noncommitally shrugging your shoulders. Like all of Shyamalan's other films, this one also boasts a "surprise" ending. I use the word "surprise" loosely as it really depends on how easily you can be duped. For instance, if have the cognizant ability to deduce that fire is hot, you won't have a problem figuring out the twist.       The story centers around a small village community who have isolated themselves from any other neighboring villages and towns. Even fear of death by disease does not inspire these people to travel outside of their borders in search of other medicines. The main reason for this is that there are supposedly creatures in the woods that surround their village. These creatures, known as Those That We Do Not Speak Of, will theoretically wreak havoc on the villagers if anyone dares to cross over into their territory. It's all very scary. Really.  Other than this dark cloud, the village is a happy little place where everyone is kind and beloved. Even the mentally challenged, possibly crazy, and sporatically violent members (or member) is cared for with infinite patience. The trouble starts when one of the villagers (Joaquin Phoenix) questions whether Those That We Do Not Speak Of are truly violent. As far as he can tell, a member of Those That We Do Not Speak Of (though they do speak of them for the majority of the film) has never hurt anyone or posed a real threat to the village. Shockingly, around the time Joaquin starts to pose these queries to the community's quaint town council, dead animals are left all over village and house doors are vandalized with red paint. Obviously it's the work of Those That We Do Not Speak Of. I mean, what self-respecting forest creature wouldn't march around with a can of paint?     I'd go further into the plot, but I realize that in writing this review that just about all the events in this movie are incidental. Much like the movie itself. With"The Village," Shyamalan has gone from being the man whose work I loathed with a fiery passion to someone whose material illicits maybe an eyeroll from me. "The Village" is just another testament to my general belief that Shyamalan is not particularly talented when it comes to crafting a suspenseful film. His slow, portentous style of film-making clashes too heavily with a script that screams for a timely pace. The irony here is that Shyamalan wrote the screenplay as well.  Word has it that Shyamalan will be directing the film adaptation of  The Life of Pi  by Yann Martel. While I'm not exactly waiting for this movie with bated breath, I am curious to see how his directing style will work when the majority of the film takes place on a small row boat. One thing I can be grateful for is that under no circumstances will this film boast a twist ending.   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Everyone likes to take a road trip every now and again. It's a great American college past time. And according to Peter Ustinov, God and Satan share this view.   The Old Man and Mr. Smith,  labeled as "a fable" on the cover, is one of the few novels written by Peter Ustinov. Until I picked up this book, I only remembered Ustinov as the actor who played Hercules Poirot in a TV movie of "Evil Under the Sun." Apparently, along with acting, he's an accomplished playwright and journalist. He's traveled all over the world, spoke a staggering number of languages, and was a member of the International Academy of Humanism. His resume makes a whole lot of sense considering the kind of book he's written.  The premise of  The Old Man and Mr. Smith  is that every once in awhile, God and Satan like to meet up and take a tour of Earth to get an idea of how things are going. Dressed as humans, the two beings hop around continents and meet and greet all sorts of people. Usually governmental types who react in different ways to the news that God and the Devil are before them. God and Satan's human forms are pretty much what you would expect. God's got the great love for dressing in all white to match his white hair. Satan prefers his blacks and constantly reeks of sulfur. Their personalities also start out on the typical slant with God being benevolent and incessantly cheerful while Satan sneers at just about anything remotely goodly. But as it is with all road trip scenarios, each character's stereotype starts to give way to what's really hidden underneath.  Satan apparently is not a big fan of violence. And despite being thought of as the Prince of Lies, can't stand it when facts are misrepresented. He has a particular hate for televangelists who claim to have met the Devil during a moment of temptation. ("Liar! I've never seen you before in my life!") In many ways, he shows himself to be vulnerable to harsh words and is a rather sensitive fallen angel. God, while omnipotent in the ways of creation, gets easily lost trying to understand the state of politics in the Soviet Union. The Vietnam War completely escapes him. And he's not very good at guessing how people are going to react when he magically produces money from his pockets. He also gets a bit...errr.... grumpy when certain things start to impede their journey.  As he was in his acting, Ustinov is very good with whimsy in his novel. I love stories that give you a warped take on what kind of creatures God and Satan are. Or really any novel that spins religion on its head. But the novel starts to wear thin about halfway through when God and Satan have a long string of episodic encounters with law enforcement officers from all over the world. It becomes apparent at this time that Ustinov is using his novel as a soapbox to expound his views on humanity and politics. I may just be a lazy reader, but I much more enjoyed the earlier sections of Satan being dumbfounded at how humans can be obsessed with something as boring as sex.   The Old Man and Mr. Smith  is definitely not as light-hearted as  Good Omens  by Terry Pratchett and Neil Gaiman ,  nor does it offer belly laughs like Christopher Moore's  Lamb . But it does provide a good chuckle and some original insights on how God and Satan would behave if stuck with each other from one crappy hotel room to the next.   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         SPOILER AHEAD. DO NOT READ IF YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW A KEY EVENT IN THIS NOVEL.      I signed my lease today for my new apartment that I will not be moving into for at least a whole month. Now, people have been congratulating me, telling me this must be a relief and that I must now be on cloud nine of happy emotions. I'm not, however.  See, I'm a cynical person. I can say I'm a cynical New Yorker, but even when I was living in the suburbs of Natick, Massachusetts, I was this cynical. I'm basically waiting to find out that my lease fell through. My broker will somehow fake me out and I'll end up 3000 poorer and homeless. These are the kinds of worries that will plague me until I'm actually living in my apartment. Which means I have a month to look forward to with nothing but sleepless nights. I'm already telling myself to not like this apartment, just in case it won't be mine.  I'm the kind of person who can never fully accept anything and be happy until I know beyond a shadow of a doubt that it won't be yanked away at the last second. If the world is always out to deny you things, then it's probably best to pretend that you like and want nothing. Just to cover yourself. It's a method that smacks of cowardly-ness, self-denial, and neuroses best handled by a therapist who likes a challenge. But because I have this mindset, I instantly developed a reader-love for Bonamy who appears in  Jacob's Room .  Like most other Virginia Woolf books,  Jacob's Room  doesn't really have a grounded plot. It's more a series of snippets wherein the reader gets to observe a person's somewhat ordinary life. Despite making him the titular character, Woolf cleverly builds Jacob's character through the eyes of the other players in the novel. You never get a clear sense of what is going on in Jacob's head as everything about Jacob is through the eyes of someone else. And the view is not that exciting. Jacob Flanders, as seen by others, is an aimless young man who falls in and out of situations without much drive or passion. He's not terribly smart and he's not terribly attractive and there's nothing about him that would single him out of a crowd. Basically, he's the kind of guy you'd meet and forget pretty quickly.  His best friend is Richard Bonamy, who logically understands the dullness of Jacob and yet feels an overwhelming sense of fondness for him. Like me, Bonamy is pessimistic and generally has a disaffected view of the world. If Bonamy was being honest with himself, he'd embrace the fact that he holds a great deal of affection for Jacob, despite Jacob's ordinary-ness and shout his friendship to Jacob from the rooftops. But like me, his outlook on life tells him that anything he wants will be stripped from him. So he does a fantastic job of repressing any feelings he might have toward Jacob as a friend or otherwise.  The upshot of Bonamy's decision is that his repression does little to soothe his pain when he actually does lose Jacob to the war. In fact, it leaves him emotionally crippled and dumbfounded as to how he should proceed to grieve. The moral of Bonamy's story is that you can put up a damn good show of detaching yourself emotionally, but you never really can.  Of course, Bonamy is a very small part of  Jacob's Room , but I never said this site would be good with general reviews. I'm making this one personal since Bonamy's story teaches me that you can try to protect yourself by swathing your emotions in denial, but it'll hardly help you cushion the blow when the ax falls. And in my cynical mind I take this to be a lesson of "damned if you do. Damned if you don't." Optimistically you can believe that if you're going to be hurt anyway, why lie to yourself about how you feel? Why not shout it from the rooftops about what you love and desire? Why not? But that's an optimistic way of thought.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Today is a good day. Why is it a good day? Because after an arduous month of searching for apartments and being constantly rejected by various landlords for reasons I was never told, I finally got an apartment. It's a nice apartment in an area that I wanted to live and I have laundry in the basement, which makes me practically giggle with joy. The euphoria of having this place almost makes me forget the memories of the last month of hell that I experienced. Which brings me to my review of Ms. Krauss' first novel.        Man Walks Into a Room  is the story of Samson Greene. In one life, Samson was an English professor at Columbia University. He was respected, well-liked by his students and led a happy life with his loving wife, Anne. A brain tumor, however, changes all that. The book begins with Samson getting the growth removed. The procedure, unfortunately, causes him to lose all his memories after the age of 12. He has no recollection of his wife, his job or his life past middle school. Inexplicably, Samson still has the maturity level of a middle-aged man, but he cannot recall anything from his previous adult life.       This novel for me is one of those books that you read and cherish in ways you can barely express. I love talking about it to anyone who shows the vaguest interest and I usually end up feeling incredibly emotional while expounding on the brilliance of Ms. Krauss' writing and observations. I once talked about this book during a date and couldn't stop talking, despite all the usual warning bells going off in my head and my eyes filling with tears. But he did end up reading the book, despite me spoiling most of it and even liked it, so I consider that a triumph.       There is so much simplicity in her style, which works perfectly to relate the kind of naked vulnerability Samson feels through most of the novel. This kind of honesty is never lost, no matter what strange turns the plot makes. At one point, the book nearly goes science fiction as Samson is contacted by a doctor who asks if he could use Samson as a guinea pig for a memory experiment he's been working on. It's a startling change from the first half of the book, which is mainly Samson attempting to piece back his previous life and in some ways, piece back his identity. But again, the writing remains strong, as did my attention to Samson's story.       To be fair, the first half of the novel is much more engrossing and in comparison to the latter half, features much more sublime images. But in a day and age where Dan Brown rules the bestseller list, I'd be pleased with reading a fax machine manual written by Nicole Krauss.   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       If you didn't already know,  Sock  is the first novel by the louder half of the Penn and Teller team. In many ways, the novel is somewhat duller than you what might expect from someone like Penn Jillette. It's a straightforward murder mystery involving a diver for the NYPD who discovers the body of his ex-girlfriend in the drink. He takes it upon himself to find out who killed her and goes about the usual routes of investigation, experiences the usual mid-point crisis where all seems lost before the final denouement. Really, in terms of plot, this novel is pretty by the numbers. The clincher here is that the book is narrated by Dickie, the protagonist's sock monkey.  Okay, just to clarify: yes, a sock monkey. I don't mean a live monkey of some previously unknown sock species. I mean as in a stuffed doll. A toy that the protagonist has had since he was a child. And no, it would not be pertinent to ask the logical questions of "how does the sock monkey see what's going on? Does the diver take him everywhere?" Don't ask such questions. I did and it brought me nothing but grief. You just need to sit back and let the book unfold.  As a narrator, Dickie is pretty entertaining, if a bit long-winded. For an inanimate object, he's very pop culture savvy. Just about every one of his paragraphs end with a line from a song (Random Note: I am SO glad I didn't have to be the one to chase down permissions for these lyrics to be reprinted.) and he references events as recent as Mel Gibson's The Passion of the Christ. Dickie is the kind of bombastic friend whom you like having drinks with, but by the end of the long evening all you want him to do is shut up. A feeling I often had toward Penn Jillette while watching episodes of "Penn and Teller: Bullshit."  What works in Penn's favor is that his choice of narrator feels like a gimmick. A bizarre tactic that has no reason for being there other than to be bizarre. You go through the entire thing, taking for granted why it is Dickie is the one telling us this story. You just assume it's something born of Penn Jillette's weird mind. Well, that's part of it. But there's more. Lots more. The fact that he can fake you out like this is a testament to his talents as a magician, I'm sure.  Overall,  Sock  is definitely an interesting read and you'd probably have some fun playing easter egg hunt with all the pop cultural references. And much like that annoying drinking partner,  Sock  does offer some moments of though-provoking insight. You just might need to drink a little in order to stay focused on reaching those moments.   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        "The Japanese believed in  mono no aware , the essential sadness of things-- that was how they defined their national character-- and it made Lisa even more lonely. But she told herself she was used to loneliness. Besides, she wasn't in Japan to have a good time. She had work to do."    After thinking about this book for nearly two weeks upon completing it, I've yet to really pinpoint why I felt it so compulsively readable. Don Lee is certainly a good writer and the plot is intriguing enough, but I was surprised by how dedicated I was at reading this. There were nights where I was falling asleep at 3am with this book open and all I could think was, "No, don't fall asleep now. Must. Keep. Reading...." I wanted there to be more hours in the day so I could read this book. I went so far as to sneak in a few readings during work when no one was watching me. It was almost becoming fanatical. And yet, what exactly inspired me to do this remains a mystery.   Country of Origin  is Don Lee's first novel. Before this, he put out  Yellow , a collection of short stories that deals with various Asians, half-Asians, immigrants and Asian-Americans. So it's not surprising that the issues of identity and nationality spill all over the novel. Set in 1980, the main plot centers around the disappearance of a young woman named Lisa Countryman. A half-black, half-Japanese graduate student, Lisa traveled to Japan to supposedly do research on her dissertation and soon disappeared. The sparse evidence left behind suggests she fell into the sex trade industry and met with an unfortunate end.  Lisa's case is turned over to Tom Hurley, a lazy, self-absorbed junior diplomat for the US embassy in Japan, who has clearly no interest in pursuing Lisa's whereabouts. Like Lisa, Tom has a split ethnicity (half-white and half-Korean) which he guards by telling people he's Hawaiian. The case is then turned over to a divorced Japanese detective, Kenzo Ota, who hopes this case will turn his faltering career around.  The book interlocks the lives of Lisa, Tom and Kenzo, going back and forth in the timeline. I usually hate this method of storytelling, but was pleasantly surprised by how easily the story flowed. Mr. Lee discusses race, corruption, the government, the sex trade, and most importantly, identity. Do our parents ethnicity determine ours? Do we pledge our allegiance to the country we were born in? Does having a split ethnicity mean we have to choose one and be loyal?  The conclusion of the mystery surrounding Lisa's disappearance was underwhelming. But that wasn't really a problem. The book served more of a way for me to start asking myself the questions above and concentrating not on what happened to Lisa, but the circumstances that brought her to Japan. Overall, the novel pulls you in with a mystery, but holds you with its sharp, prodding observances. I'd recommend this book to anyone who can afford to stay up long nights.   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        "...the castle stayed roving about the hills, and it was learned that it did not belong to the Witch but to Wizard Howl. Wizard Howl was bad enough."      Despite the fact I'm 24, I love children's fantasy books. I covet my copies of Harry Potter and I'm constantly on the search for more books in this genre.  Diana Wynne Jones is a British author who has been around long before JK Rowling was discovered. Ms. Jones at times writes stories with plots of such multi-layer complexities that adults feel the need to re-read portions over and over again. The last book of hers I read,  Hexwood , did such a turnabout on me at the last second that I felt my IQ go down a few points as I tried to untangle what was really going on. Luckily for me,  Howl's Moving Castle  is relatively straightforward.  Sophie Hatter is the eldest of three daughters. Being the oldest means she's born into having no chance of success or seeking her fortune and must contend with just leading her humdrum life, working at her family's appropriate hatshop. Things go a little awry for Sophie when The Witch of the Waste comes into the shop. Unsatisfied by the merchandise available, The Witch turns Sophie into an old woman. Realizing she has to at least try to do something about her situation, Sophie decides to leave her banal life and strike out to find someone to reverse the spell. She sets her eyes on a castle, owned by the notorious Wizard Howl.  Local town gossip has it that the mysterious Howl sucks the souls out of young girls and takes them back to his moving castle in the hills. Now an old woman, Sophie figures she's safe from that danger and considers maybe someone as feared as Howl might actually be able to reverse the spell of someone as equally feared. When she arrives at the castle, however, things are a little bit skewed from what she thought.  As it is with all the books I've read by this author, the plot never fails to entertain me. The book is also peppered with clever items (I liked the TARDIS like concept of Howl's castle), as well as rather funny revelations (I'd have never guessed Howl's true place of origin). The bonus feature of reading this book is that you will then be prepared to watch it when it comes to screen, anime-style:  urlLink Hauru no ugoku shiro    urlLink   . It's going to be directed by the man who brought us "Spirited Away" and "Princess Mononoke" so yes, get excited.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>