<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So the Yanks wound up losing (boo!) but the Marlins won, so I guess I can't be too pissed.&nbsp; Felix Heredia still sucks though.   ****   In other news, I was watching Cold Pizza on ESPN2 this morning and sometimes they have musical acts close out the show.&nbsp; Well today they had Nina Sky (which is actually not a person, but a set of twins whose names are Natalie and Nicole... so I don't get the name but whatever...).&nbsp; They did 2 songs but they interviewed them first.&nbsp; It was kinda funny though, b/c they not only have major NY accents but their voices are kinda deep, which you probably wouldn't expect by looking at them (or from hearing their songs).&nbsp;&nbsp; So I just found that kind of amusing.   ****   Speaking of amusing I have a few new favorite commercials.&nbsp; Right now my number 1 fav is of course a beer commercial (cuz even though&nbsp;I don't drink beer, they always make the best commercials).&nbsp; The one I'm talking about I believe is for Miller and it's one in their series of "great inventions."&nbsp; The invention in this one is the remote control eye twinkle contact lenses.&nbsp; They show a chick in a bar looking at some dude across the room.&nbsp; She puts the twinkle setting to one and he sees it and smiles back, so she increases it to maximum power and all of a sudden it goes berserk and she starts shooting Laser beams out of her eyes ala Superman's heatvision and it keeps blasting people all over the bar while she frantically tries to shut it off.&nbsp; Hysterical stuff.   Fav #2 is the new deodorant commercial with the Asian guy getting attacked by ninja's... insane and stupid but amusing.   and fav #3 I actually JUST saw this morning.&nbsp; I don't even remember what it was for exactly (I think it was for some chocolate-type drink at one of those coffee places).&nbsp; But anyways, it starts off with a guy talking with a major lisp and recounting a story (which they show) of how his wife was making a cake and he wanted to lick the beater... which was still plugged in.&nbsp; Needless to say, it turns on while he's licking it and his tongue gets caught in it.&nbsp; Just the visual of it (and how dumb the guy acted) had me cracking up.   Those are all I can think of at the moment.&nbsp; Anyone else out there have any favorite commercials at the moment?&nbsp; Feel free to share.   ****   Oh and last but not least.&nbsp; I went to Bestbuy yesterday and purchased 2 items.&nbsp; The MTV Spider-Man animated series (which&nbsp;I watched a few episodes of this past weekend on MTV2 and wound up enjoying quite a bit) and then Hard Knocks: The Chris Benoit Story.   The Benoit DVD has a bunch of matches spanning his career including stuff from Japan, ECW, WCW and WWE.&nbsp; Well I decided to pop it in last night before I went to bed to watch the first match, which was actually a very old match from Japan where Benoit as Pegasus Kid (when he had a mask and all) fought Jushin Thunder Liger for the Junior Light-heavyweight title.   The cool thing about the DVD is a lot of matches have alternate commentary.&nbsp; One by Michael Cole and Tazz, the other with Chris Benoit, Dean Malenko and fairly new WWE announcer Todd Grisham.   I decided I wanted to hear what Benoit's group had to say about the match so I listened to the match with that commentary on.&nbsp;   Well I thought Todd Grisham was lame before, but now I realize he is just a DUMBASS!&nbsp; The guy was asking the DUMBEST questions and obviously does not know much about wrestling at all!!&nbsp; And as serious as Benoit and Malenko are, u could hear them at points trying to stifle back laughter (or calling the guy a dumbass) after a bunch of his stupid questions.&nbsp; Someone needs to please tell me how that fool got a job with the WWE?!&nbsp; Cuz if that guy can get one I'd be a shoo-in.    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I wasn't gonna post again until tomorrow most likely, but I just had to vent somewhere.&nbsp; I am currently watching the Yankees-Blue Jays game and Jon Lieber pitched a great game and was taken out in the 8th with 2 outs.&nbsp; But then for some godforsaken reason they put in Felix Heredia to relieve.&nbsp; Now the Yanks were only winning 2-1... why on earth would u put that loser up there to pitch to one of the Blue Jays best hitters???&nbsp; Heredia's numbers are TERRIBLE!  So now the bastard just gave up a huge hit and Sheffield made a rare bad throw and the game is now tied... DAMMIT ALL!&nbsp; And poor Lieber, all that hard work for nada.  Why can't Heredia end up on the DL instead of the rest of the Yankees pitching staff??&nbsp; Cuz for some reason Joe Torre keeps on using the fool, at least if he was on the DL, he wouldn't have that option... uggh, I'm just annoyed.&nbsp; Does this game mean anything?&nbsp; No, not really, but I just spent half my night watching this game and reading comics instead of playing KOTOR, so the Yanks better freakin win.  My only consolation is I just saw that Florida is leading Philly in the 6th, Go MARLINS!&nbsp; (Mind you, if both the Marlins and Yankees lose tonight I'll be even more upset). 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I&nbsp;know I said in my first post that I prob wouldn't update this sucker very much but this thing is more addictive than&nbsp;I first gave it credit for.&nbsp; My first priority is still my journal but this is fun and I can just ramble about anything I wanna share with people that may not come up in conversation.&nbsp; So yeah, expect to hear more from me here.  ****  Turns out the war I expected in Phi Beta didn't happen.&nbsp; Pretty much everybody took my side in it.&nbsp; So that was over pretty quick.&nbsp; I guess it's good no fighting broke out, but in a way I was hoping for it, b/c it would be a good natured battle and it would have been entertaining as well.&nbsp; Maybe next time, heh.  ****  Jordan called today to finalize all plans for the Rolling Rock trip this weekend.&nbsp; So many cool bands are gonna be there like Velvet Revolver, Hoobastank, Disturbed, StainD, N.E.R.D., etc.&nbsp; I can't wait, it's gonna be a lot of fun.&nbsp;   ****  Been following the baseball standings pretty closely lately.&nbsp; The Marlins got back to .500 today, so I'm happy.&nbsp; I know it's gonna be very tough for them to win the division (they have the hardest second half of any team in the league) and I'm honestly not expecting it (even though I'm rooting for them), but I would at least like them to finish over .500, I'd be happy with that.&nbsp;   I'm also rooting on the Chicago White Sox, Oakland A's and Anaheim Angels.&nbsp; Not over the Yankees of course, but just for them to do well and have a good record and have one of those teams win the Wild Card in the AL over Boston.&nbsp; As I stated in a previous post, I'd be quite a giddy bastard if that happened. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I watched Raw last night and it kicked ass... yes the Diva search thing is one of the most mind-numbingly stupid things they've put on Raw recently.&nbsp;&nbsp;Seriously now, the seduce Kamala thing wasn't even more than a slight "heh" on the funny factor the first time they carted his ass out, and it wasn't funny the next EIGHT times (I wish I was exaggerating with that number)&nbsp;either!   Oh and Randy Orton winning the battle Royal pissed me off too... and the prospect of him winning the title at Summerslam scares me, but at least that match was good and had me all up in my seat cheering and praying Jericho would win.   But the suckiness was all washed away by the awesomeness that was Benoit vs HHH for 60 minutes in an Iron Man match.&nbsp; Not enough good can be said about that.&nbsp; And thank God Benoit retained the title.   Oh and the Yanks won too, so that helped ease the pain of losing to the Sox this weekend.   And in unrelated news, it seems I am stirring a bit of $#it (all in good fun though) with my friends in Phi Beta.&nbsp; Actually Graham started it, but I took it to a whole other level.&nbsp; We were arguing about whether Spider-Man 2 was a good movie or not (Graham said it sucked, I articulated and said it was fun but could have been better in some parts and how I didn't like how they set up Green Goblin 2, instead of Venom which&nbsp;I think would be cooler)&nbsp;and oh man did that escalate into a war.   But then when that war finally died down, once again Graham started ranting about the hotness of one tennis star, Maria Sharapova.&nbsp; He started going on about her cute face, but then raved about her ass and sent pics of her from some tennis matches she was in.   And for some reason I couldn't help but respond to his e-mail, agreeing that while she does have a cute face, she had absolutely no ass.   It's like hey, I'm Puerto Rican, we like our women with some booty, just look at who my g/f is! lol ;-)   and I said that in my response, but I just KNOW that this is gonna start another war, but at least I know I'll have Greg on my side for this one, what with his obsession with J-Lo and all, heh.   And let's see anything else to ramble about before I go?&nbsp; Oh yeah, anyone out there with an X-Box should buy Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic.&nbsp; I finally started playing it last week and it kicks much ass.&nbsp; The controls and stuff took a little bit to get used to but now that I have, I love this game... I just can't wait to get my lightsaber (yes, I am such a dork, lol).   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was just reading Online Onslaught- my favorite wrestling website and came across an article talking about how former WWF female wrestler, Chyna was on Howard Stern this week.   One of the items of note that occurred on the talk show was this (and the writer's description of what was said is totally my feeling on the subject.&nbsp; Oh and btw, Sean Waltman for those of you not in the know, is the former X-Pac or to you old school fans the 1-2-3 Kid):    -Admitted to filming a sex tape with Sean Waltman that she might release.&nbsp; I proceed to vomit and and then gouge my eyes out so that I never will see such a terrible crime against humanity.     &nbsp;  Dear God in Heaven... that'd be the SCARIEST thing ever.&nbsp; Sadly even the mention of such an atrocity gives me mental images that chill me to the bone.   Why so scary you ask?&nbsp; Any wrestling fan would know... plus think of this X-Pac plus two words:  Doggy-style.  Yup, I say that qualifies as disturbing... it'd be like a chihuahua humping a pitbull... although for some reason I can't escape the horrid idea of X-pac being the "catcher."&nbsp; Well at least sicko fanboys will have the question they've been wondering about finally answered: "just how big is Chyna's penis?"  Wait "she's been in Playboy, she's obviously a woman" you say?&nbsp; It's called airbrushing, think about that and try to sleep at night.  All I gotta say is that is just SO not cool...     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a fairly laid back weekend which was nice.   I won tix from KROCK to go see the sneak preview of Harold & Kumar Go to White Castle on Friday.&nbsp; This seems to be the summer of dumb movies (Dodgeball, Anchorman, etc), and I love it.   This weekend was also the next series of games between the NY Yankees and Boston Red Sox.&nbsp; So of course I watched as much of them as I could.&nbsp; Sadly Boston won 2 out of 3 (with a heart-breaker on Sat) but while watching these games with Ariana we came to a conclusion... Boston is a team of punks.   Seriously, look at the majority of them!&nbsp; They are all scummy looking dudes!&nbsp; And to make things worse their "better than thou" attitudes make them even more grimy.   But yeah look down the list of them... Pedro... just look at him, that face... uggh, I just wanna smack him.&nbsp; Trash I tell you.   Same with Manny Ramirez and David Ortiz... and what's with the disgustingly dirty batting hats??&nbsp; Wash those damn things u dirty bums!   Wow... I sound pretty hateful right there and I'm not, anyone who knows me, is aware of that... but uggh, they do just bother me.&nbsp; And thing is, this isn't just b/c I'm a Yankee fan, they just seem like scummy guys (not all of them I'm sure but a bunch of them).&nbsp; Even if I wasn't a Yankee fan I'd think this of their team.&nbsp; I pray they don't get to the World Series this year... the Yanks don't have to win it, just as long as Boston doesn't.&nbsp; Those guys don't deserve it.&nbsp; Maybe when they build a team with class it won't bother me so much but until then, they shall earn my ire.   Just watch how I'll laugh if(/when?) they don't even make the playoffs (Go Chi Sox, Oakland and Anaheim!)   Hmm... now I feel I gotta end this on a happier (or at least different) note.&nbsp; Oh yeah, I finally watched Unbreakable again (3 years later) with Ariana and my mom (who were seeing it for the first time).&nbsp; And I still think it was awesome, and now after knowing the ending, I caught a LOT of clues throughout the movie, which was cool.&nbsp; I also watched some of that documentary thing on M. Night Shamalyan and damn... that thing was creepy... and I don't know whether to believe it or not... but I believe it did it's job... I now wanna see The Village.   They can say all they want about Shamalyan being against the documentary and being fake, but I don't believe that this WASN'T some kind of ploy to get people interested in his movie which oh, just so happens to be opening within the next week or so.&nbsp; So yeah whether it was real or not, nice marketing ploy there.&nbsp; Props to you all if that was a work, well done.   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got home not too long ago and immediately turned on ESPN to watch my newest guilty pleasures: Around the Horn and Pardon the Interuption (PTI).   There is just something really fun about watching grown men argue over sports (and even funnier to watch them argue over stuff that's not sports).&nbsp; But it leads me to wonder... how the Hell do u get a job like this???&nbsp;   I mean seriously, they are getting paid to go on TV and argue over sports (in a friendly competition).&nbsp; I want that job!&nbsp; I can ramble on about sports and other random current events!&nbsp; Lucky bastards...   In other news, to no one's pleasure (except horny teenagers who prob have no access to porn) Catwoman opens tomorrow.   I urge you all to boycott this movie.&nbsp; It looks absolutely terrible.&nbsp; Plus I'm a comic fan and this isn't even the Catwoman from the Batman comics, the costume is terrible, the acting looks bad and even the special effects look totally lame.   Even the Daily News had the right idea.&nbsp; This is off the blurb for their review of the movie:  "Halle Berry needs to take out her Oscar every morning and swear to it that she will not accept any more demeaning, stupid roles. Unfortunately, it's too late to do anything about "Catwoman," which litters the nation's screens beginning at midnight tonight"   Just to show you how much I'm against this movie... I have a free ticket to it which I got when I bought the Batman: The Animated Series Vol. 1 DVD and I STILL would refuse to go.&nbsp; 'Nuff Said.   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know how often I'm gonna post stuff here... I already have a journal thingie (which I fall behind on all the time).&nbsp; I basically just signed up so I could respond to other people's stuff- (specifically Henry's Shot @ Greatness).   But I do have one funny thing to share...   Last night I went to the Yankee-Blue Jays game.&nbsp; And while there the topic of our pornstar names came up (I believe we were discussing I Love the 90's and how they mentioned it).&nbsp;   Well Ariana's wound up being "Dream Morris" which is pretty good, but nothing compared to mine, which was:   Buddy Dewitt.   Go ahead,&nbsp;say that outloud and tell me that isn't one of the greatest pornstar names ever, hehe.&nbsp; [Here's a hint for any slow people out there: pronounce the last name with "dew" instead of "de"]   
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Family Guy is back on Fox!  They're starting it off with a marathon of older episodes tonight before the new ones start this season.  To celebrate, here are some of my favorite quotes from the show:  Peter Griffin: Brian, there's a message in my Alpha Bits.  It says 'OOO'! Brian Griffin: Peter, those are Cheerios.  [Brian and Peter are putting a crib together.] Brian: Okay, insert rod support A into slot B. Peter: That's what... Brian: If you say "that's what she said" one more time, I am gonna pop you.  Stewie: Did you forge my name? How dare you! Is this backwards "S" supposed to be cute? I'm going to crap double for you tonight.  Peter: ...Lois comes up to me wanting to know if she can get a job, and I was like: "I got a job for you right here" [points at his crotch]... this zipper's been broken for weeks, I've had to use a safety pin.  Teacher: In French, to say yes you say oui-oui. [Peter starts laughing] Peter: Oh, man, that's hysterical. (keeps laughing) Hey, what do you say for no, doo-doo? (laughs) Hey, I'll be right back. I've got to go take a wicked yes. [I love that one... I've used it many times before, heh]  Want more?  Check out   urlLink this website     full of the best Family Guy quotes. 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been over a week since I posted here. That'd be because I was on vacation and too busy doing other things to waste my time entertaining you people (heh, j/k).  But yeah my vacation was fun, I didn't go anywhere but I did a lot of fun stuff. Me and Ariana went to Six Flags on Tuesday to celebrate our hangout from 2 years ago and I got to go on the Superman ride (which I wasn't able to get to last year), so that was cool.  On Wed we finally took advantage of "Wacky Wednesday" at the arcade in New Roc City. Basically you pay $20 and you get unlimited use of pretty much everything (including Lazer Tag, the Virtual Rollercoaster, etc) for any 4 hours from 4-10pm. There is also a deal where u can pay $10 for 8-10pm. It was tons of fun, and I have never played so many arcade games in my life, heh. It's something I'd definitely like to do again with a group.  But the main highlight of last week (the 12th to be exact) was me and Ariana's 2 year anniversary. I took her to this awesome Japanese restuarant called Asahi (it's on 48th bet 8th and 9th ave, I HIGHLY recomend it) and then we went to go see Avenue Q on Broadway.  That show was freakin HYSTERICAL. Tix are a bit hard to get (I had mine for a few months now) but if you can somehow get your hands on some, it's definitely worth it.  We bought the soundtrack to it also as we left and even though we've only listened to it once, we were already able to sing along. Fun stuff.  ****  Oh I also forgot to mention that the Friday before, me and Ariana went to go see Metallica: Some Kind of Monster. It was an interesting look at the lives of the guys in the bands. Any fan of Metallica should go see it, they'd definitely get a kick out of it.  What made that night better though was that later on after we met up with Henry and John around St. Marks we went to this Sakebar over on, I wanna say 9th street (I may be off ask me later if u are interested)- called Decibel. They've got some great food there including Skewered Chicken mixed with vegetables. I forget the name they had for it there (obviously it's in Japanese) but it was good stuff and our main reason for heading over there. And though I run the risk of me sounding like a complete schill these past few paragraphs I must also say this is another place everyone should check out.  **** Other than the Metallica documentary I wound up seeing like 3 other movies this vacation. I saw I,Robot which was "ehh" but i saw it for free so I can't complain, Collateral which was better than I would have given it credit for, but it was still lacking in certain areas (one of those being it was way longer than it had any right to be), and finally Sat night I went with a crew to go see The Village.  Now that movie SUCKED. I've seen and liked all the previous Shamalyan movies (especially Unbreakable) but this was just bad. The only part of this movie I enjoyed was the fact that I guessed the "surprise twist" like barely 30-40 minutes into the movie. Thing is it wasn't that big of a twist and also kinda took away from the enjoyment of the movie b/c it took away all the suspense of the movie for me, but hey, at least I guessed it and was damn proud of myself for it.  I did get some very good movie watching in despite the stuff in the theaters when me and Ariana spent one night in and watched both Kill Bill Vol 1 &amp; 2 back to back. Now those are some quality flicks, heh.  ****  Watched Summerslam at Phil's on Sunday night. It was a pretty good show, but they let freakin Randy Orton win the damn title. My hate for Randy Orton has been notoriously on record amongst my friends who watch wrestling, so you KNOW I wasn't happy about that.  Last night on Raw helped make up for it though when Chris Benoit went into Crippler mode and beat the snot out of Orton for like 25 minutes and was looking like the Benoit from the mid-late 90's through that whole match. He still wound up losing (D'oh!) but at least it was in a better way than the night before. So I'm satisfied at the moment, but I hope they do something cool with the direction of the show.  I also found out that both Smackdown (a PPV) and Raw will be coming to NY in October, so I'm looking forward to trying to go to at least one of those shows. Anyone else down?  ****  I leave this post with one quote I found amusing and a paraphrase of a bit I saw a comic do on Last Comic Standing this weekend.  "And dissenting views may kindly report to my ass for kissing duty."- The Rick  "...Kerry has the election in the bag. He's married to Theresa Heinz. Kerry just has to do ONE thing to win this election. He doesn't even have to campaign. All he's gotta do, is one day before the election, go on TV and say 'Vote for me... or I take away the ketchup!"- Kathleen Madigan (and Hell yes I agree. Kerry should win anyways, but this would make it a lock, hell even Republicans need their ketchup). 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is something a friend of my sister wrote and sent to her (actually it might have even been in his AOL or AIM profile).  It's kinda old but I just ran across it recently and was lmao.  I just felt I had to share this b/c it applies to me so well.  That and I think you all would enjoy it.  FUSSY EATER:  When I was a kid I was a, Fussy eater. Thats what they called it at our house.  "Hes a fussy eater."  "Fussy eater" is a euphemism for "big pain in the ass."  They'd trot out some food and I'd say,"I don’t like that."  "Why?"  "I dont know.  I know I don’t like it.  And I know if I ate it I would like it even less."  "Well, I like it. Mmmmmm! Yum yum!"  "Hey, Ma. You like it?  YOU EAT IT!"  Sometimes they would try to corner me with logic: "Well, how do you know you don’t like it, if you’ve never even tried it?"  "It came to me in a dream." Big pain in the ass.  Some things I didnt like cause the way they sounded.  "Don’t sound right to me, Ma. Say that again?"  "Asparagus."  "No, I don’t like that." Imagine. I got away with that for eight or nine years.  To this day, there are still some things I wont eat becuase of how they sound. Yogurt sounds disgusting. I cant eat anything that has both a "y" and a "g" in it. Squash is also badly named.  "You want some squash?" Sounds like someone sat on dinner.  "How would you like a nice tongue sandwich? Its made from slives of cow's tongue."  "Hey, Ma, are you fuckin tryin to make me sick?"  On the other hand there were some foods I didnt like because of how they looked. That seems a bit more rational.  "I don’t like that! It don’t look right to me. Did you cook that, Ma? Yeah? Is there a picture of it in the cookbook? I’ll bet it dont look like that."  Of course, some people will eat anything, no matter how it looks. I saw guys like that on the chow line in high school.  "Hi, boys! Whaddaya got? I’ll eat anything. What’s that called? Nevermind, gimme a whole bunch of it."  "Its rats asshole, Don."  "Well, it sure makes a hell of a fondue."  Not me. I dont eat anything I dont recognize immediately. If I have to ask questions, I pass. Im not at dinner to make inquiries. Gimme something I recognize. Like a carrot. I know I can trust a carrot. Now there are some foods that even though I know what they are, I still dont like their looks. Tomatoes, for instance. My main problem with tomatoes is that they dont look as though they are fully developed. They look like theyre still in the larval stage; thousands of little tiny seeds and a whole lot of jelly lookin slime. "Get if off my plate!" Its like that stuff at the end of an egg.  Of course I know its not the end of an egg....its the beginning of a chicken!! "ITS HEN CUM!!! EEEAAAAAAAGGGGHHH! GET IT OFF MY PLATE!" 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Grr...  I found out that Alter Bridge (basically Creed with a new singer) was coming to Irving Plaza in Oct (I believed I mentioned this in the last post).  I joined their mailing list and thus got a password for ultra pre-sale tix which started yesterday at 1pm.  Sadly the thing sold out in like 4 minutes and I wasn't able to get any.  So that sucked...  But then I come in this morning with another e-mail from them (which must've been sent yesterday after I left work) all like "we've decided to add ANOTHER presale for Irving b/c that one sold out in 4 minutes.  It will be Thurs morning at 10am."  I looked at my watch...  10:24am  DAMMIT!!  I tried to get tix, but that was all in vain and I knew it from the start.  So yeah that sucked and now my only real chance is to get tix during the regular sale tomorrow, BUT I already have plans.  First I gotta go fight some stupid parking ticket I got, and then after that me and Ariana were supposed to go to the city to go see Metallica: Some Kind of Monster.  So I'm not gonna kill my day just trying to get tix for that show.  Maybe I'll luck out and can go directly to the box office though, we'll see.  Keeping my fingers crossed again.  ****  On to happier news.   I went to the Yankees-A's game last night with the usual crew of Ariana, Christina and Rodrigo.  It was a great game.  Loaiza didn't pitch that well and the Yanks were trailing almost the whole game.  But in the bottom of the 9th with the Yanks down 6-4, Sheffield hit a homer to tie it up 6-6.  They couldn't get another run that inning though, so that meant- Free Baseball!!   Yeah, the game wound up going to the 11th with major scares from Mariano Rivera who let the bases get loaded with 1 out at one point, but he escaped that, thank god.  And the Yanks pulled through and won it with a 2-run walk-off homerun by A-Rod.  The crowd went nuts, and we all went home very happy.  ****  In unrelated news, some of you have probably heard of this by now but I was just informed of this by Alan on Tues when we went for lunch.  Apparently Trey Parker and Matt Stone are making a new feature film called Team America.  Basically it's a movie that bashes Bush, Kerry, Michael Moore, the situation in Iraq, terrorists, everything, in true Parker and Stone fashion.  Oh and did I mention the whole movie is done with puppets?  String puppets mind you.  Do yourself a favor and read this  urlLink review .  And then check out the trailer for the movie  urlLink here .  It's quite a laugh.  I for one can't wait to see it. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh man, I was just doing some paperwork here at the office- which consists of me filing away the applications students fill out to join the program in folders and I just ran across one name that I couldn't believe. There is some poor child out there named- Mathew Mathew.  It's like I've heard of lazy names in the world before (ie. John Johnson, Tom Thompson, even a fellow Fordham alum named Stephanie Stephens who people called Ditto) but this is just SEVERE laziness/unoriginality.  I just had to share that...  **** Speaking of stuff to share, websites are finally reporting on the whole Disturbed vs Finch fiasco from Rolling Rock. You can read the article from MTV.com right  urlLink here.   I'd also check the Disturbed website and their message board and diary logs for a bit more info. I'm more inclined to believe Disturbed's side of the story. But you can all decide for youself.  ****  Going to the Yankee game tonight. It's against the A's (who kicked the Yanks asses last night). It's also the Yankee debut of Esteban Loaiza who'll be pitching tonight. Every other major pitcher that got traded recently had good first outtings for their new team, let's hope that stays the same for Loaiza.  ****  Lastly, the KOTOR game is a lot harder than any other RPG I've played in a long time, even with a strategy guide. Hell last night I'm walking along and the guide is nonchalantly all like "Kill the Mandalorians ahead, and approach the speeder." So I'm like "ok, sounds easy enough... But it neglected to mention that there were SIX of them all armed to the teeth (including one with 2 lightsabers) who killed my ass in like 2 seconds.  Even once I knew what to expect and armed myself properly I got killed about 5-6 more times before finally beating them. That NEVER happens to me in RPG's. I guess that's a good thing, it makes it more challenging but damn, it gets pretty crazy at times.  Oh and I earned yet ANOTHER lightsaber, giving me the option to put on in each hand and be all badass. So I'm quite happy about that.  ****  Another thing I'm happy about- tix for the Alter Bridge concert at Irving in October go on internet presale in a few minutes. Crossing my fingers in hopes of getting some. Wish me luck! 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend I was away along with Ariana, Jordan, Gaetano and Goombah for a road trip out to Latrobe, PA for the Rolling Rock Town Fair 5. It was a huge 7 hour drive, but thank the good Lord that Jordan is awesome and had a portable DVD player, and so we wound up watching a bunch of movies during the whole ride there which made the trip seem to go by sooo much faster.  We wound up watching South Park the movie (which had us all singing along), Gone in 60 Seconds (which with the great stereo system Jordan has in his car, we could all feel the engines roaring and the fact that Jordan was practically matching the crazy speeds they were going in the movie, made for an interesting experience), the Dane Cook DVD of his unedited Comedy Central special (which was hysterical) and finally Old School, which is one of our generations greatest comedy's and of course had us laughing our asses off as we all quoted it like crazy throughout the movie.  Once we got to our hotel in Latrobe, we settled in and then headed out to a bar recomended to us by the hotel clerk.  We immediately made friends with the female bartender (even buying her and her sister like 2-3 shots) and everything was sooo cheap. It was funny, at one point the girl was all like "You're bill is getting pretty high, are you guys ok with that?" We asked her "What exactly is high?" She’s like "It’s about $96 at the moment" and we all laughed.  In the end the total bill came out to like $102.50 but for ALL the stuff we ordered it was a steal. Between all of us, we had home-made potato chips, mozzarella sticks, chicken fingers, 3 buckets of beer (six 7oz beers in each), 16 shots, about 3 bacardi type fruit drinks, and like about 4-5 regular beers (and maybe more but I can't remember at the moment).  Now in the city, getting all that would have been like $200-250, EASY. So we made out like bandits. We wound up giving her a great tip and we basically made a friend at that bar, and promised we would be back the next day (which I'm sure she was looking forward to). Those people now know New Yorkers are awesome tippers. We walked out of the bar all like ‘We would OWN this town if we stayed longer, heh." So that was cool.  ****  There is so much to say about the Rolling Rock Town Fair, both good and bad. I will start off with the bad (although it wasn't terrible and we got over those events quickly) and then move onto the good (which far outweighed the sucky parts).  The first annoying thing was that for the most part it freakin rained ALL day long until 5-6pm (and mind you the show was from about 10am-9pm), only stopping for moments at a time. But it was pretty much at least a light steady rain throughout the whole day, which made the fairgrounds ultra muddy (thank god the bleachers on the side of the stage had a covering, so that was a nice refuge) and also the mud provided us entertainment as we watched the insane people slide down this huge mudhill towards the stage (during the earlier parts of the show, more people were watching them and the mud wrestlers than the opening more unknown bands).  The second annoying part really got to me though...  Basically, we got to some seats in the bleachers and this chick is behind us chain-smoking like crazy and it was kind of annoying but whatever, nothing we could really do about it. Then this dude (prob her boyfriend) and his buddy come in (2 huge ass almost biker looking guys) and sit with her and THEY start puffing away. Thing is there was a little bit of a breeze so the smoke was blowing right in Ariana’s face and some ashes were getting on her. So she turned around to the girl and asked if she could point the cigarette away from her.  The girl didn’t say anything but immediately her boyfriend was all like "turn around" in a dismissive and derogatory manner. I didn’t hear it (I had earplugs in at the moment) but Ariana told me about it. The 2 guys were really too big for me to do anything about it though (not to mention it was a compromising position being at on metal bleachers and all), and at the moment, it was just us b/c Jordan, Goombah and Gaetano split off from us to walk around a bit.  But Ariana kept making comments to me about the smoking that were loud enough for the people to hear and at this point I had taken my earplugs out. And well the guy behind us said something about her bitching over nothing, and Ariana turned around and started yelling stuff like ‘Yeah I’m bitching about it b/c you’re blowing f***ing smoke in my face"  And then things just got ugly... a yelling/cursing match ensued, and I tried to keep the peace but the boyfriend was being an absolute dick. Ariana wasn’t even talking to him and both of us were trying to say that we were just trying to ask the girl nicely to point the cigarette away. But they were having none of it. The guy even was all like "you better shut up bitch or I’ll punch your boyfriend right here in the face." That had it for me, since we weren’t even trying to deal with him. More cursing ensued and at this point everyone was watching us (including security, which pathetically just asked if we would all calm down) and I was trying to convince Ariana quietly we should just move b/c it wasn’t worth it staying there. But the dicks were all wanting us to leave, so it was almost as if we were losing by leaving, which we didn’t wanna make it seem like, but in the end it wouldn’t have been worth it to stay. So we left, after some more cursing and moved a section over. But omg, we were just FUMING.  I had so many things in my head I wanted to say to those assholes. I’m normally not very good with coming up with comebacks and insults but I had a few good ones that came to me immediately lined up in my head but it took all I had not to say them b/c like I said the 2 dudes were way bigger than me, and also, we had to climb down these bleacher things right in front of them, so if I said what I was gonna say they could have easily just barely pushed us and we would have fallen and hurt ourselves pretty bad, so I kept it inside, but OMG did I wanna get them.  So I will vent what I would have said here, just b/c this is my blog and I can...  At one point the guy turned to Ariana and was like "Is this your first concert?!?! It must be b/c you don’t seem to know anything! We can f**king smoke all we like"  The immediate retort in my mind was "Dick, this isn’t her first concert, but even if it was that would still be more concerts than the amount of times you’ve had sex in your life... with women at least. By the way you and your boyfriend there make a cute couple. You totally have to be the catcher b/c you must’ve had something up your ass this morning to make you such a bitch."  In retrospect, it’s better I didn’t say that, cuz obviously that would have eroded into fisticuffs seeing as how irritable these guys seemed from the get-go, and that would not have been cool (although if the other guys in my group were with me, I prob totally would have said it, b/c we would have outnumbered them but alas, that was not the case).  So we moved and we calmed down. As I said before, it wasn’t worth it to start anything, cuz if we had we could have been ejected and that would have been a waste.  So yeah, as nice as I am, there are just a few things someone can do or say to me to make me explode, that was one of those things...  ****  Our fight seemed to trigger things on stage though, b/c as Finger Eleven was finishing and the stage was rotating for Finch to start their set, all of a sudden as the stage is still spinning the whole crowd could see a bunch of guys BRAWLING on stage. They’re on the floor and wailing on each other and crap. More guys jump in and at first the crowd didn’t know whether to think it was fake or what, but then security rushed the stage, but it was insane. We were able to tell that one of the bands involved was Finch, but we couldn’t make out who the other dudes were. But we saw one of the guys in Finch pick up a bass guitar and start hitting other dudes with it, but then he got taken down and it was just crazy, the crowd was going wild cheering. It was great.  But anyways, as Finch finished and left the stage, at this point we were in the bleachers and from that area we had a view of the side of the stage as well as to stuff from behind the stage. Well as soon as Finch left the stage ANOTHER huge ass brawl broke out, that only some of us up above could really see. But it was like 20+ guys just beating on each other, it was crazy. Eventually the fight moved behind a tour bus so we couldn’t see what was happening but we saw a bunch of security people running over there. So yeah that was totally amusing.  ****  Now for the better news. All in all, despite the fact of the rain and the annoyance of running into a few assholes at the show, the day was great. All the bands put on great performances, it especially kicked into high gear once Hoobastank came out and did a rocking 45 minute set of all their big hits and it just kept going from there. It was also very amusing to watch the mudpeople throughout the day.  As for a list of all the bands that played (in the order they performed too) here it is:  The Feds (a local act that won some contest to open the show) Thornley Three Days Grace Finger Eleven Finch Sevendust Hoobastank Crystal Method N.E.R.D. Disturbed StainD Velvet Revolver  Each band played from anywhere to 30 mins (for the early bands), 45 mins (for the middle bands) and an hour (for the last 3 bands). ****  Oh and we found out midway through the day that the band Finch was brawling with was actually Disturbed. The announcer hosting the event got on the mic and was all like "Well we can't NOT address what happened before, so for those of you keeping score, let's just say Disturbed 1, Finch 0"  Later on when Disturbed came out for their set, David Draiman (the lead singer) discussed the events in typical Draiman style (with lots of anger and even more profanity, heh). He was all like ‘We’ll beat your asses if u try messing with us again. We don’t care about jail, we’ll beat your asses send u to jail and when you get out, we’ll be waiting and beat the f**k out of you again and again and again. F**k Finch! F**k them right in the eye!!" It was awesome. I couldn’t wait to see how this would play out on music news and each bands respective message boards, heh.  As for Disturbed's set, it was the best of the day in my opinion, they totally got everyone in the crowd going which was awesome.  ****  We wound up leaving as Velvet Revolver was about to finish up their set. I was happy to hear them play "Fall to Pieces" and they also did some STP and GNR covers by performing "Mr. Brownstone" and "Sex Type Thing" which was very cool.  ****  Oh one very funny thing... as we were exiting the fairgrounds there was a group of 4 girls ahead of us. They were very butch looking girls. They were all super short (the tallest was prob only like 5'2), had short butch haircuts (one even had a mohawk), were all very overweight, and were caked head to toe in mud. As they passed the State Trooper at the main gate, he goes all like "We got us a group of trolls here!"  RIGHT IN FRONT OF THE GIRLS! It was hysterical, b/c he basically just said outloud what everyone around them was thinking. It was just funny that it came from the State Trooper. Me, Ariana and Jordan also said they could pass for Hobbits too (since some were barefoot at the moment too).  ****  And that was pretty much the day at Rolling Rock summed up very quickly (a lot more happened- like us going back to that bar and getting another great deal, but it's just too much to type, I think I got in the main points though).  Here are some fun quotes from the the trip that I just have put in for the crew though:  "Dude (to Jordan) I think we're lost."- Us (as we were trying to find the hotel from the concert) "Nah, dude I remember this!"- Jordan (his response to every single road we were on... except EVERYTHING looked the same!  lol) "It's ok, Keep driving!! All roads lead to Rome!"- Gaetano  "What fer you driving a cop car out here?" And "That’s the only kinda car I like to see stuck, a cop car... hyuck." - by some local Hicks who helped us get our car out of some mud in the parking lot.  **** The trip back was good too. We watched more movies (finished watching Old School, then watched Road Trip, Office Space and Half-Baked).  It was great, during the part in Road Trip where they were in the school bus listening to Twisted Sister headbanging away and going nuts, we did the same in Jordan’s car (I even mimicked Seann William Scott’s crotch thrusting thing which had everyone in the car cracking up). Oh and mind you, Jordan decided to speed the car up at this point to 115 mph for that segment, which made it even more fun.  So yeah, all in all it was a really fun trip. I think a great time was had by all. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to the Rolling Rock town fair this past weekend and started to write a blog to post here, but it's running a bit long, so I'll just finish it up later and post it tomorrow.  In the meantime though, I have to mention that this past Saturday was the 2 year anniversary of the time me and Ariana went to Great Adventure together and started our whole relationship.  So Happy Semi-Anniversary to us!  Today is also the 2 year anniversary of me getting my new car (Happy Birthday!) AND the whole me and Ariana going out on "not a date at first but sure seemed like a date by the end" night, which also featured Jordan leaving the bar with TWO chicks, and leaving poor Matt to go home with his tail between his legs, heh (sorry Matt!)  ****  And omg, I have to mention that I JUST finished eating some pizza my mom made for dinner.  This wasn't just any pizza though.  Usually she makes regular or pepperoni, and lately she's been experimenting with Chicken.  But today she made prob one of the greatest tasting pizzas... nay, one of the greatest tasting FOODs ever.  It was garlic chicken and pineapple pizza.  I wasn't very enthusiastic about it when she told me what was on it, but damn, once I started eating it, it was just sooo freakin good.  Like wanna lick the plate clean good, heh.  I just kept thinking of that line by Will Ferrell in Old School: "It's just so good when it hits your lips..."  Congratulations to my mom the chef!  ****  Oh, I guess I should also mention stuff about all the baseball trades that happened (and did not happen) this weekend.  First off, sadly the Yanks did not get Randy Johnson (although I honestly wasn't expecting it), but they traded Jose Contreras to the White Sox for Esteban Loaiza.  I don't know what to think of that trade yet.  Contreras was good against average teams but sucked against good teams like Boston (who owned his ass).  He had more and better stuff than Loaiza though.  However, Loiza does have better control.  So we'll see what happens.  [And oh how I wish they were able to tack Heredia into that trade just to be rid of him...]  But in the end, the Yanks did crap.  They're not in much of a better position than they were last week, so now we just gotta pray Brown and Mussina come back nice and healthy and stay that way.  However on the other side of the spectrum the Marlins made some awesome trades!  They got an All-Star catcher in Paul Lo Duca (who can really help the Marlins young pitching staff) and a great middle reliever in Mota (to set up Benitez) and all they had to trade was their 5th starter (Penny) and Hee Sop Choi.  But while it's sad to see them go, they got so much more in return.  They also replaced Penny with a guy from the Padres who is pretty good, so I think they are set.  The Dodgers basically just handed the NL East to the Marlins (for God knows what reason but I'm not complaining).  So lookout Braves, here we come!  ****  Oh and in other good news, I didn't get to mention before but I finally earned my lightsaber in KOTOR (it's Blue!).  So yeah, just had to share that. 
    
</post>


</Blog>