<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm also a liar. I'm not a poet. But a certain website has decided to deem me as one.     &nbsp;  About 3 weeks ago, I was really bored at work and not feeling motivated to do anything productive. I was searching online for anything interesting enough to keep me awake when I saw something about taking a quiz to test my Poetry IQ. I thought, "yeah, this should be good." I haven't studied poetry since high school, and even then, I only crammed information the night before the test so that I could forget it immediately after its completion (I was preparing myself for college). I took the quiz, which was slightly difficult but easy to guess a few answers. At the end of it, it asks you to place a poem you've written in a box. Some people&nbsp;who work for the company would analyze the poem and send you something in the mail letting you know if you might be eligible for a prize. They might even publish your work in one of their books. I had come that far in the quiz, and wanted to know what my Poetry IQ was, so decided to wing it. I haven't written a poem since my senior year in high school, when I was forced to do some horrible poetry project. Anyhow, the poem totally sucks, but these people sent me something in the mail saying I'm a semi-finalist in their competition, to be completed in August. I could win $1000! Yeah right. Anyhow, they are also publishing my piece of crap "artistic vision" in a book of poems they are releasing in the Fall. Lucky me, as one of the poets in the book, I can pre-order the book for only.... drum roll please... $49.95 plus shipping and handling. This is $20 off the publisher's listing! Lucky me. I only have to pay $50 something dollars to see my poem printed in a book. I did some searching online, based on past books they have published, and was not able to find any of their books on sale anywhere except on their own website. That leads me to believe that the only people who buy the books are the poets, who are falling for this.     &nbsp;  So hence, I am not really a poet, but will have my poem published in a book that will make the publisher a lot of money - not from the credentials of the book or by poetry enthusiasts, but by the amateurs who are tricked into believing that they have a newfound talent. If you are curious, go to poetry.com and search for a poet named Sabrina Jumper. The poem is called "Painter". There's a typo/bad grammar thing in there which I didn't catch until after they put it on their website. Just had to point out that even though I'm not a great poet, I do know grammar and have caught my own mistake. :)   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So this is my first blog ever. I guess it would be appropriate to reveal a bit about myself before I move on to more posts. Here's what you need to know.   1. I'm a blonde with a BA. I have a great bit of common sense, and know a few things about a lot of things, most of which are completely and utterly useless. But sometimes I'll slip out a comment which is completely ridiculous and stupid. I like to blame my hair color for these moments.   2. I'm a smart ass. You must accept this before we can move on and be friends (or anything else).   3. My family means the world to me. Only I am allowed to make fun of them. And I will.   4. I like silly people who do silly things. When I re-tell such stories, I will change the names of all involved. If you know someone with that name, please assume I'm speaking of someone else, move on with your life and spread no rumors.   But most of all, know that I'm not using this blog so that friends can keep up with the happenings in my life (although I might reveal the URL to a few of them). I'm mostly using the blog to get all of my stupid/silly/nonsense/useless/weird thoughts out of my head so that I do not accidentally spill them out in person and embarrass myself or force anyone to listen to my ramblings.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If there were a contest, I'd win this one. No doubt about it. Hands down, I'm the biggest jerk alive. Or even dead. I beat them all at this contest.  Have you seen  My Best Friends Wedding  with Julia Roberts (as Julianne Potter)? There's a part in there after she tells her best friend that she loves him, almost ruining his wedding-to-be. She gets down on her knees, begging for forgiveness:   urlLink Julianne Potter : I'm pond scum. Well, lower actually. I'm like the fungus that feeds on pond scum.  urlLink Michael O'Neill : Lower. The pus that infects the mucus that cruds up the fungus that feeds on the pond scum. On the other hand, thank you for loving me that much, that way. It's pretty flattering.  urlLink Julianne Potter : Except it makes me fungus.  I feel like whatever that terrible thing is that makes pus... pus. There's a girl here at the office... let's say her name is Tara. Although I don't know her very well, I think she's really nice and like her a lot. Some people on her team at work do not share those feelings for her. To back track a bit, Saturday night I went out with a group of friends to celebrate Kate's birthday (a girl on Tara's team). It was a surprise party for her. We met at Saba, and then went downtown later. I called my friend Tina (another girl at work), who does not know the situation with Tara and the rest of her team, and invited her to meet us out. She did, and we had a great time.  So this morning, Tara and Tina were talking in the hallway when I walked by. I stopped to say hi and chat for a bit. Tina asked me in front of Tara where we went after Tina left us Saturday night. Tara made the comment that it sounded like a lot of people from work went to all the same places Saturday night. I tried to shrug it off. "I guess it's the place to be," I said, shrugging my shoulders. I knew then that she must not have been invited to the party. I walked away feeling really bad that we talked about it in front of her, probably making her feel really left out.  I got back to my desk a while later, and decided to message Tina about it (a lot of us have MSN messenger at work). This is how the message went:  Sabs says: i felt really bad when we mentioned saturday night in front of tara... i like her a lot, but some of the people on the team don't really like hanging out with her... i don't think anyone invited her...  Sabs says: on her team, that is..  Tara says: hmmm....  Sabs says: shit.....  Sabs says: i thought i was im'ing tina  Sabs says: i don't know what to say...  Sabs says: i'm so sorry...........................  I don't know what happened.... I meant to click on Tina's name and send her a message. I must have accidentally hit Tara's name, since I was thinking about the situation with her at the time. Tara and I talked it out over MSN, but I think she's really hurt. She told me not to worry about it (she knew I felt terrible... I must have told her a thousand times within 10 minutes), but said that she needed to figure out what she did wrong. I went ahead and told a couple of people on their team what I did so that they'd be prepared... Between loud sobbing and tearful gushes, that is. I feel bad because not only did I make a nice, innocent girl feel really, really rotten, but also because now I know things on their team is going to be very akward for a while. I don't think the people on her team are very happy with me, understandably, but they seem to at least understand that it was an honest (although stupid) mistake. I really feel sick to my stomach. I can't imagine how Tara must feel right now... I mean, I've been around people who I knew didn't like me before, even though there was nothing I had ever done to them which would encourage that (not that I know of, anyway). But I've never had anyone  confirm  these suspicions I've had. And the other people on my team are friends of mine. Even though they probably will forgive me, or already have, they must feel betrayed. I don't want them to ever mistake me for the kind of person they have to tip-toe around, with the need to be careful about what they say when they're around me. I've never hated myself as much as I do now.  If the wrong people find this and read it later, I'm sorry. At least all names but my own were made up. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>