<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, this is my first post (in case it isn't obvious) and I am pondering.&nbsp; I will have this, but I hope no one expects a lot out of it, because it is very easy for me to forget about it.&nbsp; I just got back from Summer camp and Yearbook camp, and am happy I will be home now, because I am tired of not being here.&nbsp; I have a lot of good friends, and if they ever get annoyed by me, I wish they would tell me, so I can help fix it.&nbsp;   Yearbook this year is going to have its ins and outs. Yearbook camp was the first time everyone was together, and there was already "drama" brewing.&nbsp; There was also love with some people (at least two guys that i know of, I dont know if the girls felt the same way though).&nbsp;   When stuff happens, I will try to put it here!  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       School is once again in session, and this year I am a senior. Today went by quite quickly, and that makes me happy. If anything, I will have at least 1 hard class, and when I say hard, I MEAN HARD. My college biology class seems like it is going to be the death of me. I have three books (right now, more will come later) for the class, and all three of them are over 500 pages... they are HUGE books. Get this, it is an actual college class, not an AP class, but we were told passing the class would only give you college ELECTIVE credit, and in order to get the college biology credit, you have to take the AP test and pass it. Also, in order to teach a college class you must have at least your Masters, in order to teach the AP class, you only need your bathclor degree. So this makes mo sense to me, but I will just try my hardest! Economics was pretty intersting and I think I will have fun. Yearbook for two periods, that will be ok too. So we will see what happens now.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, I am so tired. I really have no idea why I am so tired.  I have been doing so much lately, I feel like I havent stopped. I have been doing anything Mrs. Felton asks me to do, which happens to be a lot. It is driving me nuts, I dont want to do all of her dirty work. Then, my eagle ceremony is sunday, and there has been so much to do for it. One night, I stayed up until midnight, making the scripts. I sure hope everyone shows up, because if they dont, first, I will be disappointed, but there will also be WAY too much left over food. We will see what happens.  This school year is going to be so much fun. After years in the past, I have REAL friends this year, and cant wait to spend 180 LONG days with them.  I have decided that I want to go to UCF. It has a good Journalism program, and that is definatly somthing I want to do. It looks like a good school, and I am very excited.  I am obsessed with Reality Television, so, in order for me to continue posting on here, I will write postings, talking about what happened on all of the shows I watch.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>