<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No, in short I am not.  In fact, I have no fear of being labelled any of the above (with or without singular indicators).    Since no labels exist above, let's forget about the whole thing shall we?  It is conference time at TACF, a place blessed wonderfully by God.  In fact, my sister an I are getting along quite well after 8 years here and if you had asked, no, I don't think that would have been possible without Divine Intervention.  But then there is the issue of work.  It has been too long of course, and really, you'd have to be daft to not realize it is your time to go (leave that is).  I feel it in my fingers, I feel it in my toes.  Or is it bones?  No, really, I am not deft.  I can hear in recordings what perhaps my co-worker (who may or may not have 20+ years on me) cannot.  But, does that mean I am deft?  Rightly, this whole post has been about nothing other than badminton, naturally.  You can ask any of my fellow badminton clubbers that actually, my skills are far from deft.  I have 3 raquets, two are yonex.  I use no capitals in that sentence because both raquets are the sub-100$ type.  In fact, one is after tax, a mere 2/3 of that.  The other one is a Fleet.  Not a FLEET, because not even one exists that I know that would require caps.  Caps in that case would be perhaps a  urlLink 300$ plus racquet .  And what would I do, I who disgrace even a 53$ 8200 light do with one?  Certainly not play.  Well, not any better than now.  It would be far too much power in my hand (right).  The most expensive and (and perhaps durable at that) raquet that Fleet manufactures is 170$ CDN up to 200$.  Well, mine is the 4/7 part of the last price type.  It is incredibly Sexy, though not entirely SEXY.  That is, it is not 80g with strings that ring in well over 30$.  But the grey mesh speaks for itself.  Yes, that mesh is titanium and well, if you are a fisher(man/woman) then you will be thrilled of hearing of any sort of net.    Good evening to all of me that is still fractured.  Today was looking through old photos, and my first girfriend as well popped up there.  I guess just looking was enough to say that somehow I miss her still.  Those photos are now in the dustbin.  Which is where some memories though good need to remain.  So, it took me over 2.5 years to do that, is that a measure of loss or what?  I am not deft in healing 'guess so.    From what you can imagine, this has not had much to do with "The Union" to which I belong, but I promise you that despite I have not mention that we "have" 37509 members, we are graceful to the "little guy" -- who happens to be Dave Pietre in this case, but in other cases, it may be someone else.    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       She has been my cure in days when I am not Happy   She is always laughing and that makes me Happy   When I cannot change my shorts, she says my Legs are Skinny   And that makes me to Laugh and Embarass myself      But I do not Cry because I see that she is Happy   Which whittles away all my feeling of Crappy      She is so sweet      That I am now Happy to not do My work, to which this Poem Attests.      
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      is it that hard?  i suppose i could believe in anything really.  such as the fact that this blog in fact may be the worst blog in a pile about 2 metres thick.  think about it really.  however, introspection is valuable and so... though this is rubbish, it does make me smarter.  i will not give my former name, though i may slip some hint that i am not nor ever was Howard the Duck.    and that i like  urlLink bubble tea  senbei  swedish meatballs  corn  girls with glasses and  urlLink dark hair   what?  dear me, that last won was  urlLink strange ...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Really, what is the world on about?  Can't we all just get along?  I mean, here in this office is actually the group who though unnamed, tout the anti-"The Union" attitude.  I suppose that we will let their roots rest for a bit.  WE ARE NOT ANTISOCIAL.  We are not slackers, perverts or anarchists - well maybe one is, but she moved.  We exist for you of course.  Sometime, take a look at our constitution.    Briefly, I might explain that roads are too long, straight and distant from the houses.  No, I don't like the noise of traffic, but no one does really.  That is of course, no one who has not been polluted enough by cars that he/she cannot remove him/herself from toxic environs.  Listen, all we have to do is make the streets tighter, but have ample room to walk along the sides.  Make loads of busroutes and heaps of buses and basically by way of conjestion, outlaw cars.  How many times does just one person fit themselves into a car (pollution included) and hop down to the nearest (what I mean by near is in American terms - one block and everyone else - within a kilometre or two) store, laundry etc and use their four-wheeled smoker?  Too often.  Constrict the width of the roads and do away with killing-your-kids'-futures that are driven by nearly everyone.  In fact, you may even discover that those two fat stumps below you are worthy to move you from place to place and don't cost a yen, pense, ora, penny to operate.    However, here is the hypocratic moment... if I met a girl with a car, well... that would be nice. :)  what?  not a soon-to-be-mush rant/blog?!  dear no, from this moment on i will not even use capital letters if I can remember to not.  Or ... i mean... or we could slice the rest of the world's cars and lories in half like in japan.  I've given up on this whole small letter business.  Hmm... there seems to be a bit of nonsense packed in here.  Wil...l... have... to work...it OuT... nuff      said.. ... .. . 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>