<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Without over glamorizing what it takes to make something like this happen, here are the basics.  My SFP has evolved into a small manufacturer or more technically, a component integrator.  We have been focused in our current business model for 16 months.  We will do around $2 million in revenue this year.  About $300K will be sub contract manufacturing, and the rest direct sold business. Around 50% of the remainder is in one large contract.      Today we have 9 production employees and occupy a pretty small space.  I have no other seasoned professional help other than an old retired friend that is helping me keep my head screwed on straight.  I have found that one of the things that I miss most in being in a larger company is the ability to focus.  My day shifts gears so fast that I can hardly stay on task for very long.  I go from AP to AR to Sales to Tool Fixer to Truck Loader to Toilet Plunger all before lunch.  All of that experience in "operational excellence" has gone out the window as I try to survive the challenges of the day.  My old friend knows as much about business as I do, probably more.  He is helping to stabalize the day to day task and get some organization in this rapidly growing project.  Consider that our revenue will grow over 1200% this year.  I am completely over matched some days.    Everyday has it's own host of challenges and today was no different.  I have to get out a truck load of product tomorrow and I am really pushing hard to not fall short.  On top of that, I am hoping that a customer follows through on over nighting a check for $40K for a large job we did last month.  You see the check is 15 days past due.  Normally, I would not be that concerned but that is a good sum of money and as any business teacher worth their salt will tell you, the challenge of a growing business is not profit, it's cash flow.  The employees have been paid, and now the material vendors want to be paid and I need the check to cover the check run on Friday.  Make no mistake, financially, we are strong.  Very strong, and our investors believe in us and would help us if we got in a pinch, but I want to make it without the help.  Sometimes you have to pretend the safety net is not there make the big leap.    Our goal on the line was 125 units today.  Not out of control but a streach.  All day long we could not buy a break.  I had tooling problems, line problems, and fixture problems.  This was not the day to experiment with new fixturing.  but we did, and as a result, we suffered a bit.  It seemed like ever time I went in the back, there were at least 2 people standing around and my lead was running around putting out one fire or another.  People standing around drive me crazy!  There is so much work to be done that there is no excuse for standing around talking.  None.  You can always pick up a broom or take out some trash.  That is how I sort the A from B players is when they run out of work.  The A players find work.      One day, I was on a conference call and I only had one guy working in the back.  He ran out of parts and when I got off my call, he had cleaned the bath room and was sweeping cob webs off the walls.  He still works for me.    Well lunch cam and went and we were not getting on pace.  I was really getting antsy and I felt myself snap at a few of my guys.  Then, like a blessing from God, My check came.  Whew!  I smiled and went to the bank.      When the end of the day came, I was on pace to meet my truck.  I don't know how, but I was.  I like to think it was because I ran around like a crazy person all day.  It was probably becuase I finally have a good crew and they had it under control.        
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It has been almost 2 years since this little science fair project (SFP) started.  What started with model A has revolved into model C+.  I can honestly say that I did not start this to get rich.  My goals have always been accomplishment focused not monetarily but that being said a Carrera has always been in the plan.  I wanted to run a company by the time I was 30.  Well, mission acomplished except, when I was 30 , I had no employees, alomst no revenue, was burning through my startup funds at an alarming rate, and my monthly ritual was to map out my cash flows to see when I would run out of money.  Glad to see that MBA was coming in handy.      Up until my SFP, I have been an operational guy.  To me running a company equalled operational excellence.  I was a manufacturing / systems / MRP / engineering management hawk.  I knew the pieces of the puzzle, how they fit, and what it took to deliver products.  However, if you never sell said products, all of that is pretty worthless.      Now you would think I, of all people, would have known that.  Before my SFP, I worked for a high tech defense contractor with over 25 years of knowledge in the industry.  I was brought in to "build opeation excellence through implemetation of best in class sytems".  Blah, blah, blah.  All the systems in the world were not going to off set the burden of a whole army of 6 figure plus managers and plunging sales.  And if that wern't enough, their one saving grace contract.  The one that was going to lead them to the promise land.  Was over sold and priced below cost. Oops.    While that story is best reserved for antoher time,  I should have known that the first thing I needed to do with this new venture was to build revenue.   But oh no, I was ready to manage a company.   I was ready for the sales to come in and the money to start flowing.  But somewhere along the line I forgot that the most important thing is business is sales. Period.  No sales = no employees = no profit  = no delegation =  me plunging toilets.    Don't get me wrong.  The SFP has sales now.  And employees.  And Profit.  But I still plunge the toilet.        
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For no other reason than to organize my own thoughts, I have created this Blog as a way to somehow reflect on where I am, how I got here, and how I can go from here.    I am a small business owner. Sound pretty glamorous right. It's not. To say I am a small business owner is only part of the story. I am a part owner of a small business that I run. What that means in a nut shell is that I own a percentage of a business that is mostly owned by an ownership / investment group that gave our company an unsecured loan to open operations. Essentially, they invested in me to make them money. No pressure right.    Today, one of my production employees clogged up the toilet and I had to plunge it. Other than that, it was just like every other day. Emotionally taxing and completely unpredictable. But this is what I wanted. This is what I signed up for. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>