<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A number of ladies have developed shin splints over the past 3 weeks. Below is an article Debra found on this. Please let your mentor know if you are suffering from shin splints and we will work with you to rehab them. Here's what we have recommended.   Rest the shins by pool running or aqua jogging for 2-3 days if you have access to a pool. Aqua jogging uses the same muscles as running and is an excellent way to rehab injuries and inflammation while staying on track with training. This will require a flotation belt available from most pool supply or sporting goods stores ($40 or so). Just aqua jog in the deep end of the pool for the same length of time you are scheduled to run for.  If you do not have access to a pool, cross train on a bicycle, stationary bike or elliptical trainer for 2-3 days  Ice the area for 10 mins as often as every 2-3 hours. Icing is a wonderful natural way to reduce inflammation. This is best done when the injury is acute.  Take an over the counter anti-inflammatory medicine such as advil or alieve for a couple of days.  Soak in a warm bath with Epsom salts after icing.  Massage can help when the tenderness subsides.  The main thing is to rest the area by doing something other than running for 2-3 days. When you resume running make sure you go easy.  Stretch your calf per the links below before and after running.    Hope this helps!   Shin Splints updated 6/13/03 Sooner or later almost all runners experience pain in the calf or shin. There are several types of overuse injuries that may develop in this region as a result of the repeated pounding from running. Shin splints, stress fractures, and chronic compartment syndrome have a common mechanism of development. Understanding the circumstances that lead to these injuries is the key to preventing them.The overall recurring theme that leads to overuse running injuries is excess training with inadequate recovery. Excess and inadequate are relative terms and must be judged against ones usual training routine. The more that excess and inadequate deviate from the usual training routine the less time it takes for an overuse injury to develop. Keeping this theme in mind one can now examine the specifics for how shin splints develop.A simplified view of the mechanics of running shows a foot-strike, then a loading/energy transfer phase, and finally a push off (toe-off) with the forefoot. Each foot-strike delivers a shockwave that travels up the leg. This energy must be absorbed by the musculoskeletal system. The harder the running surface the greater the shockwave. Soft grass, smooth dirt, asphalt, and concrete represent, in order of increasing hardness, the usual spectrum of commonly encountered running surfaces. Concrete is very hard on the body and training on this surface should be avoided.Distance running shoes are specifically designed to provide padding and support for the biomechanics of endurance running. They help absorb shock and facilitate efficient energy (motion) transfer. Matching the type of running shoe to the athletes specific biomechanics, and proper shoe fit are important. Similarly, worn out shoes should be replaced early because of reduced shock absorbing capacity. Runners with high rigid arches tend to experience greater pounding shock, whereas those with flat feet tend to experience greater fatigue of the muscles that support the foot -- and push-off. Both tend to develop shin splintsThe term shin splints refers to a painful condition that develops along the inside (medial edge) of the shin (tibia). The usual location is along the lower half of the tibia, anywhere from a few inches above the ankle to about half-way up the shin. The repeated running cycle of pounding and push off results in muscle fatigue, which may then lead to higher forces being applied to the fascia, the attachment of fascia to bone, and finally the bone itself. Respectively, this represents a spectrum from mild to severe. On the relatively more severe end of the scale the injury may progress from stress reaction within the bone to an actual stress fracture.In the early stage of shin splints a runner will describe a pain that is present when the training run first begins, but then disappears as running continues. The pain will often return after exercise or the following morning. As the injury progresses the athlete will experience more time with the pain, and less time without it. There is frequently a tender zone along the medial edge of the tibia that one can map out by pressing with the fingertips as they march up along the bone. Eventually, if ignored and training continued, the pain may become quite sharp and may focus on a very small area of the bone. If this happens a stress fracture should be considered.The treatment for shin splints is rest. Depending upon severity it is often necessary to completely stop running for a period of time. Generally this is done until day-to-day activities are pain free. When running is resumed  and this is where many injured runners make a mistake  it must be significantly different from the routine that lead to the injury. The concept of relative rest employs lengthening the interval between training as well as decreasing the volume and intensity of training. One can often substitute cross-training activities (e.g., bicycling) for running to help increase the interval between running days. There should be a graded and gradual increase in run training, keeping an eye out for the return of any shin splint symptoms.Stretching and strengthening the calf muscles can help prevent the injury from returning. However the most important preventive strategy is not to repeat the mistakes that lead to the injury. Examine all the training variables  surface, shoes, training volume, intensity, workout type, hills, weather conditions, etc. Seek help from a qualified trainer or coach. This all takes time and effort, but it is well worth it. Related Stretches The  urlLink soleus muscle stretch (GIF 16k) and The  urlLink The gastrocnemius stretch  (JPG 24k) copyright 2003 © Mark Jenkins, MD  
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have raised $300 so far for Nancy and sent the checks into NEADS yesterday.   I would like to mail checks collected by the&nbsp;group&nbsp;as we receive them.  I am requesting that you bring your checks weekly on Sunday when we meet.   Be sure to make a note of your donors so you can acknowledge them  with a thank you postcard.&nbsp; NEADS will mail their tax receipt directly.   Our goal is to complete the fundraising in the next few weeks.&nbsp;  I will let you know how we are doing weekly once we start collecting.   Please let us know if you need support.&nbsp; I suggest mailing or emailing the letter I circulated.  Let me or your mentor know if you did not receive the letter.   Remember each of us only need to raise under $150 !&nbsp;&nbsp;   Thanks for your generosity in the effort you are making to train and to raise these funds for Nancy.&nbsp; She is so very grateful and your efforts are going to make a huge difference to her life forever.  MaryKay   
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi all--I am also doing my runs here on the east coast in Maine...with Mary Kay's help I have been able to alleviate my shin splint pain from early last week and am continuing to be on track. (pardon the pun!!) While I am ramping up&nbsp;slowly from&nbsp;partial walk/run I plan to run that race in Oct-who's with me??&nbsp; I am anxious to meet everyone when I return next week...will be at the Aug 8th run for sure. Keep up the good work-Karen Dillen 
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           Another Great run this week everyone!             Thanks for being there, and thanks to everyone who made it in the face of&nbsp;life's challenges.&nbsp; It is a priviledge for us mentors to be of service and contribution to you.  Wendy, Debra and I&nbsp;are working hard behind the scenes every week to make your Sunday runs go as smoothly as possible.&nbsp;&nbsp;  We&nbsp;want&nbsp;this to be fun experience and an opportunity to share and contribute to each other.&nbsp;   As such I want to invite more of you to post to the Blog on your experiences and insights along the way.     Also to&nbsp;comment on what people post!&nbsp; When you share, you contribute to us all!     Remember:&nbsp;It's is not all about the running! it's really about life! &nbsp;       It's about:          Being in action.    Being your word.    Sharing yourself.    Being good to yourself.    Being able to forgive yourself and others.    Being of&nbsp;contribution to others.    Being able to stumble and get back on track...    Remembering that&nbsp;the journey is as important as the destination!       Peace, MaryKay       
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You all did such a great job yesterday out there in hilly La Jolla!  I know, I know, you didn't know about the hills, but you conquered them like true women.  Next time we send you out on a hilly course (and yes, there will be more, ladies), say to yourself, "Hill?  What hill?  I don't see any hills."...eventually your legs and lungs will catch up with your words!      Following is information about this Sunday's run.  After the run, there will be an injury prevention clinic presented by Dr. David Revivo, Chiropractor and nice guy!    What:  6 mile out-and-back course    When:   Sunday, August 1st              RUNNERS:  Meet @ 7:15 for 7:30 start.                WALKERS:  If you want to start earlier, meet at 7:00 a.m.  I will be there by 7:00 with maps.    Where:  Doyle Park, UTC area    Directions:     I-5 Fwy.  Exit at La Jolla Village Drive and head east.  Turn right on Regents Road.  Park is on your left just past Nobel Rd.    Have a great week!  Remember, feel free to contact your mentor with any questions or concerns.    Wendy  
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp;Hi Everyone, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Just wanted to send support and energy from the east coast. I am doing my runs out here, but, the heat and humidity has not made it easy. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I will be running with you in spirit tomorrow morning, I will do mine, but, will miss the company of all of you. &nbsp; I know everyone will do well, as a group there is nothing we can't handle, that is so powerful... &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Suzanne 
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The following are the remaining clinics we have scheduled.  Please note that all clinics, except for the nutritional clinic will be held AFTER our long run so we can run/walk first and beat the heat.  We hope these clinics prove to be informative for you.  We would appreciate any feedback you have on them!    July 25:  Weight Loss, presented by MaryKay Mullally and Jim Redquest   August 1:  Injury Prevention, presented by Dr. David Revivo, Chiropractor  August 8:  Core Strength Training, presented by Wendy Barry  August 15:  Nutrition, presented by Kim Brown, Registered Dietitician    Keep up the great work, ladies!  We are so proud and excited for you all!!!      Life is Short, so Step Up!    Wendy      
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The 5  urlLink heart rate monitors  donated by the generous folks at Sports Instruments have arrived.  If you (like me) are interested in cool toys... If you (like me) don't know your body's limits very well yet... If you (like me) want to make the most of this training program... If you (like me) place huge importance on stylish fashion accessories...     ...then you should contact me to check out my Sports Instruments Fit 2 heart rate monitor or buy one of the 5 from the team.  I'd be happy to show off mine (which came yesterday) or answer any questions. I'm pleased with mine after playing for a day, though our first run together will be tonight after it cools off.  Carol, if you're still interested, please let me know how and when I can get you one. Everybody else: email me if you're interested, and remember that the $80 price of the monitor goes straight to the team and your fundraising goal. Awesome.
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi everyone, &nbsp; I want to thank everyone once again for your commitment to this program!!&nbsp; You guys honestly are incredible and I  know  you are going to succeed!!! &nbsp; Please feel free to post any suggestions, or comments on the blog that will help Marykay, Wendy, Bonnie and myself adjust this program so that you get the most out of it!&nbsp; We welcome your suggestions&nbsp;and any feedback would be very much appreciated.&nbsp; &nbsp; Anything that you have to say is important,&nbsp;and&nbsp;remember for the next 15 weeks the most important person is&nbsp; YOU! &nbsp;&nbsp; We  want  you to succeed, so please help us achieve that sucess.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  As a team we will triumphantly cross the finish&nbsp;line on 24 October 2004!!!!!!!!! &nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp; Have a terrific week and happy trails! Debra 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Following is information about this Sunday's long run.  You were all amazing last Sunday!  Keep it up!     WHAT:   5 mile out-and-back course    WHEN:  7:15 a.m.  Meet at 7:15, step off at 7:30 a.m.  Clinic will follow after our run/walk.    WHERE:  Kellogg Park in La Jolla Shores    DIRECTIONS (Thomas Guide 1227-H5)    FROM THE NORTH:    I-5 Fwy. southbound.  Exit at La Jolla Village Drive and head west.  Turn left onto Torrey Pines Road.  Follow Torrey Pines Road, which will veer to the right at a stop light (where it merges with Ardath Road).  Stay in the right lane.  Turn right onto La Jolla Shores Drive.  Turn left onto Vallecitos.  Turn right onto Paseo Grande.  Parking lot will be on the left.  Park at the far end (north end) of the parking lot near the bathrooms.    FROM THE SOUTH:    I-5 Fwy northbound.  Exit at Ardath Road (it heads west).  Go past where Ardath Rd. and Torrey Pines Road merge.  Turn right onto La Jolla Shores Drive.  Turn left on Vallecitos.  Turn right onto Paseo Grande  Parking lot will be on the left  Park at the far end (north end) of the parking lot near the bathrooms.    HYDRATION:  Please remember to hydrate adequately for your run/walk.  You should drink a minimum of 8 glasses of water per day on average to remain hydrated.  The night before, make sure you do not deprive yourself of water or dehydrate your system by slamming down a bunch of beers!!  Just joking about the beers, ladies!    In the morning you should have 8-16 oz. of fluid (preferably a sports drink like Gatorade) about 1 hour before your run/walk.  WEAR A FUEL BELT WHEN YOU RUN/WALK.  Get used to sipping as you exercise to remain hydrated.  I suggest filling your bottles with Gatorade, though you might want to fill one of the bottles with water for a break from the Gatorade.   After your run/walk, drink 8 oz. of Gatorade right after your workout and lots of water for the remainder of the day.    EATING:  You MUST eat before you run/walk!!  I know you will be getting up early for these Sunday runs, but make sure you spend a few minutes making a simple breakfast for yourself.  You should eat your breakfast at least 1 hour before we start running.   You need carbohydrates in your system for your body to create your energy source.  Without it, you cannot perform adequately.  It is as simple as that.  Especially when we get into the longer runs/walks...you must feed your body.  Examples are wheat toast or oatmeal, banana.  I personally have toast and Gatorade.  I avoid any food/drink that will upset my stomach while I run (coffee, OJ).    Also, as we get into the longer runs/walks, it will become even more important for you to eat carbs at dinnertime the night before.  We can discuss this with you later.    I THINK THAT IS IT FOR NOW!  WE LOOK FORWARD TO ANOTHER FUN FILLED GROUP RUN!  YOU WOMEN ARE AWESOME!!    If you can't make the run, please let your mentor know.    Wendy  
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear Teammates, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I went to a barbeque this past weekend, on July 17.&nbsp; Everyone was asking me where Daisy was.&nbsp; I felt terrible that she had passed away.&nbsp; But I felt realyl peaceful in a way that I will soon be getting a new dog, thanks to all of your hard work.&nbsp; Your commitment to this project is overwhelmingly generous.&nbsp; Thanks to everyone that is working so hard to make my&nbsp; new dog possible.&nbsp;&nbsp; Much aloha. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; --Nancy Gorman 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       &nbsp; Hi Everyone,    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; My name is Suzanne Scott, and I was with all of you this morning, I have to admit that I was alittle apprehensive, I am somewhat of a loner and the idea of running with 40+ women wasn't something I thought I would enjoy....You all changed that for me and I want to  Thank You....     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; This is going to be an incredible adventure...we will all benefit in more ways than we could have ever imagined.    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; We have to thank Mary Kay, Wendy, Debra, and Bonnie for taking on a project like this&nbsp;and giving of themselves and their time for all of us...    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; My very Special Love and Appreciation for my "Soul Sister" Mary Kay...you know I Love You very much.    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Oh yeah, I am a massage therapist and in the very near future will set-up my table after long runs for anyone who will love to get alittle work done, legs, neck, back, shoulders....and if there are any other massage people in our group, let's work together..&nbsp;     
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey mom.. you inspire me so much. I know&nbsp;I get mad at you a lot and I'm hard to deal with but I&nbsp;think this whole thing you have put together with the help of those other ladies is really&nbsp;really great. Suprisingly&nbsp;I had a fun time running out there although it was scorching hot... yay&nbsp;I ran the farthest I've ever ran in my life..!!&nbsp;I would have never been able to do it though if you werent there behind me encouraging me acknowledging me for taking this on. Yes I've had to make lot of sacrafices to do this but&nbsp;I think it will all be worth it in the end. I LOVE YOU!&nbsp;I think im the only person my age who runs in there spare time. BUT I WILL BE DIFFERENT!! I wrote this on here because i know it would mean more to you if im not embarrased to shout it out loud! I LOVE YOU!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Seriously..&nbsp; thankyou so much for all that you have given me. the support, the advice, you are&nbsp;all that&nbsp;I could wish for in a mother and more. You truly are my inspiration and role model.&nbsp;See you soon.      Your daughter  Tara     &nbsp;   p.s. just look at this when we are in a fight okay? And then you wont get as mad cause you will know that&nbsp;I care about you even though I want to stay as far away from you as possible at the time.          
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            Thank you Bonnie!            urlLink  Mentor Bonnie Leading us in Pre-run Stretch     Originally uploaded by   urlLink  StepupMaryKay   .         
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       	 		 		 We had a fantastic turn-out for our first group run at Movin' Shoes in Encinitas.   We started with a very informative Shoe Talk by owner of the store Rick.  We had beautiful blue skies, but way too much sunshine and heat by the time we started the run, which made it a challenge for us.  Everyone pushed through though and finished!   This provided an opportunity to improve:  We will adjust the program to run first, then do the Clinics wherever possible.   AWESOME JOB LADIES!  Remember - one Step at a Time! MaryKay 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink Step Up For Life Team - First Group Run July 18th 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink StepupMaryKay .			 		 	  
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       	 		 		 This is a photo Nancy sent me recently of her and her service dog Daisy before Daisy died last month. 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink Nancy Gorman and Daisy 2 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink StepupMaryKay .			 		 	  
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What's up:  Five  urlLink SI Fit 2 heart rate monitors   have been donated to our fundraising effort.  If folks are interested, let's charge ourselves the market price for them with proceeds going toward our $6K goal.  Back story:   After doing a fair bit of research online, I bought a heart rate monitor today. I settled on the above SI model because it has the mixture of features I want at a good price and because user  urlLink reviews  RAVE about how SI makes a better product than its big name competitors like Polar.  Though I've yet to receive and test mine out, I expect it to be reliable, accurate, well designed, and backed by steller customer support from the manufacturer.   I saw a comment about sponsorship on their  urlLink website  after my purchase, and just for the heck of it shot an email to their default "info please" address. Two hours later, I got the following reply:   Karen:  how could any company turn down such a convincing agreement for sponsorship...   Here is a thought.  What if I make available 5 Fit 2 heart rate monitors for your team mates.. they can pay a fair price for them and the money goes toward the sponsorship of getting your training partner a new guide dog.   We may even figure out a way to logo the team to additionally help the cause.   Either way I love your ambition and thoughtfulness for a friend.   Warm Regards   jimmy Olmes President Wild Ideas Inc Distributors of Sports Instruments Products jbolmes@wildideasgroup.com    It sounds like this might be an opportunity for a broader sponsorship situation, but we should decide as a team whether that's something we want to pursue. No matter what,though, I'll post an update when I learn how and when we'll receive the monitors.  See you sunday,  Karen S
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thank you for all your positive energy. You guys are an inspiration to me that the human spirit is really something special.  Have a good week.  
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      At the   Movin’ Shoes  Store in Encinitas.   The address is:   897 S.Coast Highway,  Encinitas, CA  760-634-2353  Directions: Take the I-5 freeway to Encinitas Blvd; Go West to the Coast Hwy; the take a left (go South)to H Street.  The Store is in a strip mall on the left side.  We will have a "Shoe Talk" by Movin' Shoes owner - Rick.  He is openning several hours early especially for us so please make every effort to be there on time or a few minutes early.   The Shoe Talk will start promptly at 7:30am.   We will begin the walk/run immediately after the clinic, starting from the parking lot, our for 2 miles along the coast and back for 2 miles for a total of 4 miles.    What to Bring on Sunday     Your Fuel Belt:  With your favorite sports drink. For this run, I recommend putting water in 3 bottles and a sports drink like Garorade in the other 3.   Wear proper running attire:  Sports bra; cool-mesh or cool-max top and shorts; running socks and walking/running shoes.  Please discuss this with your mentor if you were not at the meeting last Thursday in which this was discussed.   Your stop watch and Heart Rate Monitor:  (If you'll be training with one).   A towel:  To dry off after the run and to put on the ground to stretch.   A change of Clothes:  or at least a dry top if you seat a lot!   Extra water:  for after the run.     Your completed Contract:  If you have not yet turned it in!  Remember to let your mentor or me know if you will not be able to make it on Sunday. If you are running late, please call one of the mentors or a team-mate.   LOOK FORWARD TO SEEING YOU!!!   
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          Week     Week of    Mon    Tues    Wed    Thur    Fri    Sat    Sun    Total mls      15     Jul 12 - Jul 18    rest    2 mls    x-train    2 mls    2 easy    x-train / rest    4 mls    10      14     Jul 19 - Jul 25    rest    3 mls    x-train    3 mls    2 easy    x-train / rest    5 mls    13      13     Jul 26 - Aug 1    rest    3 mls    x-train    3 mls    2 easy    x-train / rest    6 mls    14      12     Aug 2 - Aug 8    rest    3 mls/H    x-train    3 mls    2 easy    x-train / rest    7 mls    15      11     Aug 9 - Aug 15    rest    3 mls/H    x-train    3 mls    2 easy    x-train / rest    8 mls    16      10     Aug 16 - Aug 22    rest    3 mls/H    x-train    4 mls    3 easy    x-train / rest    6 mls    16      9     Aug 23 - Aug 29    rest    3 mls/H    x-train    4 mls    3 easy    x-train / rest    9 mls    19      8     Aug 30 - Sep 5    rest    3 mls/H    x-train    4 mls    3 easy    x-train / rest    7 mls    17      7     Sep 6 - Sep 12    rest    3 mls/H    x-train    4 mls    3 easy    x-train / rest    10 mls    20      6     Sep 13 - Sep 19    rest    4 mls/S    x-train    4 mls    3 easy    x-train / rest    8 mls    19      5     Sep 20 - Sep 26    rest    4 mls/S    x-train    5 mls    3 easy    x-train / rest    11 mls    23      4     Sep 27 - Oct 3    rest    4 mls/S    x-train    5 mls    3 easy    x-train / rest    9 mls    21      3     Oct 4 - Oct 10    rest    4 mls/S    x-train    5 mls    2 easy    x-train / rest    12 mls    23      2     Oct 11 - Oct 17    rest    3 easy    x-train    3 easy    rest    x-train / rest    6 mls    18      1     Oct 18 - Oct 24    2 easy    rest    2 easy    rest    3 easy    rest      Half Marathon      20.1      This training program is provided as a guideline and should be used with discretion based upon your current physical health &amp; condition. Please see accompanying notes 
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found this article on Her Sports online and thought it was very relevant to us and our training program. Enjoy!    Staying On Target How to meet your athletic goals in 10 easy steps!   By Dawna Stone - Her Sports Magazine  As an athlete, you’ve probably set a few goals: Run a marathon, learn how to surf or summit a local peak. Setting goals gives us something to shoot for and helps keep us motivated as we reach our successes. But while most of us are good at identifying broad goals, knowing how to achieve them is the real trick.        Following are 10 steps that will have you reaching new heights, and then setting the bar even higher.   1) Put it in ink. Write your goals on a piece of paper and tape it to your bathroom mirror, the refrigerator, your computer screen or anywhere you’ll see it every day. Be specific, read them often, and allow them to become part of your daily routine.   2) Don’t sabotage your success. We all love a challenge, but setting a goal to run a marathon for your first road race is lofty for most people. If you’ve never run before, choose a 5k, and sketch out a plan to do your first marathon the following year. Setting your goals too high gives you an excuse for not achieving them. Setting the bar just high enough will keep you hungry for more  3) Set milestones. Breaking your goal into short-term goals will lead to the biggest gains. Set daily and weekly training goals that move you one step closer to your big goal. And, just like your main goal, write them down.   4) Get group support. The old adage the more the merrier applies here. Having a group or training partner to help hold you accountable will get you out of bed for even the toughest workouts. Find a training group or club in your area, or, if you prefer, find a training partner or two who share your goal. You’ll not only help each other reach your goals, but will share in each other’s successes.   5) Set a deadline! A goal without a timeline merely leads to procrastination. Give yourself a final deadline, and create a structured timeline to complete your short-term goals. Procrastination is not an option.   6) Track your progress. Use a notebook or logbook to stay on track. Write your main goal on the first page, and each day record what you accomplished and what’s on schedule for the next day. Review your notes often, and revel in how far you’ve come.   7) Spread the word. When others expect great things from you, you’re more likely to rise to the occasion. Share your goals with your spouse, family members, friends and co-workers, and allow them to act as another support group.   8) Reap the rewards. Indulge in small rewards when certain milestones are met. Rewarding yourself with gifts that support your goals—a new pair of running shoes, a heart rate monitor—will motivate you to stay on track.   9) Anticipate bumps in the road. Goals aren’t intended to be easy. It’s common to start off strong and lose steam along the way. Realize this is part of the process, and see any bumps as extra challenges that will make your rewards all the sweeter.   10) Revisit your goals. If a bump in the road—injury, for instance—derails you, re-evaluate your time frame. Not being able to achieve your goal in the time frame you initially set doesn’t mean you have to abandon it altogether. On the other hand, if your training is going better than expected and you’re surpassing your milestones, it’s time to make things more challenging!  Dawna Stone is the president and founder of Her Sports magazine, and an Ironman athlete whose immediate goal is to complete her next half Ironman in under five hours.  urlLink  
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I would like to tell you a little bit about our beneficiary Nancy Gorman.  Nancy is a 41 year old Boston woman who suffers from multiple, chronic medical conditions including Cerebral Palsy, Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD), and Chronic eating Disorder.  Born disabled after her mother fell into a coma a month prior to her birth, Nancy has undergone some 25 operations in an effort to correct various physical disabilities.  She is also legally blind and paralyzed from the waist down.  Her condition has left her permanently disabled and wheelchair bound for life.    She has had 3 service dogs over the course of her life – all golden retrievers.  The dogs are highly trained and have assisted her in her daily life.  They have not only acted as guide dogs, but also to help her locate items, answer the telephone and retrieve things she needs to function.  The dogs have been integral to Nancy, not only by allowing her to live independently, but also for companionship and her emotional well-being.  I happened to meet Nancy in Honolulu in June 2004, the day after her last service dog “Daisy”, had died suddenly from heart failure.  Without a dog, Nancy is severely constrained physically and even the smallest of her day-to-day tasks are a huge challenge for her.  Losing Daisy has also taken a big toll on her emotionally, as she has lost her constant companion and help-mate.   Without assistance, it will take a year for Nancy to both raise the funds needed to get a new dog, and have that dog trained.  In the interim, Nancy will almost certainly be dependent on volunteers to function, and her mental state is likely to be compromised.    With the Step up for Life Program being about Life, Health and empowerment of women, we have an opportunity to not only empower our own lives in these areas, but to empower Nancy to return to a life of independence and emotional wellbeing more quickly than she could on her own.  Nancy needs to raise approximately $6,000.  Our goal is to raise this amount as a team effort.  With 20 participants, this means raising $300 each; with 30 participants, $200 each etc.  This may seem daunting, however is achievable if we can get 10 sponsors each.  On behalf of Nancy I would like to thank you in advance for taking this on and for making a difference to a sister in need.  Life is short.  Thank you for stepping up!  MaryKay Mullally July, 2004 
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       "Step up For Life”  is a Community Project about life, health and empowerment of women.  As avid runners and women who have run several marathons and half marathons ourselves, organizers and mentors, MaryKay Mullally, Wendy Barry and Debra Bond are embarking on the project to share our experience and train a group of women from all over San Diego County for the inaugural running of the San Francisco Women’s Half Marathon on October 24th.    1 in 3 women today are unhappy with their weight and appearance, are on a diet, about to go on a diet or thinking about it!   Many women want to change, and know what they need to do to lose weight or get more fit, but often are unable to get motivated to actually do it, or lack the support needed to sustain the changes. The predictable future for women who do want to change, is that they will join a gym or start to exercise; go on the latest fad diet and not get the results they hoped for.  They will get busy or discouraged; get off track; get down on themselves and feel let down. They will feel like they'll never be able to do it, and that getting fit and having the body they want is an ellusive dream!  Not a pretty picture!    The "Step up for Life" Project is about the possibility of empowering women to take on something that seems overwhelming at first, by  taking small steps at a time toward a life changing goal, with the support of other women.  So they can realize that they can do anything they are committed to do with a plan and with support.  It’s about women taking responsibility for their weight, fitness and appearance, gaining self confidence, self esteem, and being fit, trim and happy with their bodies at whatever age they may be.  Best of all, it’s about gaining friends and training partners to support us in our quest to maintain a healthy body and lifestyle in the months and years ahead!    It is also about helping a sister in need: Nancy Gorman, a 41 year old Boston woman.  Nancy has multiple chronic medical conditions including cerebral palsy, PTSD, and chronic eating disorders.  She is also legally blind and paralyzed from the waist down.  Her dog "Daisy" a golden retriever, died suddenly from heart failure in June 2004 while visiting Hawaii at the same time as MaryKay.  Without asistance it could take up to a year for her to get a new dog and have it trained. As a group we will raise money through sponsorship, for Nancy to get a new dog.  The Half Marathon Training Program is geared toward beginners, who have either never run or have not run for a very long time, so it is very achievable.  It is a 15-week program beginning the week of July 12th.    This Blogg will be used to chronicle our progress and to communicate with each other.  As of today we have over 20 participants enrolled and registered.  I would like to acknowledge everyone who has stepped up to take this on. For your courage and commitment to your lives; for your generosity and compassion for Nancy; and for your trust in me, Wendy and Debra.  I would also like to thank Joe Crawford and Lilia Benjamin for helping me to get this Blogg up and running!  MaryKay   
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have played a bit with setting up a blog for Step Up For Life! My name is Joe Crawford, and I blog at  urlLink ArtLung Blog  and also at  urlLink San Diego Blog . Here, the members of MaryKay's group can talk about their progress, and in turn, MaryKay can give her tips and tricks, as well as post schedules and the like.  Questions? Just contact me  urlLink at this form .  Thanks for reading!
      
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow! Can you believe it? This will be our 6th long run since the start of our program! Time flies when you are having fun, doesn't it?!!!  Exciting news for you...this Sunday is a backdown week.  Only 6 miles for you.  Piece of cake!  NOTE:  BRING YOUR FLUID BELTS!!!!  I'm not kidding either...  Here's the info:  What:  6 mile out and back course  When:  Aug. 22nd, 7:15 a.m. (7:30 step off).  Walkers, you can come earlier as usual if desired (7:00).  Where: Mission Beach Jetty. We will head north along the bayside and then return south to the starting point along the boardwalk.  Directions:  (Thomas Guide pg. 1267-J4)  I-5 Fwy.  Exit at Sea World Drive.  Head west. Go past Sea World. Exit Sea World Drive at West Mission Bay Drive (stay in right lane past Sea World.  Exit sign on right.) Stay in the right lane.  Spiral onto West Mission Bay Drive. Turn left at Mission Blvd. (street just before the boardwalk). Go to the end of Mission Blvd. Turn right at dead end into parking lot just north of the channel.  Please let us know if you cannot make it to the run.  THANKS!  Happy running/walking this week!  Get out there and have fun!  Wendy   
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi, everyone! Last week, the local Boston news came and filmed me and the apartment. We talked about the loss of Daisy and the fundraising efforts. I am really hopeful that we can make our goals. I know by October, definitely. It will be great to see and thank all of you in person. Have a great week. Don't forget to stretch!  Best wishes, Nancy (and Michael) 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         urlLink          urlLink The front pack      Originally uploaded by  urlLink StepupMaryKay .  
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         urlLink          urlLink Jessica lookin good before the fall      Originally uploaded by  urlLink StepupMaryKay .  
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thanks to everyone for their fundraising efforts to-date!   We have collected and sent a total of $1,195 to NEADS to-date.   I have also received $358 in cash toward airfare for Nancy and her assistant Michael to travel from Boston. I need approximately $200 more in cash to cover both tickets. If anyone can contribute toward this that would be great!  I would like to encourage you to keep sending the fundraising appeal out and to share with family, friends and collegues about what you are doing to keep the funds rolling!    Remember that our goal is to complete fundraising by August 30th.    Let me, Wendy or Debra know if you need support in this area.  As a reminder, please turn in your donations to me on Sunday. It would be best to put your name on a note on the check so I can credit you with the collection.   You guys are terrific!   MaryKay    
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We are still in the process of finalizing the hotel and pasta dinner details, but here are the details I can give you at this point...  We are going to stay at either Villa Florence or Crown Plaza Hotel in Union Square.  The negotiated room rate at both hotels is $135 per night.  We are leaning toward Villa Florence due to contract details.  Either way, you will have a great room at a high end hotel.  Regarding the pasta dinner, we are negotiating with the hotels to have a dinner in one of their banquet rooms.  So far, there are roughly 80 people who responded "yes" to the pasta dinner!  It would be best to have a dinner with a set menu and price (including tax and tip), instead of trying to find a restaurant that can accommodate us all.  It looks as though the dinner, including a pasta and meat dish, salad, drinks (iced tea, etc.), coffee and dessert will be roughly $30 a head (but don't quote me on that just yet!).  It will be such a wonderful pre-race celebration to have us all together in the same place at the same time, eating instead of running/walking!!!  When all is set, I will post a follow-up message on the Blog.  ALSO...remember to register for the race ASAP!  Go to www.nike.com/nikemarathon to register.  Make sure you register for the Half (not the Full) AND sign up for the shuttle service.  -- Wendy 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My, the week is sure going by quickly!  Sorry it has taken me so long to post this Sunday's run info.  Anyway, here it is:  When:  Sunday, August 15th, 7:15 a.m. (step off at 7:30); walkers can meet earlier (7:00 a.m.) if you want to get started earlier.  What:  8 mile out-and-back course  Where:  Ponto Beach (South Carlsbad Beach)  Clinic:  The nutrition clinic has been cancelled due to a lot of subject overlap with MaryKay's clinic.  Directions:  I-5 Fwy. Exit at La Costa Ave. and head west. Turn right at Coast Hwy 101. Make a U-turn (illegal, so be careful) at the first light (Avenida Encinas) Entrance to the parking lot is on the right before you reach La Costa Ave. The entrance to South Carlsbad Beach (Ponto Beach) is easy to miss, so keep your eyes peeled.  As always, please let your mentor know if you cannot make it!!  Thank you, everyone!  See you on Sunday!  You all rock!!  Wendy   
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           Hello Ladies!  I meant to get on here yesterday, but my computer at home is having problems connecting with the internet.  I just want to let everyone know that I am A-OK!  After spending a couple hours at Urgent Care yesterday, I left with 7 stitches on my chin.  The good news is, I can start running again in a couple days.  It has been a rough start, I had shin splints and then this (bad things don't ALWAYS have to come in three, do they?), but I am not going to let it discourage me.  I have a couple extra special thanks to give out... to the lovely ladies that were running with me during my unfortunate spill... you are awesome!  When you ran by after you had run the hill and shouted out "We ran it for you!" you managed to put a smile on my face (which at that time was almost impossible to do!)  You are my inspiration to get back out there and keep running!  Mary Kay... Thank you for helping me yesterday and keeping calm. I really needed that.  I have never had stitches, broken any bones or even remember getting stung by a bee!  This could have been a really tramatic experience for me, but your relaxed state helped me calm down and not panic.  You are a born leader!  The doctor said I can probably get my stitches out on Friday, so by our next run on Sunday, I should be 100% again.  Thank you again for all your love and support.... I hope you all have a fabulous week!  Jessica         
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It was a lovely but challenging 7 mile course today from Del Mar to the top of Torrey Pines Reserve, with a loop through the Guy Flemming Trail.  Walkers started at 7am and runners just a bit past 7:30am.   We did have a mishap with one of our sisters early in the run though:  Jessica slipped and took a fall at the bottom of the hill, sustaining a nasty gash under her chin.  Luckily I was nearby and was able to get her aid.  She ended up with 7 stitches but is fine and has been given the go ahead to run on Tuesday or Wednesday!  I want to thank all the ladies who stopped to support her and get my attention.  They ran the rest of the run for her.  Today's mishap had a few lessons and positives: First, us mentors will be sure to have a firstaid kid with us on our bikes in future.  Second, the way in which everyone rallied around Jessica and was so concerned for her well being, is a testament to the "family" we have created with our group.  Jessica we will look for that battle scar next week! Don't worry not even it will stop you.  I have to say how incredibly proud I was of my Tara who ran practically the whole way today.  Can I say that I think she is one awesome young woman, even if she is my own daughter!  Thank you Jen for being there today - we missed you!  Plus - you looked terrific out there with Tara.   Today we were joined by Karen Dillen, who has just returned from a month long vacation back east, but who has been training dilligently.  Welcome Karen!  Hopefully you will meet more of our awesome group next week when people are back from their travels!  Kathy, I have to acknowledge you for taking yourself on in the program the way you have.  Kathy has lost 12 pounds over the past 4 weeks by following the program!  Yikes that is just incredible!  Several people have had success in this area having either lost pounds of had a reduction in body fat -so keep up the great work!   I am sure I speak for Wendy, Debra and Bonnie in saying I am really very proud of EVERYONE for their commitment and determination.  The feeling of satisfaction from having the opportunity to contribute to all your lives is unspeakably great!  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Debra - I have never received any info about the heart monitor that I wanted to buy.  Last time we spoke there was two left, and you marked me down for one of them.  I forget who has them, but can you bring one to the run on sunday.  I'm writing this at 11:00 pm on Saturday, so you may not see it.  Please call me so that I can come and get it some time soon!!!  Thanks.  Sheila Reilly 858-775-0035. 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi again, ladies.  Following is the remaining run locations for the duration of our program.  If there are any changes of venue, I will let you know ASAP.   Specific information about this Sunday's run (Aug. 8) is in my previous message I posted.  Aug. 8th:  Del Mar up Torrey Pines and back --7 miles (see the previous message I posted for specs)  Aug. 15th:  Ponto Beach (South Carlsbad Beach) -- 8 miles  Aug. 22nd:  Mission Beach jetty to pier and back -- 6 miles  Aug. 29th:  Runner's Bathroom (Mission Bay) -- 9 mile loop  Sept. 5th:  Solana Beach train station through San Elijo Lagoon trail and back --7 miles  Sept. 12th: Penasquitos Canyon trail -- 10 miles  Sept. 19th: Kellogg Park in La Jolla Shores -- Low Tide Run (Will have to start earlier than usual) -- 8 miles.  Sept. 26th:  Kellogg Park (again).  Out-and-back course -- 11 miles (FAMILY PICNIC AFTERWARD)  Oct. 3rd:  Ponto Beach (South Carlsbad Beach) to Batiquitos Lagoon trail and back -- 9 miles  Oct. 10th:  Runner's Bathroom (Mission Bay) -- 12 mile loop  Oct. 17th:  Movin' Shoes Encinitas -- 6 miles  Oct. 24th:  RACE DAY!!  -- Wendy   
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi Ladies.  Following is info on this weekend's run.  Please read thoroughly:  What:  7-mile out-and-back course (Del Mar to top of Torrey Pines and back).  Core strength training clinic to follow.  When:  7:15 a.m. (step off at 7:30).  Walkers:  Come at 7:00 if you want an early start.  Where:  Seagrove Park in Del Mar.   Bring:  AID, TOWEL FOR CLINIC  Directions:  (THOMAS GUIDE PAGE:  1187,F5)  FROM THE SOUTH:  I-5 Fwy.  Exit at Del Mar Heights Rd.  Head west (turn left). Turn right on Camino Del Mar (main street through Del Mar). Turn left on 15th Street. 15th Street ends at the park at Ocean Blvd. Park on street.  There are spots on 15th Street and on surrounding streets (i.e. Stratford).  The spots on 15th are 2 hour parking spots after 9:00 a.m. so you'll be fine there.  Get there a little early to get a good parking spot.  FROM THE NORTH:  I-5 Fwy.  Exit at Via de la Valle.  Head west (turn right). Turn left on Jimmy Durant Blvd. (street before race track). Jimmy Durant Blvd. merges onto Camino Del Mar (keep heading south on Camino Del Mar). Turn right on 15th Street. 15th Street end at the park at Ocean Blvd. Park on street.  There are spots on 15th Street and on surrounding streets (i.e., Stratford).  The spots on 15th are 2 hour parking spots after 9:00 a.m. so you'll be fine there.  Get there a little early to get a good parking spot.  Please let your mentor know if you cannot make the run.  This will be a beautiful, and yes, challenging course up Torrey Pines Reserve.  Will also include a 2/3 mile trail run.  This is one of our favorite runs and hope you enjoy it too!  Let me know if you have any questions.  To your health,  Wendy 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thank you Mary Kay, Debra, Wendy and Bonnie for mapping out our runs in some of the most beautiful spots of San Diego. Part of the excitement, in our Sunday run, is anticipating where the trail will lead us. Even though we had to run up HILLS, I have enjoyed the trails and the scenery. I loved running through the seemingly country roads of Rose Canyon, looking over and up the cliffs of Encinitas and La Jolla and checking out the homes in La Jolla.  Thanks again for your time and effort. It really is appreciated. 
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi everyone,  Sorry I was not there today I had other commitments.  I'm sure you all had a great run.  I look forward to seeing everyone next Sunday.  I am so impressed with all of you, keep up the great work.  I'm looking forward to getting to know all of you as we put in the miles.  Bonnie 
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi everyone,  Sorry I was not there today I had other commitments.  I'm sure you all had a great run.  I look forward to seeing everyone next Sunday.  I am so impressed with all of you, keep up the great work.  I'm looking forward to getting to know all of you as we put in the miles.  Bonnie 
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Ladies, Just want to extend an offer to anyone who would like a massage, at anytime during the training. I am offering 1/2 hour massages for $25, and 1 hour massages for $50, and 1 1/2 hour massages for $75. Also, I will always help anyone out after a run. I work out of a salon in Del Mar on 1408 Stratford Ct., I can give you directions when you call me, my cell number is: 619-548-9242. I am at the salon on Tues, Thurs, Sat, but, can be available on Mon, Wed after 5pm. Massage is essential for keeping us healthy and especially now with our training. Take the necessary steps towards health and well -being, I promise to give you my Absolute Best. Thanks so much, Suzanne 
      
</post>


</Blog>