<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After work I went rowing with my colleagues Marco and Lucas north of the city. It has lots of canals and really beautiful scenery with windmills, cows, house boats. But the rowing coach is a real Row Nazi, so we have little time of enjoying the view.  Went to a nice brasserie afterwards with view over the lake and had some delicious garlic mussels. How expensive, but how good!
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The weekend was planned to go surfing, but things seldom goes as planned. Minke arranged a hair cut for both uf us 8.30 SATURDAY MORNING, so we had an early night Friday. After the daybreak haircut (it came out pretty nice), we had a nice lunch and headed for the beach.    .  The beach of Maasvlakte is pretty nice. You drive through the industrial hell of Europoort and West Rotterdam and then you are there. No surf though. Shallow waters, long way down to the beach and uneasy wind made my choice.   Tanned and slighly sunburned we went out to eat Chinese in the evening. Wonderful, 3-dishes dim sum. Some beers and a nice glass of Havanna White afterwards.   Sunday (now) seems to move on in silence. Worked on my photos while Minke slept on the couch/watched Schumacher winn again, alternately. I really wanted to go to  urlLink Grevelingendam  for some sailing, but rain and the sudden drop of wind (and of course, a slight hangover) made the decision for me. So we did some shopping, Minke went home for her cat and here I am, ready for dinner.       
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello everyone. This is my first posting here on my new blog and I am just checking out if it is working.. 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally some really good wind. Got trown around and took some good photos. Great day at the Grevelingenmeer!   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The whole weekend was dedicated to the beauty of Summer. Saturday we went to Hoek van Holland, "Holland's end", a reall nice beach straight out of the inlet of Rotterdam harbour     Sunday we went all the way to Zeeland and the Nordzeestrand. Bigger and better. Also did some nice surfing.
    
</post>


<date>15,April,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Hawaii is a Mecca for all waterpeople. The scuba diving, surfing and windsurfing is incredible. I was living there for 6 months and did my thesis, but I was a poor sucker without a car. No car - no windsurf. But I bought a cheap surfboard and went for the windless action. Diamond head is a good spot.     Kailua is the prime spot for windsurfing. The massive trade winds hit the west face of the island dead on here. On this day, there was little wind though.        
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      The narrow inlet to Oslo barely has space for both passenger ferries and windsurfers. But it is the best spot within reach from the city. So go figure..  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      This was before I got my board...went out to Larkollen and looked. Nice and pretty. But cold. A surfboard. But no surfers.     
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Went out with my colleague Fredrik and tried out Larkollen. Fred has a red board, so it mathed my blue just fine.     Here is Fredrik riding my equipment     On our way back we had to do some refilling of Fredrik's car    
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Doing some repair after my mast hit a bit too hard.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Eirik is ready with plenty of stuff     We drive to Sola Beach close to Stavanger and starts rigging     Not so much wind though..typical when you hit the water   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>