<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The thing about the  urlLink assless leather chaps and hi-cut leather briefs  sold in  urlLink Mervyn's  across San Francisco is that they were manufactured in some sweatshop in Asia.  Some poor Chinese lady is going blind sewing your leather under- cum -outer-wear.  She's gotta wonder who the hell is buying this shit in that faraway country called America ( Mei Guo , or literally translated,  Beautiful Country ). 

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   For those of you feeling  urlLink nostalgic over Sweeney , you're not alone.  Did you know that Sweeney was also a muse for T.S. Eliot, who wrote a series of poems entitled  Sweeney among the Nightingales ?  Included in this series were the celebrated poems  The Hippopotamus  and  Sweeney Erect .   Recently, an unfinished manuscript entitled  Sweeney in Manly  urlLink Buttless Chaps   was discovered by researchers granted access to T.S. Eliot's estate.  It will be auctioned by  urlLink Christie's of London , and is expected to bring in more than £800,000.  After serving as inspiration for luminaries of the 20th century including the brilliant playwright-composer Stephen Sondheim and the staff of  urlLink KOIN , Sweeney continues to guide us in a unique vision of the so-called "Post-post-post-structuralist era." 

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   John Cage's musical composition  urlLink  As slow as possible   for organ added two notes on July 5.  The notes are changed manually by an organist, and weights keep the notes depressed for their duration.  The piece will end in 636 years, provided the project continues to be funded, provided there are willing organists for the greater part of the next millenium, and provided we don't  urlLink nuke  ourselves into oblivion before then.  In the four bars taking place between 2481 and 2489, there will be a spectacular flurry of hemidemisemiquavers.  For perspective, this piece is about five million times the length of a Mahler symphony, and about one hundred million times the length of a typical Beatles ditty. 

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My brother just started as a surgeon at Stanford.  He had an ID card made, but the staff forgot to put "MD" after his name.   No big deal , he thought.  He's not one of those MDs that insists on rubbing his education in other peoples' faces.  He goes to the OR to start a surgery where he is the attending physician.  When he enters, the anesthesiologist looks him up and down and says, "Excuse me, we were  masks  in the OR."     What a jackass,  my brother thinks to himself.  As though I've never been in an OR!!   He puts on his mask.  Then he waits for the anesthesiologist to put the patient under so that he can go to work.  He waits.  He waits.  He waits.  He waits.  He waits.  Long minutes pass.  The anesthesiologist stands there idly, sighing.  Finally the anesthesiologist asks him, "Are you the attending?"    My brother answers, "Yes, this is my case."    The anesthesiologist chides him in the same snotty voice, "Well, I was  waiting  for you."    And my brother thinks to himself,  I've been standing here for 10 minutes!  

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Dry heat upon my brow?  Oh!  time was, when as the sunrise nobly spurred me, so the sunset soothed.  No more.  This lovely light, it lights not me; all loveliness is anguish to me, since I can ne'er enjoy.  Gifted with the high perception, I lack the low, enjoying power; damned, most subtly and malignantly!  damned in the midst of Paradise!  - Herman Melville,  Moby Dick  

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was high last night, and I guess it was important enough to write the following things before passing out:   The words form the hull of a ship.  Sentences make the planks.   They are all shapes. The word "narcissism" is curled around a boulder.   I have absolutely NO recollection of having written this shit.  I can't wait to try it again!!! 

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Don't eat Grape Nuts right after having a root canal. 

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Walking home from the gym yesterday, I heard voices behind me.  Icky, angry voices, shouting nonsense incantations.  The street was utterly deserted when I turned around. I was all, " Fuck , not again!  I just got that fixed!"  urlLink This trippy shit  blows.  My guess is that there were people around the corner, out of my line of sight, but having to guess is the real problem at hand.  When the  urlLink eggs  were talking, that one was pretty easy.  No guessing there - even  I  knew, at that very moment, that the eggs weren't  actually  talking. It sure was mesmerizing, though.  The door to my bedroom opening and shutting by itself - that one was scarier.  The bearded man in the green jacket - now, that was the prosopopoeia of pure anxiety.  But none compare to  urlLink this , this specter among specters, this waking nightmare, this unshakable shame. 

						
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    You can feel like a mental patient, but that doesn't mean you have to act like one - Marsha Linehan   This statement is from an article by Benedict Carey which appeared in the July 13, 2004 issue of New York Times.  In it, Carey outlines the principles of  urlLink DBT , including an extraordinary description of the Eastern philosophical roots of distress tolerance:   One thing patients learn very early, for instance, is to notice when their emotions begin to stir, allow themselves to feel the storm whip up, then let it pass - all without doing anything.  This Zen-like self-observation, called mindfulness, is an exercise not in avoidance but in feeling and enduring emotional pain.   OK, fine - Behavioralism is  so   urlLink 1950's .  But who would have guessed that an integration of Western behavioralist philosophy (well, actually, the mind-experiments developed to debunk behavioralism) and millenia-old Eastern approaches could have resulted in such a powerful and practical form of therapy?  Linehan is a hero to me!  Hip Hip Hurray, Marsha Linehan!!!!  Of course I am referring only to non-psychotic disorders here. 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Awwwwww, how  cute ! 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We are all  solipsistic  blogging poopheads.  Any more self-absorbed and we'd be auto- tampons .  Oh wait, am I allowed to allude to menstruation on this site? 

						
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Oh no, the  monstrous worm of happiness  has taken hold of me!!!!!!!  AAAAAAAAUUUUUUGGGGGGGHHHHHHHH!!!!  

						
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I think this is why J.Po and I like our boys damaged:   Unto a broken heart No other one may go Without the high prerogative Itself hath suffered too.  - Emily Dickinson   How many loved your moments of glad grace, And loved your beauty with love false or true, But one man loved the pilgrim soul in you, And loved the sorrows of your changing face.  - William B. Yeats 

						
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It happened again - only this time, when I was running, it was an obese black teenager and his skinny little pals.  I was running the opposite direction that they were walking.  They saw me, started whistling and cat-calling, and the fat kid started running in front of me.  Every time I tried to pass him, he would step to the side to block me.  Not that he had to step very far, seeing that his bouncing, blubbery wide ass took up most of the sidewalk.  His friends were all laughing and hooting and shouting and yelling obscenities at me.  After a scant 20 yards or so, the guy ran out of breath, and I was able to step around him to continue my 10 mi run.  Fucking kids. 

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Is it time to leave California?   New Jersey may be my next home. 

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The other day, when I was running on the Embarcadero near the ferry building, a white dude in a rastafarian hat started making fun of me.  For a good 20 or 30 seconds, he ran alongside me and started pestering me, saying things like, "Hey, where you running to?  Are you in a hurry?  Why are you in a rush?  You gotta learn to chill out!"    I expect he thought that I was a soul-less, controlling, minutiae-obsessed person.   Why not enjoy the moment?  he might have been wondering.   Why not soak up the euphoria?   Of course I'm guessing what he was thinking -- why would he choose to poke fun at a total stranger?  What he didn't know is:  That day, because I had run so much that week, the very first step I took that day was tiring.  But instead of stopping, I ran 8 miles.  The pain didn't stop, and I didn't either.  Every step was release from emotional pain, towards physical pain.  Joy was absent; my only satisfaction was that I encountered the physical manifestation of pain, and instead of shrinking from it, I sought it out more.  Use a razor blade to make the cuts you want to make, and you are labelled an emotionally unstable freak.  Go for a punishing run on a cold, windy day, when the steps you take are excruciating, and you are hailed as "hard-core" (at least by some -- clearly the guy in the big rastafarian hat wouldn't have thought so), even though they bring identical release and sense of control in an otherwise reeling inner world.  Is it cheating to pursue a socially acceptable form of masochism?  Again, I think of the statement,  You can feel like a mental patient, but that doesn't mean you have to act like one .  In this case, I feel like one and I act like one.  But others don't see the secret meaning of my actions, and somehow, that makes it OK.  Even "healthy."  Why? 

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've been listening to an arresting CD called  urlLink  Hamdullilah,   a collection of religious songs from all over the world.  The  urlLink narcissist  lent it to me.   Taqtouqa Al Iabaliyya is what arrested me. He sings no emasculated, angelic praise to God.  No:  he reverberates from his viscera to his sinuous throat-strings.  He sings in this instant, in this world of flawed bodies, of fruit-bearing landscapes and famines, of loves supreme and mortal enemies.  This  world at  this  time, this double conviction which is our only given.  His singing, intended to praise the transcendent, instead celebrates the corporeal present.  To this I say, yes, yes, yes!  But with God comes the false hope that our lives have purpose -- purpose, which robs us of our magnificent autonomy, and which seeks to wrench us from our only given.  So I reject God while I greedily devour every drop of the blood that He draws from believers.  This is my desire for belief. 

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Philosophers of the mind and logicians assert that even with great empathy and imagination, as a matter of principle we can never fully understand another person's thoughts.  We cannot shoulder another's pain, much as we would like to, nor can we share in another's ecstasy.  Our lives are ours, and ours alone, to bear.  But sometimes, we play music with others, or we dance a pas de deux, or we pass a baton in a race.  The most exquisite moment of all chamber music is the breath that we take on the upbeat before the first measure.  Suddenly, out of necessity, we are our fellow musicians because they are also us.  For a quarter measure, before we sound the first notes, the walls that keep us from each other are made permeable.  Rilke writes,   Who knows? perhaps the same bird echoed through both of us yesterday, separate, in the evening.   Can this quarter measure be domesticated?  We see the same stars.  We crave the same sensations. 

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   OK, so how good is the evidence that tryptophan is linked to depression?   urlLink Unclear:    Conclusions: A large body of evidence was subjected to very basic criteria for assessing reliability and validity, and was found to largely be of insufficient quality to inform clinical practice. More well-designed studies are urgently required to enable an assessment of what may be an effective class of agents.  

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink This article  looks a bit dodgy, seeing that it's for selling something, but it is interesting nonetheless:   Eating a high protein diet to provide more tryptophan only worsens the problem by even more increasing the intake of the 5 competing amino acids. Ironically, the only dietary strategy that increases brain tryptophan supply is to eat a high carbohydrate diet.  When large amounts of carbohydrates are eaten, the body secretes large amounts of the hormone insulin to lower the ensuing high blood sugar. The insulin also clears from the blood most of the 5 amino acids that compete with tryptophan for a ride to the brain. Tryptophan then has the "bus" all to itself, allowing more tryptophan to reach the brain.  This strategy is instinctively known and practiced by many people who eat large amounts of carbohydrates like bread, cakes, pies, ice cream, chips, pizza, candy etc., especially when they are feeling depressed, stressed or anxious.   OK, from now on it's Thanksgiving every day for me!!! 

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink This article  points out that different diets have different entropy to free energy ratios depending on the metabolic paths required, and that certain diets - particularly low-carb diets - may be particularly metabolically inefficient and therefore weight-loss inducing (emphasis on the word "may").   A review of simple thermodynamic principles shows that weight change on isocaloric diets is not expected to be independent of path (metabolism of macronutrients) and indeed such a general principle would be a violation of the second law....The second law of thermodynamics says that variation of efficiency for different metabolic pathways is to be expected. Thus, ironically the dictum that a "calorie is a calorie" violates the second law of thermodynamics, as a matter of principle.   Well-stated!  (That being said, I plan to continue my near-constant intake of pancakes, pastries, desserts, potatoes, pasta, rice, and cereal, and to keep exercising.  Weight maintenance can also be achieved through many paths!) 

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Research described  urlLink here  seeks to address the effects of the amino acid tryptophan on major depression.  It appears that even in remission, depressives show different responses to stimuli than people who are not depressive.  Two bottom lines:  1.  "Since brain function appears to be disregulated even when patients are in remission, they need to continue long-term treatment beyond the symptomatic phase of their illness," says Neumeister.   2.  People with a history of depression are more likely to experience fleeting symptoms and brain overactivity when sapped of [tryptophan].  So make sure you get enough tryptophan, especially if you have a history of depression! 

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I just got an e-mail from this chronic narcissist that I have been obsessing over (mainly because he is insanely good looking, incredibly intelligent, artistic, and athletic - four traits profoundly missing in the last person I dated).  His e-mail is of the following format:  "Dear You,   I Me Me Me Me.   Me I Me me me me me.   Me Me myself ME. ME ME me me.   Me .  Me Me.   me me Me me me.  Me me me me me me.    But enough about me.  What do  you  think of me?  Sincerely, Me."  It must be strange to walk through life as though it's a Fun-house, regarding other people as mirrors that reflect their images back.  Instead of having a dialogue, he throws words at me to see how I'll respond, and to see whether or how I can inspire his continuing monologue.  But we do not exist to grant him unexpected views of himself!    This has me wondering - can a person  actually  be this narcissistic?  He sure acts like it most of the time.  Can a human that is intelligent in so many ways truly be unaware that we are all autonomous entities?  How narcissistic can a person be while still carrying out a life that appears well-adjusted? 

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Here  is a more in-depth and thoughtful analysis of the happiness vs. money dynamic in developed countries than is usually presented in catchy aphorisms.  Apparently, if you're more happy, you are less likely to commit suicide.  Now I know!  Bottom of line of the article seems to be that money, when used to purchase non-material conveniences such as a shorter commute to work due to neighborhood location, can contribute to happiness.  However, when used to purchase so-called "conspicuous" items such as a larger house or a bigger TV, money does not increase happiness.   The article also acknowledges that within a country, people who have money are on a whole much happier than people who have little money.  Nice to see an honest assessment of poverty.   Too many bourgeois assholes glorify low income - they think they're  keepin' it real  by going to hip "dive" bars and "dive" restaurants.  They feign solidarity with the working poor.  BULLSHIT!  They go home to their yuppy apartments with track-lighting and granite countertops to smoke their weed and talk about the cool dive they just discovered. 

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Seen at Ranch 99 Market:   SPECIAL!!! Dr. T.C. Chan's Fritillary 'n' Loquat Syrup!!   $4.99!!  You save: $0.00!!    

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My brother is too adorable.  On Friday, he made cookies in honor of my parents' arrival (scheduled for Saturday).  When my parents didn't get here until Monday, he was all annoyed.   

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My grandfather, from Taiwan, visited more than 30 states in 1959 or so, when he was visiting the U.S. on business.  He encountered quite a doozy while travelling in the segregated South - sit at the front of the bus, or the back? 

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My parents were just up visiting my Uncle and Aunt in Kirkland, right outside of Seattle.  While there, they paid homage to Costco (a Kirkland original).  Nestled between the plastic lawn furniture, the 1024-pack of pork chops, and the industrial sized Drano was a  Bösendorfer  6-foot grand piano.  Not just any piano - a  urlLink BÖSENDORFER !  It was priced at $50,000, marked down from around $80,000.   

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    All men are dogs.  Eventually, they bark.  

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Po:  I wish we were lesbians, because I'd be so attracted to you. Sophist:  I really wish that too. 

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Last time I wrote on benzos , some interesting stuff came out of my fingers.  I decided to try it again last night.  Woke up this morning to find the following on computer screen:   each time i come into consciousness, it's a step backwards from a truly revealing entry.  i couldn't have challenged her to swimming, since they were too short, and you were tall. vvvvvvvv vvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv vvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv vvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv vvvvvvvvvvvvvv vvvvv vv vvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv vvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv vvvvvvvv vvvvvvvvvvvv b vvvv m   Guess I really leaned into that "v" key.  I actually abbreviated it for the purposes of this blog.  "v"s filled up half of my computer screen. 

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Knowing what I do, how can we now be friends? 

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I recently received this noisome e-mail from a guy on Orkut.  Is there no syntax left in the world?   Merely saying hello since your words and beauty caught my immediate attention captivating an otherwise insipid moment with your spell. Thoughts lush in transient passion beholden to your fleeting glimpse; to your warm charismatic smile & soulful eyes ample in discernible empathy to such enchanting allure. Truly for sure.. -P.   

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I don't know what to make of  urlLink this .  It's too easy and tempting to label someone "an untreated alcoholic with paranoid and megalomaniac tendencies," particularly when that person has screwed up so spectacularly in so many ways.  This article bothers me in at least two ways: 1) It relieves GWB of responsibility for his atrocious actions. 2) It perpetuates the concept that a person is purely defined by their diagnoses.      I wonder if this is how people will be labeling and ousting me when I mess up, as I am certain to do many more times in my career.  Disturbingly, I feel compelled against my will to defend the indefensible GWB.  Credit  urlLink here  for pointing out the article. 

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was just putting on socks to go running, and I noticed one had a hole in it.   Darn it , I said.  Then I realized - darning holes in socks is likely where that phrase originated.  For some reason, that delighted me.    Now I have new socks on and I'm going running in pursuit of the fabled Runner's high.  I've become pretty happy after running for long periods, but have never experienced the euphoria that  urlLink some liken to cocaine .  Anyone out there have experience with this natural high? 

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I read in the NYT that in France, a six-pack of abs is called  la tablette de chocolat .  Very appealing.   

						
</post>


</Blog>