<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I'm reaaaaally bored at the moment & waiting for my impending monday! My b-day party is going to be loads of funness. As it turns out, Josh &amp; Dro have off days on my b-day so its gonna be good for everyone. yay! The only thing is that Josh might have Smokey Joe's practice (it's a play) but thats not til like 7 o clock. Anyway, thats pretty much the only intresting thing going on with me right now, which is alot compared to usual. peace out.... must go get peach cobbler now....      -xoxox-   -Jess-  
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Some one asked me to put a like to their blog because apparently, my blog has "potential". But, i'm just a nice enough person that i'll do it. Here you go random person i dont know:  urlLink http://chiraag88.blogspot.com      &nbsp;  Anyway, I think this place needs to have a thing where you can just upload pics without that stupid blogger bot crap. And you should be able to upload them straight from your comp, just cuz some of us arent complete computer geniouses doesnt mean we dont have the right to share our pics too. grrrness! Picture uploading should be fast & easy &amp; straight&nbsp; form your computer..... but i guess one person's opinion cant change anything. And dont even get me started on that! Those poor etheopian children.....    &nbsp;  -xoxox-   -Jess-  
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hello once again! I am planning my party already! We are gonna have cheese cake, and everything will be decorated in pink, and we are gonna watch movies & just chill. i think its gonna be uber funness! I love my friends.... they are always there no matter how bad i am to them... i love them so much. I wanna say thank you to Dro &amp; Court for being totally supportive & making me feel sooooo much better. I love you both so very, very, veeeeeery much. I also love Peyton, Josh, &amp; CJ ssssoooooo ver, very much also. All i can really say is this : i'll never turn my back on any of you & i love you all so much, you guys are my bests!!!!! Well, now that that mushy moment is over, i must be leaving to update other journals, buh-bye-bye!     &nbsp;   -xoxox-    -Jess-    
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I certainly never expected today would be so very boring. All i've done today is go shopping with my mom & sister for school supplies. Usually i'm hanging with my friends, or planning something with them, or i'm talking with them on the phone and/or IMing them. But not today... no. I have had no contact what-so-ever with my 5 beloved bests. I posted my b-day plans on my lj &amp; hopefully i get some phone calls from them all with good times/dates and weather they want icecream or cake or maybe even pizza. No one interesting is online except Courtney but her away message is up ....so bleh! I am hoping one of my ppls decide to call tonight or tommorow so my mommy knows what to buy. I can assure you all the party will be veeeeeeery pink. *insert evil laugh here*. peace out!    &nbsp;  -xoxox-   -Jess-    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Court's par-tay-ness was totally fun today. Our usuall 6 showed up & we just hung at her house. We had ice cream sundays &amp; we played with the scary, evil confetti. But the sparklie pink ones were NOT evil! lol. We were gonna go to the pool, but Josh & Dro didnt wanna get all chloreny smelling b4 they went to work. Me &amp; Josh got in another fight, not as major as last time, but i ended up pushing Josh over onto Dro.... u'd think we'd be more mature at our age. lol! Then Josh & Dro had to leave 4 work &amp; It was just me, Court, CJ, & Peyton. We sat &amp; talked for a bit, with some silences (but at least they werent akward! lol!). Then Peyton's dad called & she had to leave. We bid her aloha, then we went back inside &amp; just talked for a while. Then we decided we wanted to go to Angelina's to eat to suprize Dro, but then we figured that it was a nicer resturaunt & we didnt wanna get him fired so we didnt. Cuz, i mean, its not like just going into Petsupermarket. lol. Then we just sat around &amp; watched Cyotte Ugly. Then Court's grandparents came & it was time for me to go home. I bid them adue &amp; that was it. Well, until next time, aloha child!    &nbsp;  -xoxox-   -Jess-    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  p.s. Dro, thanks for getting the A*Teens stuck in my head!!!  
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Ello again! I am about to go off to a day of party funness at my friend Courtney's B-day party. It will be me & muh bestest buddies - Peyton, Court, Josh, Pedro, &amp; CJ. I dunno what we'll be doing, but most likely it will involve circling up & talking. I just printed Court's splendid b-day card &amp; i'm about to go get some food & then go to Court's to pig out on ice cream sundays. I'll tell you how it went when i return. much lurve!    &nbsp;  -xoxox-   -Jess-  
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hello every one, this is my first entry here at blogger. I am already the owner of an lj, a xanga, and a tardcore journal. I guess you could call me a collector of sorts.... if in fact you can collect online journals, or "blogs". As you can probably tell, i am a huge dashboard confessional fan. Emo is definately my fave genre of music, but i also enjoi punk, indie, ska, metal, etc. I am also in love with Drama & Musical Theatre. I have been in Drama 1 &amp; 2 and i have done the musicals "Godspell" & "The Wiz". I am going into musical theatre in this, my sophmore year. I write poetry &amp; songs, it is my vent for emotions. My mom suggested getting me into dance, which i am seriously considering now cuz i might need it to help me as far as musical theatre goes, cuz i kno my carrer will be something revolving around that. Last, but certainly not least, my friends are the most important thing to me. Especially my best friends - Peyton, Pedro, Courtney, CJ, & Josh. They are my world &amp; i love them to death. I'll post some pics of us all in my next entry. Well, guess thats all for now, except, I CANT WAIT TILL COURT'S PAR-TAY TOMORROW!!!!!    &nbsp;  -xoxox-   -Jess-    &nbsp; 
      
</post>


</Blog>