<Blog>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         urlLink From JPL:   NASA's Spirit rover recently took this false-colored picture of the dunes on the floor of endurance crater.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      An article came out ( urlLink hep-ph/0408045 ) today that combines all the major measurements of  urlLink neutrino  mass into a global constraint.  This is a big deal because two results from entirely different types of experiments have forced the masses into a small allowed range.  Neutrino flavor oscillation experiments provide measurements of the mass differences between the types of neutrinos, and cosmological measurements put bounds on the absolute mass.  They work in opposite directions in the sense that differences in mass imply a lower bound (mass can't go below zero, so roughly 0+difference gives a lower bound) while cosmology gives an upper bound (if they weighed more, then we'd start to notice).  This is the first time the upper bound and lower bound are so close, thanks to a cosmological measurement of large scale structure from the Lyman-alpha forest:  urlLink astro-ph/0407372 .     (click  urlLink here  to see a funny picture).
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In the news today, an  urlLink article  explains how young men in Finland can avoid some military duty by having an internet addiction.  On the trip to Canada with my parents, I had excess free time and a laptop, so made a  urlLink music video  with garage band and the help of a 45 minute laughing fit.  What does this mean--no military service?  98% of the material in the song is prefab from garage band: drums, organs, tango horn section, and the picture was taken by Jie Li here at Princeton.  From me: the dumb random melody and arrangement.  Let me know if the file format isn't convenient.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A crazy animal:    Bow Lake:  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Recently, an article proposing a theory to reconcile CDMS and DAMA has appeared on the archive,  urlLink astro-ph/0405362 .  This model, introduced in the review article  urlLink astro-ph/0407623  and worked out in a cosmological setting in  urlLink astro-ph/0312607  and  urlLink astro-ph/0312605  claims that we may coexist with a mirror universe of particles that behave as ordinary matter (baryons) and form atoms, but interact with the visible matter gravitationally, or only very weakly, so are invisible to us.  One potential problem for mirror matter as dark matter is that mirror matter is baryonic, while the most successful models of dark matter to date are not baryonic.  The traditional problem with baryons is that photon pressure in the hot gas before recombination dominates and gravitationally-induced structures can not grow.  Once the gas decouples from the radiation, after recombination, structures form.  Yet, to get the amplitude of gravitational clumping we observe today, we would need and density perturbations at the time of recombination that are much larger than indicated by the CMB.  The way to get around this is to introduce a non-baryonic sector of cold dark matter (CDM) that starts to clump significantly before recombination.  If mirror matter baryons had the same thermal history as ordinary matter, then none of the necessary density perturbations would form before recombination.  Assuming we can get around this problem by breaking the symmetry early on, to give them different thermal histories, there's still another problem.  Once mirror matter starts to clump non-linearly it will behave like matter and the effects of pressure and interactions within the mirror sector will lead to quantitatively different predictions on small scales.  Eg. cold dark matter is thought to form roughly spherical halos, while baryonic matter forms disk galaxies because it loses energy more readily than angular momentum through interactions.  Then again, CDM is not a gem on small scales because pure CDM simulations give too much substructure and cusps in spherical fits to their cores.  Please post comments on issues associated with mirror matter and the CDM!  More to follow...hopefully.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One of the most exciting results from modern cosmology is that we understand very little of the total mass in the universe.  A small  urlLink fraction  is due to the visible matter that we understand fairly well, after having stared at it for so many thousand years. The rest is new to us and open to speculation.  Constrained speculation.  (See  urlLink astro-ph/0403324  for background and  urlLink astro-ph/0310723  for recent measurements.)  If the particles that make up dark matter interact with ordinary matter, made of protons, neutrons, etc., then they may be detectable--several projects are striving to do that and two have reached drastically different conclusions.   urlLink DAMA  recently made NYT headlines by finding a significant detection of the signs of dark matter they had expected,  urlLink astro-ph/0307403 .  Unfortunately, another project,  urlLink CDMS  reported a negative result, incompatible at 99.98% with DAMA, based on the models used (see  urlLink astro-ph/0208010  for some of the issues).
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome.  My homepage was gathering dust and a total of   on a garbage disposal in a dorm somewhere.  It also had about the same content.  While the content won't change, I hope that the readership will improve now that I have the following gimmicks: 1: physics essays and news from the  urlLink archive  2: pictures and paperweights 3: ignert things  Let me explain in reverse order.  Ignert things, because I lived in Missouri for 8 years and this is how we say ignorant (or not), will be dedicated pointing out things that I think are important.  I was thinking about a deeply earnest commentary on current politics, international intrigue, and other things that I'm qualified to discuss, but instead entries with this title will signal a mindless scavenger hunt for you, the reader, to locate items in the New Jersey area.  And Beyond.  A good friend of mine told me that from that day forward I would associate Abraham Lincoln with my watch--I still do.  If someone asks if I make any unusual associations, it's always that one.  The point of this is that by tracking down a particular door, screw, or piece of gum stuck to a table somewhere (picture will be included when possible) I hope that the readers will attach more significance to something they might see everyday, or find something new that they like, restaurants in NY, etc.  What product placement.  This is an experiment, but I'd like to make the Niagara falls of doorknobs, cash registers and bathroom graffiti, the one that everyone has to go check out.    I'm not big on commentary, as you can tell, so there will be plenty of pictures for friends to see what I've been doing lately etc.  The last category, otherwise known as "actual content" will be a collection of links to articles in physics, abstracts and essays.  A lot of what I do as a grad. student is go through lists of papers and try to filter out interesting material.  I'll try to set links to those articles and give some basic background.  The archive is revolutionizing how developments in physics are published and retrieved; hopefully I can convey some of the excitement.  Eric
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You want it made out of foam?  It is made out of  urlLink foam !
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Next fall I'm going to be a teaching assistant for a yet-unannounced class in the physics department.  To get all the new grad students excited about teaching, the local "Center for Teaching and Learning" has a program for new TA's where they explain the basics of "effective" teaching.  They just sent me an email about their orientation program with some funny responses from previous grad. students,  "Clear, concise presentations, very useful activities." (Humanities)  "The section on how to lead discussions, the case studies, and the micro-teaching were all very helpful to me." (Social Sciences)  "It will help be to be more comfortable in the class." (Sciences)  "...a well-planned and valuable experience." (Engineering)  Is this a joke, or are we actually  that  predictable?  Can you really break grad students down by type--into humanities students reciting Strunk and White, social science students discussing case studies, engineers planning their well-planned experiences, and then to the terse, nervous scientist who forgets to use deodorant on the first day of class, despite all those warnings of the McGraw center?  I think the answer is often yes, but don't worry, I always wear deodorant.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Povray  has added a nice feature that allows users to render isosurfaces: you give it a function of (x,y,z) and ask it to plot the surface where that function takes on some value, f(x,y,z)=c.  A good example of this in physics is the Fermi surface--the surfaces in electron momentum space that correspond to some energy.  For an  urlLink fcc  crystal structure you can dig up a formula in  urlLink Ashcroft and Mermin  and draw in the Brillouin zones: (here's the  urlLink povray file  to do this)  urlLink    I went a little crazy after this and plugged in different structures and povray settings that probably don't have any physical relevance, but they make nice pictures.  For much more imaginative and attractive uses of isosurfaces, see  urlLink Tsutomu Higo's  page.  urlLink fcc Fermi surface, single BZ boundary   urlLink fcc Fermi surface, single cell   urlLink fcc Fermi surface, several cells   urlLink bcc Fermi surface, several cells   urlLink bcc Fermi surface, several cells bounded 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last quarter, a  urlLink europop song  was spilling through the cracks under the doors and livening up the dreary halls of UChicago's Broadview dorm.  I think the song needs to make its way to at least the D-bar here at Princeton, or maybe, just maybe, to cross the wide divide of the Springdale golf course to the undergraduate dorms.   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was in NY this afternoon and had dinner at  urlLink J.G. Melon  (photo research courtesy of Google), known for its socialite atmosphere and delicious hamburgers.  I'm as much of a socialite as I am a hamburger, but I liked it.  It's very well decorated inside and brought back a lot of  urlLink memories  for me, related to some  urlLink comments  by fellow grad student  urlLink Andrew Moroz .  I had dinner with the UChicago columnist/blogger and NY native  urlLink Phoebe Maltz .  Before dinner we saw a dog in Central Park that needed an exorcism.  I think I'll leave her to explain that.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I heard about someone who analyzed an abstract question by breaking it down to the letters.  That's a lot more than I do most of the time, which usually involves some head scratching while thinking about where to get lunch, and noticing some cracks in the floor.  Unfortunately, both of these approaches fall short of the desired approach in academia of taking a question like, "what is justice" and writing the Republic.  What's interesting to me is that these three classes of responses are similar to the natural response to reading books full of nonsense like, "htsi si a ojek" (flip the letters and this says, "this is a joke").  Some people will reduce it to letters, some will spend years interpreting it, and some won't take it seriously without a context.  What's the difference?  Joke articles, twin languages, and ciphered books can show how much credibility, consensus, and practicality distinguish overly abstract questions that people like to worry about from total nonsense.  These articles are fun because they fall right on the border of what people bother worrying about.  If they were any more quacky, they'd fall off the map, if they were any less quacky, they'd probably be too boring to worry about:  John Baez gives a great explanation of two of these:  urlLink the Voynich manuscript   urlLink the Bogdanov affair  And then there's Sokal, the one we know that was intentional:  urlLink Alan Sokal's site 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>