<Blog>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   this is me,,, cool huh...  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello   

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   this is one of the local school garden we did.this area is for those students who want to have a break or trying to study in a peaceful manner,while enjoying the tropical scene around them.  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello   

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     my beloved daughter, Bea,.... where ever you are,,,theres only one thing i want you and Joy rose to know,,,,Papa Loves you so much!!! ..And i just hope and pray, both of you can grow up to be a fine lady,,dont&nbsp;ever forget ,"Papa Loves you both very much,,,,Mwaaahhh!!!&nbsp; urlLink       

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    how does this look?!!!!,,like it?,,well this is one of my sample in landscapes, showing a pool in a spah concept, a bit of tropical. this project is on the process of building now, still havent finish the details yet,,"bagal ng feedback ng arkitecto dito"&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    one of my samples of showroom design. We didnt manage to get this project, but somehow were there to meet the people here at Osim.&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     some of my firends here,some still together w/ me stayin in one roof, and some went home ready,,,sad...&nbsp; urlLink        

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    may niece in the states. Shes so lucky she`s been there since young,thoug born in manila and raised here in singapore, her parents manage to migrate in us and stay there for gud, "ang galing na magingles nito!!!!, talo pa c me....&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    well,how`d you like this photo w/ my catch?....&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well, how to say it this,,,its sort of "taboo", but lets c then,...   first four years of stayin here w/ my previous family,,,gud boy pa c me, dont even know where the red district is or is there any pub around for foreigners.  Cut it short after my family went home,&nbsp; and left here alone, hten i started to roam around and c what singapore is about. Its a businessworkd over here, everybody`s got to work for $$$, discovered the red district,and girls are asking %20.00 short time for 20 minuites,,,"how to do?"  then the rest is history, of me,,,,...  A lot of our kababayan here specially those in tourist visas,shortime stay are also secretly workin here in pubs and alike. Some who is lucky enuf manage to be married to a local and become a resident here, af ter that,,,,its history again,....hehehehe,,, its hard to continue, coz its really taboo,.. u got to be here and leave here to know.  There`s a lot of those typical stories here. So, how,,,would you like to stay here and see for yourself?    

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well, here youll see some profile about me,,,and my work, how i see people specially sa mga "kababayan ko".  &nbsp;There are also some suggestive things regarding your home renovation if your currently doin your house now, some tips, comment as nad suggestions. See for your self..      

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink PINOY SURVIVOR....ATBP... [BLOGGER PREVIEW]  

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    another scheme of the side garden..  Posted by  urlLink Hello   

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink PINOY SURVIVOR....ATBP...  

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   another scheme but same area at the side of garden,,,this is more simplified and less budget ofcourse... but i still prefer the first pic....hmmmm...  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello    

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   yah,,,same house but htis time its the rooftop garden..  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello   

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...it is not easy to be one, i should know,coz ive been a father once, i had 2 girls and now i couldnt even see them,....its personal but just let you figure it out...  a father is somebody who is a very good provider, a hard worker for his goals and dreams,w/c is primarily hes family. A father is someone who you could depend on of whatever it is, financially ,spiritually, intellectually. But through the hard times a father should be assisted by his wife her personal friend and confidant. a person who you can depend on wether times are bad and easy. A father, is still a father wether he goes far away from home and long to come back for the reason of hope and fulfillment, who is trying hes way to stay survive in order for hes family to survive. A wife should always be there caring for there kids and telling them things not to forget there father, for whatever it is ,,,hope shouldnt be forgotten, faith should always stay strong, and will should always be the inspiration to keep"  a father become a father ."  

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   some magnificent buidings at the very heart of singapore....nice huh?....  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello   

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   another great spots here is "the esplanade" at my back,,and yours truly,,,sorry for the face its kindah hot that time....  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello   

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   business establishments, such as the raffles hotel is one of the great spots here in singapore.  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello   

						
</post>


</Blog>