<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         We had to be in sch by 7.10am for drill. "So early" However, i must admit that today's drill was quite good and i was quite happy. Lets put on an even better display on national day!! Ya, guys!! We had bible study then, when we read the bible for 30 minutes. Mr Kang, later told us some stories! Haha. Those types that start with; long long time ago...*yawn*. Haha, i m joking. When for lunch with Jeremy and we were making quite a lot of noise in Delifrance; making prank calls on people. Fortunately, we were not chased out. HAha... and chris msg me when i was walking back home, and asked me whether I want to go out. Crap! Fish! Stingray!     Wat else??     
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Liverpool lost 1 nil to FC Porto by a Carlos Alberto's 85th minute strike. However, i was quite pleased with the way they played. It was a tight game that could have gone either way. One goal was always going to win it and it went Porto way. They were unlucky but thats soccer. By the way, i was impressed with their style of play and i think it is a good sign for Liverpool. Rock on man!!!!!    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hey, Liverpool beat Celtic 5-1 while chelsea&nbsp;only won by 4 goals to 2. Shame on chelsea counting the amount of money they spent compared to liverpool. Jeers to chelsea and cheers to liverpool. HAhAHA!!!        
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Yah!! Did not attend school today. Was feeling sick n tired and so decided to take a day off from school. Haha. Though i wasn't really sick. Went out in the afternoon. Received a call from my school chinese teacher and she asked me to take the test on thursday. HAi!!! Boring!!! Got to be in sch early. Anyway, dun think i m going for cross country, r u(chris). But i m still going to darren's house. Btw, chelsea juz spent another 20 million pounds on another useless player. Wat can i say... All the best for my chinese test.     
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hey, just wanna tell u tt chelsea sinks! They have a bunch of useless and overpaid&nbsp;players managed by a equally useless manager. So agorant! Chelsea also have a russian chairman who knows as little as a 2 months old baby about football. And he only knows how to spent money on lousy player. Hai, what else can i say. Not tt i dun wish to say positive things abt chelsea but i cun think of any. Anyway, they belong in the nationwide league and shld be playing there the following season. Haha!! &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         The weekened is going to be over. So fast right!! Hai, wonder if there is any school work. Anyway, had a busy day today. Went to church in the morning, had meeting with the other bb guys before proceeding for service. Some Gb girls went too. (surprise!) After church, went for lunch before going somewhere. (not going to tell). Tts all for now. Btw, can anyone tell me how to link other blogs to mine.    
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         wad a bad day!! Woke up at 5.30am even though it is a weekend  .  Had to reach school by 7am for drill practice for National Day. However, it started to rain just minutes after stepping into school. Wad luck!! Still, we had to practiced our drill uder shelter though. Later,&nbsp; with a few other bb boys n officers, we went for lunch. My lunch was horrible. A plate of rice with 3 other ingredients cost me 6 bucks. Very Expensive!! Took a cab home with Sean and he dirtied the whole cab with the crumbs from his bread.&nbsp;Fortunately, the taxi driver was blur. Haha. Saw the damn Chris online and he talked crap and fish. Hehe!!!&nbsp;         
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I can't believed that chelsea won. wat a lousy winner!!! they were on the backfoot for most on the game. juz lucky to score. their manager is also so proud. wait until chelsea get thrash and we shall see wat he have to say. anyway, arsenal is still the best......wait long, chelsea...    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        oh, i overslept today and missed cell and was late for church. Can't be help! EPL is back... the atmosphere in church was a little different. i dunnoe why??? haha. when for lunch with wee hiong and earnest and they went to bet on soccer later. oh no, have not do my hw yet. how?? its 8 plus aready. hai, nvm...just hope that chelsea lose...not that i like manchester but i juz cun stand chelsea. prepare for a thrashing by manchester!!!! 5-0!!! hohohoho...   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Liverpool was quite disappointing yesterday. though they did not lose, i expected more than that, maybe its still early?? I just hope that they dun play the boring style... and i think it may be wrong to sell owen, they really need to buy players.    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Its being some time since i last wrote. HAha! anyway, had a very tiring day today. had physical training in the morning, really difficult. then, we had to use our brain to study for the bible quiz competition. was abt to go for lunch when wee hiong called me to ask me to follow him shopping. hai, followed him and in the end, ended up buying a Liverpool home jersey which cost 75 bucks. i m so broke now. all his fault, asked me to follow him out. grrrh.... anyway, liverpool is playing later in the evening, and i m confident that they will win by 5 goals. hohoho!! but i think chelsea will lost. we shall see....    
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Oh, we had a really good parade today. Something unusual as we had swimming. However, we had physical training and bible study before swimming. We played ball games in the swimming pool. It was fun and it got quite rough sometimes. HAHA!! Anyway, heard from some people that we did quite well for our marching on friday. Well Done boys and girls!! OH YA, its my cousin 7th birthday. Happy Birthday Marcus...   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        It's a sad week. A friend was gone juz lyk this. It was a huge shock to all of us. No one had expected it. Such a nice and likeable person. He had being called up to be with the lord and we shall meet again in heaven.    
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Liverpool beat As Roma 2-1 earlier this morning. Goals by Cisse and Owen was enough to secure a victory. Heard that Igor Biscan was impressived too. Things look good!! And to make things better, Chelsea lost to Ac Milan 3-2. Boo! This shows that money does not bring success. Liverpool will be the Champion this season!!!    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Once again, the weekend is going to be over. Had a busy and tiring weekend so far and as a result, i m left with tons of homework. Help!! Help!! I still need to study for 2 tests tmr. Wonder how m i going to fare tmr. Haha. Oh, I was stuck in a place for 3 hours today because it was raining lyk cats and dogs. Forgot to bring my umbrella. HAi! And I came home really late because of it and got a scolding from my mum. Okok, Look lyk i will be burning the midnite oil. Anybody burning the midnite oil too?? Haha!!       And, I think i lost my tagboard??!!@@    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>