<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    this cat huh... very bad right? haiyo..tsk tsk tsk&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    these are pictures i took using my ex..T610.the SCDF are washing away spilt oil on the road and the traffic police is watching out for the traffic in other words EXTRA2 la...&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    this iis is a pic of my friend using his N-gage FIZO&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    K... this honda CBR 900 (valentino rossi) cool la but too yellowish right?&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    i think this hayabusa looks better.. would be a dream to be on her ....YEAH!&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    this hayabusa is a dream bike... very expensive cant afford it except if its a model&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        k la.. start studying.. bfore its too late.. on thursday night/friday morning.. i cant sleep. i thought of many stuff. one was what the F was i going to do after my 'o'... cant stand myself always play. whats up right... even i dont know. Judging from the space in my pants i think i loose bout 5cm.. bout la .. u think im that F in' clever or wat huh.. my friend email account full so cant send her stuff all that.. (2) also tak le harap sms her tak reply.. nvm lar u think i care bout her? no!! no a single F in' thing.. i just waitin for (1)...to my parents went out my sis go school and go ndp training... then i cleaned up the house.. just inserted FIFA 2004 in to my N-gage then this morning had fun  with Fizo.. then on my way home thought of the word FIFA.. once (1) something bout FIFA la.. dun want to tok bout that small thing... Today and to morrow my school will be participating in the north west art exhibiton..at plaza..To (1) out there trust me i will kill myself if i loose contact with her.. trust me..   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Whats up blog? Today stayed back for chemistry test and physics practical. Wanted to say sorry to (1) cause I asked me whether there is a test today or not. I said no, but then fat bastard Mr. lee say got test. K la “sorry for saying today no test K?” after physics practical some people were planning to play pool. Wanted to follow but..(adela) then ask a friend called weixian what time self study finish then he said “330 la” with low voice HAHAHA. There a friend called Fauzi, he pulled (1) s hair. I knew he was just playing but then, why he dare to pull someone’s hair.. It’s disrespectful. Like chui say “incorrigible”. I think I wont go steady with (2) so boring..la. Everyday thinking of (1), plain tired of that but just cant stop myself from thinking of perfect HER. Done nothing much to say already la.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Whats up…today I stayed back in school thinking I would go home with (2). Actually I stayed back in school to do my design n technology artifact. I think I will not go steady with (2) la. Cause look at the time. A few weeks more and the pre prelim will start. If I go steady with (2) it would be distracting RIGHT? So, I’ll wait till after ‘O’s maybe I start flirting to (1) only then. And I’ll repeat maybe k? Respect is something I have for everyone. Its just the amount of respect is different. Can’t wait for prom. For the people whose thinking of something bad…haha ish ish ish wats up man. I have great amount of respect for (1) k? So don’t you bull shit. That’s all for today blog blog blog wats up man  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been thinking bout what (1) said to me..She sounds right..never seen (2) going steady with someone for a long period of time. One example is Radzi(my friend)&nbsp;he got steady&nbsp;with (2) only for about two&nbsp;weeks. (1) is the only girl i thought of living my whole life with. Imagine--> me married to (2) then a few month later we get divorced. What the F. who would take care of my children(if have one lah..). People who get divorce... hai..is..is...cant stand them. So i take a few days more to think of this.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Few days ago i started to talk to a gerl name _ _ _ _(2). Nothing much happened. Last month i ask her whether she had a stead... she said she got one.. today i ask her, what his&nbsp;name was. She said currently she does not have one..(she broke up lah) that nevermind lah.. At night(juz now) i told another girl called _ _ _ _ _ _(1). I&nbsp; requested (1) for five words that fits&nbsp;(2).She said she cant think of any word.(1)asked me why i asked bout (2). I said i wanted to go steady wif (2). (1) asked, why i chose (2) when there are better gals out thera.&nbsp;I replied "what better gals, U" she replied no la.."....i kinda noe how she lyk ok...tak takot ditipu ke?" ... her last message for the day was for me to take care and be careful it could be painful.. Then (2) sms me giving me a goodnight paragraph saying:     &nbsp;   Mengundur Daku Ke Alam mimpi,    Dgn izin tuhan akanku kembali.    jika pergi dan tiada kembali,    ku pohon doa keikhlasan di hati...    selamat malam buatmu sahabatku     
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Today got long story but this first one is just a test k?   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today went surfing... web lah.. found,observe drool over some hayabusa pictures.. too bad la cant ride them when im 18  the CC too high.. NEWSFLASH------>today mr/mrs mah is leaving school,for good, sorry there, next A girl name liza sent an email to a person known as zulkickflip. she mention something bout juz friends.. to know further details stay tune on channel 14..next two news one good one bad.. bad news is on monday Zul will be taking his o levels oral.. good news a prediction by our own predictor mr PAT(rick).. now.. mr PAT please.. good um..um..um..good watever, my prediction for today is a man in 5 years will die in a road accident involving a vespa and a HAYABUSA.... And that wraps up the news for tonight..GOOD NIGHT..&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    drool over this charming bike..to see more just search in yahoo.. hayabusa pictures&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    cute cat huh? wonder where  i get all the pictures? -wont tell ya. and one more thing the red hayabusa appeared in mission impossible 2 so catch it in action--only on channel i&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Radziyani aka RADZI (duh!!) using my phone&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    a stupid bastard singing..&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    he is doing what you think he is doing..poor whitie...picture sent by nurliza..&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    liza sent me this picture&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    wet DuDe...&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    so cute ... kidding!! just blogging la&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    aint she cute?&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>