<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I wanted to write about    junk food    today, but the day started quiet grey and the mood is different.  It feels like although a lot of people believe me (thank you all out there),  NO ONE  really believe in me, or truly think that I will win at the end. Further more, I'm not sure that I believe in me, Don't get me wrong, I'm not breaking up but the chances are pretty much against me no matter what I'll do and no matter what She did, does and will do. Depressing! Isn't it?  I played with the thought of what would I do today, after such a year, if everything in matter would disappear.......  Probably -  a fisherman in Iceland .   &nbsp;    

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   J. went out yesterday to meet Joe  OR  Kim  Or  both, in Brooklyn  Or  the city.  At 21:45 gave up the idea of seen Ber a sleep and took off.  Have no idea when did she came back.   Just fixed the time stamp - I was't awake that late yesterday.      

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Project Ber is on the move .  I am exited, scared,speechless, happy, nervous and I my hands shaken' but I promise myself and I promise Ber to write and do everything that I can to tell the story.  One mission is already month and an half behind me. No more cigarettes!!!. I don't know for how long? And I don't promise eternity but I'm clean and proud of it.     

						
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Friends of mine  G  and  J  just had a baby. He was born four and a half weeks ago , healthy and beautiful or as his proud dad say the cutest baby in the world. I saw them today for the first time - a new family and they looked comfortable with each other as it should be.  G  is going to be (or better say already been) a good daddy and  J  is a natural by birth so the baby is in good hands. They called him  Hudson  after the river which I find as a nice gesture for mother nature, it's almost like calling a kid Thames , Nile or Yarkon in England, Egypt or Israel. It's very cozy to be named with such a known name, makes you feel at home where ever you go. There's a  Hudson  street almost in every city over the US, and Little  Hudson  will be able to say proudly that these street were named after him, and no one would be able to argue. I know the feeling. I, actually, stopped making a story or turn my head around every time someone is calling my name here ( Eli  = " My God "). I got used to the fact that people need to mention me when big events occur (for the good and the bad). And as a modest guy, I take it naturally and wave for blessing from time to time (so as give kisses to little kids and old lady's).  Before  Hudson  was born I offered  G  an idea to make some money by supplying a demand in the market that no one have still put his attention to. I suggested to quickly learn to identify the baby's cries (when we spoke about it he was still nameless), record them and burn them on a CD. " Your Baby's Cry for Dummies " was a possible name for this wonderfully which could help hundreds and thousands of new parents around the world to relate and understand better their new baby and the way he express he's needs. Not only that, I also see a lot of potential in the single/gay/lesbian community or just by the people that gave up the idea of having a baby by themselves and that still want to experience that sweet sounds of nature. Imagine setting an alarm for the middle of the night with the fresh sound of a crying baby....  Any way  G  &amp;  J  and little  Hudson  -  MAZAL TOV  - the way they say it in my language.   

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   On Wednesday they made me a small celebration of my Birthday with a cake and a song At MOLA. Good chocolate cake with candles as it should. I had to make a wish and blow off the candles which I Did four times. The damn candles just wouldn't turn off and would turn back on few seconds after I blew them off.  One would think about the consequences on my wish?!!!  Happy Birthday!  

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I like  HOT DOGS!    I admit that I would probably say yes to an hot dog seven times out of ten, and I'm not that picky about them I would rarely say no because it is a hot dog from that brand or another. And don't try to tell me that  HOT DOGS  are made from the lauziest pieces of meat in the best cases and from other crap on other cases, It is me who claimed that  HOT DOGS  have a minimum content of any meat at all and that it is very likely to find pieces of newspapers in an  HOT DOG . I still Like them, though I never really try to find signs of newspaper in them - I just take a bite and enjoy.    Are  HOT DOGS  junk food?...... Probably Yes, though I'm not sure that that is the common answer here in the US and especially in Manhattan.     Ber likes  HOT DOGS  too!.   He likes to nibble on them , sometimes with the bun and sometimes without. Unlike his dad he won't say yes to an  HOT DOG  every time and the rate of Yes would probably go down to four Out of Ten times. But he does like them and enjoy eating them nevertheless. Sometimes I am committing a sin and I ask him if a would like to have an  HOT DOG , on other times I let him grab my hand an pull me to the  HOT DOGS  stand by he High school. So.... I am feeding My son Junk Food!!!. I am guilty.   Don't let the fact that we are eating a lot of other things together to change your opinion.    Don't let the fact that he is having  HOT DOGS  with other people to change your opinion.    Don't be fouled to think that the same Pasta that I make as other People is O.K. - It is Junk food - believe me.    And don't let my efforts to touch fruits so he can have them spread dust on your eyes, these fruits are probably Junk Food ( and not an Organic one).    Junk Food is as it seems is a matter of the person that consume it and a factor of his/her hunger, But I'm guilty anyway, so enjoy the  HOT DOGS , Viva le Junk!!!!   

						
</post>


</Blog>