<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I'm in the middle of packing for my trip to TN.&nbsp; I actually went about a month ago for Ashli's birthday.&nbsp; Ashli is my beautiful niece who just turned two!&nbsp; Well, I'd best get back to packing - I would like to leave as soon as possible once Maureen gets home! 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     Serene Path   urlLink       This picture was taken at Long Hunter State Park in Mount Juliet, TN. This was part of the two mile trail. Gorgeous scenery. Deep breath...exhale...ahhh     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've never tried a blog before, so here goes.&nbsp; Maureen and I are going to drive to TN tonight because my grandma is really sick.&nbsp; She has not been well for many years, but this time she is really NOT WELL.&nbsp; She will be leaving the world soon and I look forward to seeing her for what will probably be the last time.&nbsp; I am excited that Maureen is coming with me.&nbsp; I don't think that she's ever been to Nashville and I think she will really enjoy it,&nbsp;despite the circumstances.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;      
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My mind is blank.  Actually, I have so much on my mind that it is hard to put it into words.  I am in TN again.  This is my third trip in less than two months.  I've come to try and help my sister as she is caring for my grandmother...so this is no vacation.        I have to try and find a job as soon as I get back to TX.  I know work is a four-letter word, but it is necessary.  Paying bills is a good thing.  Personally, I'd rather win the lottery, but you have to play to win and I can't afford to play.          
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Maureen and Ashli  urlLink    - see post below - 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The trip to TN was wonderful.  Maureen had a great time and I don't think she felt at all out of place.  Ashli loved her and everyone else thought the world of her as well!  Now she's trying to claim Ashli so we finally decided that I would let her have joint "auntship".  It was good to see my grandma again and I don't think that it has really hit me yet that she won't on this earth much longer.    
    
</post>


</Blog>