<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      woke up around 11 plus... bum ard @ home... later, ard 5 plus, mom,dad,sofea, yasmine and me went to mustafa center to get some gift for my kuz wei yue... well he's going away to San Fransisco for further study... got him a Adidas basketball singlet...coolios... like those niggers outfit..hahaha... then while waiting for my dad to fetch us from mustafa center guess who i met?????... Fandi ahmad... hahahha... he looks sooo diff... but still "i just met fandi" on our way back we went to get him a sweatshirt.... its those hip-hop black sweatshirt...SUPREME...super cool..  Later at night we went to choa chu kang.....oh had a big MacDonald feast        hip-hop....niggers....      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      hah the poa test wasn't dat diff as i tot it would be.... well actually the tot of dropping the subject next would be sooo wrong...oh well god noes... hahaha... well during eng we watched man in black and we had to do a grp work and write a report....terence, jeremy, swee shiong, habsah and myself were in a team. Well we din really have a gd artist in our grp sooo our dearest ming herng volunteered to draw for us the alien....well if the name ming herng is mentioned in the picture it's always up to no gd.... hahah he drew the alien and wrote my name as if i was the alien.... like wat the fuck... hhahahah that piece of work was suppose to be posted at the board.... he always get screw me up.... he's always up to no gd...       well guess wat i had for my lunch?? 2 bulls eye egg,3 sausages, 5 bread, cucumber and a steak.... wat the hell....im sooooo gonna be the fat gal on graduation....        &nbsp;
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    me and nora at the pool side&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      Ph   ew!! At last MT oral is over.... well it din turn out the way i expected...hahahha i tot i would soooo screw it but hahhah i think i did myself proud....it was held at CVSS.&nbsp;the invigilator was super duper funny... they were both females...well the topics was abt&nbsp;handphones, and branded stuff..... both the advantages and disadvantages...oh and wat the hell can u believe dat they dont know the brand&nbsp;HEADS and VON DUCTH??? wat the hell... hahahah...guess branded stuff is not in their dictionary a...      &nbsp;   Oh met aili, ashik's closest fren... she's ok. quite frenly... hahah...oh and also a fren from rvps... coolios...oh also im so happy coz i could solve like almost all the question from the australian math competition... very tricky but i manage to solve it (i think its correct ah) hahahha... oh we skipped a few lesson... hahahah.. me and habsah, we&nbsp;din attend the first two periods of F&N... we had our early luch to get ready for our oral... 
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      Oh luckily there weren't any SSP for social studies. I was super tired. Ming herng beg me to lend him my dvd "honey". i actually told myself nvr to lend him my dvds anymore.... hahhaha... well if u guys are wondering wat the reason is....i'll tell ya. well it was last yr dat i len him my 8 mile dvd and only a few weeks back did he returned it to me and dat also i had to ask from him. Well i was glad dat it wasn't gone or anything so i brought it back.... two days later my bro took all the dvds and started cleaning the disc.... and he ask me " farah did u're fren like change the 8 miles dvd to a chinese dvd??" wat the fuck???? i den showed ming herng the dvd and guess how he reacted??? he laughed and said eh dats the dvd for prayers... i went wat the hell.... and he said maybe lost lor... ass la he... so dats the story of y i din want to lend him my dvds.        &nbsp;
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						        &nbsp;today like any monday blues... most teachers wasn't in sch...so yea it was kind a waste of time...we sat at the study area doing our own self study.... and as usual..if u dont noe me i would sooooo slack and scribble my notebook during the self study...i just ccan't get myself to&nbsp;concentrate...and darn my prelims is in less den 2 weeks.... im sooo getting myself in deep shit...oh i just watched&nbsp; the movie '13 going30'....Oh my god...the show is super nice...i would soooo recommend it to u ppl...GO CATCH IT DUDES!! It's like my current favourite movie...hahaha...oh well i'll just write til here then... will try to upload pic( if dats possible) hahaha...cheerios!         &nbsp;      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       hey    ppl ...supp???? haha just got this thingy started like a few days back... hahah...my class had this flag day raising thing at town... we had to meet at the YMCA. at 6.45 am we all met up at sengkang train station.&nbsp;Rain was&nbsp;pouring heavily and they expect me to raise fun?? hahah... went to plaza sing to have my breakfast and took pics wif the guys...oh there were mats and minahs all over the place man.. hahah...   
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      haven been updating my blog....been busy revising for my prelims... sat for SS and eng ppr 1 on fri...its wasn't dat diff... God noes will i pass it this time... gotta start revising for my other subjects....  
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      arghhhh hoobastank with an A...(there's an inside story for dat).... they're having their concert today.... yea and i meant TODAY.... at Sentosa... omg... i sooo wish i could go...arghhhh....they must be performing like rite now....arghhh...  
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    HOOBASTANK&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      anyways have u ppl heard abt gals making use of their guys??? man how the hell did i get myself a fren like her.... she's very calculative and materialistic... damn her man and her boyfriend is too dumb to know dat he was actually being make used off and being lied... hhahaha crap la she... Oh and u noe wat??she can just like make up stories of her own and tell eveyone its real... ass man...damn fuck up...  Had to stay back for 3 hrs for geog self-study and teacher wasn't there.... ahhahah we resulted to having our own conversation... hahahah   
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						         I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved Tap on my window, knock on my door I want to make you feel beautiful I know I tend to get so insecure It doesn't matter anymore It's not always rainbows and butterflies It's compromise that moves us along My heart is full and my door's always open You can come anytime you want       woah super nice song with a superb lyrics     
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						        argh...this kuz of mine, redz, he's fucking pissing me off man... he just won't stop bitching....arghh... oh well mondays.... crap its always borin... mrs raj was away for the sec 3 camp so yea we had to do our own self study...later during MT...as usual we kind just laze ard... well i just dont get it why must there be a MT lesson... its like not fruitful at all man.... sucks...eng was great thou...hahahha...ans most of the question... superb and i got the highest point ...   
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink      clockwise:wei yue,me,syabil,yasmine,sofea,shi han,liyana    urlLink             

						
</post>


</Blog>