<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You ever notice that you feel great when you are compared to someone or something else and&nbsp;you&nbsp;come out on top?&nbsp; I really noticed that again today.&nbsp; I felt great when I someone told me that on of the other new hires that I work with was having a harder time with the work.&nbsp; I should have felt bad because he isn't totally used to the work yet, but no.&nbsp; I had to feel good because I was more or less being told that I was better.&nbsp; How very juvenile of me.&nbsp; But there are little things that can make your day, such as being honked at&nbsp;over twenty&nbsp;times while walking up and down a trucker route.&nbsp; Don't ask me why but you still have to feel good when someone admires something you are or something you can do.&nbsp; We all like praise, but is there a point when it becomes like&nbsp;an obsession.&nbsp; I think there is, like when you almost rely on those kind of comments from someone just to feel like you are wanted or needed.&nbsp; As people we need to feel like we are something that has a purpose, and that we are admirable.&nbsp; It is something that we all crave, if you get it from doing charity work, that is great for you.&nbsp; If you get it from receiving awards, that is good for you too.&nbsp; If you get it from guys who check you out, then you may need to assess how low your self worth is.&nbsp; We will only tolerate abuse, in any form, to the level that we abuse ourselves.&nbsp; We will&nbsp;stop taking the abuse when it hits that point.&nbsp; And if our self worth is that low then we will take everybody's personal opinions so personally that we will become, dependent on the compliments of others.&nbsp; We need to realize that we all have different strengths and abilities and that there is more to us than what meets the eye.&nbsp; If we need to have other look bad in order to make us look good, then we have to stop and think.&nbsp; When we are no longer able to make ourselves happy there is a problem.&nbsp; When we become dependent there is a problem.&nbsp; When we are only happy when someone else is miserable there is a problem.&nbsp; If you have no self worth there is a problem.&nbsp; I'm not saying if you ever feel happy because&nbsp; in someone's eyes you are better than someone else you should go see a shrink.&nbsp; But I'm what I'm trying to say is we should remember that even if no one says it, we are something phenomenal, and even if people disapprove if there is something that truly makes you happy you should do it for yourself.&nbsp; Yes, there are other people in your life that probably matter a lot, but what is the point in living if you aren't able to enjoy yourself?&nbsp; I want to enjoy my self, so I try to do whatever makes me happy just so that I don't forget how important it is to enjoy the moment, and not live waiting for the future.&nbsp; You have to see what you have, and not what you don't, who should be able to decide what is beautiful and what is not.&nbsp; Everything is beautiful in its on way.&nbsp; Who is to judge what is right and what is wrong.&nbsp; If your intentions are good that is all that matters.&nbsp; This probably made no sense, I'm just going to stop babbling.&nbsp; This went from organized thought to the way people talk in coffee shops.    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I seem to be listening to music that causes me to go nowhere but further into my own world.&nbsp; Every single one of the CD's that I have bought in the last three months are rather depressing.&nbsp; All I can think about is how I haven't even talked to two of my friends since Saturday, granted I don't talk to one too often ... But the other one I was talking to twice a day for the last couple of weeks.&nbsp; So as you could probably tell I feel low, like almost as low as I did last summer when I spent all of my time in my basement reading and seldomly talking to anyone.&nbsp; I just want to get out of this rut but there is nothing that I can feel like I can do about it.&nbsp; I try to be social and all I can do is really sit there while I am being hit on by guys at work, for&nbsp;that matter they don't even look that bad buy I'm not even really responding to it.&nbsp; My goal this summer was to have fun and powder the shell that I have been working on breaking out of for the last nine years.&nbsp; I feel as though I am invisible and none of my friends would even notice if I didn't talk to them in two weeks.&nbsp; I may seem like the type, at this point anyway, that would commit suicide but hear me out, I think I would never do it because it just isn't worth it.&nbsp; It seems pointless at times but in the past it has always gotten better, and plus then you are just caving in, you are taking the easy way out.&nbsp; I am a person who doesn't like to show when they are weak.&nbsp; This is one of those times, I need to get out of this rut for my own sake, not for anyone else but myself.&nbsp; I would like the guy who I like to not be so blind and notice me, what he says about why he likes my friend is exactly what we have.&nbsp; In theory we would be great together, in theory.&nbsp; My music is all, "poor me" as my friend would say.&nbsp; I need something that will just mellow me out without making me obsessed with the negativity that is my mind.&nbsp; Actually the thing that would ultimately help would be to find an activity that I don't think while doing.&nbsp; Most people would say it is impossible but I think I may think too much.&nbsp; All I seem to do is go through all the "what if's" in my mind.&nbsp; I need to get out of the madness that is my mind and my alternate reality, and get back to the real world.   
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Why is it that whenever there is something or someone we want we just can't have them?&nbsp; Is it that they do not desire us or that it just isn't possible for us to have everything that we want.&nbsp; Lets face it, when a celebrity says, " Money doesn't buy you happiness," we reply with, "Bull shit."&nbsp; But even if you have all the tools at your disposal, sometimes we just can't get what we want when there is nothing stopping us in theory.&nbsp; For instance an apartment that you totally were meant to have, you met all of the requirements, you can actually afford the rent, and it has a kick ass location, and yet someone else got that apartment.&nbsp; And then there are jobs, you go into the waiting area early, a lot of the people arrive after you, you have experience that exceeds their expectations, and you look awesome in the dress code without so much as being next to the line of non-acceptance, but someone else who in your opinion less qualified then you got the job.&nbsp; And last but not least, there are guys.&nbsp; You have similar interests, you look good together, and there are no awkward pauses even when you first meet them, but there will always be someone else that they have their eyes on.&nbsp; This someone else may be a friend, or better yet your best friend, or someone who has nothing in common with the person, or who doesn't even have the same feelings toward the person when you are right there.&nbsp; How crappy does life have to treat us???&nbsp; There is always something missing, it is near impossible to be truly satisfied with your life for even a second.&nbsp; I mean, I listen to the guy, even give him pointer on how to get the courage to ask someone out who isn't even interested in him, sure I could like say, "I think I really like you," or something along those lines but no, I have to be the "friend."&nbsp; The worst part is that I am the "friend" for both sides.&nbsp; I feel like I should help the guy out to get what he really wants, like I know his intentions are good but that isn't what is meant to be.&nbsp; And for the non-interested friend, I have to feel more obligated to helping them out more simply because I have known her longer, and she wants me to have to break it to the guy that she really isn't interested.&nbsp; Wouldn't be so hard, IF I DIDN'T LIKE THE DAMN GUY!!!&nbsp; I don't like his friends, I don't even like some of the things he likes but it is like I feel a connection with him when I try to help him, he makes me want to be a good person and do the right thing.&nbsp; I am happy to try and help him gain confidence, mean while I can't even do the things that I am telling him he should do, such as just tell her to her face that he really likes her.&nbsp; Last night I even had the perfect opportunity to tell him how I felt but I just couldn't do it.&nbsp; I told him that I normally have a hard time opening up to people I don't know that well, and he asked why I could do that with him, my response was "I really don't know, I just can."&nbsp; Sure it isn't as bad as it could have been but it was an opportunity that I shouldn't have turned down.&nbsp; But it was my birthday, and I still haven't confessed and told him that there isn't really a way that my friend would ever go out with him but, I still missed an opportunity that will probably never happen again.&nbsp; But that is that sad story of how my brain and my heart have conflicted within the last two weeks.&nbsp; I think I got the most of that out of my system.   
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "Whoa, there are chicks on this ride" Had to put that one in otherwise I would totally forget it. I don't have too much to talk about other than the fact that I seem to be putting back on some of that weight that I lost, so that sucks. Ummm... Yeah... I really don't have anything to say, so I'm just gonna leave it at that.  
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I am so over Kevin. But as for the Carmicheal situation, this looks like it will become a force to be reckoned with.  
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I lost my phone today, but I got it back. I was sooooooo incredibly like, frustrated, and pissed and scared at the same time. But this little kid found it outside of 711 so yeah after I called it and he answered it, I arranged to meet him so that I could pick it up. He was like 11 and his name was DJ. So that explains the title of this thing. I also got sunburned today, I've gotten burnt about 7 times this year. I didn't have enough time before Gabe got here to put on sun block, but the whole it was 40 degrees outside thing didn't help. But it was fun after I got my cell back. We walked around a bunch, and I got a plain cheap tank so that I can go with Sean and Carmicheal to the water slides. But I still don't know who all is going. But I thought last night was fun with them, so I agreed to go. Hmm, I can't really think of anything to talk about so this is all I'm going to write. 
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So, yeah. I met Sean today, as well as Carmicheal. I don't know how to spell his name for the record. We wandered around Vernon a bit. I t was overall pretty enjoyable. Carmicheal is pretty nice, not overly punk or anything, though his 3 piercings would possibly suggest otherwise, friendly, thinks a good bit actually, and his looks aren't disappointing. He does the whole physics, math, info tech thing. So he seems like the kind of guy I may end up interested in. I've more or less only talked to him once, but I have met him once before. For like 1 minute. Sean seems a bit friendlier during the summer and I am actually thinking about going to the water slides with them on Sunday. For the record the title of this entry does have something to do with what happened today, but not too much. We went to Safeway and they stole two cans of pop, well actually Sean did. But it isn't a big deal. It's just I couldn't think of anything better to title this entry. So there you have it, actually they left like... 16 minutes ago. So I really don't feel like I have that much to talk about... I just felt like I should record this little bit so that it seems like I actually did something today aside from attempt a tattoo design yet again and sleep. So yeah, that is all I'm gonna write because I have to meet Gabe tomorrow at noon. 
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I love days off, actually I just like the idea of them. I like to have things planned for my days off, and normally I do more walking and work-like activities on these days than when I am actually at work. It is kind of funny. Hmmm, well... I'm trying to lay off on the spending of money but it isn't working too well... I spent close to $100 dollars in a week. So yeah, I'm trying to stop that. My first step will be to not go into the mall during at least lunch... For that matter not go into a place where I can easily spend the money in my bank account with my card. This will be hard. What kind of a place doesn't accept debit cards nowadays??? Well I will just have to control myself because at this rate I won't be able to afford it... And plus I want to go shopping... Like hard core before school... It is like the thing I look foreword to in the summer. But this isn't news to me but it does tend to shock people, as soon as it turns August, I start to become impatient waiting for my school schedule. It might sound weird but like I do enjoy doing noting for a while but then I get depressed and really bored, and sometimes I get fat so it isn't a good thing for me to do absolutely nothing during the summer. Most people go out and do the whole beach thing, but I really don't like the beach, I don't really like the outdoors that much . So as a direct result of that and the anti-social factor that tends to happen to me through the summer, I spend a lot of time in my basement. I just like having decisions where I can alter them a bit to better suit me, but they are still set enough that it isn't all up to me. Example of set, going to work, it is scheduled and I can't really turn down the shifts because then I will lose my job. Example of up to me decision, deciding whether or not to go to college. But I like things where I just go with it, and that is what school is for me. I get to alter my courses, choose my friends, and decide how I should dress. But I more or less still have to go, work is less lenient but it is still structured enough for me. Like before I was all I'm going to college but now I don't even know if I want to go. Well I'm tired now, so that is all I'm gonna write.  
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        One day I'm like "I really like him," the next after he is aware of the fact I'm like "I'm so over him," today I'm like "I don't know how I feel about him. Do I believe his friend or do I believe my heart, or should I believe my logic?" As you can tell I most likely just need a person undaunted by this situation to tell me what to do and how to feel. There are times when I think he is lame, there are times when I think he is my savior and there are times when I just want to be friends. I AM SUCH A MESS RIGHT NOW!!! This is so un me. I am the girl that never had a little "boyfriend" in like grade two... For that matter I am the person who has never had a boyfriend... I'm the person who didn't really have a crush or anything until like high school. I'm the person who doesn't believe in love. I'm the person who put "Pawn an engagement ring, bonus if its mine" on my 50 things to do before I die list. This isn't me. I was logical, I was sarcastic, I was ... Sara. Now I'm this lame mess that doesn't get attention from any guys, whether they like me or not. Am I that undesirable??? Am I the person who is destined to die alone??? I give up on trying to figure this mess out.  
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Ok, I admit, I cheated. But wouldn't you had the opportunity presented itself? I got Jerry to tell Kev that I liked him. Sure this way I have no real way of telling how he reacted to it but still. I do feel somewhat relieved. I don't really feel like talking right now so that is all I really have to say. 
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I feel like I have been uncovered from the dark depths of loneliness. I have been talked to by people! My one formerly depressed friend is more optimistic! And I have been told that yes, I should have a party. I feel good today, and that seems to be a rare thing in my world, to be truly happy for even a moment. I'm currently doing the ever so harsh task of loading all of my CD's back onto my computer. So far I only have like a third of them on here, but it isn't that bad because if I had a music downloader for the last few months that I have been without one this task would be worse. I'm also not putting my crappy CD's on here again, I'm the kind of person who never throws out CD's, but rather keeps them as a reminder of were I have come from, so that I hopefully I only progress instead of regress. Though I am listening to my somewhat depressing music, I am not feeling depressed... THIS IS GREAT!!! Um, I'm feeling bubbly so I'm going to pointlessly babble until I get tired of typing. I was watching the A&amp;E thing on Blonde Bombshells, sure I've seen it like 3 times already but I'm just fascinated by them. The 3 that the thing is on are Jayne Mansfield, Brigitte Bardot and of course Marilyn Monroe. I think their appeal is that their confidence was amazing, they weren't really concerned with their figures, though the 50's were the time for curvy women. They had this insane control, Bardot sure maybe she wasn't the most politically correct person but she did the whole save the animals thing as well as politics. And Mansfield she worked so hard for what she loved, sure she went downhill really fast near the end but you need to look at the good things about a personality right? And Monroe she was someone who had this control, it didn't really seem like she had that much, but look at how many people were behind here at the height of her fame, also self destructive near the end. But there are qualities that you have to admire about a lot of people . You just have to look past the traits that you think are undesirable. They can be friends, politicians, musicians or even volunteers. There is always something there, and that is what I tend to search for in other people, even if they may appear to be weird, and I seem to think that there is something else going though their minds I will try to figure out what it is, and if it is a trait that I admire.  
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Why is it that when ever I have good intentions people have to test me in one way or another. Like testing my patience or tollerance. Why can't they just do the damn thing like they do every other thing they do throughout the day. But no, they have to take a really long time and pushmy buttons. Well, there are virtues that I may possess, but I don't believe that patience is one of them. That is my rant, I just wanted to get that out. 
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I have this thing about guys who work in grocery stores. It is kind of odd. It is like, funny. Ok it isn't that weird considering how many guys I know that work in a grocery store, but still. There was this one time, and it was like the first and most memorable incident. I was in Safeway and I was with my friend and her sister. Her sister was going down to the states for a while so she was picking up things like toothpaste and a toothbrush. I think that we had dropped off her artificial leg earlier that day, so she was on crutches and as you may know, it isn't pleasant standing in line while on crutches, so I stood in line for her. And we had been driving around for at least an hour because we went to Kelowna for the day. So I was to say the least beat, due to me being prone to motion sickness. Any way, I was in the express checkout lane when this guy working the cash register was apparently checking me out. I didn't really notice at that moment or I would have responded better. But from what I can remember he had sandy blonde hair, he was tall, kind of typical guy lanky, and he may have had braces. I think I had braces or I just got mine off recently at the time, so it didn't really faze me. But he was all, "How are you today?" My response was, "Fine," but I mumbled it because I was drained. And after that and I paid for the stuff he was all, "Have a   great   day." Serious emphasis on the great. And as soon as we got out of earshot, my friend and her sister started laughing their asses off. I couldn't figure out why. They were all, "You were being checked out by the express checkout guy!!!" well it is kind or amusing when you think of it. And it was really amusing, though it may not sound like it, you just had to be there. But now I work in a grocery store, I have two jobs in the one store so there is plenty of time to check out the half decent guys, so yay for me. But there is this one service clerk who went to my school but he graduated this year and I still have a year left. Anyways, I think he is to say the least hot. I have the whole time I knew him. So like... 4 years. But he had a girlfriend, who I've known since kindergarten, but she cheated on him so he dumped her. Any ways, I do believe that he has been checking me out the whole time I've been working there, so like 3 months. But the problem is that he doesn't talk to too many people, like casually. So, as a result of my hypocritical ways of being to chicken to make the first move. I think that if anything were ever to happen, it would be a few months. But I'll keep you guys informed. And there are a few other guys, but I'm more interested in Josh at the moment. Did I mention that I am almost over Kevin? The key word being almost, there is no telling if it will start up again. But yeah, I'm tired and I have to work in like ... 8 1/2 hours. So this is all I'm going to write right now.  
</post>


</Blog>