<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "I also count all things loss for the excellence of the knowledge of Christ Jesus my Lord, for whom I have suffered the loss of all things, and count them as rubbish that I may gain Christ and be found in Him, not having my own righteousness which is from the law, but that which is through faith in Christ..."&nbsp; (Phil 3:7-11)   A question has been posed to me (and I have also wondered) is this: "If my righteousness is only through faith, and not works.&nbsp; And if all my righteousness is as filthy rags, then what's the point of trying to be 'good' all the time?"   Well, our goal is not to "'be good all the time".&nbsp; Listen to Paul in these verses.&nbsp; He wants to know Christ.&nbsp; He wants to know the power of&nbsp;Jesus' resurrection and the fellowship of His sufferings.&nbsp; Why does he press on?&nbsp; "I press on, that I may lay hold of that for which Christ Jesus has also laid hold of me."&nbsp; (v.12)   Jesus died for you.&nbsp; But that's not all.&nbsp; He has a purpose for you.&nbsp; Press on!&nbsp; Know&nbsp;Him!  &nbsp;  On a personal note: I went street witnessing with a friend last night.&nbsp; We met many people who knew God and went to church, yet couldn't tell us what the Gospel was nor why Jesus died.&nbsp; There was one guy though who, in retrospect, I'm&nbsp;convinced is one of the reasons God lead me out last night.&nbsp; He was an older muslim gentleman... I'll just ask that you pray for him... pray that God will work in his heart to seek truth and to see Jesus.   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "... Jesus, who being in very nature God, did not consider equality with God something to be grasped.&nbsp; But made himself nothing, taking on the very nature of a servant, being made in human likeness and being found in appearance as a man He humbled Himself and became obedient to death even the death on a cross." (Phil 2:5-9)  "... work out your own salvation with fear and trembling.&nbsp; For it is God who works in you both to will and to do for His good pleasure" (vs. 12-13)  Has the Holy Spirit laid something/someone on your heart?&nbsp; Is it really going to be that inconvenient for you?&nbsp; Humble yourself and serve God by doing that thing or loving that person.&nbsp; What is this life that we should store up treasures on Earth... "where moth and rust destroy and where thieves break in and steal"?&nbsp;   We can even tie this back into love with discernment.&nbsp; Don't just love the people who can benefit you (i.e. love your boss b/c they can give you a raise) rather be sure to love people who can't repay you in any way.&nbsp;   On a personal note... I'm going street witnessing tonight with a friend from church... if anyone's reading this... you can pray that we will be humble and that God will soften the hearts of those that we interact with.&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ... "that you stand fast in one spirit," &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "with one mind striving together for the faith of the Gospel," &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "and not in any way terrified by your adversaries."&nbsp; (Philippians 1:27-28)  This seems to expand on the whole  love smartly  idea.&nbsp; If we are loving smartly then our lives will show these results, namely unity in the faith.&nbsp; Paul goes on in the beginning of chapter 2 encouraging them to "be like minded, having the same love, being of one accord, of the same mind."&nbsp; "Let nothing be done through selfish ambition or conceit but in lowliness of mind let each esteem others better than himself.&nbsp; Let each of you look out not only for his own interests, but also for the interest of others."  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "And this I pray that your love may abound still more and more in knowledge and all discernment..."&nbsp; (Philippians 1:9)  I read this passage about a week and a half ago and I've been gearing my devos around this subject.&nbsp; Here are my thoughts...  Over and over in the Bible we are reminded to "love God" and to "love one another".&nbsp; This verse in Phillipians changed my perspective a little bit.&nbsp; The apostle Paul is praying that the Philippian's love will grow in knowledge and discernment.&nbsp; This tells me that it is preferable to love  smartly  rather than  blindly .&nbsp;   So what does it mean to "love smartly"?&nbsp; It means that we have a goal to our love.&nbsp; We have a purpose for loving.&nbsp; That purpose (as Paul summarizes in v. 11) is to glorify and praise God.  Paul lists four direct results of the union of love with knowledge: 1. Ability to approve the things that are excellent. 2. Sincerety 3. Be without offense 4. Be filled with the fruits of righteousness  So what applications can we draw from this? Suppose a Christian brother comes up to you and says that he very hungry but he has no money to buy food.&nbsp; What is the loving thing to do?  Up to this point, my default " loving " answer would be: "give him some food/money".&nbsp; It's quick, easy, and when I'm done I can walk away feeling quite righteous because of my unselfish charity.  However, if I were to love smartly my actions would differ depending the specific situation.&nbsp; Remember that my goal is to glorify God.&nbsp; We know that God desires His servants to be good stewards of what He has given us (time, resources, etc).&nbsp; If it turns out that this brother is just lazy and jumping from charity to charity getting free meals and squandering the money he receives, then the loving thing to do would be to confront him and point out his hypocrisy.&nbsp; I would even say that the loving thing may be to let him spend a day or two without food in order to shake him up and get him serious about his responsibilties.  Bear in mind however, the story of the prodigal son.&nbsp; If he repents of his ways then we are to forgive and restore him.&nbsp; (Repentance of the mind is reflected in the walk and is different than merely repenting of words.)  I'll try to keep you posted on additional thoughts and corroborating verses... 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hmmm... this is an interesting paradigm shift.&nbsp; Many great people in history kept personal journals and recorded daily events along with what they learned or felt.&nbsp; Then many years after their death someone published it and let the world see into the mind of such an extraordinary person.&nbsp; Here... we've sped up the process and cut out the middleman.&nbsp; Now I can record events along with my thoughts and feelings and instantly make it available to billions of people around the globe (not that I think even the smallest fraction of those people will&nbsp; know  about this log&nbsp;let alone  read &nbsp;it).&nbsp; With that being said... here begins my journal...  (We'll see how current this gets kept... )  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok... pardon me if I take a break from 1 Corinthians for a week and skip over to something I heard preached over the weekend. (I fled the county during hurricane Charlie... err... I decided to check up on my parents in Ft. Lauderdale over the weekend. :) So this is from the pastor who spoke at my parent's church)  The message was about being in the 'wilderness'.  He spoke about how the Spirit led Jesus into the wilderness before He began His ministry and how Jesus often went out to the wilderness ('solitary place') to pray.  Two of the main points that he made were these: 1.) God often brings you to the wilderness to get your attention and 2.) Don't leave the wilderness until you have a sense of purpose.  That struck me because oftentimes I feel as if coming to Florida was God sending me into the wilderness.  In the past I've compared it to be like God sending Moses to Midian for 40 years.  So my question is: God why did you send me here?  (What is my purpose?)  In praying this question to God he brought a passage of Scripture to mind: Romans 12:1-2 which says: "I beseech you therefore, brethren, by the mercies of God, that you present your bodies a living sacrifice, holy, acceptable to God, which is your reasonable service.  And do not be conformed to this world, but be transformed by the renewing of your mind, that you may prove what is that good and acceptable and perfect will of God."  Do you see God's answer to my question?  Well... God's response to my question?  If you want to know the will of God, you will not be conformed to this world.  In fact you will let yourself be transformed by the renewing of your mind.  The Holy Spirit is right now renewing my mind.  However I need to make a decision to allow that change of mind to change my walk... and when my walk is changed... I will not be conformed to the world's standards.  But God went on... the next passage that came to mind was 1 Corinthians 13: 1-3 "Though I...     speak with the tongues of men and of angels...     have the gift of prophecy...     understand all mysteries and all knowledge...     have all faith, so that I could remove mountains...     bestow all my goods to feed the poor...     give my body to be burned...     but have not love, it profits me nothing."  What good does it do to have a changed life but have not love?  God doesn't care about that... He is not a 'kill-joy' God who wants me to be miserable.  He wants to set me free so that I can love.  But what is love?  Verses 4-7: "Love...     suffers long...     is kind...     does not envy...     does not parade itself...     is not puffed up...     does not behave rudely...     does not seek its own...     is not provoked...     thinks no evil...     does not rejoice in iniquity...     rejoices in the truth...     bears all things...     believes all things...     hopes all things...     endures all things."  Pray that this will impact me.  Pray that I will let myself be transformed by the renewing of my mind.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "But with me it is a very small thing that I should be judged by you or by a human court. In fact, I do not even judge myself." (1 Cor 4:3).  It seems to me that the word 'judge' in this verse is referring to "evaluating how righteous or faithful a person is." I say this for three reasons:  1.) The issue Paul has been addressing is that the Corinthians were making a judgement as to who was more spiritual Paul or Apollos. 2.) I read the transition from 4:2 to 4:3 like this: "It is required that stewards be found faithful, but God is the one who determines that, not you Corinthians." 3.) In v. 5 Paul again says that God will reveal the heart: "I know of nothing against myself, yet I am not justified by this; but He who judges me is the Lord. Therefore judge nothing before the time until the Lord comes who will...reveal the counsels of the hearts" (4:4-5).  God will reveal whether or not a person was righteous in their hearts. A mans actions, even though they may seem righteous and holy, may come from a corrupt and selfish heart. The point Paul is making to us is: we are not to be the judge of that... God is. I love the fact that Paul says he does not judge himself, I tend to to do that a lot... judge my own actions trying to figure out whether or not I'm doing things with the correct motive. It is true that we are not to be selfishly motivated, however, in those situations where everything gets fuzzy, I'd say: make the decision that looks like you're loving the person... and let God be the judge of your motive.  How is this different than in 5:3 where Paul says: "For I indeed, as absent in body but present in spirit, have already judged... him who has done this deed." This situation does not require a judgement call on a person's motives. This is regarding a person who is committting an undisputable act of sexual immorality. There is no question of guilt and the person shows no repentance or remorse about their actions. Therefore "deliver such a one to Satan for the destruction of the flesh, that his spirit may be saved in the day of the Lord Jesus." (v. 5)   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "For the wisdom of this world is foolishness with God." (1 Cor 3:18)  Paul is addressing those "wise" and smug Corinthians who like to rock back in their chairs and compliment themselves on how much wiser they are than all these other Christians.  Why do they think like this?  Their reasoning is because "I am of Paul" or "I am of Apollos" (v. 4).  They are giving their allegiance to men and boasting about how this makes them better than someone whose allegiance is with someone else.  How does Paul reply to this?  "Let no one boast in men" (v. 21) and then "therefore I urge you, imitate me." (4:16).  What does it mean to imitate Paul... read 4:12-13:   "We labor, working with our own hands.  Being reviled, we bless; being persecuted, we endure; being defamed, we entreat."  The Message translates that passage:   "We pick up odd jobs anywhere we can to eke out a living.  When they call us names, we say, 'God bless you.'  When they spread rumors about us, we put in a  good word for them."  "Imitate me."  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Now if anyone builds on this foundation with gold, silver, precious stones, wood, hay, straw, each one's work will become clear; for the Day will declare it, because it will be revealed by fire; and the fire will test each one's work, of what sort it is." (1 Cor 3:12)  I've seen this passage differently this morning than I've seen it in previous times.  Normally I apply this to a persons actions or works that he performs in his life.  However, putting this into context we see that the "building" that is being constructed is the Church (1 Cor 3:9).  Paul is talking about the worth of the materials that we are using to build up the Church.  (When I use 'Church' with a capital 'C' then I mean all Christians... the body of Christ... as opposed to just our local congregations.)   So what does it mean to use "gold, silver, and precious stones" as opposed to "wood, hay, or straw" to build the Church?  Wood, hay, and straw are cheap, easy to find, and easy to use.  It doesn't take too much effort to build a structure quickly.  Is that how we build the church?  Does this describe a Sunday School teacher who prepares their lesson the night before?  What about the person who counsels a friend by throwing out a number of Christian cliche's and then hangs up the phone without really listening to and praying with their friend?   To build with gold, silver, and precious stones takes time and effort.  Labor in prayer for and with your friend.  Spend all week preparing and re-preparing the Sunday School lesson.  Jesus says "Seek and ye shall find, knock and the door will be open"  That applies to salvation, but it also applies to our current walk.  Seek Jesus, desire to know Him, desire to know the Father's purpose for your life, desire to love the people that God loves.  Put your blood, sweat, and tears into this effort.  This has immediate application to myself.  First, I find myself guilty of my two examples: last minute Sunday School lessons, and cheap counsel (although not always).  So I myself need to work on that.  Second, even these postings... I sit here, read a chapter, and in 20 minutes spout off an interpretation and application, then go to work.  What effort went into that?  Here is my disclaimer on this... :)  My primary reason for beginning this blog was to force myself to find some application in my daily devos (devotions, quiet times, scripture readings, etc).  Far too often I'd read a passage (often times losing my concentration and daydreaming (or even regular dreaming) multiple times) and when I'd get done, I'd close my Bible, walk out the door and not remember a single thing I had learned.  My thought process is that if I decide to post what I've learned, then I force myself to find some application in the passage and not only that, I have a record of all the things the Holy Spirit has taught me.   So you, as a reader, be aware.  These postings are not necessarily 100% theologically sound... but if you have some time, spend some effort thinking about these things post comments, ask questions or point out inaccuracies or inconsistancies, or even let me know how this encouraged you.   Alright... time for work... have a great day!  (and put some effort into it)  ;) 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "For where there are envy, strife, and divisions among you, are you not carnal and behaving like mere men?" (1 Cor 3:3).  We must be very careful about creating divisions in the body of Christ. One of the more popular divisions today is with individual churchs i.e. "my church is better than your church." We must guard against strife [def: contention for superiority], with other Christians. Have you ever tried to be a "better Christian" than someone else? I think that's strife. Why is your goal to be better than them? Your eyes should be on Christ... and if they are on Christ then your desire should be to build up the other person even more.  I think I'll end here... there's more I want to say about the 2nd half of the passage... but I slept in a little bit today... so I'll pick it up tomorrow. But the point of today is:  Are you jealous of someone because of something they have that you want? Are you tired of Mr. or Miss perfect always getting all the praise for everything they do? Are you not going to hang out those 'backslidden' Christians because they go to the wrong church?  Grow up. Life is not about you (or me for that matter... a fact I'm still trying to learn). These people are people that Jesus loves. Jesus died for them. If He has taken the time to love them... why can't you? 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Though many of us are not wise by this world's standards God chooses to reveal His mysteries to us through the Holy Spirit.  That is one of the reasons that God gave us His Spirit... to be our Counselor.  The Spirit teaches us the things of God so that we may be able to judge all things yet we ourselves cannot be judged by anyone (1 Cor 2:15).  We have the mind of Christ (v. 16).  Do any questions pop into your mind about this?  Here are some of mine:  - What about all the sinful acts that have been committed by Christians claiming that "God is telling me to do this...". - If all Christians have the mind of Christ, they why is there such disunity in the Church? - How do we know what is from the Spirit and what is from the flesh?  I don't have time to go into it now... but I believe the answers to these questions lie in passages like Romans 12:1-8 and Philippians 2:1-16.  Can you think of any other passages?  :)  (I've turned on anonymous comments...)  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "I thank my God... that you were enriched in everything by Him in all utterance and all knowledge, even as the testimony of Christ was confirmed in you, so that you come short in no gift" (1 Cor 1:4-7)  It is so encouraging to me to know that in Christ I have everything I need to live my life.  However so many times I catch myself wishing that I were smarter or more talented or in some way more equipped than I am.  God's reply to me is in v. 27...  "But God has chosen the foolish things of the world to put to shame the wise, and God has chosen the weak things of the world to put to shame the things which are mighty; and the base things of the world and the things which are despised God has chosen, and the things which are not, to bring to nothing tht things that are..."  God intentionally made me not as smart or as talented... and why?  "... that no flesh should glory in His presence." (v. 29)  He did it so that I would recognize the power of God in my life.  And I do.  Have you ever given someone advice that turned out to be exactly what they needed to hear?  Have you ever done some little task at work that turned out to be praiseworthy in the sight of your boss?  Have you ever gotten a better grade in a class than you thought were possible?  Don't compliment yourself on these things... praise God. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In the last half of Philippians 4 Paul is speaking to them about their generosity. The verse that hits me the most is v. 17. Here it is in context:  (v.16) "For even in Thessalonica you sent aid once and again for my necessities. (v.17) Not that I seek the gift, but I seek the fruit that abounds to your account."  Paul's desire is not that he, himself, would be well fed (for he has learned to be content in every situation (v. 11) but that the Philippian church would be blessed by God for being generous. His compassion is to see someone else's relationship with Jesus grow, even (although not in this case) at his expense (1 Cor 8:13).  Last night I went out street witnessing again. Although I must confess that my heart wasn't in it. I was doing it more because it was a good thing to do than because I wanted someone to meet Jesus. Oh to be more like Jesus (or even Paul for that matter). Will I ever truely have compassion for people? Yes. :) "For whom He forknew, He also predestined to be conformed to the image of His Son..." (Rom 8:29). "... for it is God who works in you both to will and to do for His good pleasure." (Phil 2:13).  As my dad would say: "Keep on keeping on." If you are a Christian, God is working in you to conform you to the image of His Son. Pray and yearn toward that end. If you're not a Christian then you need to know Jesus. Post a comment, send me an AIM, or at least check out this site:  urlLink The Good News  . 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Why should we stand fast?  Paul gives us the reason in the preceding verses: "...Jesus Christ who will transform our lowly body that it may be conformed to His glorious body." (3:20-21)  We stand fast because He is doing a work in us.  He is actively transforming our bodies to be like His glorious body.  (See also Rom 8:28-30).  What does it mean to be standing fast?  Paul lists three things that should characterize this lifestyle: 1.) Rejoice in the Lord always (4:4) 2.) Be anxious for nothing.  Through prayer and thanksgiving make your requests to God (4:6) 3.) Whatever things are true, nobel, right, pure, lovely, admirable, if anything is excellent or praiseworthy, think about such things. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>