<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      John Kerry ended his speech with the familiar words "and God bless the United States of America."   But the post-speech celebration was missing one thing...the downpour of red, white and blue balloons.&nbsp; My parents and I speculated that the lack of traditional balloons&nbsp;might have&nbsp;something to do with security.   We suddenly heard "I need more balloons, more balloons, I need more balloons!"&nbsp; And we realized that the voice did not belong to the familiar voices of Wolf Blitzer, or Judy Woodward or Jeff Greenfield.&nbsp; The director of the convention was somehow miked by CNN.&nbsp;   We were amazed that no one had notified CNN that its audience was hearing much more than the convention's background music.   Balloons began to trickle from the sky, but at&nbsp;a&nbsp;rather slow rate at first.&nbsp; As the urgency of the director's demands grew, my father commented, "he's going to start cussing soon."   Sure enough, the guy yells, "where the hell&nbsp;are the balloons." And&nbsp;about a minute later "what the F*CK are you guys doing up there?"   An apologizing Wolf Blitzer and Judy Woodward quickly tried to amend the situation and explained that was the director of the convention.&nbsp;&nbsp;And soon enough&nbsp;thousands of balloons and tons of confetti filled the FleetCenter.   Could CNN be the&nbsp;FCC's next victim?&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Men and women in business suits hustle along&nbsp;Washington's &nbsp;streets and tourists still cram Washington attractions, but in reality the city has come to a screeching halt.  Every summer the city becomes Washington's version of a ghost town.  Senators and&nbsp;Congressmen&nbsp;vanish quickly for a month in their home states.&nbsp;&nbsp;Parking spots still exist after 8:30 a.m. at Metro stops.&nbsp; President Bush isn't even here.&nbsp; Much of what really makes the city unique - and intersting to journalists - have left.  This is my second summer reporting in DC.&nbsp; It's amazing how fast-paced and lost one can feel when Congress is in session.&nbsp; But stories seem to vanish along with the 535 legislators who seem to control so much of the activity that goes on here.  Last week I couldn't even cover all the stories that I wanted.&nbsp; This week I can't think of a single one to write.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I think I would have preferred a happy, constant medium.&nbsp;  I know some businesses in Washington's busiest time is DC.&nbsp; But for someone looking for something to write about...it feels like a ghost town.  &nbsp;  &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bloggers at the Democratic National Convention have become one of the biggest hypes at this year's Democratic National Convention.&nbsp; The media reportedly hoarded convention bloggers &nbsp;at a "blogger breakfast" this morning.&nbsp;   The collection of bloggers should bring new, refreshing voices to the conventions this year.&nbsp; (Republicans have also agreed to credential bloggers, but not as many as the Democratic convention).&nbsp; Bloggers can provide a real voice that can accurately capture the awe - or lack there of - of the conventions.   The conventions hardly evoke the anticipation they used to when the party's presidential nominee was uncertain.&nbsp; We've known since February John Kerry would be the Democratic nominee.&nbsp; And, hell, we've known President Bush would be the Republican nominee for four years now.&nbsp;   For me, the convention seems to be one big party.   As 15,000 media representatives flood the Fleet center this week, I wonder - why all the hype about this one huge party?&nbsp; I think bloggers can make the conventions more real and more understandable.&nbsp; Through first-person narratives they'll help make sense of all the excitment.   I will cover the Republican National Convention at the end of August for two newspapers.&nbsp; I might find some fun, quirky stories to write about the South Carolina and Mississippi delegations.&nbsp; But what I won't be able to express - is the chaos, fear and downright confusion I am likely to feel.&nbsp;   But these bloggers can do just that.&nbsp; And I'm using their blogs to help me prepare for the Republican National Convention.   A collection of blogs can be found at  urlLink conventionbloggers.com .&nbsp;&nbsp; Check out  urlLink http://www.seetheforest.blogspot.com , for a blogger who's awed by the attention they've drawn from the traditional media and a&nbsp;few photos.   &nbsp;     
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've pondered the idea of starting a blog for a long time.  But I wondered...should I start one about my own life? (which is rather boring)  One that I could use as a resume builder and comment on real stuff? (I'm an aspiring journalist).  I don't think I've made up my mind on any of those, but I figured I would at least begin one and see where it leads me.  So here&nbsp;I go...&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>