<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently told my roommate that our different approaches toward life is comparable to our brands of shampoo lining the wall in our shower. To each his own. Our individual, personalized hair products is one of the only items we do NOT share (as a household item). She religiously buys Pantene shampoo and conditioner. She has used this line of shampoo for as long as I've known her - five years. She never switches brands or tries something new. When I confronted her about this phenomena she said she keeps buying it because it's her favorite. She likes the way it makes her hair feel and enjoys its scent. I agree. I like Pantene, too, yet it baffles me that she doesn't get an urge to ever try something new. Could there, just maybe, be a brand of shampoo that is significantly better? More appropriate? More suitable for her hair type?  I have tried and experimented with a vast array of products: Vidal Sassoon, Thermasilk, John Frieda, Dead Head, Agree (before the line got discontinued), Ultra Shine, L'Oreal's Vive, etc. Why? I enjoy variety. I know what I like. Do I feel like a fruity smell today or more of a sensual perfume aroma? I like knowing I am not obligated or invested in simply one brand. On the best of days (after I have pondered on my hands and knees in the aisle of CVS for over 20 minutes trying to decipher "what" shampoo and conditioner I am in the mood for) I make a new purchase and spend the rest of the day anticipating its test run. If I am disappointed with a brand, I finish its contents and swear never to buy it again (I must admit, I have contradicted myself in the past - I am only human).  I remain uncanny when offering advice on this subject as I continue to research, buy and test. If I am satisfied with a brand's effect, I am instantly gratified knowing that I have made another wise choice amist the land of shampoo. We all have choices to be made, we just don't always acknowledge them. And what appears to be a mediocre decision, such as this one, can quickly become a life and death dilemma. Tomorrow could just possibly be my introduction to yet another "new" product. Will I indulge? It is entirely my choice. Lining the shelf, when I least expect it, "it" could call out to me. Will I take the risk? You bet I will.      
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I will be a painter.&nbsp; This afternoon, a marathon runner.&nbsp; Tonight, a waitress.&nbsp; I welcome change and wish to step forward in some direction - any direction.&nbsp; Have I lost my spunk?&nbsp; Am I missing out?&nbsp; I am not sure of many things anymore.&nbsp; As I get older, I wish to become wiser and more practical.&nbsp;&nbsp;Currently, I&nbsp;am experiencing what I have come to recognize as a moderate yet daily rampage - throwing half of my belongings away (I am somewhat of a pack rat) and repainting my house.&nbsp; I work until I am tired and hopeless and then want to kick myself for plastering every hole and painting every corner to perfection.&nbsp; Why do I care so much?&nbsp; I want to know.&nbsp; My first instinct is to blame it on passion.&nbsp;&nbsp;I become to emotionally involved in everything I do.&nbsp; Yes.&nbsp; This is me.   I have not accomplished as much as I hoped for in my 25 years of age.&nbsp; I've met few people that succeed in keeping me entertained.&nbsp; I have a handful of close-knit friends, yet an enormous pool of acquaintances.&nbsp; I am a dreamer.&nbsp; A romantic.&nbsp; A storyteller.&nbsp; I love movies and books and what I desire most is simply interesting conversation over a steaming cup of coffee or glass of chardonnay.&nbsp; Tomorrow will be a new chapter.&nbsp; I think this to myself every night before going to sleep.&nbsp; Tomorrow my life could change.&nbsp; I will welcome the day as if it were my last.&nbsp; When my alarm rings I repeat myself.&nbsp; Today I will be a painter.&nbsp; This afternoon, a marathon runner.&nbsp; Tonight, a waitress.&nbsp; One can only try to change things for so long.&nbsp; I make my days diverse and&nbsp;I do struggle to ward off routines.&nbsp; What I will finally&nbsp;admit to myself is that re-arranging doesn't equal change, but taking on new obstacles, being sporadic, daring&nbsp;and courageous...in fact,&nbsp;does.&nbsp; I want to do everything and nothing.&nbsp; Is my picture of life too grand?&nbsp; I have no idea where to&nbsp;begin.&nbsp;&nbsp;Every day I remain thirsty, as&nbsp;my weeks&nbsp;remain&nbsp;calm.&nbsp; Familiar.&nbsp; Indelible.         
     

    
</post>


</Blog>