<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Get online!", they all say. "You're nobody if you aren't on the web!" Bah! So I go through the trouble to make myself part of the oh-so-saturated online community, making my presence felt with  urlLink this blog  (heh) as well as putting some stuff up  urlLink for auction  on eBay. Does anybody bite? Well, if you are reading this you might be me. I guess what they say is true, sex really does sell. And since I ain't sellin any...
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lend me your fears.  I was thinking on how we are all the same, and that no one goes through life without knowing some hardships. About how easy it is to take the cynical route and criticize  urlLink everything . I was thinking about how everyone feels alone in this world, and that no one really is.  But somehow I can't finish that thought. For some reason, the compassion is waning from me. It's like all of the good in the world is somehow trumped by the inconsiderate, loud, assholes that make up the majority.  People aren't nice, bottom line. It not that no one cares anymore, it's that all anyone  can  care about is themselves. We are all just one big market sector, waiting for the next  urlLink reason to be  like we didn't already have one. Don't get me wrong, I love technology. But we don't  need  these things.  Quote of the day:  "Everything in moderation... even moderation."  What's  my  reason to get up every morning? I love my family.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I surprisingly found myself awake at 3 am on Saturday morning, searching through blog entries from  urlLink ilovebees  for what I thought were clues to a  urlLink mystery . Instead, I was unknowingly playing an  urlLink Alternate Reality Game  the likes of which resembled something out of  urlLink The Matrix .  Even having spent a great deal of my post-adolescent life on the Internet, this was a new concept to me. I thought that sort of thing only happened in  urlLink movies , and the Internet existed for little more than  urlLink porn  and  urlLink pop-up ads .  What wasn't surprising, was how the people who  did  know what was going on from the beginning, were taking it so seriously. I mean, even when I thought there was a real mystery to be solved, it still seemed like more of a game than an actual adventure. While for those who must have spent days online interacting with  urlLink quasi-fictional characters , were totally immersed in the obvious falsehood. While intruiging, I was sure at most it could be was a massive hoax. But then again, my sceptical nature led me to almost  urlLink banning  myself from one of thier online forums in a simple attempt to lend some suspiscion to the mix. Perhaps I'm just not cutout to be one of these people.  I never was very good at team activities.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Maybe that's what the WWW should have stood for. On second thought, perhaps not. Where else can anybody decide to post pictures of dismembered or mutilated children and actually profit from it? Why, the Internet of course.  I long ago discovered that if there is a name for any sort of sick, twisted perversion, it could be found on the Internet, and with pictures! No matter how hard one tries, there seems to be no escaping the deranged minds of those who seek to protect the right to show these things to anyone willing to pay a few bucks to get off on that sort of thing.  But I have not let myself become desensitized to it all, like some people I know. The kind that seek out these new, exciting ways to shock themselves into becoming totally and utterly void of any compassion towards the innocent (and not so innocent) victims of this trend in technology. The means to expose the masses to the true nature of society. The murderous, self-indulgent, self-obsessed, self-loathing, consumerists who feed off of every click.  I mean, not too long ago when I was a teenager, girls didn't do private shows on webcams for the world to see (so long as they pay). Kids weren't being stalked by perverts on the other side of the planet via Instant Messenger, with full streaming video and audio. People weren't interested in pictures of suicide bombers, post-deed, rendered by thier acts...  Or maybe they were.  Maybe it's not the technology that has corrupted us. Maybe we've always been this way.  I get a kick out of when people ask the question, "What happened to people's morals?"  What morals? We've been mutilating, murdering, raping, and everything else since the beginning of time. It just wasn't televised.
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What am I doing?  Every day I see nineteen year olds in Mercedes', guys in thier twenties with incredible physiques, perfect hair and clothes that cost a fortune. I read about how successful this company is, or that person became by the time they were 30, and here I am on the cusp of 27 years old and still struggling to make the bills.  Why? Why am I not rich?  I'll tell you why (like I'm not just typing this for myself). It's because I work for someone else. I sit by day after day questioning the motives of my superior, while I could be motivating myself. I wait for the day my boss tells me to do it my way instead of doing it that way all along. I mentally masturbate myself into believing I will some day be in a position to make my own choices, at my own expense, and that it will somehow work out for me.  Who knows, maybe it will. I've come this far, right?  The real question is, why am I waiting to find out? I can't stand to hope that one day I will be able to provide my family with the right kind of life, all the while not knowing for sure if I will. I know I am wasting precious time surfing the Internet, reading about things I will never truly know, playing games when I should be bettering myself. And at the same time, I have freinds who are complacent with just getting by. They buy big screen TVs and game consoles and motorcycles when they make half of the money that I do and have twice as many bills. How can that be? They don't care to succeed.  All they care about is making it through another day without sacrificing anything for thier own, petty enjoyment. Well... not me.  I will succeed, dammit.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This truly is a wonderous time we live in. Being able to store thousands of songs in the  urlLink palm of your hand , carrying a  urlLink supercomputer  anywhere you go, even being able to  urlLink scare the living shit  out of yourself, all with the greatest of ease.  That is, if you're filthy fucking rich.  This must have been what the Bible meant by surrounding oneself with temptation. Then again, the Bible said a lot of things. I find it easier not to cheat on my wonderful wife than to not buy myself a new powerbook, ipod, mountain bike, Armani suit, etc...  In fact, I have never found it difficult to remain faithful in my marriage. I  have  found it diffucult however not to bury myself in debt to satisfy my need to have every new gadget that hits the market. Am I a product of marketting? I don't think so. I think it's more that I love technology and everything to do with it. The fact that I work in IT and can still enjoy sitting in front of a computer on my own time is a testiment to that.  It's just too bad my wallet can't keep up with technology. 
    
</post>


</Blog>