<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         You asked me if I am okay How could I say I am nearly in decay? I said yes, I have always been feeling alright But I know that you can feel how I’m suffering inside  I told you it is easy to cope with despair Just think that life isn’t always unfair Psyche yourself about happy moments That’s what I said, you complimented me and you were impressed  My dear you will never know how much I am aching for you You will never feel how my heart bleeds when you are with her But don’t worry I won’t falter  I want to thank you instead for making me stronger  I am not saying indeed that I cannot move on But as long as the two of you are together I will stay behind To support and listen to every word you say Just by doing so, my sadness fades away  Hey you are very special to me I don’t know what you did but I’m glad you’re in my life Our friendship is enough as of this moment I cannot ask for anything more  I know that you care for me I feel the same way for you Always do take good care of yourself Someone over here is always praying for you  Moonchild26/7/28/04/9:30pm    
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        the rays of the sun begins to fade     as i scan the heavens like i was seeing your face     i can no longer stand the pain and the agony      of staying in this infertile land of sorrow       &nbsp;   dominion over my feelings i cannot feel     you own it and that what's real     i laugh and i cry when you instigate any of these emotion     why does it have to be this way?       &nbsp;   i just want to love you in a special way     i want to be in a world where both of us can stay     forget about the world even for a little while     but the world is cruel, it is not his style       &nbsp;   my being is slowly breaking into pieces     i hope someday someone will find and mend it     yet hopes are still up high     that someday it will be you and i.....   
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hush now baby don't cry I have always been here to dry your eyes You may not know it but I always see you through And no matter what the world may bring I am here for you I may not have the courage to tell you why That from a distance I love you more as the days go by Ever since the day I saw your face You are in my mind I just can't erase I know you are hurt and I know you are down But always rememeber joy will come around So please be patient and please be strong Because in loving you can never go wrong As I see in your eyes that sparkle of tears I have always been wanting to drive away your fears So please believe me when I say I love you Because that is what's sacred and is very true Baby come on do not turn away I know you can make it so please stay Do not leave us here for surely you are gonna be missed Sooner or later my identity I will unleash I hope you will give me a chance to prove That heaven and earth for you I can move Baby hush now don't ever cry I am always here to love you that I can't deny.   
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      how stupid i am to believe in love what a shame, im too old for that nonesense turning 24 recently, i thought i was in control of my total being but alas!just by one blow everything i thought i knew were put into oblivion  blame it on initial attraction, or should i say, lust? (lol) i dunno, but the minute i laid my eyes upon this man my world started to brighten as if i was in unison with the colors that comprises the rainbow how stupid i was, i was totally blind...  without having second thoughts i let myself fall into the trap when will i learn?this is not new to me first of all i always fall in love with the wrong guy... :( im quite aware but even if he is, the love just felt so right  confusion invaded my senses though for quite sometime i cannot really fathom  Is it love or just attraction  whatever it is, i am to blame i was made to believe that there was something wherein i have something to look forward to yet now i can see it was all a game...what a shame..... :( 
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Tired of this pain which love has brought Expectations were unmet yet the heart still yearns for the beloved To spend even just a spare amount of time Surely the poignant wounds would heal, the tears would subside  Unprepared for what transpired one fine day Destiny’s surprise of introducing Unresolved however was the connection felt Was it true, was it mutual….the answer is still point blank.  Was the loving heart taken for granted? Was it a victim of a foolish game? How sad, how cruel if affirmative How could he?  &nbsp;  
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why did it come to this point My love for you I have to conceal It hurts deep inside But I have to that is why  It's hard for me to pretend as if nothing happened It aches everytime I think of that one single happy moment Yet we've drawn the line, now here we are Arguing, hurting each other for no reason at all  Can't we stop all these and just have one last kiss? If that is all we can have then it would be more than fine I still love you... I think I will always do....  cielo/8/13/04  
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Bakit hindi masabing mahal kita? Hindi pa man umaamin ay tinuldukan mo na Sapagkat para sa'yo ako'y kaibigan lang Walang labis, walang kulang  Halos gabi-gabi ikaw ang laman ng gunita Sa pagtulog, paggising man ikaw ang naaalala Nahihirapan man itong aking puso patuloy pa rin akong nagmamahal sa'yo  Puno man ng hinanakit sa damdamin mo para sakin Kaibigan mo pa rin ako, di kita kayang lisanin Kaligayahan ko na ang ikaw ay makasama Kahit panandalian, buhay ko'y sumasaya  Hanggang kailan kaya ako magdurusa? Mapagod kaya ako at mawalan ng pag-asa Sapagkat malinaw mong sinabi sa akin Matalik na kaibigan lang turing mo sa akin...  ouchhhh...pero yan nakayanan ko for u joyce....   cielo/8/9/04  
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Why did it have to start If it would end just so soon? No regrets that's what I said But I wish I can get you out of my head  Why don't you let me love you? I'm not asking you to love me too It hurts me keeping this feeling What shall I do?  If forgetting you means sleepless nights I'd rather think of you and go on with the fight If turning away means hating the world I'd definitely stay even if you I can't hold  If love means sacrifice for us I won't disturb you and I will never make a fuss Instead I'll cry in the dark silently While I whisper my love for you eternally  You came into my life so fast You caught my heart in just a blast My heart is aching and I don't know how to mend it Here I am again in a mosh pit  Who can save me, I guess no one I want to sulk until I wait for the end to come I am so down and hurt I have nowhere to run  Please somebody help this poor heart Shattered into pieces because of a missing part When will the sufferings cease? Can somebody show where its missing piece?   cielo/8/9/04 PM (d ko alam time)     
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      August 9, 2004     I would like to share one incident wherein I was touched by the Lord. I would like you to share this in your prayer meeting. AS you’ve always known me I am open to you and I always acknowledge my mistakes and appreciated my flaws. There are times wherein I should have learned from it but still I falter. But this time I think God opened my eyes in order for me to know who I really am and have tested the limit of my faith.  There are Sundays wherein I am lazy to attend mass, I justify it by talking to the Lord, telling him that it would be hypocrisy if I come to His house unwilling to hear mass. SD’s sister and brother-in-law are Baptist. We’ve been introduced so I know them personally. SD’s brother-in-law is a Pastor and so they invited me one Sunday to attend their church gathering. I was caught in a situation wherein I cannot turn down the invitation so I went. It was 9AM but I was advised to go before the said time. As I was listening to the preaching, a realization hit me. And it hit me hard. I was so ashamed of myself. “Bakit kailangan pang imbitahan ako ng ibang relihiyon para lang mapagtanto ko na ang pagsisimba ay isang kasunduan at responsibilidad ko bilang Kristiyano, bilang Katoliko?” And I told SD about it. I told her na I feel ashamed of myself dahil nakakaya kong magsimba lang kapag gusto ko samantalang sila nung inimbitahan ako gumising pa ako ng maaga. And so I thank GOD for not making me insensitive and deaf of His reminder to me. Right now I am slowly renewing my covenant to HIM. I do not care if anybody condemn me for being honest about this. I am proud instead to acknowledge my fault. I know that GOD has forgiven me and no matter how many times I would undergo spiritual dryness His Divine Providence will ensure me of his overflowing love thus making me nourished with his guidance and protection… Praise God…. God bless the CFC community..I thank God for you are my parents and I’m proud that you raised me to be a better human being. I may not be noble nor perfect but I am someone special made by God. For me that is enough……    moonchild26 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      He is a man yet a child within Full of nobility and responsibility How can you not admire someone like him? He can be naughty but he can be serious when he needs to be  How can I ever forget a friend like you? You are the big brother I never had If I were to have one even just for a day, I would choose you I am lucky to know you, kalkalub  You are such a nice person to get along with Never did I feel left out in our group You always find ways to keep us amused Remember the words we created?  Kalkalubee you will never be forgotten You are a part of my life and no one can take that away from me I am your friend, your sister And now it is time for us to part  Goodbyes are never that easy But I know that in our hearts the memories of our laughters and tears Will keep us sane and stronger Bye kalkalub, but again let me just say....BYE FOR NOW......  cielo/8/6/04 8:50 pm 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Sabi mo magkita tayo, natuwa naman ako 
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here I go again same old feeling I wasn't in the mood for searching But you popped into my life just like that And now I cannot help my heart to stop  From thinking of you, dreaming of you You are so faraway from me what can I do? Staring at the ceiling every evening Seeking for answers for this terrible yearning  Who are you to let me feel this way? Why do I want you to stay? I am beginning to fall that I am sure But I guess I will never be emotionally secured  You belong to someone else But who knows we can never tell If destiny will allow us to be together I wish it could be forever  Let me love you in my mind Reality for awhile I want to leave behind For in my thoughts you are so real Your kiss, your touch I can feel  Allow me to say these words right now I love you, I want to show it but I don't know how Please don't laugh nor ignore my feelings You envelope my world, my total being  cielo/7/24/04/4:38 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          Emptiness envelope me every now and then   As if nothing or no one can fill the void within   My dilemma of my identity was a problem way back   Before my heart on you were struck      How can I forget that day I looked at you in the eye   I wanted to calm myself God knows how I tried   But I can’t help thinking of you   I just want my reverie would come trueI dream of you and I together      Loving each other forever   But reality bites I guessYou are taken; why was I put into this test?   I hope I can stand the pain of losing you   Funny how it seems since I don’t have you      I just wish we had spent more time that day   When all my worries and fears were away   The time when I first saw your charm   Why did you not hold me close in your arms?      Now I’m longing to feel your body into mine   Perhaps we can be oblivious of this space and time   Love, I don’t know if this is   Yet you I can’t resist      Just by thinking of you my passion starts to grow   But I know it’s not right, I have to let you go…   Slowly I have to forget you   Though my heart will be battered and blue      This is what is right and justI can’t have you, and that’s a fact.    Just like this, it had to end so fast.      Cielo/7/26/04/1:41am  
      
</post>


</Blog>