<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So today was about the same as yesterday, but without the cockroach thank god! And I also found a computer in the reception of the Verdemar Apartmentos (It was one euro for ten minuites) so I went on there to check e-mails etc and ended up having a short conversation with Helen about where we were staying.  Oh the other BIG thing that happened that day was that on the way home Dad and Stuart wanted to goto the electronics shop so Dad could get a new digital camera so Me and Mum went home before them. On the way back I told her I had something to tell her that came up the night that we stayed up late. When we got back I told her all about how I felt and that I was questioning my sexuality two years ago and now I feel that I also like women as well as women. She was totally cool with it, and admited that she also had a couple of crushes on girls when she was my age, but she is a bit in deniyal as she said that it may pass when I get older etc. She also advised that I dont tell Dad until I am really sure (WHICH I AM) because she doesn't know how he would react. But I plan on telling him soon anyway because I dont want to hide who I am and pretend to be something I'm not. Thats about it for day four!  
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Well, at this point in the holiday, what we do everyday was basically the same. We relax by the pool, sunbathe, have some snachish lunch, relax some more and get ready to go out for some dinner. I wont go into much detail as it will just bore you, trust me.  The only thing that was different from the other days about today was that we had a lovely visistor....ICK! We had a COCKROACH!!!!!!! I didn't really want to kill it, but if I didn't get rid of it I wouldn't of gotten any sleep that night, watching for it to come and crawl around my bedroom floor. My Dad couldn't catch it because it was too fast so I got some inceticide that we had from the tiny ants we spotted the first day and literally ended up spraying the whole can of it on the cockroach. But that didn't kill it, but it had slowed it down so my Dad scoped it up with some paper and I thought he chucked it over the road, but he put it in the BBQ. So it ended up dying slowly of stavation rather than the incetiside.  Anyway that night we ended up going back to Slow Boat II because it was the easy option and we knew it was good food there. Thats about it for that day.    
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       After a good nights sleep I awoke to the sun shineing high in the clear blue sky. I was second up, my Mother being first as usual. We were still waiting for someone to wake us up and tell us it was a dream or someone would knock on the door and tell us that we got the wrong apartment, but it never happened. Soon my Father awoke, followed by my Brother and after a splash in the pool we all got dressed and headed down to the small supermarket to get some nosh for breakfast as we had nothing in the villa.  Soon after finishing our breakfast of french toast, jam and such forth, we all again, went into the pool or sunbathed. This was the continuing theme until lunch, when we went back to the supermarket to get some bread, cheese, ham and other things for a snachish lunch as we were going out for dinner.  Upon finishing everyone went back to what they were doing previously. My Father, reading his newly purchased Bill Bryson book. My Mother reading some other book she had brought along, inbetween floating around the pool on our huge rubber ring. My Brother diving in and out of the water with a pair of googles that were designed for children and didn't fit around his head. Eventually abandoning the straps and just using sucktion to sick them over his eyes. Then there is me, sitting in the shade, or sunbathing (or as I call it, burning), or taking a dip in the pool. Swimming underwater most of the time, my favorite thing to do in the water. While me and my Father were in the pool we heard a chirping noise coming from near by, we discovered a small turqise, black and white parakeet. It stayed around for a while and we managed to get really close and take some great photographs of it. I can't wait to see them.   urlLink    A photo of Lanzarote that we could see on our walks into town.  urlLink      Soon the sun began to lower and we all dried off and got changed and strollled down town. This time my Mother spent along time deciding where to go. I was pissed off at this time because I was burnt and my feet ached becuase flip flops are not designed for walking lond distance. She finally decided on a grill resturant called "Poco Loco". Bad Choice. I have had better ready meals from the supermarket. We all vowed never to go back and that tomorrow night we would go back to "Slow Boat II" as we knew we would get good food and service.  Once we were back we stayed up a bit later and jsut talked about almost anything. My Brother brought up his repetetive joke of me being a lesbian. I was being sarcastic and agreeing with him and I sneakly asked my Mum how she would react if I was a lesbian. She said she would abandon me or thow me out if I was that way inclined. This clinched my feeling to tell her about being bisexual, but not tonight.  Soon I began to feel tired and setteled into bed and difted off into dream world....*Zzzzzzzzz*  
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Wake Up Time was 3am, thats early. I had decided that I would only get about one hours sleep due to my previous weeks sleeping habbits. I still tried to get that one hour, but alas I cannot force myself to goto sleep at the drop of a hat. So I ended up just staying awake in bed listening to my music until the time came to leave for the airport. Once everyone was awake and had taken in some form of caffine to keep awake, we stuffed our suitcases into the small boot of our small car. It only just fit mind you. I think my Mother packed way to much for one weeks worth of holidaying. The way to Luton went faster than normal and I only saw one other car coming in the opposite direction, well what do you expect at 3am!      Soon we had parked the car in the long term car park and hopped onto the shuttle bus round to the departure termial, struggeling with the sheer amount of lugguage we had and stuffing it along withour selfs onto four bus seats and left the larger on in the asile beside my Father. Once the bus stopped we all dragged our tired selfs and our luggage to the check in gates. We didn't have to wait as long as I had expected to be checked in, we only stood in a small que for about five minuites and we were at the check in having our tickets and passports scanned and checked by the eyes of the woman who was weighing our lugage. I was quite suprised that we hadn't gone over the limit. She handed us our boarding tickets and my Mother said that we had seats A, B, C and D in row 29 and that one of us would be sitting on our own with two stangers. No one said anything as we knew that the person would be Dad.      By this time everyone needed refueling with food and caffine and we stopped at the cafe before proceding to the boarding louge. My Mother needed some caffine quick, so while she went to do that My Father, My Brother and Myself went to check out the small shop that sold almost anything you would need for your travels in one place. My Brother brought some sweets for the flight while my Father and Myself scowered the books to see if there was anything worth buying. After some consideration my Father decided to purchase a Bill Bryson book he had yet to read called "Notes from a Big Country" to read on the holiday.      We went to meet my Mother in the cafe and she decided it was time to move onto the depature lounge. By this time I was not looking foward to the flight or the holiday at all, and knowing what charter flights are like, I knew that we were all going to be crushed into a small space for the following four hours. We had a couple of drinks at the bar, brought some breakfast to eat on the plane as we had decided to save money and our taste buds my skipping the in flight meal. We all headed to the toilet once more before eventually boarding, and by this time the display was now flashing red saying that it was the last call for our flight.      We all rushed off to the depature gate before having our passports inspected for the third time already and got onto the bus that took us round to the aeroplane. Along with an odd 30 other tired passangers we climbed up the shaking stairs to the crampt aeroplane. We took our seats and as always I got the window seat. I like to know whats happening outside, and as I predicted the seats were very uncomfertable. Not only are they too small for a very short skinny person, but I am tall and have a larger ass, so I was not very happy. It was so uncomfertable, I couldnt bare to sit there for more than about ten minuites, never mind four hours.      After a rather dodgey take off, and some squirming in my seat and a long four hours of turbulance we landed in Fueteventura. It all looked very dry, not much greenery to be seen, and I was starting to worry what our holiday would end up like. After getting off the plane and collecting our luggage, we made our way round to the First Choice rep to find out where we would be staying. She said in a rather high voice "You Will Be Staying at the Maxogarden Villas" finishing it off with a cheesy grin. We were all a bit puzzled by the 'villas' part as we had booked late and payed less than 1k for this holiday and only had the garente that we would get a three star, one bedroomed apartment that sleeps four adults. We decided that it must be a big villa that is split into apartments, we wouldnt get our own villa for the price we paid...would we?      Soon after a seemingly short coach ride, we were dropped off outside an apartment complex called "Verdemar Apartmentos" and were told that Maxogarden Villas were under their management. We went down to the reception and the receptionist told us that our accomadation was still being cleaned so we would have to wait an hour. So we went and sat by the pool bar and had a couple of drinks and puzzled over where we would be staying. As we were surrounded by alot of green and white apartments with a communial pool, we guessed we would get one of those.      Soon our accomadation was ready and we were told how to find it, by crossing the street for some reason. As we approched the villa looking accomadation we thought that she had given us the wrong instructions and I saw a "No Diving" sign and a life ring on the wall outside the patio. We wouldnt get a pool, no way. The keys fitted the door and we walked in. It was amazing. I looked out the window and saw a small pool thinking we must share this with another family. We all walked out onto the patio/pool area and saw more french doors on and my Mother said "That must be another familys part of the villa, we will probably share the pool too." We decided to look around the accomadation a bit more and we went down what seemed like a never ending corridor to find not one, not two, but three bedrooms!!! We werent sharing with anyone, It was all ours. We were all speachless, there were no words for it. We were all thinking "Someones made a mistake. Any minuite now someone will come and tell us we have a small one bedroom apartment across the road". But no one ever did.      urlLink    The pool at the villa where we stayed.  urlLink      After and amazing shock, we decided to explore the town and find somewhere to eat. It was quite a long walk to the main town. The only aminetlys near us were one bar called "The Flistone Family Bar" and a small supermarket that sold all the essentails that us tourists need. The town was busseling with life, its was huge. We caved in and decided to go have a chinese as it was the easy option out and we were all tired and hungery and didnt want to walk around for the next hour trying to decide where we want to eat. It was a nice looking place called "Slow Boat II". I ordered spring rolls to start, and then crispy chilli beef for the main course with some egg fried rice (or egg friend rice as it said on some other chinese resturant menus). It was the best Chinese I have ever had. Everyone else agreed. We decided to skip deserts as we were all full and we felt feeling great.      After the long walk home, we sat by the pool, had a couple of drinks and a chat and decided it was time to hit the hay.      That was my first day. I will be updating the other seven days over the next seven days, lmao.     
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yep, I will be leaving in approximatly  5 hours and 10 minuites . I will probably get no more than an hours sleep if anything due to my current sleeping patern, I usually get to sleep at 2am. So that gives me an hour before&nbsp;I have to get up again to go to the airport. Might get some sleep on the aeroplane, but that will only be if I can't keep my eyes open. You see I am very strange about travel, I can't sleep when I am traveling. I have to be aware of whats going on around me, don't ask why I am just odd like that, get used to it.     &nbsp;   I will miss  Kat  so much, but then I can't wait until I get back as she will be here. It's hasn't sunk yet that I will get to  see  her,  feel  her,  smell  her,  hear  her...*Drifts Into A Day Dream* It just seems unreal. well I am sure I will wake up and smell the coffee when our first meeting comes up. She said she may goto the airport early to pick up her brother just to  spy  on me, lmao. Bye for a week! I will update when I get back, I promise.    
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well I said it, I will be leaving the country in the early hours of tomorrow morning. I am going away to the  Canarie Islands  (One called something like Furtaventura) with the rest of my family, so there will not be any posts for a week...But I will write down what happened each day and then when I get back type it up on here so you know what's going on.     &nbsp;   Soooo today I will be doing mostly packing and stuff, but inbetween that,&nbsp;I hope to get a chat with  Kat  before I leave as she will be arriving here while I am on holiday. Damn I wanted to be here when she arrived, and even meet here with a hug when she came through the arrivals terminal at the airport. I will be thinking of here alot this week, more than usual, and thats a lot!     &nbsp;   This morning it was quite odd as I awoke from a dream, I'm sure it was about her, but I can't remember, and she was the first thing on my mind, and she is normally the last thing on my mind before I goto sleep. Yes, go on, you can say it, I am obsesed with the girl. haha. I'll get back to you later. Bye!    
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I think this is really funny. To try to offend me, my brother says "Charlie your a lesbain" which I find funny because he has no idea that I am bisexual, hahah. So I just go along with him agreeing and saying "Yes I know Stuart, is that ok with you" it's&nbsp;rather funny. Dont you agree?  
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hmmm well I found this on someone else's blog, who siad they got it from someone else, you get the picture. So I thought I would like to do it, here goes...  &nbsp;   Choose a band/or artist and answer only in song TITLES by that band::  Avril Lavigne    &nbsp;   Are you female or male::  Too Much To Ask &nbsp;    Describe yourself::  Complicated   How do some people feel about you::  &nbsp;Anything but Ordinary   How do you feel about yourself::  Unwanted   Describe your ex girlfriend/boyfriend:  Who Knows   Describe your current girlfriend/boyfriend::  My World   Descibe where you want to be::&nbsp; Together   Describe what you want to be::&nbsp; Nobody's Fool   Describe how you live:: &nbsp;(for) Tomorrow   Describe how you love::  Things I'll Never Say   Share a few words of wisdom::  Why   So there you have it, I didn't have too mant titles to work with (only 27, ha) but I tried to fit them best I could. Well they fitted better than other artists I like. See you for now...      
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well I guess I should start somewhere? hmmmm. Want to know a little about my life at the moment? Oh you do. Okay then, be prepared this could be long...     &nbsp;   At this point in my life (well today and the past week or so) I have been  Very  happy, which for me is strange. I think I would have had to start this out a while back for you to have known that, well lets just say I can get very depressed, it's more of feeling sorry for myself, ha. Any way, the main reason I am happy at the moment is because of a girl I meet online. Yes a girl, and I am a girl, yes I know, well if you knew me better you would know that I'm bisexual. Anyway, continuing...I meet her on a website I had been visiting for about a year, and we just began to talk about everything. Soon I found myself falling for her, and I thought 'Sure I may like her, but she may think I'm an Idiot for falling for someone I have never meet and may never meet.' But, she told me that she felt the way that I did even before I said anything. Still I thought I was a bit crazy as I knew I would propably never meet her as she lives over the other side of the world from me. One day she told me she was going to be visiting  London  this August doing charity work in a soup kitchen and asked me if I would meet her when she came. Of course I said yes, and yes I know that it isnt even august yet, but wait a moment. Then our feelings became stronger for each other, I told her that  I loved her , it wasnt just a crush, and when I said it I ment it. And she said it back, I was so  happy .     &nbsp;   Then one day, she told me that her brother was applying for a job in London, and they were looking for a house there. Next thing I knew was that they had got the house and it was in a&nbsp;village called &nbsp;Barton-Le-Clay,  I couldn't believe it, she would be moving just  15 minuites  away from me. We would be able to see each other all the time, not once in a few years. Then one day, I got another one of my long awaited e-mail's from her, I couldn't wait to read it, but I should of known better, as after the first few lines I realised that this wasn't going to be a happy letter. She told me she had been to a three day Christian getaway(She's christian if you hadn't noticed), and at this place she had been able to give up her&nbsp;sin, and that was&nbsp;homosexuality. She told me she no longer loved me as&nbsp;she would a girlfriend or a wife, but she&nbsp;still loved me as a close friend or a sister. It hurt&nbsp;so much that day. Everything seemed unreal. Blurred by the light. I was so confused and I&nbsp;couldn't understand anything that was going&nbsp;around in my mind. I didn't understand how her homosexuality and love for me&nbsp;could just disappear over night.     &nbsp;   After a lot of talking and crying, we finally sorted things out. She said that she did still love me, and I was the only&nbsp;girl she liked anymore as she didnt want to&nbsp;kiss this girl as she&nbsp;did previously. It's all very long and complex,&nbsp;I'm sure you don't want to hear it&nbsp;all. Anyway, I&nbsp;was asking her questions about&nbsp;what had happened and I had&nbsp;one last question for her, was she still moving here? She told me she was, but without her&nbsp;Brother, as the job for her brother fell through and she was going to move on her own, but get a different house or appartment that she could afford. She will be working in london, she already has a job position waiting for her, and she is hoping to find a place to live in the bedforshire area so we can still see each other.     &nbsp;   So thats why I am so happy at the moment. Long story hey! Anyway I will tell you alot more as the days go on, or if you have any questions then add them to the feed back! See you for now!     
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      YES! I finally can get some work experience. I will be working for 2 weeks at Prosol where my Dad works for 2 weeks starting on monday. It's not really work experience as I will be paid 100 quid for the 2 weeks, but I will be able to use it on my CV when I get my first job. But it clashes with when I get my GCSE results so I will have to give a letter with my signature to either Saya or my Mum to get them for me. I wont be doing anything really exciting but its paid work and my Dad says that the two women I will be working with are really nice so I'm not complianing. Bye for now. 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well Saya, Kyra and I all went swimming today to Hitchin swimming pool. I was pleased when we got there that I still was a Junior becuase I'm 16, I was suprised that they didn't ask me for any ID, lol. We had alot of fun, spent most of the time in the outdoor pool because it was a nice hot day for once. Suprisingly I wasn't as self concious as I thought I would be, previously I conned my way out of going swimming with them last time I was asked, but it wasnt as bad as I thought it would be. We had alot of fun and it was some good excersise, the best conbination. We are thinking of going on a regular basis now because it was so fun.  Afterwards we ended up going over to Sayas and we watched one of her Japanese DVDs called 'Spirited Away' as with all japanese cartoon films, it was a bit odd but what do you expect. One of my favorites is called 'Kiki's Devlivery Service' and another one Kyra particullary likes is called 'My Neighboor Totoro'. Of course I can't under stand Japanese (only a few phrases Saya taught me), so we always watch with sub-titles. Saya doesn't even understand most of it as she has forgten how to speak most japanese. After that me and Kyra headed home and I didn't do too much after that. Bye for now. 
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I havent been doing much today, other than thinking too much about Kat. I love her so much that words cannot explain. I aslo added some more finishing touches to her painting today (still not happy with it yet though) and I don't know what she will think of it. For me it is a symbolism of her and thats why I liked to paint it so much, because it reminded me of her with every stroke. Actually I don't think I ever stop thinking of her, I never find my self suddenly thinking of her, I find myself thinking of her all the time.  The only other thing that happened today was that Saya rang me to ask if I was going swimming tomorrow with her and Kyra and told me that her Mum was picking me up with her and taking us to Kyra's and then taking us onto Hitchin swimming pool. Otherwise I spent most of the day catching up on stuff I had missed. Oh and I also ordered a new PS2 game with my new visa electron card which I can use on some websites and in some stores, instead of carrying cash around all the time. See ya for now. 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Finally I get to go home. I don't want to bore you by repeating my self, but it was exactly the same as the journey there, just the opposite way around. One of the things that also annoyed me about the flight was that 'The Day After Tomorrow' was showing and we got some headphones so I could listen because I hadn't seen it before and really wanted to. The kind of headphones they game me though are not normal ones, they were the smaller ones you stick in your ears, and my ears are too small and those things are too big and they dont fit and constantly fall out because I cannot get them in properly in the first place. So I ended up not watching it and was very pissed off.      When we finally got of the plane we waited for a while to get the luggage, and then got back onto the shuttle bus to take us back round to the long term car park. Once we got there my Mum was joking about the car not starting again once we get in it after leaving it for a week. She cursed it. The car battery was dead to the world. Dad tried to get some help from some near by drivers, but they were in the exact same position but they had called the AA so we would wait for them to turn up and see if they would help us out even thought we arent members of the AA. Once he got there he did agree to help us out thankfully and gave us a jump start that would give us enough power to drive home. Dad slipped him a tenner for his help and he was happy.      I couldnt wait to see the cats again and sleep in my own bed!!! Even if it is uncomfy. All the cats were very crawly especially TC, Max and Tigger, who started mieowing if you stopped stroking him. lol. I aslo got a txt message when I got home from Saya saying that she was back from Japan but was a bit jet lagged and I couldn't wait to catch up with her.      Later I had a call from Kyra asking if I wanted to go swimming with her and the others, of couse I said yes, even though we have all known each other for 3 years but nver been swimming together, lol. SO we arranged to go swimming on Friday. Thats about it for that day.  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Our last full day has arrived. Tomorrow we will be on a plane most of the day, I hate traveling in those conditions. Anyway....We did the same as most days....again. BORING! lol. Apart from we packed aswell. For our last meal we went back to Slow Boat II and had a great meal. I was not looking foward to tomorrow, but tried to get some sleep anyhow. Going home tomorrow!!! 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       It will be our last full day tomorrow, but we will probably be doing the same kind of thing anyway. Relax and swam most of the day. I went back onto the computer (something I should stay away from on holiday) that was in the reception for about 40 minuites! LMAO.      We went out to a resturant that specalised in Canarian and Italian food, and the meal was very good for a change, lmao. During the meal I joked about stuart having a boyfriend to get back at him for his repetetive "Charlie's a Lesbian" joke. Dad said, and I quote "If Stuart came home with a boyfriend I would kill him....Slowley" and then to return the favour Stuart asked "What about if Charlie had a girlfriend?". Suprizingly, but unfairly he said that, that would be ok with him. Stupid man. Why is it ok for girl on girl, but not guy on guy. Typical straigth male view. I used to think better of my Dad. Well at least I know that when I tell him he will be ok with it. Thats about it for today folks. Goodnight!  
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well we did the same thing as most days, very boring from other peoples P.O.V but it was very relaxing.  We went out to a Italian place with very loud music, ow my ears! lol. Nothing else to tell about that is exciting or different. 
      
</post>


</Blog>