<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, for those of you unacquainted with my travels over the past year, I'm current in grad school at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign.  It's not quite LA Tech, but I make do.  I've been working on some pretty esoteric problems in power systems, so I'm pretty sure any more details about what I'm doing would be cause for some type of beating.  Lately I haven't been able to engage in anything of any real excitement here(unless eating funnel cake while listening to a demolition derby counts) due to a pretty strict regimen of work and little sleep, but I'm certainly up for reading about someone else having the fun I'm missing.  There's also an open invitation to come up and watch me study for my qualifying exam in November.  Yes, that goes for all of you.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I can only assume that everyone's elses silence is out of awe at the power of my first post. Please don't let that stop you. People will want to read your posts even if they aren't as amazing as mine -- our readers are realistic.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I much prefer that opening to Lucas's "A long time ago in a galaxy far, far away," but I have to admit that one of my favorite parts of a very funny speech a friend of mine used to give revolves around the fact that, although  Star Wars  is futuristic, it's supposed to have happened in the past. Remind me and I'll tell you the joke sometime. Or if you have ten minutes, do yourself a favor and  urlLink watch the speech .
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Trying to get a list together and hopefully get at least some mild timeframes for Matt's last party as a free man (excepting of course the night before his fune..err, wedding).  Last conversations put the approximate date of the gathering near March 12th or March 19th. The two major venues I heard mention are Las Vegas and New Orleans. I'm mostly inclined to go with a majority view, but please be aware that not everyone who 'gets a voice' has access to this forum.  My personal vote - for both financial and lazy reasons - is New Orleans. With a good crowd, it's hard to beat the French Quarter and Uptown for drinks and tomfoolery.  Assuming we could get people to land in New Orleans at close to the same times (or a couple of times), I'm not opposed to providing transportation for the weekend.   I know golf courses and paintball facilities within 45 minutes of New Orleans.  Live music is everywhere.  I'm sure I can speak with a few friends to find the right gentleman's establishments for poor little engaged Matt.  Anyway, Vegas is also an option, I just have to do more research for it.   Thoughts, suggestions, gibberish... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      James Lileks has his problems, especially as a blogger, but he deserves a special place in the web hall of fame for his  urlLink Gallery of Regrettable Foods . Do yourself a favor and check out  urlLink Meat! Meat! Meat!    Warning:  Probably better if you aren't wolfing down a meatloaf sandwich while viewing this. And don't do it at work unless you coworkers are accustomed to unexplained giggling interspersed with the occasional guffaw.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>