<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink THIS &nbsp;IS THE DAILY RESULT OF THE GENERAL OPINIONS WRITTEN DOWN HERE...     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever wondered why there is no real joy in this life? Why every happiness is only a short break  in this great stream of misery? THERE IS NOTHING!!! FUCKING GET IT! 
    
</post>


<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wednesday, 28.07.2004 Seems like it`s getting a little better. A hint of summer has come this morning - the sun shines, makes it a little warmer as yesterday und enables me to produce enough serotonine not to feel as bad as yesterday. Work is slightly more fun today. Hope this is not only a little grain against the big grey rock of the other days. I wish I could have fun again... Strange to be a biomechanic organism, dependent on external factors like small water drops between me and the sun. I don`t want to be a machine! 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink EVERYTHING IS NOTHING  is the place where I will try to put down general statements about being miserable - don`t even bother to check it out, haha... 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday, 27.07.2004  Weather is still not as it should be. Cloudy sky, low temperature, grey atmosphere...  Have to set up and try to think of any action that might fuel me despite of these negative conditions - something to look forward to, like a good meal, like getting drunk, like meeting someone...  But again, there is just coffee in here to raise my blood pressure which is near comatose. Life slowed down to an almost unrecognizable frequency...  I want summer, I want sun, I want warmth, I want laughter, I want life!!!!   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Monday, 26.07.04 Monday sucks anyway - weekend`s over, been to short, back to work... Today`s even worse - cloudy and foggy weather, low temperature, rain, depressive atmosphere, pressing me down to earth, into the earth, makes me sink into the ground. Feeling pushed into the chair, unable to make conversation, unable to follow other`s thoughts, hanging on to mine which circle around warmth, the darkness and peace of sleep, eternal sleep. Getting tired and sleepy. Coffee won`t help it, doesn`t wake up, just makes nervous.  Sitting in the office, having to read through websites like  urlLink http://www.dvd-player.pl &nbsp;- it is the job to register those... counting the minutes until this day is over and I`m able to sink into dreams of a summer that hasn`t come yet and probably won`t come this year. Let`s see what tomorrow brings.. 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Guess why there hasn`t been an update during the last two weeks... The sun was shining and I was trying to catch as much as possible of the sun`s positive energy. Lying around in the park, swimming in the lake, sitting in the evening sun, having some beers... life could go on like this FOREVER! Unfortunately, the clouds are coming back these days. Seems like summer is over this year. Back to normality, back to miserability, back to everything which is... ...nothing... 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got up much too early due to heat, cutting sunlight and droning noises from the construction site on the street below... too little sleep can be a drug, too... Then read two mags/newspaper, both with very personal content. First, a review of my band`s first demo - and not a bad one! Feels good to read someone else is having fun with my art. Second a portrait of a lobbyist in Berlin who works in a job that I was applying for half a year ago. If I was now there... less problems, I guess... who knows... again, I feel like a leaf in a storm, being blown in any direction without almost any influence where the ground is touched.  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sun and summer have finally arrived. Blue sky instead of grey clouds. Endorphines are set free. The skin burns and to this moment, it feels good. As good as the sweat from the heat smells... Coming to life, growing like a plant, raising towards the energyproviding mythical power in the sky, the golden burning goddess. Again, how weak must a human be to be so dependent from his surroundings? 
    
</post>


</Blog>