<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        This film first came out in the 1980's directed by Mr Rob Reiner and starting the late River Phoenix.  This is based on a book by Steven King the body iv not read the book but if it like the film it should be a relay good read.  We all so see staring Jerry O'cnnell who plays Vern you may have see him in the film scream 2 to name but 1 and a well know 24 star.  Its a well maid coming of age film a bitter sweet story your cry at the sad parts and cry with larghter at the funny parts.  All in all its 85 mins of your life you want miss just fill with a worm fuzzy feeling       
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         let me start with one of my all time fav wrighters/dirctor Mr Quentin Tarantino now i know this will sound totle bi but if im going to stared any were its going to be here   the 4th film (so we are toled by the titles by i think he done more) is up to date his best work  Uma as the bride totle set out to do all that every thing that a women who have been messed around by her man wants to do.  I realy do think this is a all girly film, girl power hit the screen in way that even men can watch with out sitting there thinking hang on this is one of them chick flick ladys please sit back watch and take in how it should be done if your best mates and boy friend have done you wrong  and if blood is not you cup of tea dont worry as the fight sceens are filmed in black and white (but if you can watch holby city there is not much diffrent i think) just think its water.  lucy liu i hate to say once again she is playing the same old same old a pushy big mouth brit still the women she plays shows that even in a verey meal word women can be top dog more girl power comming out there  from stated to finsh it tarantino all over jumping for one part of the story to the other with out it being in order with blood and coolness its out on vid dvd and showing on sky ladys watch this with your man (if you have one) and at the end smile and say your taking lessons in self defence and if not watch with all your girly mates and enjoy women doing it for themself who said girl power has gone      
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Im looking at this fine director and thinking he may end up in my list of top 5 people that what ever thay do it must been see. iv seen 2 out of 4 of his films and im up for going to see the village, he makes good films they have meaning to them storys with in storys levels and deeps im liking his work.    
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         D irector  Mr  Sam Raimi main leads Tobey Maguire, Alfred Moline and Kirsten Dunst  In this the next chapter we see peter parker go Thor the run of the mill porbs of a young man his age needs to face and the added bonus of being spider man  its got all the first film had big scenes played out with live action and c.g.i. (is it me or is the c.g.i. stuff noticeable?) and a story line that appealing to all ages good v bad but bad's not a evil as he likes to make out and did I miss some thing or is Anita m the only person not to know who peter is and why if every one else knows she don't find out (what going on there then).  As I left the pitcher house I felt as if some thing was not right a bit let down im in to my comics I like to get in to plots but in the movie the story seems to be going to fast and not sticking to how it should be.  You don't have had to see the first one to see the 2nd one its not had to get in to and you don't need to be a geeks who is too in to sci fi/comic land to enjoy lets hope this Stan Lee story runs the full un like x men not much happening there.  I cant weight to see 3, spider-man 1 out on DVD and all that spider-man 2 to come out soon.    
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I have been reading David Beckham My side this is his story in his words  After reading vicky's book (learning to fly)  and reading in the papers of what others say I decided to read what the man had to say of all of the going on's in what the Beckham family call the Beckham bubble    This type of book can be read by not only the die hard fan of the Beckham's but David talks a lot about foot ball so men your in for a good read there but also how him and Vicky meet they 1st date and so on all so the weeding, at times I do feel that he may be trying to hard to paint him as some one a lot different form how the press put him, just as a normal dad family man and that's what he is if you strap him (and what lady wouldn't) of all the press and money and left him alone he be no different form your dad or brother.  Bless if like me your nose or in to your footy big time its a read you wont get bored with.  If you was to ask any of my friends what kimi's pet peeve they says Beckham she thinks he gay and im sorry I still do please if you like to know more on why I think that please drop me a line.  The book its in hard and paper back and on tape so you have lots of way's to get your hands on it.      
      
</post>


</Blog>