<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Carrie's cat is sick, so I am gonna spend the night and try to help out. Hope we can get it to take some water, which she seems to be refusing to do. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man will this rain ever stop. Two days straight now, it has been raining. Pittsburgh must be a swamp, by now...  WWE RAW was a good show last night. My first wrestling show live. The Battle Royal was really cool, the Triple H/Chris Benoit 60 minute Iron man match was spectacular. The highlight of the evening however...  THE FLAIR FLOP  Yes... I have finally seen Ric Flair get the shit kicked out of him... pause in the corner... walk forward... stagger a little and fall forward flat on his face... IN PERSON! My life is complete. Hot crowd, great action, although we did chant "Here we go, Steelers!" during the Iron Man match. Us Pittsburghers... class ALL the way! 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       NP:  Axel Rudi Pell - Legions of Hell  Well, this marks my first blog entry. My track record generally isn't too good with these things, when it comes to updating them, but, eh. What the hell.  Anyway, went job hunting today. Not very promising. Probably gonna suck in my pride and try Walmart on wed. Anything is better than I have now. I have tried for them in the past. Hope my luck shall be different this time.  I will be putting my Resume' online at hmas.org in the near future if anyone reading this wants to check it out and hire me ;)  -Reno 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, I tried posting one of these twice in the last week and both times it didn't come up, so this will be the third time. If you are able to read this, then you know that it worked. if not... well blogger can fuck off and I'll go back to livejournal (or better yet start my own blog).  Anyway, tomorrow is the opening of insidepulse.com. It'll be nice to be able to read columns by my net god, Hyatte again. A week without him is like a week of not being able to jerk off. Passionless, boring, and all together unsatisfying. Now I can have a mental orgasm all over myself. Should be fun. Welcome back Cool Hy, you fucker.  Well, that is all I can think of. Now. If you'll excuse me, I plan to go stuff my face with Hostess Cupcakes. I can put a BOX away and I don't gain a pound, you bitches!!!!!!!  Reno 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>