<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I used to keep a journal when I was younger.&nbsp; Intimate stuff: pre and early teen angst. It makes for cringeworthy reading.&nbsp; Little banal details, like when I used to go fishing with my friend Ian, and how when we walked back from the lake (1.7 miles), and how cross I was with him because despite letting him borrow my stuff, he, who lived at the bottom of a hill, would not help me carry the equipment to my house, at the top of the hill.&nbsp; And he always seemed to catch the bigger fish.&nbsp; Little things. Like how Bruce was always able to get a girlfriend, in a routine that oddly seemed to follow the pattern of girls I fancied: that is, I like Emma, a week later he is dating her; I like Laura, a week later, he's dumped Emma and is seeing her; I like both Melanie and Rachel, a week later he is surreptitiously snogging both of them, et etc. Oh how I tried to render in words the pain I felt.&nbsp; Cringeworthy then. And utterly banal.  But these were all personal thoughts and intimate feelings, that because I was writing them in a diary, for my perusal only, I could explore and try to capture.&nbsp; So, journals are private places.&nbsp; This upsurge in the number of blogs is interesting then.&nbsp; very interesting.&nbsp; It seems that only very few of the blogs I have ever skimread are purely personal writings.&nbsp; Most blogs seem to have three purposes:  1. They are written, in a present-centred memoir sort of way, not for the sake of the individual author but for the readership: people write accounts of what they have been doing and what they have been thinking for the sake of those with whom they might lack daily contact and want to keep informed of their wheres and wherefors.&nbsp;   I call this the NARRATIVE BLOG  &nbsp; 2.&nbsp; People take on altered personas when blogging: they represent themselves slightly differently to what they are.&nbsp; As some sort of exercise in self-image improvement, they make out that their lives are infinitely more exciting than they are.&nbsp;   I call this the CRYFORATTENTION BLOG  &nbsp; 3.&nbsp; Some blogs, and the ones that are the finest to read, are mere streams of consciousness.&nbsp; Flows of thoughts.&nbsp; Ideas.&nbsp; Genuine personal engagement with personal issues, written in a way that exists not only for an audience reading, but for the benefit of the individual blogger trying to think ideas and thoughts through.  I call this the THOUGHT RECORD BLOG  &nbsp; I guess all blogs have aspects of all three.&nbsp; This short one does, certainly.&nbsp; I wrote that I wanted my photographs published: I lost interest in photography when I was 14; it's just something I thought sounded more interesting than a prediliction for habit forming pub sports.&nbsp; I guess I know when I'm writing this that certain people I know will read it.&nbsp; And that people I don't know might do so too.&nbsp; Which makes writing reflectively difficult when you are are always wondering about what people are going to think about what you say.&nbsp; Or whether any of it will come back to haunt you.&nbsp;   Is blogging then twenty first century storytelling? Personal narratives written for the many with individualism carefully sculpted to the wants of the audience; but not always anonymously authored?&nbsp; I wonder.&nbsp; I think blogging is a peculiarly modern phenomena.  I still think there's more to say about why. But I think it's worth thinking about: personal subjectivity meets the politics of writing on one of the most public fora possible.&nbsp; A case for further research.  Time to go now.  

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Insomnia is both a very bad film featuring Hilary Swank, Robin Williams (against type) and Al Pacino.  It's also something I have been suffering from of late.&nbsp; 7am the other night.&nbsp; Laying in bed for 5 hours with nothing but my own hyperactive brain to keep me company.&nbsp; Thank god I don't have to get up for work at&nbsp;8&nbsp; againthese days.&nbsp; I've tried reading, but that just doesn't help.&nbsp; Guess the not drinking and not going to bed pissed is having its impact.  Think the answer is to start working overnight.&nbsp; Sunrises are always better than sunsets.  

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink http://halloumi.com   The message says it all.&nbsp; I'm hungry for squeeky cheese, and there aint any!  

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Howdi Pop-Pickers, This is the e-journal of someone who has recently decided to try his best to do less of the following things: - drink less beer - cut down on the smokes - eat less ready made convenience store sandwiches.  Conversely, I need to: - exercise more.&nbsp; 13 stone at 5'9" aint too good. - start doing some things that are 'meaningful', whatever that means.  I guess that's a pretty ordinary lists of wants and want nots.&nbsp; But, heh, if I can't be disgustingly self-obsessive in a blog, then where can I?&nbsp; Thing is, I reckon, that I spend too much time with people younger than me.&nbsp; I have buddies my own age, but they seem to have their own private worlds of girlfriends, board games, pot habits and 9 to 5 jobs.&nbsp;&nbsp; I'm a perennial student, however: have been at Uni now for the best part of ten years, and whilst I may now be writing up a doctorate and teaching undergrads, I still seem to find myself hanging out with those that are a good seven years or so younger than me.&nbsp; Spose thirty, which isn't that old really, is approaching apace and I want to at least meet some life objectives by then.&nbsp; Doesn't help that one of my few older friends hung himself and his dog from a beauty spot on Christmas Day leaving on his suicide note, "Where has all the time gone".&nbsp; Silly melodramatic beggar.&nbsp; Anyhow, life objectives, that is, have a job, a car and my own house; but more than that, have run away spontaneously for weekends at a time to weird overseas locales because I feel like it, have sex with people&nbsp; whose names I didn't know the day before, get some of my photos published, have someone write to me because I'm semi-famous enough, slap Liam Gallagher, et etc.&nbsp; Instead it's just an odd routine of routinelessness that goes nowhere; that merely loops the loop, bringing me back to the same place, only slightly dirtier, maybe a bit podgier, certainly a lot&nbsp;emptier, and predictably just as restless.&nbsp; Adventures are not adventures when they're preplanned.  Anyhow, thought I'd go to church again, and try and find&nbsp;God.&nbsp; Again.&nbsp; I didn't go.&nbsp; Something else cropped up, as it has done for the last five years.&nbsp; Had a spiritual dimension to it though.&nbsp; Ended up on an unplanned excursion in the Lakes, eating at the Mason's Arms (just on the other side of Cartmel Fell) which is perhaps one of the best pubs I have ever visited.&nbsp; Really.&nbsp; Was only able to have one pint cos was driving.&nbsp; A good thing since there were so many fantastic beers on offer.&nbsp; I'll have to get fit and cycle there next time.&nbsp; Or just make a myriad of one pint at a time visits: the food alone warrants it.&nbsp; Then walked up a nice hill called Gummer's How.&nbsp; It was all a bit serene:* the views were spectacular, the effort was exhausting, and it got dark a little too quickly for comfort.&nbsp; My ex kept ringing, threatening to 'end it all' as she often does, so trying to navigate my way down a rather steep hillside, with very sharp crags and soggy slipperary mud in the fading light, in inappropriate footwear, seemed rather appropriate.&nbsp; I didnt fall over, let alone fall off a cliff face into the murky depths of Lake Windermere below, so I'll take that as righteous intervention.&nbsp; Not really.&nbsp; What was spiritual was that while stood at the top, I was reminded just how small I really am. and it was an adventure within an hours drive.&nbsp; Who needs Munich?  Don't get me wrong, I am always acutely aware of how petty my gripes are and what small fry they compared the fucking blue whales of big-issues other people have to carry around with them on a daily basis.&nbsp; But in feeling small, I appreciated the people I do know; realised that although a lot of friendships are transient, they're friendships nonetheless.&nbsp;   This is a new me folks.&nbsp; I predict the non-binging, 5 fags a day only, 5 fruit and veg, workaholic, Mr Multi-Sociable person I have decided to become will last about a week.&nbsp; But heh, an inch is as good as a mile.&nbsp; Yeah right.  By the way: - I will refuse to vote at the next election.&nbsp; I have an intense dislike of Blair, but no other parties are worth it.&nbsp; Greens used to be, but the local Green councillor&nbsp;nearly ran me over whilst driving a people carrier.&nbsp; Twatface hypocrit.&nbsp;I for one think that conscious destruction of the ballot paper is a political message that needs to be counted and taken more seriously. - I used to be a bit of an animal rights activist, but have since settled down into being a contented vegetarian.&nbsp; I fantasise about renting an allotment.&nbsp; Two problems with that: one, I already fear I'm turning into Arthur Fowler (Eastenders addicts of old will appreciate the analogy); and,&nbsp;I can't seem to drag myself out of bed until after noon these days, and I hear the best time to nurture one's fledgeling veggies is first thing in the morning. - I like thinking, a lot.&nbsp; However, too much thinking leads to thoughts of outlandish scenarios, so I come back to a solid need for good empirical evidence, so long as that evidence is properly thought through and it is realised that the interpretation of that evidence is synechdochically subjective.&nbsp; Confused? Try my job.  OK, off to bed now friends.&nbsp; Ebay has furnished me The Carpenter's Gold album.&nbsp; Excited about falling asleep listening to Rainy Days and Mondays.   *  There's some pics on this person's website: gratitudes to them, whoever they may be.&nbsp; They seemed to enjoy their holiday though.   urlLink  http://www.luphen.org.uk/public/2002/2002lakes4.htm    

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Oranges: off to edinburgh tomorrow lemons: to help my sister move house, not to see any of the festival. 

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Rant time, then.  More brainfarts as one commentator required.  Three things have been getting on my nerves recently.  1. The irrationality of Ex-Girlfriend 2. The Ease with which Melodrama becomes a Constructed Moodswing Indicator amongst people that should know better 3. This staying off the booze business.   1. The Ex. Without divulging too much information, the lady and mother of my child that left me on my birthday two and a half years ago for an old man that keeps ferrets, has been particularly irritating of late.  Why?  Well, we don't argue any more.  We don't bicker.  I let her keep the car, and heh, when I visit, she now allows me to drive it.  She is being nice to my family.  She is seeming to be more emotionally and mentally stable than ever (and she has had a lot of mindaltering issues to deal in her time, the poor mite).  But she is being nice to me.  And I'm finding this incredible hard to understand. I'm not used to it.  She doesn't ring me up to cry down the phone anymore.  She hasn't mentioned suicide for nearly three months.  She is on the cusp of giving up the fags.  She isn't moaning about her image.  This is all very odd.    I think she's fallen in love with someone, and I am finding this rather odd to come to terms with.  I mean, it's not that I still like her in a coupling up kind of way, but usually when I go on my fortnightly visits, I stay on her sofa (and apart from engaging in the nookie) things were mostly the same as they were before she left.  Shopping, play areas, days out, arguments, washing up together, bamboozle.  (The ferret man isn't on the scene anymore, by the way).  It's like my pretend family.  The flip side to my split life.  And now it's like she has moved on and I am left in this unpredictable limbo space.  I don't think I ever fell completely out of love with her, but could happily co-exist with the frequent visits, etc etc, so I saw enough to know I was relieved that we had split up, but also saw enough to justify that I hadn't invested so much of my love in someone so unworthwhile.    Now all I can see are the good sides, and it is making me mightily confused.  I don't want to get back together with her (even though, in terms of seeing my son as frequently as I possibly can it would make sense).  We'd drive each other beserk.  She doesn't know the meaning of the word monogamy, and I don't know the meaning of the word jealousy.  I just found the ferret man funny.  That's why I think she left, to prove a point - that I should take her more seriously.  However, the thought of her being happy with someone else, yes, HAPPY, is really annoying.  And the reason I can think of for why is that it means I'll have no excuse to happily meander through my up-north life companionless if my pseudo-relationship life down-south is to end.    Guess that makes me the irrational one.  Hmmmm, needs some thought.     2.  Constructed Melodrama.  I have had to put up with a hell of a lot of emotional shit in my short life.  A manic depressive mother, a violently alcoholic father, a bulimic depressed ex, the death of my grandfather (my pseudo - dad) because of hospital error and it's attendant after-effects on the above.  In short, I have become incredibly cold to a lot of life's little worries.  I don't mean to say that this is indicative that I don't give a toss about people that are upset about things that seem minor to me.  Rather, the opposite.  The smallest of problems, in one person's specific context, can really be to them something so bad that creates in them such tremendous anger, or upset, that they cannot do anything but express their emotions via the backdoor route of melodrama.    Melodramatic is defined, by the first web dictionary I could get hold of, as: "showing much stronger emotions than are necessary or usual for a situation".  I think when someone is upset by something, it is human nature to exaggerate the emotional response to the cause, either as a cry for attention, or as an attempt towards articulating the problem in one's own words so one can see the banality of the issue and then move on.  I have no problem with this.  It's a very human thing to do, and something we all need to do from time to time to stay sane.  Where I have a problem with Melodrama, per se, is where people turn to it in a routine manner as a method of either   (a) trying to generate sympathy instead of just saying in plain terms what the fucking fuck the matter is,  (b) trying to persuade onself that they are a victim when, if common sense is allowed into the equation, no victim status exists.  Indeed, when someone is so content with wanting to be a victim, that tiny things are played up, via melodrama, to deliberately inflate the problem, and consciously endorse the constructed victim status (c) Melodramatically state the intent to do something less than good, thus creating the impression that the emotive responses of the person are far greater than indeed they might be, but using melodrama as an excuse to blame poor actions on emotions when one really should know better.  Now, I have not explained these very well here.  Don't get me wrong, melodrama has it's purposes.  As a cry for help, it can very effective.  As a way of allowing people knowledge that you're hurting, it is effective.  As a way of asking for help, without saying 'will you help me', it is effective.  But the deliberate deployment of melodrama as a way to try and enforce sympathy and justify dickheadedness, is, in my mindset, very very wrong.  As is the continual use of it over things that, if they were thought about properly, shouldn't warrant such reactions.  Someone asked me in Truth forum whether I thought men crying or women crying to be the most beautiful.  I found it extremely hard to answer.  I have seen so many tears that I find it hard to sympathise unless I know what the problem is, and know that the problem, for the person, is big enough to warrant it.  For me, at the moment, the best kind of tears are either those caused by chopping onions, or those that are spontaneous responses to happiness.  3.  I've been boozeless for a very long time now.  apart from the odd glass of red wine with meals.  I'm going to go and pissed now and play some darts.  Excellent.  I'll probably start crying about how nobody loves me, or something though.  I can be such a melodramatic fool, you see. 

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok, someone asked me to picture this scene...  Monica Bellucci, Alyssa Milano, Elizabeth Shue, and Barbarella mudwrestling in a competition to win my affections.  Sadly, I couldn't.  

						
</post>


</Blog>