<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I honestly think that certain stones bring certain energies to the bearer. This has also been noted by many cultures across the globe. The Maori of Aetearoa is one such culture whom believe in this. They believe that the bearer of, and even those who just lay their eyes on pounamu, or jade or nephite or serpentine, will inherit the  Mana  of the stone.  The following qualities have been attributed to Pounamu:   Kindness   Comes through in its wamth, lustre and brilliance   Honesty and integrity   Its interior can be viewed from outside revealing its inner beauty   Bravery   Can only be broken but never twisted out of its true shape formed by the artist   Friendship   Becomes warm when worn against the body and soaks up the body oils of the owner becoming one with them.  Different shapes also signify different things,&nbsp;I have a carving of a Toki or an adze, and that brings Honour and Strength to the bearer.&nbsp; I forgot to wear it today, and the strength has definitely been lacking, not only physical strength (thats due to my tubbiness, no excuses there), but also my emotional strength.   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The sedentary office life has taken its toll, as I 'accidentally' glimpsed into the mirror during my lunch break, I noticed that I have become a tubby bitch. The cheekbones that was once quite prominent is no more, they have gone, wrapped in a cosy blanket of Cal blubber. Its disgusting. Time for a revamped excercise regime, gotta find ways of losing weight, all I have is Dragon Boat, but that is wearing thin. I am often reminded that its my damn Virogan personality that makes me change my mind so often about so many different things. One thing that hasn't changed since I was 9 years old, however, is my fondness for Martial Arts. From the childish ninja impersonations to&nbsp;the deep cultural pride that has developed, I have always found some sort of derived benefit.  Having said that though, I find my beloved chosen tradition to be somewhat lacking. Not enough conventional western cardio excercise, and thus, my tubby ass.  I'm just looking for excuses for my laziness. I'm just a lazy biatch, no more excuses. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If we could look at the world in&nbsp;a trance of wonderment, appreciate all its amazing life forms, see the sky and the earth in its natural glory and to not be distracted by the overload of undigestible, incomprehensible load of knowledge, so called news.   News produced for&nbsp;privately owned networks, market-driven companies, using the public's free air space. You're paying for your own air space! Its not news, its entertainment. Get cable instead.   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had such grand plans once, everyone does I think. Everyone plans and these plans become 'knowledge', or atleast what we think is knowledge, in reality its nothing more than expectations. Expectations however is nothing more than a goal. While its nice to have, it never really is the place where your dreams come true, because invariably, you have new plans.   But imagine if we did know, I mean  really  know  , what our future held for us. Think about it, it may not tell you&nbsp;what&nbsp;you want to hear exactly, it might not match your  plans . What then?&nbsp; What if you were destined to become a pauper? I don't know about you, but I don't think I'd like to hear that! Would you really want to know?   Whats the point I hear you say? No point silly, its a blog!   But here is something I've been dwelling on for the last 3 years:  Expectations  can all too often end in  Disappointment .   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When confronted with instances of verbal racism, all I could do was giggle nervously like a schoolgirl. On the one hand I despised the Redneck, but on the other, I felt powerless to criticise, afterall, I was at work and everything&nbsp;I said was being recorded,&nbsp;I also empathised with the verbal progenator's particular&nbsp;situation (put there by my employer) and somewhat sympathised with him. He only knew what he heard, and that happened to be a persistent telemarketer with a thick sub-continental accent. Despite that, I should not have laughed and encouraged such anti socio-politico-cultural behaviour. I am part of the problem.   I've put a '1' after the title because I know this is a subject that I will continue to touch on in the days to come.   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The quarter life crisis is&nbsp;probably one ofthe most&nbsp;terrible things in life, it ranks EQUALLY with the other -life crisis'. For sure, they're different issues, but when it boils down to it, its all about life decisions.   I look around me in this call centre, and catch my reflection,&nbsp;I look hot! But thats not the point, the point is, I am surrounded by people of all ages, in different stages of their lives.  I really should  take some mental notes, and I suppose in many ways I have. I can't do this forever, my ego won't allow me to. It may seem like a sorry point to be motivated by, but its a source of motivation nontheless.   Now all I have to do is work out what I'm going to do in the near future to correct the position I have found myself in.   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Life is so transient, so mutable, so ever changing. the winds of time alter everything in its path. Those of you who think that things won't, are seriously deluding yourselves. But hey, I guess thats the beauty of life, the very same things that creates momentary grief for us, is also, at the very same instance, the thing that we all write about, the same thing that motivates people like me and Sheryl and the next blogger and...er well maybe not you, since you're looking into this window,&nbsp;a window of&nbsp;my time, in your time. Whats time? But anyways...  Its all beautiful isn't it? 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its nice to be important, but its important to be nice. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would like to write something positive today. Afterall, it is raining and the Earth is being nourished. I've been on a roll lately, emotionally, I'm feeling strong, I feel like I can do anything! I think I have been in a rut (did you know that the term 'rut' means 'A condition or period of mammalian sexual activity')....I wish. No, I've been a rut of diffidence. I'd say for a year maybe more. Its refreshing to be able to stand back and say to myself 'You're da Bomb!' and not feel like I'm kidding myself. I can't guarantee that this will hold for long though, but, with the help of some unlikely friends, I'm taking measures to re-establish my old self, hopefully without some of those deleterious traits of mine.  Its all about keeping the big picture in mind, but even that can be too small at times!  Its all good though, I'm applying for a job that is placed in Canberra. The application is taking all the positive reinforcement that I can summon, and even then, its not all that inspiring!  Its hard to stay positive! I'll try again later! Its already taken me 1.5 hours to type these few lines! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up at 6:15 this morning, feeling great. I decided that I would feel even better at 6:30am, so I went back to sleep.  I got up at 6:30 and had a slightly sore neck, and decided to sleep it off.  At 7am, I got up, with a very sore neck and I felt like shit. In fact, my neck hurts so much, I still feel like shit!  What a day! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trying so desperately to fit into the mould of society, I find myself lost. Lost in my thoughts, lost in my directions.  Resisting the natural ebb and flow of the individual, the developing self. The dynamic self.  Still, nothing is solved, pollution still abounds, however, restoration and gentrification processes are in motion. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel so uninspired.  Its all because of time. We can control almost everything, we affect most things, but one of the things that we will never beat is time.  'Give it time, give it time'. But time is what turned all my todays into yesterdays. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes indeed I'm, alone again And here comes emptiness, crashing inIts either love or hate, I can't find in between Coz I've been with witches and I've been with a queen  It wouldn't have worked out anyway So now it's just another lonely day, hey hey Further along, we just may But for now it's just another lonely day  Wish there was something I, could say or do I can resist anything but, the temptation from you I'd rather walk alone, then chase you around I'd rather fall myself then let you, drag me on down  It wouldn't have worked out anyway So now it's just another lonely day, hey hey Further along, we just may But for now it's just another lonely day  Yesterday seems like a, life ago Coz the one I love today, I hardly know You I held so close, in my heart oh dear Grow further from me with every, falling tear  It wouldn't have worked out anyway So now it's just another lonely day, hey hey Further along, we just may But for now it's just another lonely day 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It feels like I'm climbing a mountain. At the moment, I have reached a giant, steep hill, and the burning rays of the proverbial sun is blaring down on me, there is no respite. I cannot see the peak of this mountain, so I can only just continue to climb until the view gets a bit better and the path a little less steep. I know that eventually, there'll be breaks, and the shady coolness of some wise, old tree. I also know that I'll reach a lookout some time in the future, where I will have a very clear and crisp view of what has gone before me.  How far away that time is depends on how much walking I do, the speed of which depends on my work rate. If I keep stumbling along dead-end paths then it will take all the more time to get to the pinnacle.  For a while, it was hard deciding which mountain to climb. I would start on one, and after a little bit of trekking, I would decide that I didn't like the flora and/or fauna I encountered, so I would start on another, and before the end of the day I would have started on several different mountains but would find myself, again, at the base of all these different mountains, having made no ground whatsoever.  At times the path can be rough, and hard to walk across, but its never impossible, how far you can go depends on how committed you are to reaching the peak.  My problem has been:  Which Peak?  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes you look back at your life, your experiences or your relationships. Then you look into the hypothetical present, and then you are left with the prospects of 'what ifs' and 'maybes'. But I think the worst of all, are the questions that begins and ends with 'Why?'
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It so easy to be flustered by the negativity of other people. You might be zooming along, minding your own business and all it will take is for an unhappy person to ruin it for you.  I started this entry with the intention to write about something else, but I was rudely and abruptly interrupted by a North American intent on getting her way. Sorry love. I wish I was able to just not be affected, but I'm tired and all I want to do is sleep....again. And now, I can't remember what I wanted to write about. I think it was about how fickle Humans can be, no, thats what i'm writing about now!  I do believe it was about how funny inter-personal relationships can be. Or rather infatuations. Perhaps I am admitting to a certain infatuation of my own. Regardless, I've noticed how I am often speechless. I am rendered mute. So what am I saying? ...Its rare for me to be mute, I am a very talkative induividual, in fact, when I was in pre school, I had my mouth taped because I spoke so much. Can you believe that? I was like 3 and they taped my mouth up! You don't believe me? You have to keep in mind that I was still in an Asian country back then. Ahh... Its always refreshing to laugh at yourself!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every so often I will find myself in a state of confusion. I ask questions about myself and my life direction. New reasons arise for why I should do this or why I shouldn't do that. All too often it is easy to get carried away on these whims. Unfortunately for me, life isn't so fatastical. But then again, I never do regret the life decisions I make. I may wonder, retrospectively, about the time lost or perhaps even wasted, but never regret, because i know the life experiences I have gained can never be taken away from me. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>