<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Vanaf nu is Aerodynamik voor 10 dagen de leider van onze clan! Vragen of opmerkingen of andere zever --> AERODYNAMIK :p:p:p
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tot over 10 dagen dan beste mensen :)
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Morgen zal de site beheerd worden door Aerodynamik wegens mijn verlof:p Veel succes Aerodynamik!
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tot slot moeten we natuurlijk nog een woordje zeggen over de veelbesproken contextgevoelige advertenties die je te zien zou krijgen. Wel, in de praktijk blijkt dat allemaal nog goed mee te vallen. Advertenties verschijnen netjes in de marge, net zoals dat het geval is met de gesponsorde links in de Google-zoekmachine.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gmail heeft ook een erg handige zoekfunctie waarmee je aan de hand van trefwoorden heel gemakkelijk je mail kunt terugvinden. Ook handig is dat e-mailconversaties als een pak kaarten op elkaar gestapeld worden.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aan elk mailtje kun je een of meer labes toekennen om zo orde te scheppen in je inbox. Dat is ook nodig als je echt zinnens bent om bijna al je e-mail te bewaren in je postbus die tot maximaal 1 gigabyte kan bevatten!
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gmail mag dan wel 'bèta' zijn, daar is niks van te merken in de webinterface. Die heeft er zelfs geen probleem mee als je even offline gaat. LInks heb je mapjes als Inbox, Starred (zoals het vlagje van Outlook), Sent Mail en Spam (3). Gmail filtert spam automatisch en doet dat behoorlijk goed. :)
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OSM isn't any longer supported on the site! Sorry for the inconvienience. We hope to fix this soon.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      BOEE!HI HI HELLO         Wolfenstein   Posted: Jul 25 2004, 07:21 AM      Administrator   Group: Admin Posts: 14 Member No.: 1 Joined: 21-July 04  Warn: (0%)    o.O  just what I thought  , your real crazy naughty azzhole...    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1 versus 1... an duel between 2 people with 1 goal...'victory' . 2 random nations side against side wich will I get? 10 minutes of peace time in a normal game...  First I'v immedially began to build with the nation i did get...Poland. I'v used my usual strategy and so started building building by building. And I realized that things went quite well! After 7 minutes or so I'v got my diplomatic center. In the meanwile I was building up my army with pikeman. I set them up in a squad of 72 pikeman. When my diplo was build i started building archer and grenadiers and set their rally point into my army of pikeman. I'v got quite a big army but I saw that my opponent who played with Russia was very good too. It wasn't going to be an easy game. And it wasn't.  When I thought I was ready to go to battle I set up my army as I wanted to be. And of I went. With my army of archers,grenadiers,pikeman and some sich cossacks I reached his defences (or attacking force, whatever you want to call it) and then on a few meters of them I stopped. 2 armies facing eachother...1 of us who whas going to win this battle. And I'v attacked first with mij pikeman his pikeman and luckely I saw it was going well. But my archers, thats another story. Russia send lots of sich cossacks to my archers but quick I could stop them with my grenadiers but not before a great deal of damage was done to my army. I decided to retreat with my army (or what was left of it) and regroup. But my enemy used that moment to attack my army too!  When I finaly reached my 'regrouping point' the half of my army was killed in his attacks. But when he came near my regrouping point he made a big mistake. He first sent a wave of archers into the frontlines wich I easily killed. And before he know what was going on his army of archers was totaly destroyed. Now I hurried with my new army to his base wich was now as good as undefenced and destroyed his diplomatics center and his barracks. Now it wasn't difficult at all anymore to gain victory with al his fighting forces destroyed and his important buildings destroyed and finaly after quite a lot of time: VICTORY! 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Truky? Poland? Spain? It was random nation so you did not knew what nation you would get. The game started as 1v1v1 although soon we saw that I was the most strongest off all. So both enemys where afraid I would atack em. But I only atacked the best one....(enterprise) I beated him quite fast 72 pike vs +/- 40 so noty real warr ...So I was walking in base then I was being atacked by shenron.. I managed to survive the atack and was fuly going on shenron... This was hard because he managed to build up a huge army, and I lost lots of men vs enterprise. I atacked shenron again I can close I managed to get a blcksmith,and 2 townhalls but then shenron had made very much sich cossacks and then.... he won ground on my in my base.. I used all my peands to stop him. man we fought like hell. Then his siches where down... but I managed to make a 2th 17th century baracks... so 2 time more pikes I aatcked again, and again lots of sich cossacks game but this time I won them and continued in his base. Meanwhile he had made a new blacksmith only that one did not lived long couse m naughty little archers..then his defence felt he had not much gold left so he could not make more sich cossacks I can in his towen and demolisted some buildings....then he should watch so I left some peands alive... but suddenly he deleted all and became defaet.. (meanwhile enterprise managed to knock of all my pikes in his base and he was making a new army!) then I looked enterprises base @#$%&! damn not so good you can imagine(he ahd 2 baracks from the start off) then I was lucky that my archer atempt worked on enterprises diplomatic centre and his blacksmith menaing his aarmy woyuld not grew annymore... meanwhile I made 100 siches who where all done then we went in a Huge battle... his pike archers and grenadier vs my pike sich and archers...I won bnut not on low cost I had only 25 sich cossacks left... adn a hand full of pikeman(50) out of the 150 who went into battle then I started to demolish buildings the suddenly enterprice said that was a good game and left.  the end   it ended in 2v1 like you see.. unless this war we are still friends stronger even our friendship ever has been. this is also good to train allot like it started in training... even I trained and learned alot of this... TIP: nation doesnt matter turky+pol vs spain and spain can still win, it depends on Luck and Tactic  Aerodynamik 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nation: wich nations to take in Millions, the best nations are : Denmark, Prussia, Ukraine, Saxony, When no powernations (England, France)  -Denmark couse their musketeer wich are build very fast and can shoot very high 117.  -Prussia couse their hussars build faster + cheap stables Bad point muskets are expensive and build slow.   -Ukraine couse their serdiuk they don't shoot very much in a single shot but this units fire rate is much faster then normal musketeers + their hetman (450 hp, attack power 350)  -Saxony couse their grenadiers they are build extreme fast their fire power aint so high but you will have allot of shooter(more then when you have musketeers)  -When no powernations England couse they have cheap stable, so more hussars  -When no powernation France couse they ahve cheap stable, so more horses + special dragoon from stable max shoot power 89  How to build:  TIP: (use the shift butten, hold shift while placing buildings to let peasands continue to next building)  Use 18 peasents, lets them make 1 townhall and 1 mill, meanwhile they are building the buildings select 18 peasents who make a 18th century baracks (repeat this 6 times). 6 Peasents will remain let them make a blacksmith. When the peasents are done making the townhall and the mill let them make a storehouse, folowed by a market. The peasents from the blacksmith will make a 17th century barrack, folowed by a academy. (Do the fore harnasses upgarde in the blacksmith mounted units building speed 4 times faster), when the market is done move that peasents also to the academy to let them build it. When the academy is being build you should do the market trick noteyou are the left side from the 2 places where to select resoursers). Select 25000 gold and trade this to iron, then select 825000 iron to gold notehold shift and push on +1000 in order to select 100000 at a time) do the same for coal to. When you finshed your market trade you academy should be almost done. When the academy is completed do the ''raise miner salary -75% building time'' upgarde cost 9050 gold, this will help to complete the 18th century baracks faster. When this upgarde is done do the reduce musket cost the the academy and start making musketeer from the 18th century barracks, do all fire rate upgardes and the fire power upgrades (firepower upgardes in this line 30%-20%-10%-15% this gives max shoot power). make 2 more 17th century barracks (total you will have 3) do the officer defence and attack upgrade and then make unlimited oficer. Make 5 stables wich make unlimited hussar, and maka diplo where you should make around 500-600 dragoons do all the other upgardes at the blacksmith accept the food and building defence ( use the building defence from the academy that one is better). Make also 6 cathedrals where you make priest (they can heal a little of your soldiers a bit) When you are around 7.30-8.00 minut's start making out of 6 18th century baracks pikeman.  Army lining up:  Use the attack underway button with all your units except your pikeman. only place officer and musketeer on stand ground (both in atack underway mode, we do this with the musket in case hussar come between them the 18th century musketeers got a banjonet, but their firepower better then their banjonet so shooting is a better opsion). note: place all your units close to eachother a big front is more difficult to hold then a small one. use you peasents wich are doing nothing as shoothing flesh place them near your musketeer. Line up your hussar behind you army at the 2 sides, (in case his pikes fall then run then in his musketeers) when fighting walk you pikeman with the spear up! then they walk faster and when they in the enemy let their pike down so they can attack for some reason this works better then when you do it from the start. when you run out of pikes and peasents use your officer as shootflesh, when they are gone use your dragoons note: (your musketeer are the most importand!) do everything to keep as many alive as posible.  Afterbattle:  When the war is over just walk in his base and first destroy his blacksmith this will prevent pikes from his barracks and hussar, then get his academy then he wont get anny more officer. then its just a case of destoying all the buildings. note: when you run out of peasents you will be defeated so its nice to destoy all his mines and his townhals.  GL in your game and remember you may loose in the begin but you learn by looses and my manual to win it's just a case of play allot and learn from your mistakes. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A normal game with random nations and 10 minutes of peace time...what was it going to bring, what was it going to be?   The war was between Russia (aerodynamik ) and Sweden (Enterprise) versus Bavaria(Killer 999) and Poland (Tony). An off we went. I started building but quick I was a bit tired (my fingers hurted ) but on the other side things went quite well. I had builded my academy and finaly a diplomatic center. I managed to set up a little army with archers from my diplo and pikeman from the baracks and went to the enemy's base. But things went not quite well when i'v got there i soon got the feeling I was going to loose much of my men. I tryded to get to his diplomatic centre and try to destroy it but I failed. Aerodynamik managed to get his army smaller but that wasn't good enough for me. I had to regroup and luckely(with again a little help of aerodynamik , so you can see what teampower can do ) I finaly managed ,after quite what losses, to get trough his defences and destroy his diplomatic centre with my archer. Now with his diplomatic center destroyed it was as good as over for him. On the same moment Russia (aerodynamik ) attacked Bavaria (Killer 999) with a squad of well trained pikeman. Bavaria on the other side also came with a squad of pikeman but the expierience and strength of aerodynamik was no match for him, so he was as good as chanceless against the destroying force of Russia And so in no matter of time aerodynamik got trough the 'defences' (if there where any:p) of Bavaria and managed to destroy most of his important buildings. With our good tactics and a bit of luck we've got VICTORY. So never underestimate the power of teamwork  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nation: wich nations to take in Tousands, The best nations are: Poland, Russia, Algeria, Turky, Ukraine  -Poland couse their pikeman from 17th century barracks are made faster then avarage pikeman  -Russia couse they can easy make multiple 17th century barracks (only wood and stone)  -Algeria couse they have the best archers in the game wich are made very fast ( attack 199 each arrow and on buildings 150)  -Turky couse their tatar (made from stable) and their janissary (musketeer)  -Ukraine couse their serdiuk who have high fire rate and their hetman (made from stable, hp 450 attack 350)  How to build:  Let 6 peasents create a mill(do the mill upgarde to) and the other 12 make a townhall (make unlimited peasents), when the buildings completed make a storehouse. Then make a market as fast as you can couse it very importand! Market trade: 5000 coal for food, 3000 iron for wood 1000 iron for stone and 500 gold for stone. Make another townhall(make also unlimited peasents).Then make a blacksmith folowed by 2 barracks where you make pikeman when you are russia or poland, algeria makes archer, ukraine makes serdiuk, turky creates janissary. Then make a academy when finished do the ''new woodworking tools (wood extraction +100%)'' upgrade this helpes to get the wood faster to make a diplomatic centre, then go colect wood if you did everyhting good you should already have enough stone(except for russia you need to mine more stone then) so everyone on wood. Let 10 men work on the diplomatic centre meanwhile make at least 1 iron mine and 3 gold mines (when you are turky or ukraine make more iron and coal mines)(make in the diplomatic centre unlimited archer for poland and russia, infantryman for algeria ,ukraine and turky). When time and resoursers you can make extra barracks, or stables.   Army lining up:  Poland and russia:  Set your pike man in a formation (can be 15-36-72-120-196) best one do do is is pieces of 72 use with your pikes atack everybody underway and stand ground (a extra atack bonus) don't move your men anymore. then use your archer to kill the aponents pikeman use your archer as I say, how stupit it may look it's the best way. use ctrl+a (all units) select your archers and put then on atack disable then when u see a big spot of allot of enemy pikes walk near, and let your archers fire in a huge salvo ( just use your mouse to select where to shoot) almost all his men will die. Keep repeating this move with your achers, when almost all his pikes are gone sett you pikes losoe and kill his archer (you can do this very easy by leting 30 sich cossacks(made in diplomatic centre) around in his archer you can do this as a raid but not raid his base but raid his army ).  ukraine and turky  Line up your shooter (musketeer) with atack everybody underway Don't use stand ground! select your infantryman and put then atack underway and stand ground just before your shooters so that your shooters are safe keep a eye on enemy siches who could get your shooters from behind. Here you can also use sich cossacks to get his archers.  algeria  Line up your archers with atack everybody underway Don't stand groudn them! line up your infantryman on atack everybody underway and stand ground (just to keep enemy bussy) then let your archers shoot at the huge flocks of pikeman when enemy almost dead releasy your infantry loose. Here you can use siches to to get enemy archers.  Afterbattle:   When you are in his base, get his blacksmith no more pikes mean he is lost, then get his market before he can tarde stuff to make a new blacksmith. Then get his diplomatic centre. Note if you have no peasents you are defeated, so get his townhalls and his mines.  GL in your game and remember you may loose in the begin but you learn by looses and my manual to win it's just a case of play allot and learn from your mistakes.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nation: wich nations to take in normal actualy every nation is good in normal if you know their tricks but I think these nations are the best. Poland, Rusia, Turky, Algeria, Ukraine  -Poland couse their pikeman from 17th century barracks are made faster then avarage pikeman  -Russia couse they can easy make multiple 17th century barracks (only wood and stone) so more pikes  -Algeria couse they have the best archers in the game wich are made very fast ( attack 199 each arrow and on buildings 150)  -Turky couse their tatar (made from stable) and their janissary (musketeer)  -Ukraine couse their serdiuk who have high fire rate and their hetman (made from stable, hp 450 attack 350)  How to build:  Start by let 6 peasents make a mill and the other 12 on a townhall (make unlimited peasents). then place 5 peasents to cut stone. The other make a storehouse, when this building is finished palce them to go cut wood. Then make a market the trade: 1000 coal foor food, 200 gold for wood, 200 gold for stone. Then create a blacksmith folowed by a 17th century barracks (make unlimited pikeman) note: don't Upgrade your pike man waste of gold! Then when te barracks is done make 1 iron mine and 4 gold mines the unlimited peands go to the mill to gamble food. Trade iron and gold in the market for wood and stone to buy a academy, build the academy with people from your mill, dont wory about food just buy some more. When academy finished place them back to your mill. then place unlimited peasands on wood. Just trade gold and iron again to gain stone and wood to buy a diplomatic centre. When it is fisnihed make unlimited archers. Make your pikes into a squard. (then they are stronger ). make more mines, unlimited peasents to stone. Start on the food upgardes (possible a 2th townhall) and wood upgarde then go save for the big stone upgrade+ 300% stone, stables and other good stuff in most time it will come to diplo and not much further. when you have diplo you can upgrade pikes but diplo is importand!  Army lining up:  Place your pikeman on attack everybody underway and stand ground and your archers behind them. It's also sweet to preform little raidings from side in his base with 5 archers, this is verry effective or just grab his mines. then he will be able to make less men, couse no resoursers. Use again the archer tactic with salvo's this is the most effective way of using your archers. when he got archers just make 10 siches and walk them into his archers. note becareful for little raiding's they are very effective! Note when both teams are weak so it going even, use your peands they are very strong they hit 20 and some nation peands got 100 health good fighters.  Afterbattle:   Try to get his blcksmith meaning no more pikeman for him so he will have little chance of surviving. then his market so that he can't trade things to make new blacksmith. then gte his diplo. Note when you have no peasands you are defeated, so it's nice to destoy his townhals and his mines.  GL in your game and remember you may loose in the begin but you learn by looses and my manual to win it's just a case of play allot and learn from your mistakes. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It seems that there is not very much activity on the forums and on the site! Visit (if you can) once a day the site and the forums and read new treads and topic and reply! Without your support the clan isn't what is should be, a nice and respectable clan!
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tournament  There are plans to hold a tournament for Cossacks. If you have suggestions about how and when it could be done, send it to one of the councilmembers! More information will follow soon!
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Site-update  For a while the site has a new layout. If you don't like the theme, you can change it on the left. (see theme select). There are some difficulties with to forums but we hope to solve this as soon as possible. (now on the left is the forum for Cossacks, in the upper you'll find RTCW)
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you have nice ideas and suggestions for the site, mail them to me
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Members  Currently we have 13 Cossacksmembers and 4 RTCW members.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are now 3 council members: Enterprise  Aerodynamik  Orbit  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A giant lurks on the coast of North Africa. Build into the very living rock of the libyan coastline, the Siegfried battery dominates the southern Mediterranean. Siegfriends colossal 15 inch gun is terrorizing Allied shipping and protects Sicily from Allied attempts at invasion. Here in North Africa, The Allies and the Axis are put face to face, it's a fight to the death.  Number Info: 1:> Axis North-West MG 2:> Gun(cannon) ''Controls'' 3:> Allied East MG 4:> Allied West MG 5:> Axis West Bunker MG 6:> Axis South-East MG 7:> Allied Assault Ramp 8:> Back Entrance of the Axis Main Bunker 9:> Command Post    Mission objective destroy the Gun(cannon), this can be done by constucting the assault ramp, or by the axis main bunker entrance. Blast your way in, when you are lost inside the Axis Bunker, follow the ''blue tags with a cannon'' on it. When you reach the gun just drop some Dynamite (engeneer weapon and arm it with the tang push ''5'' above typing keys ) next to the gun, if able place more in case it gets defused. When dynamite explodes you win. Note: you can capture the axis west bunker, for the back entrance some axis need to come out so door opens or you need enemy clothes (covert ops) when they say destroy the generator folow the ''red lighting tags'' in the bunker place dynamite and back entrance ''extra doors'' open There are 2 doors 1 realy big 1 narrow. enjoy 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The once-peacefull desert town of Tobruk is torn asunder as Axis and Allied forces struggle for tactical and strategic dominace. Tobruk's narrow backstreets and byways are the setteling for a desperate face-to-face clash of elite forces. It's an all-or-nothing fight to the death.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are four game modes in Enemy Territory, each with their own particular style of play: Objective Mode, Campaign Mode, Stopwatch Mode, and Last Man Standing.   Objective Mode In the Objective game mode teams must accomplish a series of tasks or objectives to win. These objectives can include everything from taking control of specific points on the map to destroying key installations. A team must complete all the primary objectives in the time limit to win.  Campaign Mode Campaign mode is a form of Objective mode that allows players to compete against each other in a series of related maps. Players can increase their Rank and Skills over the course of the campaign and carry them from map to map. Skills and Rewards persist from map to map for the duration of the Campaign.  Stopwatch Mode In Stopwatch mode, teams must accomplish the objectives in the shortest possible time. At the end of a round the teams will switch. The team that was defending will now attack and must now beat their opponents' time from the previous round. Team-switching is not allowed in Stopwatch mode.  Last Man Standing (LMS) Last Man Standing is a form of Team Deathmatch where players must completely eliminate the opposing team to win a round. Players have only one life. They can be healed with Health Packs from Medics or Health Cabinets, but will not respawn if killed. In LMS there are no skill points, XP does not count towards your score and there are no objectives other than to wipe out the opposing team. There are no Last Man Standing Campaigns.  Respawning, Reinforcements, and Max Lives In all game modes except Last Man Standing, players will respawn after they die, meaning that they'll come back to life at the team's spawn point with full health and ammo. Players will respawn in reinforcements, or timed waves, that run continuously. The amount of time left until the next reinforcement respawn is shown in the upper left of the screen when a player is killed. The player will only respawn at the next reinforcement period if they've hit the Jump key (Space) before the clock runs out. If the player hasn't hit the jump key, they will stay in limbo and will not respawn. Players can use the reinforcement time to configure their class and weapon in the Limbo Menu.   All game modes apart from Last Man Standing can use the Max Lives option. This option makes the player pay a price for using up all of his lives. The penalty is set to a default three respawn cycles until he can rejoin the fray. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Enemy Territory's maps can be played in a variety of ways, but mainly involve constructing, destroying or taking Objectives. The objectives can be studied in the Command Map by hitting (G) or the Limbo Menu by hitting (L).  To switch to a weapon or tool, press its corresponding number key or cycle to it using the next/previous weapon keys. To use it, press the fire button. Short taps of the Fire button will fire single shots. Hold down the fire button to fire in a long burst or to use a tool for a longer duration.   Players will suffer damage from weapons (their own team's, as well as the enemy's), from falling from height or drowning. Players can be healed by picking up Health Packs, either from a Medic or from a Health Cabinet.  If a player runs out of health, they die. They can now either be revived by one of their team's Medics, or go back into the Limbo menu and choose another team, class or weapons load-out if they wish. Players in Limbo will respawn in the next reinforcement wave at the Spawn Point they've specified in the Command Map.  Players can always check on the status of objectives and their teammates' locations by checking their Command Map (G). The Command Map will also display any battlefield intelligence gathered by their team's Covert Ops.  Players will be alerted to developments on the battlefield by their Command HQ - automated audio messages telling you the state of play and what your next objective is.  Players can also talk with each other, either by typing text messages (using the T Universal Say or Y Team Say keys) or actuating the pre-recorded voice messages in the Voice Chat menu (V).   Players can also form FireTeams to coordinate their tactics. Players can talk to member of their own FireTeam by using the U FireTeam Say key.  Players will be rewarded for good teamplay with Experience Points, extra skills, promotions and medals at the end of the game.  Don't step on the little flags in the ground - they're Land Mines and they'll kill you!  If you find you can't perform an action or fire a heavy weapon, you probably don't have enough Power Bar.  Building Command Posts will help your team to fight effectively. While not the primary goal of your team, building and protecting your Command Post while destroying the opposing team's Command Post will give your team a definite advantage. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *1> *2> *3> *4>  you will get promoted when you use heavy weapons (mortar, panzerfaust, tompson, mp40, (when you are a soldier), flametrouwer and mobile MG42 note: also all the other MG's count as heavy weapons the ones who engeneers need to fix with unlimited ammo.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Axis and allies clash in the previously peaceful surroundings of a winter woodland fuel depot. The snowy woody hills and valleys will be the scene of a mortal battle. Face to face, it's a fight to the death, only victor will survive.         
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *1> Bionoculars (item) *2> Physical fitness *3> Improved health *4> Trap awareness  you will get promoted when you are in the scene of action allot ( kill somone and you hurt yourself then heal yourself etc.) 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *1> Improved use of medic Amunition *2> Improved Resoursers (faster load of usable medic items''med kitt, adrenaline'' *3> Full Revive *4> Self Adrenaline (unlimited stamina for short while)  you will get promoted as you do medic skills ''health packages, revive people'' 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *1> Improved Resoursers (faster load for airstrike and ammo boxes) *2> Improved Signaling *3> Improved Air, Ground support *4> Enemy Reconision (covert ops in your team's clothes)  you will get promoted when you suply people with ammo or when you use the ''air suport bomb''  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *1> Improved use of light weapon ammo *2> Faster Reload *3> Improved light weapon handling *4> Akimbo lugar or Akimbo colt (dual handgun)   You will get promoted as you use ''hand guns'' (colt, lugar) tompson (note: soldier tompson is heavy weapons) and mp40 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *1> Improved use of all scoped weapon ammo *2> --------------- *3> --------------- *4> ---------------  You will get promoted as you use covert ops skill's (sniper, sten, FG49 , taking enemy clothes
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today the Extreme European Warriors are almost 2 months old! More information will follow
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today the site has got 1200 visitors :) 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now you can find articles related to RTCW:ET in the 'articles' section. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now in the articles sections you can find all promotions! (soldier,medic,engineer,...)
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please be more actif on the site and the forums! You'll make the clan much more cozier and nicer! RESPECT!
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YESS! AFTER A LOT OF WORK I FINALLY MANAGED TO GET THE FORUM UP  AND RUNNING AGAIN! Thanks to Aerodynamik :):) 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Great, the forum went down :(
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm now setting up a database for tips and tricks for RTCW:ET
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Great, the site is now fully up-and-running!  urlLink www.extremeclan.net  ! :) comments are welcome! 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things are not going as well as planned with the website but I hope it all will be fixed tomorrow :) 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my first message, I'm trying it out now! :) 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since today the site has an new lay-out!
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm finally back from vacation :D great isn't it :p
    
</post>


</Blog>