<Blog>


<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Introduction This consumer guide will focus on the needs of a typical HPU student.  Although it discusses desktop PC options, another important purchasing decision to consider is whether to purchase a laptop or desktop computer. Many graduate students at HPU are required to travel for their work or live outside of Hawaii, so the benefit of being able to work on assignments while traveling may be worth the investment in a laptop.   Prior to purchasing a new PC, you should determine your computer needs.  For example, will it be used for office work, graphic design, web design, surfing the internet, or playing video games with heavy graphics? After identifying your needs, you can then choose their own computer specifications. For example, if you’re looking for the best gaming experience, you should spend more money on a 3D graphics card. If you will be using it for work all day, you should invest in a better monitor and a better CPU.    Here are the topics discussed in this consumer guide:   urlLink Software  •	 urlLink Suites  •	 urlLink Security  •	 urlLink Operating Systems    urlLink Hardware  •	 urlLink CPU  •	 urlLink Video and Sound Cards  •	 urlLink Networking    urlLink Peripherals  •	 urlLink Hard Drives  •	 urlLink RAM  •	 urlLink Optical Disks  •	 urlLink Monitors  •	 urlLink Printers    urlLink Buying Tips  •	 urlLink Hardware  •	 urlLink Monitors  •	 urlLink Printers  •	 urlLink Networking     Software  :     System Software - Operating Systems : An operating system is an integrated system of programs that manages the operations of the CPU, controls the input/output and storage resources and activities of the computer system, and provides various support services as the computer executes the application programs of users (O’Brien, 2004).   There are many choices in the market such as Windows XP, Windows XP Pro, Windows XP Media Center Edition 2004, Windows 2000, Windows 2003, MacOS, and Linux and so on. The Microsoft Windows operating systems are the most popular amongst college students.  The Windows XP Media Center Edition 2004 brings together the best of previous Windows editions, blending home entertainment, productivity, and communications in one seamless environment. Windows XP Professional offers powerful networking enhancements for business and pro users.  Windows XP, Home edition, is a popular choice. It offers simple and efficient operations for most productivity and online purposes. The operating system has had some issues with security and bugs, however, Microsoft has been getting better at dealing with security issues.  According to Guth and Boslet (2004), Microsoft this week has issued a Service Pack 2 (SP2) to Windows XP. It is designed to fortify the operating system against a range of computer viruses, worms, Web-based scams and other threats. The software is excepted to be distributed to 100 million PCs in the next two months through automatic Internet downloads. SP2 adds security in three main areas: by turning on protective firewall software and other security features previously turned off by default; by adding controls for protecting against online attacks; and by adding windows and instructions that Microsoft says will make it easier for computer users to manage security features.    Application Software : Software that performs the basic functions of word processing, spreadsheets, databases, and presentations are most useful for college assignments. Since some classes may require the use of Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, or Access, it is recommended that you purchase a Microsoft Office suite.  Microsoft Office 2004 is a suggested software suite that meets all of these needs.   Security Software : Since most classes at HPU require some use of the Internet, security software is a good investment.   Spyware takes information from a computer system without the user’s knowledge or consent. Getting software to deal with issue is very important. Some examples of good anti-Spyware programs are Ad-Aware, SpyBlocker, SpyCop, Spyware Blaster, and Popup Blocker.   Another recommended security software is anti-virus software. All computers can be easily exposed to computer viruses. This includes computers at home, at work, and at school. Viruses propagate in so many different ways; users are better off installing anti-virus software that will protect their computers rather than attempting to avoid exposure to a viral threat. In other words, if you use the Internet, read e-mail, stick floppy disks or CD-ROMs in your computer, or use wireless access networks, you need anti-virus software. Depending on the situation of the user, the level of security needed may increase. As a base, the software that should be installed is McAfee or Norton.    Hardware  :   CPU : One of the main parts of desktop and laptop is CPU (Central Processing Unit). Consumers should know which type of CPU is best suited for them. Each processor offers unique benefits.   Here are a few examples:  The Intel - Celeron is the lowest-cost processor, and can be found in many base models. It is well-suited to basic computing, basic office productivity software, and most online use.   The Intel - Pentium 4 is designed to handle the demands of such applications, and can handle more data at a higher speed, up to 3GHz and beyond. Processors that offer HT (Hyper-Threading) Technology can handle two data threads simultaneously, which is much better for gaming and the serious number-crunching needed by many multimedia applications.  AMD’s - Athlon XP processor is similar to the Pentium, with nearly the same processing speed under certain conditions. While not an absolute match of the Pentium 4, it is a very popular, less expensive alternative.  Since many HPU students use their PCs for work, as well as school, it is important for you to take into consideration your entire computer needs. Recommended CPU speeds are in the 1-2 GHz range.   Video and Sound Cards :  Most purchased desktops have video and sound cards integrated into the motherboard.  Integrated cards use system memory, so the performance on the spec sheet may not translate to actual performance. To improve a PC’s performance, you can install an enhanced sound or video card. However, these cards will cost around $ 100 - $ 300, depending on the quality and memory of the cards.   Usually, these cards have their own memory and processing chipsets. Therefore, they will reduce the load on the CPU. For video cards, look for a minimum of 64MB. A card with 128MB or more is a good choice if you are interested in 3D gaming or graphics and video editing.   If you want enhanced sound performance, avoid going with an integrated sound card. Many dedicated sound cards can now connect straight to your home entertainment system, with some even delivering Dolby Digital, 5.1 Surround for multiple speakers. Be sure to choose a card that suits your needs, both present and future.   Networking : Internet access is important as well since HPU offers numerous online classes. Make sure that your PC will meet the requirements for cable modem service from Roadrunner or DSL service offered by Verizon.   Wireless network adapters are becoming a networking standard. They reduce cable clutter, and enable users to get online from public areas, such as around campus, at a coffee shop, in a hotel, or at an airport.  For at home networking, the speed of wireless routers is around 108 Mbps and cost around $60 – 100.  Also, when purchasing a router, it's nice to have a built-in print server on the router so that any PC on your network has access to a printer.   Peripherals :   Hard Drives :  Generally, the standard for a desktop should be around 80 GB to 160 GB. However, if you do a lot of graphic, video, audio editing or want to store a large music or photo library, you might look for more like 200 GB.  For regular use, 160 GB is sufficient. Also, don’t forget to choose a high speed hard drive such as 7200 RPM or 10,000 RPM.    RAM :  Consumers should choose DDR-SDRAM because it offers more speed than SDRAM.  The most common DDR-SDRAM speed is PC2100 266MHz. If a system uses HT Technology, consumers should be sure to look for at least the PC2700 333MHZ DDR. As a starting point, consumers should look for a minimum of 256MB or 512 MB of RAM, although it is not uncommon to see systems with 1GB of RAM or more nowadays. Generally speaking, upgrading a computer’s RAM is the single most cost-effective way to enhance a system’s performance.     Optical Disks :  There are many optical disks available in the market such as CD, DVD, CD-RW, DVD-RW, and Combo drives. DVD writers are an increasingly popular optical drive option for PC users who want a much larger, removable storage medium. Whereas CD-R/RWs can max out at about 800MB, DVD+/-/R/RWs can take up to 4.7GB or more. They are ideal for huge files like digital video data and large collections of music and digital photos. Plus, as a DVD player, these drives turn your system into a self-contained entertainment system. CD-RW drives remain a popular choice as well and it is recommended that you purchase a 48x speed drive if opting for this type of optical disk drive.   Monitors : If you want to look for image quality and sharpness, you should consider an LCD (liquid crystal display) flat panel instead of a standard CRT (cathode-ray tube) monitor. In addition, LCD monitors consume less power, are easier on your eyes, and look pretty cool. However, they cost you more than regular CRT monitors.   Printers :   There are various types of printers, including inkjets, laserjets, and multi-purpose printers.  Inkjets are the least expensive and are recommended for printing images.  Laserjets are faster than ink jets and are frequently used in business settings.  Inkjets will meet the needs of a typical HPU student.  Multi-purpose printers are very convenient and save consumers on trips to Kinko’s.  They have the ability to scan, print, and fax documents, as well as scan different types of media cards (Secure Digital, Sony memory sticks, etc.) to import to your PC.  Some multi-purpose printers even scan documents into Microsoft Word, saving you the time of retyping something that you don't have a softcopy of. A consumer should evaluate his/her needs to best determine which printer suits him/her best.    Buying Tips  :   Hardware :  My PC came with a 40 GB hard drive, so when a 120 GB hard drive went on sale at CompUSA, I swapped it out and can now use the 40 GB hard drive for storage space. Therefore, if you need to cut back on costs and find a computer with a small hard drive on sale for a decent price, you can always buy a new hard drive later and save money that way. This also goes for RAM and other hardware equipment. Last year, I replaced a CD-R drive that came with my generic brand PC for a Sony CD-RW for a fairly cheap price. You can also save money by purchasing hardware from OEM (Original Equipment Manufacturer) companies, rather than from name brands. You'll basically get the same product for a better price.    Monitors :  LCD monitors are a bit pricier than CRT's, but if you shop around, there are great deals. Office Max had a 17" NEC LCD monitor on clearance, and, since I took the floor model, the manager gave me a 10% discount. After the $70 rebate I printed off of a forum, I paid only $300 for a monitor worth close to $500.    Printers :  Multi-purpose printers can be pretty pricey, but I saw a basic model at CompUSA for about $100. Otherwise, an ink jet printer will do just fine and come fairly cheap as well. Sometimes you can even get a package deal, which includes the PC, monitor, and ink jet printer together for a discounted price.    Network Cards :  Wireless cards run fairly cheap.  CompUSA advertised a card on sale after rebate for $9.99.   References
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Assemble a consumer’s guide for HPU graduate student’s who need to purchase a new desktop computer. Collaborate on the content of the guide and have the leader post the final document on the blog. The content should address both hardware and software. Assume the HPU graduate student lives in Honolulu and takes the same classes as you.   
    
    
</post>



</Blog>