<Blog>

<date>03,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The 1st day of army... beri beri scared sia. heard from all those ppl outside that army beri xiong de and sergent beri fierce and a lot of ah beng... all this is all in my expection le... wake up damn early sia then nid to report to amoy quee camp at 11am... so early also dunno so early for what... as i m approaching the camp, fear grew within me as i saw group follow by group of strangers going thru the camp gate, people of all shape n sizes sia, some fat some thin some tall some short sporting all different kinda of hairstyle beautifull embedded with different colours... beri scared that wont be able to mix well with all these strangers of different walks of life... There is an mini bus at the gate to bring us in. Thats was totally not i expected... a mini bus that is so small den no air con somemore, only got those sliding windows. The mini bus drive past an sign that shows 20TH SINGAPORE ARTILLERY BATTLION and stopped at the entrance. For once i thought that maybe army isnt really that bad as me n parents along with some others in the mindbus were greeted by soldiers of different ranks with an smiling face and warm reception. maybe ppl words cannot really believe ah... i went over to register then i was given an green card (11-b) which the officer that gave it to me told me this will be my nirc for the next 2 years le... along with a water bottle bearing the name army 21 and a bag. i was then directed by ushers in army uniform to the seating in front of the stage. Hanging boldly on the wall is the 11TH MONO INTAKE. sitting anxiously with my parents we waited for the ceremony to start, the beginning of hell... An officer walked up the stage with an smart uniform and adress us as new recruits of 11TH MONO INTAKE. along came an video which show what will we be doing as recruits. All the mud, sweat is all i should expect. After taking the oath of allegiance we were directed to some refreshment... Hmmz the cakes n drinks taste quite good so i was expecting good food in camp huhz... After refreshments all parents were invited to leave the battlion(camp) i bidded farewell to my family as it will be 2 weeks staying in camp and the reason is to let us get used to military life... stupid right. Reluctantly my parents went home while i prepared for the new start...
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After all the parents went home, the battlion is filled with teenagers like me. teenagers who are here to accept their fate... We were divided to three groups which is named after alpha, bravo and charile... we were brought up to the room and so called bunk by an army personal, i belong to charile wich is at the 4th floor... sux sia alpha 2nd floor then charile still have to walk up so long way up. 4th floor lehz... after leaving our bags in our bunk, we went down to 
    
</post>


<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Early in the morning rain no stop sia... good day to slp sia... go buy 4d le hope to win lohz cuz pocket like very empty like that lehz... haiz now pocket empty + pay cut to 350... arhz! how to survive ah??? sad sia no clerk job for me... just got my posting le... be storeman ah. sux sia have to live together with dust and stores... feeling is... (sux). the medical officer bluff me one, he say i will become clerk but in the end i become a man of store... haha storeman. So happy today, got a very good start of the day... now then i knoe my words got carry some weight one... not jus plain word but words taken in mind by others...hmmz okok i juz end here ba. nice day everyone...
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! finally the 2nd last day of couse le... after this one whole week of training how to keep myself awake during extreme boring lectures... haha i have finally mastered th skill of playing afool in class rather then sleeping... hmmz the test to determine that did we learn enough to pass the couse is rather all bout common sense la... got ppl take down notes in every lectures n people who sleep through the whole days and when the results were revealed, people who sleep the whole day have an average that is much higher then those that got pay attention in class sia... actually its all in the brain not on the lectures one... haha... like me la, sleeping in class, playing afool, teasing teachers... notorious is the word... haha juz like my sec sch life but i still pass with an result that no one will expect me to get... best ah... tml have to go back last day... stupid sia, go back give back the camp pass then go eat breakfast then go home le... stupid rite? even the breakfast also must ownself pay sia... a lot of ppl cheat in the test sia... thats how most of them pass... the sergents n bigger ranks ppl jus like come then ask u dunno rite then they give ans secretly... haha not hints lehz... its ans... but i never copy la... i anyhow guess also can get good grade sia... haha thats why they say saf tests cannot fail one... its beri hard to fail but beri easy to pass... with all the sergents help n retarded common sense... its juz like that... tml is going to b a short short day... if u wan me send u hm tml den tell me k... 24hrs avaliable... aniwae its an cold day today so keep urself warm n DONT catch a cold k... :o)
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sianz sia today go take mc from polyclinic then get one day mc so no need go course... haha my acting skill best ah talk to doc a while then he give the mc le... haha save money ah no nid go private clinic... hmmz didnt really did anything today lohz but brought durians again today haha yesterday also got buy, like got craving for durians daily sia... jia lat liaoz, confirm sick if continue eat sia... must curb le... tml early morning fotta go course again haiz the long bus journey beri beri sianz... bo bianz have to go eh u still haven ans me that *uUu* questionz lehz... aniwae take care... 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (" n also not forgetting to *uUu* (should know who huh)... thanz also for being there for me always whenever i m in trouble, stress, sad or even in confusion... u nv failed to show ur concern... thanz alot... at least i know tat i m not alone... =) ... n also i m say sorry to *uUu* for sometimes u know... make u frustrated wif me... so sorry... mayb i will learn how to let out my troubles tat is bothering me ")-quote frm ur blog  (" n also to *uUu* out there... u nv fail to show me ur concern whenever i m down... thanz also n sorry for always making u frustrated... so sorry... know u meant well... but mayb i will learn to open up my feelings...")-quote frm ur blog   that *uUu* sound like mememe lehz... haha m i right? or m i bei hiao bie???  ___________________________________________________________________________________  (" haiz.. recently dunno wat is happening to me... i really dunno... things seems to be not the same anymore... not the same... after tat time, things were different... i m really very scare... cant afford to let such thing happen again... argH... god u really have to help me thru this... i will pray hard... very hard..." )  recently i met up with god le. he know that u r praying so hard le. he said to me that all the external factors are superficial, look on the inside n u will find peace... if u are scare then tell me wat happened... i will protect u or do whatever i can one... just tell me huhz. aniway was really happy when u told mi that u told ur mum about me... althought till now i still dunno why u dun wan me send u home this kinda things but ok la, i dun wan add stress to u... juz wanna tell u that whatever happens or whatever choice u make( 2 choices i told u yesterday )i will agree to it one althought how :o( i will b... happiness is like clapping hands. it always take two to achieve... i love you... now n forever...
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmz going to watch the fireworks at esplanade at night but i dun really noe the place well so meeting 2 frds together with my bro going down... too bad sia some ppl cannot go... met up with 1 frd at hougang at bout 7 i think then continue going down to dobby ghaut meet another frd... haiz too bad i didnt realise that she (the frd that we are meeting at dobby ghuat) have an time keeping problem sia meet her 7.30 she 7.45 then come. hai we miss 5 trains... finally she came then we boarded the mrt... its was like packed sardine like that lohz. beri beri the squeezy ah. almost cant breath... haha. luckily when we reach the fireworks haven started yet or i will chop off that ger head sia. lol. everywhere was people, all size n pattern sia, some even brought grass mattress go there to find an comfortable place sit... the comercial bluff ppl one say what it will starts at 8.15 on the dot but when we reach there it was 8.05 then the first shot of fireworks were launch into the starry night le. it looks more like end at 8.15 on the dot sia... the fireworks were just fantastic. pattern that even national day dont have they also got, including star shaped fireworks, fireworks that burts into 7 colours when launch, fireworks that look like falling stars. the finale was just as fantastic... its like all the stars suddenly burst and the trail left in the sky was enchanting. it was an beri beri good firework display which i think everyone agrees as the applause was even louder then the fireworks sia... a lot of couple went and i think such beautiful scene should be shared with that someone but too bad... thought of asking u go next year one but i heard 2004 was the final year le... too bad rite. i noe. aniwae i juz end here le... 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wake up at 4 am today sia... so tired as yesterday watch tv till 1 plus 2... still got things to do sia... only 3 hours sleep... how to ta han... :o( Had to go set up water point for Tiger Trail... its is an running event in jurong camp... had to go set up the water point to provide water supply for thirsty runner. the day haven even break yet... its was still pitch dark the took the army lilitart vehical to an forest like training ground which the runner is going to run though... haiz of all the people my sergent choose me... beri beri tired lohz... there are two kinda drinks that we must set up for the runners 1st is redbull another is 7up... that jungle area so mani mosquito... wanna catch an nap also cannot sia with all the mosquito making that irriating buzzing sound when they flew past... soon the run started at jurong camp while we waited for the runners to run past our area... sun is rising le luckily not hot ah or else confirm beri pek chek one... when runners started to run past us, we started to critize all the people running thru... it was really getting beri bo liaos ah so we talk bad about all the officers n sergents from different battlion. haha we can talk bout they run like ger sia, some hair loss till beri jia lat ah den some wanna act say, take off shirt run but eventually those were the one that run till like going to die already... hmmz this 12km run is also quite a killer ah... haha sianz ah from watching people who ran beri fast to ppl behing lagging behind by walking... we critize almost every sing runner... haha bo bian too bored le arhz!!!! when we offer their either redbull or 7up, they will ask for plain water... haha got good drinks they dun wan. stupid one dunno how to enjoy siaz. when we running as a platoon in camp, only got plain water then these runners here got good drinks then dun want they dunno how to enjoy sia... then my commander of camp who was also running mixed the 2 drinks together then dranks few cups of it then he started to invited his frds to come drink, telling them to mix both together... then i realise that when redbull mix with 7up, it will forms plain water ah haha...after the run was completed, we went back camp n sleep for the rest of the day le...
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today whole day slack at home also dunno do what sia... so sian... wanna fix my remote control car but dont have the necessary thing, wanna sleep but not tired... haha basically whole day walk walk from room to room sianz ah... haiz sianz ah tonight go back again... never mind going ORD next year le... Today go back then stay till sat ah super super sianz ah... that stupid sergent la... say whole camp go thailand then we cannot even have nights off... sTuPiD aRhZ!!!! I m going to craete mani mani trouble for him till he bei ta han. humph dare to play with charile people... haha... its going to be a long week... dun wan go think of it sia... going to do painting of the blocks all these... wasting my time arhz... army sux...       ~nO oNe CaN uNdErStAnD wAt I'm GoIn tHrU..[cOnFuSeD]~... is the email mean what it says??? or m i looking too deep in??? haha only GOD knows... Added new javascript games for u to enjoy urself in case u r bored...
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      aiyo y nowadays weather so hot one... cannot ta han ah, can even sweat when playing computer... haiz all my camp ppl going thailand for oversea training le, suck sia i cant go... zhao zhi dao i dun go for the operation then i will stay as fit for combat so can go chiong with all my frds... life as an storeman is rather bored lohz... dunno y ppl think storeman good to do... thinking that we have an easy life... wat they dun see is all the paperworks n all those bo liaoz things that we mus do... hao huai nian last time as an gunner, all the chionging n suffering with my frds... started to think too much nowadays, neccessary oso think, not necessary one also think... kana contaminated by SOMEONE sia who is always in a state of confusion one... haha... i beri afaid that she do not have time fer me lehz... this ger jus dunno how to arrange time one... is an lasting relationship so hard to achieve. i will do all my best to blend into her scedule but will she do the same??? dunno... yi shen yi shi you zhe me nan ma? jus pray for the best is the onli thing that i can do now... i no nid to be shy bout my feelings here as i didnt publicise my blog at all. only u noe my blog add n its all written for u...
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SiaNZ sia have to book in camp again tonight, the long straight road in is really getting on my nerve sia. everytime must walk in so far also dunno why they build the camp till so in wards. hmmz thot its gonna be another boring night that have been wats going on always but something happened that changed my mood for the nite and basically change my onlook about life, something that gimmie new hope. Its is a ray of sunshine for me... haha u muz be think whats that hope right? haha actually its someone that i have been waiting for beri beri long le... i wan very much to be with her but after breaking her heart long ago, i thot thats the end of our fate but tonight when i ask her about this thing, instaed of changing topic as she always did, she actually told me that i MAY still stand an chance... wow i was beri beri happy lohz, like i jus won 4d like that, even more happier then that lohz, although it is only a MAY but its just the thingy that i have been waiting... finally... finally sia all this is happening to me. If all my past months of suay-ness (bad luck) was created because it was all to exchange this chance to be with her... i most willing to take all the bad luck... even if one year of bad luck i will oso take... hmmz thats all folks
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Augest le... hope to throw every sway things that happen last mth away... this mth hope be better lohz... if it continues so sway i really cannot take it le... everything u can imagine can go wrong sia also dunno what happen sia... nothing goes my way at all... TIAN ARHZ!!! plz help me ah... i beri beri stress le... cannot take it le... hope everything will be fine this month haiz...
    
</post>


</Blog>