<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm working on a series of poems about working in an office. This is a first draft, mind you, of the 4th poem in the series:  On Kindest Regards or a Business Memo  To Whom It May Concern:  I know we only speak through email, and I know that I work in the Collections Department of a company you don’t care for. I know you hate to see my name in your inbox; I know you are behind on your payments. But I wanted you to know,  before my six syllable name my title, address, email, telephone and fax numbers, extension one hundred and eighty-three, I write Kindest Regards and I mean it.   I write to you on the authority  of the temp agency that hired me at ten dollars an hour. I write to you because it is more interesting than checking my empty email account. I write to you because someone instructed me to, but I write Kindest Regards to say something.  It is the only moment of poetry I have between invoices and work orders, between copy paper and electric staplers. That signature, that ending is the only moment I write with absolute seriousness. I contact you to tell you that you are delinquent, that you owe this company. But I conclude with a hope that you see my humanity  through the filter  of a collection notice, a final notice, a notice that your account will now be handled  by an attorney. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There is this other blogger. I have a total thing for her. I wish I could tell her how her posts make me feel. ARGH>
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You see, there is this poem about asking your past lovers to forgive you for loving this time like you have never loved before... and I used to know exactly what she was saying. I would even tell girls about it, like it was something to be proud of. I would say, "I always love like I'm coming home." And they used to nod and get that misty sad look in their eye, and I'd think what a fucking mess I am, and I'd think, is that REALLY true?  But then I met her or she met me, or rather she saved me... and when I say 'saved' I mean like salvation. Like fundamentallist Christians mean it. I mean, she SAVED me.   And now I want to sit down and talk to that poet, and ask her if she thinks there is ever an excepting to the rule about always feeling like this... because I never have before. I mean, I really do love her like I have never loved anyone before. This is the exception to brillant poems, she is my otherwise, my hold on she's a comin', my last love. You know, like the kind of last love like how you always find your keys in the last place you look love. The real, honest to goodness, perfection of love.   Call me a fool, if you'd like. Call me anything you'd like, but you better not let her hear you. She may be a fem, but she's scrappy and she'll beat you up. That kind of love. The kind of love that stretches one moment of letting myself be happy into seven months like a blink of an eye. Maybe you think this is bullshit and someday soon, I'll discover the truth, but you know what? I don't give a shit if you don't understand. Because if you were my most perfect lover, you would know exactly what I am talking about.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I suppose I should have a few. I've been told I need to keep a couple lined up like my love for doc martins even in the piss-hot heat of summer, but I think I learned about secrets the hard way.  Once, not that long ago, a secret meant a lie. sometimes mine, usually someone elses.   and so, I guess I keep it all on the out and out just to prove I'm not hiding anything. There is no truth that I have not bared like a teeshirt you are embarrased to wear into a family dining restaurant.   Dyke. Poet. Fool.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>