<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My name is Marci and I am 41 years old and mother of 2. I have been in a relationship for ten years now( wow ten years- long time) I am 5'2" short and a well endowed curvy person. I love playing pool, fishing, camping, bike riding and spending time with my family. I love going for long drives in the country. My favorite things are watching wildlife in their own habitat and taking pictures of them. I enjoy cooking, crafts, sewing and playing on my computer as you can see. I like to think that I am a people person for the simple reason that I make friends easily and have many of them. I am a very opinonated person who will tell you the truth regardless if it hurts your feelings. I am the baby of a large family of 13 and growing up was quite interesting.After all of this - what else is there left to say.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My sister came up to visit a few weeks ago and usually when she comes up -its usually a big party. However I was shocked at the fact that she didn't want to immerse in these activities. She lives down south and of course I live in the north - North Bay, On to be exact. Well she wanted to go fishing and walking and all that stuff that comes with living up north. Anyway, I humoured her by taking her fishing as its one of my favorite past times. Well let me tell you- we had such a good day. We packed a picnic and with kids, dog and husbands - we ventured out. She doesn't know the first thing about fishing and putting a worm on her hook was hilarious. She was definitely a northern girl turn city. So I asked her why she didn't want to indulge in our usual events of partying and such. Well this is what she told me. "Down in the city- we have cool stores and malls, we have places like sportsworld and such but everything we do, we have to pay a high price for. You guys up here, have the lakes and camping and fishing and waterfronts and all this is free." She went on to say how we have the bush to walk through and places to pick strawberries and blueberries and we get to see to see wildlife without having to pay to go to a zoo.We have waterfalls and trails that we can just walk through without much worry. You know until she mentioned this, I never realized just how lucky we are. I guess sometimes you just get so busy in your own little life that you tend to take things for granted. Well until that day I had taken it all for granted but my thoughts have changed. I love this little place I live in and she is right, we have alot to offer. I certainly appreciate it much more now. Thanks sister for opening my eyes. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>