<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       First entry! I've been flitting around looking for new websites to blog because I just don't like blogdrive.com anymore so I decided on this one (I was bored looking).    Right what will I start off with? Oh yes, it's the 28th of July today, it's Traceys 15th birthday today. If you don't know who Tracey is, she's an EX-friend of mine. &nbsp;I sort of miss her but I don't want to be friends with someone like her ie. I don't want to be friends with a whore.  My mam has finally booked the tickets for Italy. We depart on the 7th of August, my dad follows us over on the 15th and we all come home on the 31st of August. I'm looking forward to going but at the same time I'm not. My mam is such a control freak. I want a holiday, not some nagging me constantly. If I sit a certain way, she'll tell me to stop, she constantly makes snide remarks about my weight, remarks not I'm not femimine enough. I just like lounging around in a t-shirt, jeans and runners, whats wrong with that? My holiday consists of staying in my room, reading,, listening to music, drawing and going out for meals and maybe sit out in the sun once and a while but my mother wants me going to out to the swimming pools, prance around the Italian guys (I would but I'd look ridiculous), wants me to stay out in the sun like she does, have you seen the ads with the people sunbathing it's gross. I have an obsession with McFly. How cute are those fellas? Especially Dougie. I must get their album. Okay, so here is my list I've compiled of what crap I have to bring to Italy. 1*  Make-up  I'd throw myself off the balcony or I'd rather be eaten by vicious dogs rather than forgetting my make-up. 2*  Magazines  What would I do without them? I wouldn't be able to live without knowing the going ons of Brad Pitt and Orlando Bloom! 3*  Books  Hmm, Bring all Louise Rennison books, buy her new book, steal a few from Serena and  must finish  first Lord of the Rings book without falling asleep or eating paint chips from the walls to see if my tongue changes colour. 4*  CD's  With my brilliant taste in music (saying that I'm listening to the Spice Girls) must bring all CD's. 5*  CD player  no durr! 6*  Sketch pad and pen/cils  I'm going to try being arty farty and sitting out with the balcony with a CD of dolphin noises and&nbsp;paint a landscape. Yeah right. 7*  Hair stuff  Mousse, hair brush, clips, bobbins, hot curlers, sparkly stuff, hairbands. 8*  Dublin flag  I'm going to hang this on my wall, and Maurizio has to go into my room he can marvel at my patriotic-osity. 9*  My bag collection  From my blue Marilyn Manroe bag to my sporty adidas one.. I'm bringing them  all,  which is around 13 respectively. 10*&nbsp; Wash stuff&nbsp; face wash/moisturiser/fake tan etc. 11*  Tennis racquets!  I have to practise my ughs, aghs, uhhs while I'm over there. 12*  DVDs/Videos  X-men1 and 2, never been kissed, about a boy, legally blonde, the green mile, try steal my brother Smallville DVD's. Or maybe The Office. 13*  Clothes/ Shoes  duh. 14*  Picture of my beloved Belle   Oh my god. I bring two bags over to Italy. Well I bring a suitcase for my clothes and stuff not bag and I bring my schoolbag for my crap like magazines and stuff. All over my school bag is... I love Fabio, I love FN, M 4 F. I'm going to have to steal Serenas bag from college. Rah. I like this blog :) Yayness   
      
</post>


</Blog>