<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yo pimps and hos its the world famous whit here and well tommrow is the big day the friday night lights r coming up and were strapping it up. But o yeah, shit were playing against one of the best QB's in the state. U know what though fuck it i'm going to try to break his damn leg if i get a hold of it. lol damn bastard. well i finally got to talk to rachel some today. and well she saw things the same way i did and wanted to go back to the way we were before we started going out. So i think that will kinda help too cause i think we kinda needed to get used to school a lil more. But yea its a good day when u get cha girl back, i even got a ride down to the field house in the pimp mobile. (92 cutlass sittin' on 10s) Well i gots to get some sleep but hey rachel sry i missed u on here i'll talk to u tommrow at FCA. Holla   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yo pimps and hos its the world famous whit here, live from Swofford CTS class again. Right now were supposed to be taking some gay test thing but u know, fuck it. Well i was right bout the "we need to talk" shit, she said that she just aint in the relationship mood. Well shit say something a month ago, but o well. U know i never did ask if she actually liked me or what i think i'll do that today when i get back to school. I dont mean to sound like a dick but shit if u like somebody and they like u back then, know u. Dont get me wrong i really like being friends with her but if we aint goin to go out now then i would at least like us to be like we were when we were talkin but not so serious bout it.  Like a lil more freedom and shit  not tied down. but w/e, i tried not to talk to her that much today cause i was still kinda pissed so if u read this then just give me a day or so to get over it. Well now i got to go work on some fucking piece of shit computer catch yall on the flipside.  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yo pimps and Hos its the world famous whit here coming to u live from Swofford's CTS (Computer System's Tech.) class. fun fun fun. It really aint all that bad cause we just sit around for most of the time. shit h/o we got a fire drill brb. Aight back, anyway this day has already sucked donkey balls cause today at lunch Rachel said the four words that every guy loves to hear "we need to talk". As guy u might know what i mean but personally i dont see how it could be something that bad cause shit we just started goin out and she hasnt been acting weird but i dont know. but say it was something bad then i would be bumed dude i mean ....... well u know. wel i gots to go its break time but i'll let yall know how it goes lata.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yo pimps and Hos its the world famous whit here coming to u live from Swofford's CST (Computer Systems Tech.) class. Fun Fun Fun. Nah actually we dont do much of shit in here. I've already have had a shitty ass day and at lunch i heard those 4 great words every guy loves to here "we need to talk"  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yo pimps and hos its the world famous whit and i have just steped up to the new level of coolness. Well today was the second day of school and when i was talkin to rachel i noticed she was acting kinda weird bout somethin cause she acted different. Then she was like did u read my blog from last nite, and i was like nah my computer was fuck up which it really was. Then i planed on readin it during lunch but she said nah wait til u got to swofford to read it so i did and on it she was like " i think its time for us to go out and we need to talk bout it in person". So i was oooo snap. when i saw her again i was like yea i read something on the internet today at swofford and right then she knew what i was talkin bout. And of course she said yes! cause i mean come on who can turn down this huh? yea nobody. But anyways then i saw her at meet the cardinal and she had on these tight pants omg. And she even gave a little present afterwards before she had to go cause u know i'm that good. So yea now i offcailly goin out with her, so that has diffently rised my coolness level.  Ps:   and   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>