<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    HI&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Up close and personal?  For real?  Think again...  Hi. If I've directed you here that means I like you more than just a 'net flirt', (i.e. on my friend list) and want to be totally open and honest with you. Being open (vulnerable) and totally honest (no alcohol needed) does not come easily for me at all. Consider yourself a friend... That is if the following matters don't influence what we've begun 'in light gestures' already. Btw...I don't like having many friends. The few I do have I would die or kill for. Perhaps I neglect them too often (I like staying home, hate talking on the phone), but when they let me know they need something, they got it! That is until I fall in *Love*. At which point I shall X you or invite you to our next party :)  Whew, here goes...  1) Boss = Sugardaddy. Literally. He's Pres of a sugar co-op but I'm not actually on the payroll. I'm on allowance. Altho I appreciate him, I don't like him. I much enjoy the places he brings me (museums, tours, theater) but I hate he's rude to others (very snooty. "Step aside, I'm coming thru"). I much enjoy our converse (latest news, history, opinions) but tears flood from my brain to my gut when he closes the door behind us.  2) I don't 'actually' work because I don't like to and I don't want to. Home is where my heart is. So call me domestic... I know where my kids are, everything they do. Do you?  3) I am Very Proud of My Babes :) Considering the life I've exposed them to ( I hide nothing from them) I realize the few flaws they do have... are all my fault. I must be a great Mom. They have very few flaws and those that do exist are matters they make up for with common sense. For instance, a) Tab does poorly with school grades (Ms. Too-Popular to study). But she has gotten 2 raises at her first job for being quick, hard-working and honest. She also hoards her $ and has a bigger savings than my 3 sons.  b) Other than not having a nice nest egg (they want it they get it immediately) I don't think my sons have any flaws. They all are highly intellegent, considerate, responsible, hard-working, understanding, and fair. The 2 eldest are in longterm relationships and are totally faithful. And the youngest wants the same (altho 14-21 yr old women rarely understand how to acquire such yet).  4) Drinking and smoking weed is my only comfort with having to deal with issue 1. (And issues I have with insecurities). As for the drinking, I keep it on a 'socalizing only' level. And I don't go out socializing often. Maybe 2ce a month. And as for the weed, I never buy it. (Thanks to my friends :) I oft go without because...  5) I Never ask for anything. If I am in need of help my family and friends recognize my need thru a hint or knowing what my weaknesses are. (I don't lift anything over 20#'s and I have to be dragged away from sales racks). Sometimes even they don't pick-up on the hint. And when it turns out to be something I can't handle alone... Procrastination and Bitch mode sets in. No need to fear vengfulness but pouting and/or x-communication is very probable.  Well, if you want to know anything more I'm sure you'll ask.  Oh. And if your someone who's just become disgusted with me...  I Really Don't Care. Good Bye and Good Ridence! ... I mean come-on, who wants an un-understanding, judgemental, self-centered, nimrod taking up their time?  
</post>


</Blog>