<Blog>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The debate of the summer season... is it To-may-toe? or To-mah-toe? awwwww my fluffy princess Steven and I had the cutest argument in the world.. which kept me giggling non-stop. He says To-mah-toe... but not Po-tah-toe.. awwww and he also says pass-tah instead of pasta. I love my princess so much. he's so adorable. and I'll kill anyone that says any different. I'm serious, I'll hunt you down, and rape your ass with a rifle, and as you are about to oragsm, I will pull the trigger.. At least you'll go out of this world somewhat pleasured.. I know it will be pleasurable to me to kill anyone that says anything against my fluffy princess, or me.. or US. GRRRRR. All of you douches that don't know what the fuck love feels like... its the most amazing thing in the world. so silly.. and fun. and intense. and god its amazing. it keeps you floating. I just might even change the way I say tomato... That.. is a big commitment to make.     I love you my fluffy princess.        [2008 is the best year in the world.]  
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wow.... I really hate girls that are so insecure with things that they have a phobia of being accepted by others that don't even know them. Complaining about how they hate EVERYTHING about them, and would give ANYTHING to change it.... but not for themselves... for the acceptance of others. I think that's one of the most self-centered things in the world... Walking into a room, and thinking that everyone is thinking about you. Why the fuck should I be thinking about what you look like? Your fucking clothes don't match, at least you're covering your body. *sigh* Appearance means nothing if you aren't comfortable in your skin. one of the saddest things in the world are people that just can't let go--and allow themselves to FEEL gorgeous. This phobia of strangers already formed "opinions" of you is ridiculous.... ESPECIALLY because you already make the assumption that they have this grudge towards you-by appearance, when they probably aren't even thinking about you AT ALL. Sorry... just. Wow... Insecurity can be fucking ridiculous. and I know that is very hypocrite of me to say--but shit. At least I can feel fucking good in my skin, and not give a shit what others think--I'm just worried more about what I think of myself, not others.. shite. ANYHOW.  ciao.  
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Random... Awesome Links:    urlLink The Most Amazing Photographer     urlLink Best Magazine     urlLink Animal Rights Organization     urlLink Disgusting... Government.     urlLink Yay for dreams!     urlLink Do I Need Therapy?     urlLink For Susie, Since she wants to learn about Buddha     Taking too much time to go through all of the great links that I go to... hmmmm How aaabooouuttt you figure it out for yourself. YAY!  
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This morning, I was pulled from my bed, on a basis of four hours of sleep... at 7:30 in the morning. Not awake, or in the mood for morning, I dressed without saying a word, and if one was talking to me, a simple groan, or nod would fill in what I didn't want to say.   Leaving the house, we make it to mums work, where we have to wait around for this fat arse man to unload some boxes into the storage room at her store... Taking FOREVER... and stopping to say that I look like I'm having "SOOO much fun.."  Yeah...shut it fat bastard and get to working..  I think.. but instead I shrug and quietly say "it's early."  DON'T FUCKING TALK TO ME... FUCKING RAPIST.  aaahem. anyhow. So then after we left from there, we drove to MY bank... but when I went to this womans office that I needed to speak to, she said I can't access my account without my grandmother... *sigh* mum had to go in and talk to her, and then we still had to end up calling my Grandmother Susan to come up there. Waiting 45 minutes for her, mum and I kept ourselves entertained by talking about my Steven, and about my trip. and I cashed in my coins---which turned out to be SEVENTY DOLLARS WORTH! Boo-Yah! So grandmother finally showed up, and we got it all sorted out. The man that re-did my account... then cashed the cheque that Steven's mum sent me... Seven 100 dollar bills... I was ready to pass out--its so real.. We stopped into mums bank to put that money into her account, because we are purchasing the ticket via credit card. Then we went home, to collect my dad.. drove our asses out to Norman, and went to this post office that had an office that does passports.. Sitting down in a chair... excited.. so excited I feel sick.. The lady asks me into her office, and I sit down, give her my information, and she asks why I am going. "To see my boyfriend..."  mmmm I love the way that sounds... She took my photo--wasn't great, but wasn't bad either. and Then we were hungry. so we went to Classic-50s drive in, and got some cheeseburgers and pickle-o's. Then we went to my Uncle Virgil's clinic, and I got to talk to some of the nurses that my mum grew up with, and telling them about December.. and they flipped me off.. Jealousy. Tut. and lets seeeeeeeee. I GOT HOME. and i got the bestest picture in the world from my steven... its really fucking amazing. HE'S A GOD... GOD DAMNIT HE'S SO SEXY. bbbuuuuuuuutttttt i thought i could write longer.. and now i am falling asleep... going to take a shower and sleep wake up as a curly head. YAY! goodnight steven. i love you so much...xxxx you're my life.  my dream is coming true..   
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink My Steven.  The sexiest person I have ever seen... 
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *sigh* I think I may have  urlLink symptoms of a kidney infection .... Not sure yet, but if the pain persists--then I will have to go and see my Uncle Virgil-something I am dreading... will start drinking some more water i suppose...starting now. I just got back from being at the school... Not fun. I just realised why I hate these people... going into the building, the anxiety started creeping up.... seeing people I know and who...I really don't want to know. I wish they were all new people--all strangers.. I wish I never had classes with them... But that is something I cannot change. hmph. Certain persons that would not talk to me, or acknowledge me--until they were far away from their clan of wankers. Though some of the girls, and some boys were helpful, and actually talked to me like i was their old mate that i am... hmmmm... didn't run into anyone that was a great mate of mine though.. Found my locker, remembered how to open it. opened it, and did it a few times, as to make sure that i could do it. I also had my photo taken for my I.D... but i am very nervous of the outcome of that picture---because i think i looked like shite-or at least looked like a retard sitting there, not wanting my picture taken. hmmmm the world is cruel... the school was fucking hotter than a mother. no air conditioning turned on, on this 90+ degree day... We finally did whatever we had to go, and left. and here I am... the pain in my side/back area= kidney area still here... but am trying not to complain about it, because um.. there is no need to complain. Still have no idea where my cupcake is. He said he would be on early today...its already 7:30 in the after noon there... is that very early? i think not. but thats okay. I am sure he is busy doing something, and for that... i can excuse his lateness.. *kisses for my steven* i just miss him. goodbye sweet sweet world... I may be dying of an infection in the near future... goodbye.   
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Outside my house...I tip-toed bare foot, with a zip-up hoodie wrapped around me, hiding the lack of bra of my pajamas... Waiting patiently for the  urlLink Fairy Dust of the Heavens  to come raining down on my head, falling delicately to the Earth, and sliding down its  urlLink Blanket of Night ... Though... I only caught a glimpse of two of the thousands of particles charging down on top of me... The real Art-Show is to begin at around Two or Three O'clock in the morning... I laid down on the  urlLink cold, hard concrete  outside the apartment building... and noticed how lovely it is--that things are all different upside down. I peered at the apartment stairs, from laying upside down... and noticed what a weird thing it is, that they lead down stairs.. when there really is no down stairs... hmmmm strange how one thing can work as two.           I did make  urlLink a wish  though, on the two "shooting stars" that I witnessed... but they are of those that I cannot say--or else they won't come true... Though, it would be nothing that anyone could ever possibly guess.. No.. not even you, my cupcake. I am regretting taking Tylenol PM awhile ago--because the drowsy effect is engulfing my body and mind as we speak, or as I type symbols at your face... Because I would really enjoy sitting up to witness this Dance.      (Sorry out of context-was about to refer to Google.com for some information-addiction.... when my fingers slipped from G..to D... revealing that my mind really wanted to go to  urlLink www.goodle.com  instead. Realizing that simple mistakes may lead you to tiny treasures... Though, this mistake did not help me in any way---perhaps it may help you...someday. Perhaps if you are working in the industry of Ondol).    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Still my day is full of nothing. Am waiting on my cupcake (new nickname for my poopie-steve) to get back from Dooblin. In the mean time, I've been watching  urlLink The Big Lebowski  (sorry.. still trying to work out this whole link thing... can't get it quite right yet...) Anyroad... Is a cool movie though. Weird. 'Man.'  Oh! Last night..my dream was so weird. I was in school, and I was telling everyone about my trip to Ireland and seeing steven and all... But the thing was---I was so excited to go, that I had forgotten everything that happened....I had taken pictures and such, but I hadn't gotten them back yet to know what was on them.. and I couldn't remember anything..at all. hmph. This will not happen. YAY!  
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I'm having an abnormally great day. I got an early night last night, around 11:30. It rained...pounding against my window, woke me up, but I was soon back to sleep. I woke up early this morning, at 8:30. Grandmother called me to make sure that I got ahold of the bank alright. On Friday I am going to the bank to cash in the cheque that Lesley (Stevens Mum) sent me for Seven-Hundred dollars, and then I am changing in my change-for dollars... Then we will go and turn in the papers for my passport, have my photo taken, and then purchase my plane ticket to Ireland for December 26-January 14th! (we were able to change the date, so I get to stay nearly THREE WEEKS!) I just got done playing with my hair, and I put on makeup-something I haven't done myself for the entire summer, except when mum insisted on my wearing it for her high school reunion. Tomorrow I have to go up to the school to get my photo taken for my school I.D. and tomorrow is also Cody's 23 birthday! Today Steven is in Dublin with his mate Igor (Iggy) and they are running about doing their normal geek/computer nerd routine. (which I absolutely love....) Oh yeah! Also this morning, after I woke up, I was super hungry, so I made a homemade pizza! It was excellent! Anyhow, am going to go entertain myself.  Cheers!   
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       TO DO: WELCOME THE PILL ACCEPT THE KNIFE EMBRACE THE INJECTION PHYSICAL PERFECTION INDIVIDUAL HAPPINESS
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The meaning of life is not answered in your favourite magazine, nor is it advertised on television. You will not find it in a bottle of alcohol, or in the amount of money you hold in your pocket. It doesn’t matter what style your hair was, or if your black, matched your blue. No one noticed when your purse didn’t match your outfit, or that your earrings were two complete different kinds.  That day when you had lipstick on your teeth, was only embarrassing for you. When you were walking down the sidewalk, and tripped, did you notice that no one laughed, or paid any attention to notice. You aren’t the center of attention, and people are not paying attention to those little details that you spend so long in front of the mirror working on. You go to the salon to get your bikini area waxed, even though you cringe, and its one of the worst pains… why do you go through with that? To impress him? Impress him, by taking off natural hair on your body? By the way, he’d rather see you without a bra, than in that push-up wonder bra… The ice cream you had for dessert, isn’t what caused you to gain that pound. So what is the meaning of life? It certainly can’t be found in all the material possessions you own. Do they truly make you happy? Or when you saw that little girl with the curly hair, holding onto her dads finger, make you smile more than the slinky black dress that you bought for $125… Happiness is not bought, Happiness is found. Happiness is an expression that shouldn’t be hidden by Botox. Those laugh lines- - are so sexy to him. Let loose, be wild, have fun… laugh. Eat, Drink, and be Merry. Don’t you want people to look at your life, and notice how much fun you have had, and remember all the laughs they had with you- - instead of all the things you bought them? Life isn’t perfect, and it isn’t gift-wrapped. Stop searching for happiness at .com… That one true love--- is out there. The soul mate you are searching for, stop searching, and he’ll find you. Look in the mirror, and see all the beautiful ‘flaws’ about yourself, because those are the first things that he will cherish the most. When you’re with your mates, instead of putting yourself down, boost yourself, and them up. Men are attracted to your confidence---because you look radiant, and glowing when you are. Diamonds shouldn’t be a girls best friend---who says they last forever? Silky smooth, lips as sweet as candy, tight blue jeans, skin that shows in patches, strong and smart- but you don’t know it--- good little girls, they never show it. Hair that twirls on finger tips so gently, hands that rest on jutting hips repenting, hurt that’s not supposed to show, and tears that fall when no one knows. Yes, Madonna, I know what it feels like for a girl. And we don’t all have to be material girls, even if this is the material world. No, this isn’t some feminist column---it’s about being REAL. Being a real woman… with REAL thoughts, REAL ideas, AND REAL bodies. Eating what you want, because you want it. Going off that diet, because you really hate it. Not spending 6 days a week at the gym, but instead, spending 6 days a week having FUN. If he doesn’t love you for your body the way it naturally is, then he doesn’t love YOU. If you are happy with yourself, and love yourself---so will he. Chances are, he worries about the EXACT same things about his body. C’mon baby, just vogue. Pose for the camera, wave at the crowds… flash your smile, be proud. Be true to yourself---that is the meaning of life.   
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Good morning!  Do you know who I am?  I’m insecurity.  You know those two extra pounds you hide behind… that’s me.  When you wake up in the morning, and get out of that shower, you stand in front of the mirror, naked… looking for those flaws.  You allow your stomach to relax, and poke and prod at it… sucking in, to see just how many inches- - you need to lose.  Getting a bit closer to the mirror, you look at your skin… my my… look at those pores!  Going down to your chin, you notice a hair, it just SHOULDN’T BE THERE! You reach for the tweezers, and out it comes.  Scrunching up your face, and stretching it out, you notice those nasty bags under your eyes- - is… is that a wrinkle??? NO… you get closer… that just COULDN’T be a wrinkle! You reach into your medicine cabinet, and pull out your anti-aging crème, that one that your lady at the make up counter swore that Angelina Jolie uses.  After applying the goop, you move to your forehead… perfect, a nice zit. How did you know that was going to happen… the day that you have an important meeting, you just know that that’s all they will see. You squeeze it, trying to get out as many ‘toxins’ as you possibly can, then fill it up with a ‘cleanser’ that is dermatologist recommended- - you first found it inside a fashion magazine. Stepping back, you look at your body again, turn to the side, and look at your stomach, then looking at the side of your butt, and finally, when you are satisfied that you can’t do any better, you leave the bathroom, and turn off the light.  Now that you are in your closet, searching through all the most fashionable clothes, and then noticing at the back, all of your old clothes, that are worn STRICTLY at home… you pull out that black mini skirt- - black is slimming you know… need to make sure that those two pounds are under control. Finding a nice blouse, one that cuts down low enough to see cleavage- - that way, you are sure to get attention from the male co-workers… Putting on your push-up bra, ‘gravity defying’, you slip into your clothes, and reach to the shelf in your closet, and pull out a pair of three-inch heels… so you will look taller, and it will make your calves look firm.  You look at yourself in your full-length mirror, making sure that you look smooth, skinny, and beautiful… no make-up on yet, adjusting your breasts, and checking your panty line, you go to your vanity, and begin the process of fixing your hair with the many products that you purchased at your favourite Hollywood salon.  Next, you apply a moisturizer to your face, anti-aging. You pick at that spot on your forehead again, wishing it would wait another day to come up.  Grabbing the base, you begin to pour the skin coloured paint onto a sponge, and apply it to your face, covering all of those pores, spots, discolourations, and wrinkles.  A light powder to assure that it will stay, you smile, add blush, and then are on to pampering your eyes, and your lips.  After all of this, you think you are finally ready, a few extra touches, a couple more clear coats of paint on your nails, and you are ready to leave. WAIT. You can’t yet! Almost forgot to set the VCR to record your favourite program that comes on at noon! When you think you are finally ready to go, you grab a low-calorie breakfast bar, and a diet cola… nothing like a good caffeine rush in the morning.  Your mobile rings as you are heading out the door, you answer it, as you are getting into your car… backing out of the garage, you aren’t paying attention to anything, except for the bit of celebrity gossip your friend is informing you on, about a television show last night.  So now, you are driving down the busy morning high-way, on the mobile, chatting away, and you realize you didn’t put on your favourite lip-smackers lip gloss… now applying that… you allow your knees to steer for you… luckily, you made it, even though you witnessed at least one crash on the way to the office building.   Later…  You don’t think you did well with the interview, the lady that gave it was a complete bitch, and she kept staring at your teeth. OH GOD… was there something in your teeth? Oh how embarrassing!  You call your friend back, and tell her the horrible news of how you don’t think you did your best. She comforts you, in telling you that the lady is just jealous because you look better.  You throw off the comment, but secretly admire that compliment.  Driving home, you stop into a fast food restaurant, order a cheeseburger, french fries, and a diet cola… you eat while you are driving home.  Arriving at the house, you go to the freezer and get that pint of Devil’s Brownie Double Chocolate Fudge ice cream, you slip into your sweat pants, and T-shirt, pull your hair out of its bun, and sit down at the couch, feeling around for the remote to click on the television, prop your feet up.. and indulge in the taste of sugar.  You now hate that you ate that ice cream, you were on a diet, and that just ruined it… you go to your scale, and you see that those two pounds, have some how made it to three pounds.  You can see it now- - soon, you wont be able to fit into that slinky dress, your shoes will no longer fit… no guy wants you, you are fat, you’re a slob, you have a bit of cellulite on your rear, you will be a lonely spinster hag, for the rest of your life… You are ready to commit to your diet again, but just one more bite of that ice cream and you are done!  You finally get into bed, and fall asleep to the cold glow of the television… ready to start the day over, with looking at yourself in the mirror.  Did you have a nice day?    
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Here in America, I find that the most disgusting, self-centered, self-absorbed thing that I have ever witnessed... is the ever popular mobile, or cellular phone.... Have you ever noticed how people are so important when they are on their phone? Nothing around matters, how loud they speak, whether they are driving, or walking around in a fucking store... That little voice they hear in their ear, is the world. It gives people some sort of a power, to be walking wherever they like, and talk for hours to "important" people.  *s i g h*  I have lost faith in the human race... People will never learn.  
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Welcome little child, welcome to our world. Here we have everything stocked, everything and more. Here on this planet, you have one mission in life: consume.     Buy those shiny things that you find amusing. Attractive. Beautiful.    Be beautiful, be skinny, be wanted.    Look like the glamourous model in the popular fashion magazine,    Buy those jeans-that have the well-known label.    Be cool. Be accepted.     Thinking for your self is now out of season. It’s not cool, It’s not attractive. It’s dull.    Watch the shows that we tell you to, Fear when we think it’s necessary. We have control. Get used to it. Accept it, Embrace it, Know it. Don’t fight for the rights, don’t fight for the cause. Soak up the goodies, and smile with that dollar in your pocket. Appreciate nothing-climb the latter to higher-heights. “Ugly” people are below you. You have no time, no use for them.  Blossom sweet child. Leave that innocence behind, there is no room left for that.     Creativity is dangerous.    Intelligence is fear.    Beauty is everything.    Branded…so you don’t disappear.    Welcome new child…       We’ve been so kind as to issue you a number, if you have any questions or comments, kindly place them away from your head, no one wishes to deal with them. Remember. Consumption is power.     
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Which way would you prefer?      Our highly qualified staff will connect you to machines that maintain blood flow and oxygen levels.     This prevents the brain from dying while your body is cooled to a point at which it no longer requires oxygen.   Your blood is then replaced with a liquid preservative designed specifically to support life at low temperature.   Once this process is complete, your body is immersed in silicone oil and lowered to -79°C.   We then transfer you to a liquid nitrogen-filled chamber for further cooling.     Over the next two weeks, you are lowered to a temperature of -196°C. You will then be ready for long-term storage.  You will remain frozen until science has achieved complete control over biological processes.   At that time, you will be thawed and your ailments treated.     You will have a fresh lease on life, in a new, more advanced world where aging has been abolished.  	      We’ll wrap your body in a woolen shroud without any embalming fluids.   You will be buried in a place on the forest floor that you have chosen.   Your family may want to perform a ceremony there.     You can be buried in a casket if you like, but it must be made of wood, wicker, or bamboo.     Ultimately, everything must decompose, so if you do choose to have a casket, it can’t contain any metal or other non-biodegradable material.   Once your body is laid down in the earth, the displaced dirt is filled in and the topsoil is replaced.   You can mark the grave with an inconspicuous, discreet wood carving instead of a headstone or plastic flowers.   Over time, the carving will return to the soil just like your body. You can also plant your favorite tree over the grave.  That way, your remains will provide nourishment for the growing sapling, and you will feed new life.    [face the facts].      Set me free, I beg to roam where the paths take me,     climb the hills the earth gives me,     and swim the harsh sea,     until it drags me to my death.     I want to look in the mirror and see the aged lines of laughter,     gray hairs of stress,     I want to embrace life,     nature,     beauty.     I want the world and what it has to offer.    I want to be free. 
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hold your breath as long as you can.  But keep reading....      Here’s what you’ll experience:  
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Simple perfection This is what you are to me- You may have flaws... But they are those I cannot see. You have me falling in pieces- Into your arms. You keep me comfortable, You keep me warm. The voice you use - melts me so much... I'll be a puddle in your hand - I'll drip to your touch. I fall for you so deep, I fall for you so hard-- I have to prove this to you in person-- Actions speak louder then words. Like silly putty you will be, In my body, we'll rock steadily. You know all the secrets of my mind... You keep me tempted when we're apart, You keep me awake thinking- Of our fairy-tale start. You put stupid songs in my head, You put a goofy smile on my face All i'm craving right now, Is your loving embrace. If you leave this world without me, You know I'll die too, Because every inch of me, Is all an inch of you. I'm so in love with you Steven, I can't get over it yet. If love were made of money- I'd be sleeping in debt. I'll give you all of my riches, I'll give you all of my poors. I've given you all of me. I've opened up all of my doors. Let me sink onto you Fall to the floor... Let me be the landscape For you to explore. Let me be your art. Let me live your mind. Let me live in your thoughts. Let them never subside. Keep me from harm, Kiss me when I'm scared-- Keep me expecting, So I'm always prepared. Steven I love you I love you so much... I cannot ever express these words enough. I. Love.                       Erin.  
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wow... That was so not cool. I had just written out a fairly nice sized Blog.. When this young feline, Lodon, craves my attention. Hopping up on my lap, but then onto the keyboard, where she types a few words with her paws.. or more like a few //////////////////// anyhow. so then she is resting behind the keyboard... oh but not for long! nope. She wants to leave-so that is now the process of climbing back on the keyboard....which erases EVERYTHING.... *sigh* she knows what she did, she's sitting behind me on the top of the chair reading every word of it... slapping me in the face with her tail..     Annnnyhow.   
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              I just got off the phone with Elizabeth (one of my mothers co-workers) and she wanted me to babysit her son for her... I seriously don't know how well this will work--considering that I will be working on a basis of 25 hours lack of sleep. AND not to mention that my hubby just got back.. and I am in dyer needs to talk to him... BUT I need the money-I need clothes for school. All of my pantaloons have holes in them, or are too big that they fall right off my bum. So... I really have no choice-because it is a need. And it isn't like he is this little baby, that you have to change diapers. All I have to do is keep him entertained... that is-if she decides that she wants to invest. I've no clue how much I should get paid? I was thinking like 20 bucks... But I don't know what the rate for babysitting is these days.. Twenty dollars for an entire day would make me happy no matter what.         I just brushed my teeth, and my mouth is all buzzing and tingling. Is a great fresh mint feeling. If only I had my Steven to share the feeling with... hmph. I just got a message from Iggy saying that Steven would be on soon, and that he's sorry it's taking so long... Damn right he should be sorry... grrr... he might actually miss me---like completely.. like I might be gone by the time he gets here... which would be very very sad. and I think I'd cry...       But I have faith in him that he will be here soon!!!! and that I will get to talk to him for a bit before I go--that is-IF-I go. No idear yet.      *sigh*   I love how I can make my life seem so dramatic, just by adding a simple *sigh*.                  : )    
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Right now. I have been awake for TWENTY-FOUR HOURS.... doing absolutely nothing. I miss my steven. and he doesn't fucking care----because he won't come and see me... MAKES ME SAD. damnit... but I can't stop smiling because I'm thinking about him too much... *sigh* have been in goofy 'i'm in love' smiles since we last talked on the phone.. it's crazy what he makes me do, and feel.. BUT RIGHT NOW I'M HARDCORE PISSED OFF.... [no i'm not. just kidding] JUST MISS THE BASTARD! : ( wheere oh where did my sexaay stev-en go. oh where oh where could he beeeee? perhaps he is still putting together a computer repair JUST so he can come and talk to meeee...  i miss you.. [i wrote that song JUST for you baby.]      love.  
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Insomnia: Want of sleep; inability to sleep; wakefulness; sleeplessness.     No matter how tired I am... How much I am truly CRAVING to go to sleep... laying in bed, turning over... blankets on, blankets off. pillow. no pillow. shift body to end of bed. turn all the way around. different position. Move to living room. sit in rocking chair. close eyes-rock... turn to other side. Move to couch. lay on one side. change to other. flick on television for sound. close eyes. hum. move something as a rhythm... Slink down to the floor... lay flat. turn.turn turn. sit... rocking on the floor... crying dry tears. begging for sleep. Running a hot bath at 4 in the morning. slip into the tub-head rolls to the side and one sleeps...in hot water, head resting against a bottle of shampoo... Okay, I must be relaxed now---let us go to our bed, and we will sleep... wrong.         Next night... Tylenol PM. two tablets. sleep never comes. same. EXACT thing...     Next DAY...benedryl. dozy [doze?]. Midnight rolls around. one tylenol pm... two in the morning... one more tylenol... nothing. Take a hot shower.. climb into bed only to force myself into sleeping...     Today-lazy all day, but tired. exhausted. no medicine. want sleep. go to lay down during day--for nap... sleep does not come. One in the morning--Two... crawl into bed... lay.. lights off. silence... nothing. radio.. nothing. cuddle into pillow... hmph. I'm still awake. So it's apparent that none of that worked. I decided tonight, not to fight it. see when it comes. God I want sleep so bad. I don't even understand why I can't...     Reason why my "insomnia" doesn't make any sense: I am not anxious over anything. [unless being excited about school would do that?] I'm not nervous... I'm not depressed. I haven't changed my diet in anyway. The only thing that my thoughts are on--is Steven [the usual] and December [the new usual].          hmph.     I skipped my period for July. Though I started having signs of starting---and I never did.. WHICH that just pisses me off... because that's fucking ridiculous for my body to trick me like that... first with being emotional. I'm emotional enough as it is--but SHIT. and then with the craving of chocolate-in brownie form. and then my boobs-breasts-whatever being tender. and my body being sore. lack of interest in being all raur with Steven-more of 'I need tons of hugs'... and all of that---for no period. WHAT THE HELL IS MY BODY TRYING TO DO TO ME. why can't it just stick to a fucking schedule... GRRRR.              Oh. Also, Mum and I aren't going to Mississippi any more.. due to lack of money--and I need some clothes for school, instead of sand in my bum from the beach. Mum called my Grandmother today, left her a message saying something about   "Erin needs some new knickers"   only she said   'panties'   but I have gotten used to hating that word. New knickers I do indeed need. I want super cute ones. Grandmother is normally a cheap old broad that gets them in packages of however many-at Wal-mart.... not cool...   "why don't you get some that come up higher, will tuck in your tummy and make you look slimmer"    *sigh*  in the dressing room, trying on pants...   "pull them up to your WAIST"       "grandmother... I don't wear them like that. and there isn't any point in getting them if that's the only way they fit-because I wont wear them."        "well you should! it looks cute, and makes you look slim"    ARGH! why does she have to do this to me? why the conversations about "looking thin"... I hate shopping with my grandmother. reasons... The only places she will normally shop with me, are at department stores.. Dillards is her favourite. Also. asking me what size I am--when I honestly dont know. then picking up things that she thinks SHOULD fit me, when I know that they wont--and will just make me feel worse in the end. Another, she has to sit in the dressing room with me, watching my white body come out of my clothes, trying to hide my stretch marks from her...the fucking lights in the department stores don't help. If the clothes are a bit too small, she says "  you can have your mom move the button over a bit."   instead of just getting something else that fits.. Therefore-I end up with cheap ass shit, that doesn't fit, and I don't like it to begin with---aand... the button is shamefully-moved over. *sigh*  I now think that my insomnia has moved more into my insanity... I could swear that I just looked at the clock at it was five in the morning... that was actually... AN ENTIRE HOUR-GONE. wow... I love lack of sleeeeeeep. maybe it will all catch up to me, and I can sleep for 72 hours. that would be lovely--except that would mean time away from my schteven... and he is who I crave the most out of anything, or anyone. and I am needing him so much...  Anyroad.... I guess I'll go--do something. Until the next entry.  xx  
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I just got my new school schedule... I go from 7:50 in the morning, to 2:20. which I like that a lot!  first hour:    Algebra 2       Andis      [first hour algebra. yikes! must think so early..] second:      U.S. History    Block      [good good, wanted this teacher!] third:           English            Parent    [heard this teacher was excellent, easy to sleep in.] fourth:         Psychology     Hiatt        [I ACTUALLY MADE IT INTO PSYCHOLOGY!]  fifth:            Adv. Art           Ozment   [so excited that we have a new art teacher! bechtol was ugh] sixth:          Chemistry        Hirtzel     [excited about chem-only its at the end of the day-- : ( bad idea.]    anyhow. am going to take a nap! cheers.   
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I love feeling like a girl-but I hate being girly... If that makes sense. Like... I love that after I shave my legs, how smooth they are, and I automatically feel prettier. Or fixing my hair makes me feel better. I'm not much of a fan of wearing makeup-unless it looks completely natural--so I was just in the bathroom, playing with funky makeup. Is silly really... Because I didn't do anything too out there-just did it how other girls do theirs... It was fun, but I decided that that isn't me... hmmm anyhow. makeup is silly..  xx  
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Last night sucked... Sleep would not come-even after taking THREE Tylenol PM... *s i g h* After tossing and turning all night, moving from location to location-I finally slept.     Dreaming, I was off in a land where I couldn't do anything to protect myself-first I was with my cousin [one of the pretty ones] getting a dress that I was going to wear to prom... [Erin does not go to proms--especially since her boyfriend is thousands of miles away] but she wanted to go-so she got one of her cousins ugly old dresses. Blah. Then Cayla and someone else wanted to go and break into this blokes house... he was rich, and he was one of their friends, so we decided to do it... WELL BY US BREAKING IN.. they meant me doing it.. after searching about a bit-I decided to get out, and let them in instead... As I left, I started jogging back to my "grandma's" house---which was my Ex-Aunt Cathy's house. When running, a car pulled over, and it carried a man inside, "can I ask you where you are heading?" he said.. "no. just leave please."   he got out of the car and started running behind me.. "well it's an odd direction that you are going to"  i started to get all nervous-running faster.. "i'm going to the cemetery!" i said, pointing to a cemetery that just happened to be next to my "grandmas" [i quote that--because i called her that--but i couldn't ever ever call her that in person] house. blah blah blah. He continues to run after me, and so I tell him that I have MACE with me, and asked him if he wanted to be sprayed---so that he should just leave me alone...  running got slower and slower--harder to run, like the grass was thick. He said it was okay, because he had some as well... *sigh* I didn't even have mace, all I had was a keychain and keys to get inside the house...  Finally! I get to the house, open the door and turn around, and he's standing there---somehow, on the keychain, was a small bottle of mace--and I sprayed as much as I could in his face, slammed the door... trying to lock it--but he kept trying to get in, as I was holding it shut... la la laa.. finally.. dream ends. grrrrrrrrrrr I hate dreams like that!!!!!!  Am sad.... I miss my Stevie Poopie..  : (  
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yay! Time for celebration! I finally figured out how to do this shit!   aaalright, so I suppose it is time for a real entry? no?  Last night, I talked to my Poopie-Steve for THREE hours! We talked about everything! Even about our hypothetical kids---which are to come in the future. I'm so in love with him...  Right now, my Steve-O left me.. He is gone to Cork, Ireland, and he won't be back until Sunday---So...I don't get to talk to him until then, OR Monday... : (  sad... I don't know what I am to do without him that long... It isn't fair!  So today, I have done nothing. After a sleepless night, I finally got up at 12, I brushed the chompers, and I thought a lot about Steven, and about December.. and about our conversation last night.   [very giddy right now about all of that]  and lets see.. I called my dad-he was at my mum's work, and asked him if he would bring me home some Chinese Takeout... and HE DID. of course. AND IT WAS FUCKING EXCELLENT! I love. Which, I think I'm about to go and have some more of it, because it sounds super-urb! I just got out of the bath tub... Shaving my legs. London had to sit in there with me though-she won't leave me alone. So she was sitting on the side of the tub, her wild tail going crazy, and as I'm lathering my leg with soap, she puts her paw on my knee--stopping my path of shaving. As a patch of soap is gone, wiped away by the razor, her little nose pressed against my newly smooth skin, and began to lick away.. After a while of her curiosity about what I was doing, she got down, and curled up in my soon-to-be-used towel, and began giving herself a bath...with her tongue.  hmph. Right now, she's curled in my bed, letting the rays of the sun put her to sleep. Cats...are weird creatures. OH AND STEVEN! that damn spider..yeah I didn't kill it last night... AND IT WAS A FUCKING JUMPING SPIDER! Because I found it again today... and tried to kill it numerous times.. but it kept jumping.. FINALLY I SMASHED THE BITCH! yaaaay!  Anyhow, Iggy is chatting away to me, shaaooo... Imma gonna go chat him up!  Love!  
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wow... Blogger is so confusing the shit out of me. Em... Okay I'm new at this! Virgin! *s i g h* Let us see...I made an entry-my first, last night... But...I don't know how to get to it? I also changed my template? but whateva. This is fucking strange... We shall see what happens. if not, Erin will go back to a Blurty. hmph. So I'm going to publish this shite, just to experiment. Don't mind me...  xxx  
    
</post>

<date>29,lipiec,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am not in pleasant moods currently.  I have been trying to change my profile for my Blogger, but, it isn't showing what my books are that I enjoy. It shows everything else, EXCEPT that---and that's all I really want shown. I even took away my Interests, and my Music. But no... No Erin.  My favourite books, smell like paper. I love the smell of words, I could go to the book store and sit for hours smelling the books. I'm addicted. Nerd?  yes.  Tonight, Steven called me. He did! We got to talk on the phone for roughly THREE HOURS! It was so great! That Irish accent of his---melts me. Takes away anything bad in my day, and makes it perfect. I even forgot that I was annoyed with Blogger just now. *s i g h*   Love is amazing...   I'm in a dreamy state right now...I can't really focus on this, [my first], entry. Replaying over and over the conversation that I had just two hours ago... life is sweet.    Goodnight world. I am so in love.  
    
</post>


</Blog>