<Blog>


<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is it all about? 
     

    
</post>


<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DATELINE 17th AUGUST  ALBION ROVERS DATE SET The date and venue has been set for the Bell's Cup tie with Albion Rovers and it will take place on Tuesday 31st August at Hamilton's New Douglas Park with a 7.30pm kick off.  The prices have been set at £12 adults and £6 concession and it will be cash at the turnstiles.  To clear up any confusion, Partick Thistle do not have, and never have had, any objections to the match being played at Hamilton and are more than happy to fulfill the fixture at Douglas Park.  When asked the question by Albion Rovers we intimated that, given the choice, we would rather play on grass but were happy to abide by their decision.  STENNY STADIUM DETAILS The Stand only for this match will be all-ticket for Thistle fans.  The tickets will go on sale from Firhill on Thursday morning at 9.00am at the following prices: Adults - £12 and Juveniles/OAP's - £6.  The terracing is also open for this match with prices of £10 adults and £5 Juveniles/OAP's - no tickets are required, however, for this area.  It will be pay at the turnstiles on the night.  HAMILTON STADIUM NEWS For the forthcoming game on Saturday against Hamilton Accies, Jags fans have been allocated the Spice of Life Stand (behind goal) which seats 2,100.  Supporters should enter by turnstiles 10,11 or 12, and should have the correct money if possible.  Supporters are asked to use every seat.  Any supporter unable to gain entry to the Spice of Life Stand will be accomodated in the wing of the Main Stand (Sainsbury's End).  The prices are £12 adults and £6 under 16/OAP.  RESERVES SET FOR ACTION The first reserve game of the new season will be played at Firhill on Wednesday 25th August against Falkirk.  The kick off time is 2.00pm.  FIRST WIN ACHIEVED In another very entertaining game, Thistle came out on top against Airdrie United by the odd goal in five.  Juan Ramon, Leigh Hinds and Jamie Mitchell all netted to send most of the 4011 fans happy.  The team was:  Arthur, B Gibson, Milne (Panther), Murray, Wilkinson, Fulton (Howie), Mitchell, Fleming, Ramon, Hinds, Anis.  Unused Subs: Pinkowski, A Ross, A Gibson. Speaking after the game Derek Whyte expressed his pleasure: "It was good to get the win and take some of the pressure off.  Getting that first win was important and I thought we thoroughly deserved it.  We scored some great goals, the first from Juan was something special and I think a candidate for the goal of the season already.  I don't think that we had any failures in the team either.  Defensively we were disappointed to lose the goal in the manner in which we did.  Andy Wilkinson did most things right but Owen Coyle made life very difficult for him and I am sure he will have learnt quite a bit.  The partnership between Hinds and Ramon looks very promising and overall it was another excellent game and great value for money. A special word also for Kenny Arthur, his game was excellent today with a couple of excellent blocks and well in control of his box and his kicking, that was very pleasing, as was Kenny Milne's return which seemed to give us greater balance."  CULT HEROES RESULT The voting has now closed for the Football Focus Cult Heroes.  There were many, many entries and the top three that go forward for National voting are Chic Charnley, Denis McQuade and Alan Rough.  There were 39 players voted for in total ranging from players from the 1950's right up until the modern day and it is a big thanks to all who voted.  The winner of the autographed ball is Brian Peters and we will be in contact with him shortly.  GERRY SET FOR THE KNIFE Co Manager Gerry Britton will be missing from action for the next two weeks as he will be going under the knife to cure a problem on his left knee.  It is mainly a tidy up that is required and it is something that has been troubling him since the end of last season and it was hoped that it would clear up but it is now requiring a minor op.    ROSS COUNTY GAME Confirmation that the scheduled Boxing Day game with Ross County will now be played on Monday 27th December with a 2.00pm kick off.  FIXTURES August: 21 v Hamilton 24 v Stenhousemuir (CIS) 28 v Ross County 31 v Albion Rovers (Bells Cup) September: 4 v FALKIRK 11 v St Mirren 18 v QUEEN OF SOUTH 25 v St Johnstne October: 2 v RAITH ROVERS 16 v Airdrie United 23 v CLYDE 30 v ROSS COUNTY November: 6 v Falkirk 13 v ST MIRREN 20 v Queen of the South 27 v Raith Rovers December: 4 v ST JOHNSTONE 11 v Clyde 18 v HAMILTON 27 v Ross County 29 v FALKIRK January 1 v St Mirren 15 v QUEEN OF THE SOUTH 22 v St Johnstone 29 v RAITH ROVERS February: 12 v AIRDRIE UNITED 19 v Hamilton March: 5 v Falkirk 12 v ROSS COUNTY 19 v ST MIRREN April: 2 v Queen of the South 9 v Raith Rovers 16 v ST JOHNSTONE 23 v CLYDE 30 v Airdrie United May: 7 v HAMILTON  SEASON TICKET NEWS With the club now back in Division One next season, a revamp of the season ticket prices has taken place.  As from today the new prices are as follows: ADULT - £225 CONCESSION - £115 UNDER 12 - £60 The matchday admission prices will be £13 for adults and £7 concession. Any supporter who has purchased an adult season ticket so far at the SPL price, the club would like to offer a new home or away top for the difference, a saving of £3.  A voucher for the Club Shop to the value of £20 or £10 will be available for those who have purchased concession or Under 12 tickets.    
    
</post>


</Blog>