<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; With an extensive&nbsp;background in Broadcast&nbsp;Journalism as a Television&nbsp;Assignment Reporter,&nbsp;a Television Morning Show Host, a&nbsp;Movie Critic, a Television Weather Forecaster, and&nbsp;as a Radio On-Air Personality, I have&nbsp;the rare&nbsp;ability to report&nbsp;The News, comment&nbsp;about anything of interest and conduct Informative Interviews, Rate the latest Film Offerings from Hollywood, explain Weather Events and even critique the latest Music in The Top 40. As a Print Journalist, I have acted as an Editor, a Staff Writer, and a Magazine Columnist, and I authored and illustrated&nbsp;a Children's Book entitled "The Frightening Lightning" under the pen name of "David Cooper," (a play on my real surname,&nbsp;Cubero,)&nbsp;published by Candlestick Press,&nbsp; copyright 1984, &nbsp;therefore I am more than capable of&nbsp;bringing to you written&nbsp;reports that may or may not directly effect you, but will nonetheless make for a VERY interesting read.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; My experience&nbsp;isn't simply limited to reporting News via the various mediums listed above, I have also&nbsp; made &nbsp;The News Headlines&nbsp;and been a part of News Events and History&nbsp;as a&nbsp;local Politician, when I&nbsp;ran an&nbsp;unsuccessful campaign&nbsp;to unseat&nbsp;a long-time&nbsp;School Board Member in 1986. Although I took 39% of the overall&nbsp;votes in the general election and wound up in a run-off against the incumbent, I was ultimately&nbsp;defeated and vowed never to dabble in politics again.&nbsp;I&nbsp;have also been a U.S. Soldier, seeing battlefield action in both The Grenada Invasion and&nbsp;The&nbsp;U.S. Invasion of Panama. I am presently&nbsp;a Part-Time Police Officer and I once worked&nbsp;a Part-Time&nbsp;Los Angeles County Paramedic.&nbsp;Having these particular&nbsp;experiences, I&nbsp;have insiders insights into many areas of Public Interest, from U.S. Homeland Security to War to Crime&nbsp;and Punishment to Emergency Medical Care and Treatment to Politics.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; From the age of 10 months until my early 20's I was a working Film and Television Actor in Latin America and in Hollywood. In childhood I reached a certain level of stardom in Mexico and Puerto Rico. In Hollywood and New York I was at best a character actor.&nbsp;However, by the time I reached my early&nbsp;teens&nbsp;my acting opportunities began to fade into the sunset-just like the ending of a bad B-Western Movie. As time marched on, my acting roles&nbsp;became&nbsp;so occasional that I just gave it up altogether, what with&nbsp;ALL my other pokers in various fires. Nevertheless, I have this insider's experience as an actor&nbsp;and I&nbsp;even&nbsp;maintain Hollywood&nbsp;contacts that I can call upon to provide the latest information from&nbsp;The Hollywood Scene. Just a side note, in recent months I have landed a couple of film roles, small though they are, I may be making a bit of a come-back. One can always hope.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I am always asked how that&nbsp;I have managed to squeeze all of this experience, knowledge and activities into my 42 years of living on this&nbsp;Planet. It's quite simple&nbsp;really,&nbsp;I&nbsp;gave up sleeping long ago. Well, I sleep sometimes, but this propensity to "over-achieve" comes from the&nbsp;teachings of my beloved late&nbsp;Puerto Rican Jewish Parents who taught me that&nbsp;this world is a huge place&nbsp;and full of opportunities for adventure, while life is too&nbsp;short. I learned that if I wanted to delve into the exciting&nbsp;things that are out there for all of us to explore, I would have to work hard and sacrifice such luxuries as sleep and "me-time."&nbsp;Armed with this&nbsp;recipe for exhaustion,&nbsp;I have made it my goal to grow old without ever having thoughts of the things of life that I might&nbsp; wish  that I had done.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;My hobbies include Flying Airplanes as a Private Pilot, Scuba Diving, Amateur Astronomy, Internet Surfing, and Amateur "Ham" Radio Operations. These also give me the abilities to report to you the latest from the Worlds of Aviation, Aeronautics,&nbsp;Astronomy, Aquanautics, Internet Activities and The Various Aspects of amateur Radio. This promises to make this BLOG one with something of interest&nbsp;for&nbsp; all  readers.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>