<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Album:OPIATE  song :Sweat  I'm sweating, and breathing and staring and thinking and sinking deeper. It's almost like I'm swimming. The sun is burning hot again on the hunter and the fisherman, and he's trying to remember when, but it makes him dizzy. Seems like I've been here before. Seems so familiar. Seems like I'm slipping into a dream within a dream. Must be the way you whisper. The sun is setting cool again. I'm the thinker and the fisherman and I'm trying to remember when but it makes me dizzy. And I'm sweating, and breathing, and staring and thinking and sinking deeper and it's almost like I'm swimming. Seems like I've been here before. Seems so familiar. Seems like I'm slipping into a dream within a dream. It's the way you whisper. It drags me under and takes me home  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK OK OK. I dmit I was knockin the bloggers when i first herd about em. I was like "great more computer junk to block out" but i guess i can deal with it,ill just use my evil powers for good,maybe. tee-hee.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know I've been blessed enough to walk this earth for 24 years,well 22 I had to sit up and crawl first. Anyway I have only been in about two serious relationships,not including the one im in now. I've been taking a lot of heat lately about my age and things like that. Everyone calls me a little baby(I hate that)!  Why can't Our friends and family be happy for us when we find someone to care for,share life with and that will be there for us through thick and thin?  I noticed that people can't stand to see you happy no matter what you do! My girlfriend and I have been together for a wile now,we started out as friends and it wen't from there.   We keep it quiet though only a few people know what's what or should I say,only a few people Think they know. everybody is trying to bring me down lately but no one has the NUTS to say anything to my face! all i get is a bunch of dirty looks and I hear a lot of negative comments. what's next people,are you going to try to burn me at the steak? oh I know better yet just tie me to a pole and stone me! will that make you feel better, hhhhmmmmmm!? Words don't hurt me,so keep talking ok I welcome your camments. You all are smarter than me so why can't we discuss how you feel about me face to face? Oh I forgot I'm just a (BABY).
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      08/02/04   Yes my fellow readers and writers tis I again. yesterday my hours got cut right after I came back from an hour lunch.(second job). I have never worked for a company that lets low-class,wanna-be important Muthaf**kas run things! this young found out that she cound not intimdate me so she uses what little power she has to try and piss me off! I guess my fellow co-workers see me as a youngster and think they can do or say anything to me and get awaw with it. FFUUUUUUCCKK that!!!!!!!! O-k-k-k! change is coming,now is my time. I'm not taking anymore sh*t from anyone. I get up at 4:30 am mon-sat and walk to my first job. past all kinds of pimps,ladies of the night,drug dealers and maybe murderers and robbers. I'm not afraid of them,i'm not afraid of some snot-nose,low class wanna-be manager. my advice to anyone going through this or any similar situation. STAND UP FOR YOURSELF. If you act like a PU**Y then people will tru to F**K you!
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday, July 20, 2004 boy toys  as different as my friends and i are, we all have a few things in common. We are all in our 30's and have all had flings with boys in their early, e-a-r-l-y, 20's.     they are cute and fun and we use them and dump them! we're such bitches! why do we do it!     going in we know we don't want a relationship!     Here's the truth!     They think we're smart and sexy!  they know we've done every position at least twice and just the thought of that sends them over the edge!  poor, innocent bastards! we know they fall in love easily and still we continue! we talk about books and present ourselves as their intellectual superiors! We tell them about past relationships playing on their youthful jealousy and feelings of inadequacy. this leads them to always perform their best.  they begin to idolize us! They say, " i love you" 100 times a day. we love the feeling of being worshiped and against all that we know is right, we tell them we love them too!!!  one day we're allowing them to bask in our glory and they do something "young."  probably something we thought was cute AT FIRST! that's when  we begin to lose interest.  like february 1st and the christmas puppy... the shit starts getting old.  of course you get over it and they act psycho and all we can do is blame ourselves.  but it was fun for a minute!      so basically we use them to stroke our abused egos then get bored and break their fragile hearts! i guess someone has to break them in. might as well be me & my friends!    oooh look!  a cute boy!    
    
</post>


</Blog>