<Blog>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I guess I missed the other one too much ^_^ I changed it back, but If u wanted to see what it looked like go to www.Xanga.com/xXOrangeJuicyXx
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Whoa, I made my blogger look exactly like my xanga! I wonder If I'll miss the other one... nope! hahaha! o well, bye ^_^ 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Yeah, my girlfriend cheers me on when I'm too shy to sing and she doesn't get all worked up over every little thing. She laughs at my dumb jokes when no one does. She brings me Manga I've never heard of just because, yeah, just because. And my girlfriend watches Anime with me. She's so shy. Intimidated. I know that she needs me, but not half as much as I know, I need her. I know there'll never be another guy that she'd prefer. and when I feel like giving up, like my world has fallen down, I sign onto AIM. She's still up watching adult swim and I can hear her pretty voice. She always gives me the right advice and I know that everything, know that everything, know that everything, everything's gunna be fine.&nbsp;I know that everything, know that everything, know that everything, everything's gunna be fine. And my girlfriend walks with me when it's too dark to see and it doesn't seem to matter that I'm not all muscley. She laughs at my dumb jokes when no one does. She plays tennis and guitar oh yeah, she's my dove, yeah, she's my dove. And when I feel like giving up like my world has fallen down I sign onto AIM, She's still up watching adult swim and I can hear her pretty voice, she always gives me the right advice and I know that everything, know that everything, know that everything, everything's gunna be fine. I know that everything, know that everything, know that everything, everything's gunna be fine!  Ok, I know it's a total rip off of "Josie" but this is what I really want in a gilrfriend although it isn't that important that she plays the guitar ^_^;;  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Yo! I'm AJ. My life revolves around anime and manga aswell as almost all things related to Japan, especially earlier Japan. I love music and play Sax and Bass Guitar. My favorite anime changes rapidly, but anime I enjoy usually air on Adult Swim and the International Channel. A great deal of my friends also enjoy anime, but not as much as I do. I usually judge a new anime by the artwork, then the story line because I know if the artwork sucks, then even if I like the story, I will get sick of it. My Bass skills shock my family and friends mostly because I spend at least 4 hours a day practicing. Blink 182 is my favorite band, but I also like Linkin Park, Sum 41, Simple Plan, Hoobastank, and some J-pop like The Pillows, Every Little Thing, and others. I spend more time on my Xanga site at  urlLink www.Xanga.com/xXOrangeJuicyXx  but I thought It would be fun to have a blogger thingy too. My favorite song to listen to and to play is Adam's Song and I am currently seeking out a band to play to drum, guitar, and keyboard part. As of yestarday I was working on a song called "Hinata." I got the bass down, but I'm still working on the lyrics. O well... I guess I'll see you around.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>