<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        it's me.&nbsp; i am at work, bored.&nbsp; rather be bored than be too busy here.&nbsp; too busy means too stressful.&nbsp;        &nbsp;    started atkins on monday.&nbsp; was doing good until last night, had pancakes....oops.&nbsp; starting over today.        &nbsp;    i haven't been to church in what seems like forever.&nbsp; i feel bad about it.&nbsp; i can tell when i haven't gone or read my bible in a while, my attitude reflects it.&nbsp; i need to go this sunday.&nbsp; i have been working sunday mornings (did i mention i work in airline operations - 24/7 operation) so i get lazy when i get home and don't go on sunday nights.&nbsp; i am excited though cuz my church is starting a new service on saturday nights.&nbsp; it's suppose to be "cooler" more geared towards the younger crowd. funny cuz my church is pretty edgy anyway, so getting edgier will be intrigueing....        &nbsp;    ok, so why do people just naturally feel that they are superior to others.&nbsp; ESPECIALLY when they are clearly not.&nbsp; i work with this guy who just talks down to everyone around him, especially women.&nbsp; seriously i think he thinks we are all trailor trash with an i.q . of 10.&nbsp; we are all management level here so with a few exceptions (and funny...those exceptions are boys) we are all pretty intelligent and most of us have college degrees......i have to work with him all week.&nbsp; so get to put up with his superiority complex.&nbsp;maybe he is trying to compensate for another area of his life that he is lacking in.....just sayin...............wow!&nbsp; i just heard him talk down to his boss....now he's really daring.....        &nbsp;    so, going to eat my protein breakfast.&nbsp; I want to lose 29 pounds before 10/26.&nbsp; reason is a secret....will reveal that later...........        &nbsp;    oh, this democratic convention itself is not getting on my nerves. as a matter of fact it's helping in my decision making for this upcoming election.&nbsp; i'm registerd democrat but have been pretty much independant for that last decade or so.&nbsp;&nbsp;       &nbsp;    I am a confused girl in search (again) for what I really believe in.&nbsp; I know I believe in absolute morals, I believe in feeding the hungry, protecting children, in education......But I don't believe in making the rich richer, feeding the homeless' drug habits....so, where is that middle line?????&nbsp; I used to be so sure of what I believed in.&nbsp; Was a member of several organizations, an active member.....But now I question those things....I am older, I am a parent.&nbsp; things change and so do my thoughts......   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>