<Blog>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So reasons to be cheerful coming right up but first a little moan. I’m pissed off at  Reckless ; I rang him yesterday morning & told him of my ordeal &amp; got no reaction whatsoever. Even  Temper Tantrum  expressed concern & sympathy for me, but no, not  Reckless . I cant but think “ Hey you’re my friend, part of the criteria for that role is caring about me &amp; occasionally expressing that.” Right, bring on the happy stuff! I had a nice kip today at  Funny Dance ’s where he &  They Used To Be Even Bigger  (his wife) looked after me, bless ‘em. Then I went to see  The Boy  &amp; we spent a lovely couple of hours together. We went sledging, albeit for only 10 minutes, but it was a lovely father-son moment that is making me smile as I write. He got me the best of REM cd for my birthday, which is cool. Now it’s all about looking forward, in an hour or so I will be paying for my most extravagant e-bay purchase, a multi-track tape recorder (portastudio, if you like). I am giddy with excitement about its arrival; I can make some music, get some of my rather excellent (if I do say so myself) songs down on tape. Can’t wait! Then tonight  Buddy With Boobs  & I are going to London to see The White Stripes. The last time I saw them it was an almost religious experience, which prompted me to write “Jack White”: a song that may get recorded soon! Yay! Then on Saturday night my friends &amp; I are going out on the razz! I aim to get drunk & have a ball. I’m considering constructing an “It’s my birthday- giz a snog!!” badge. I’d fucking love a snog! On top of all this I’m excited by the prospect of  Reckless  &amp;  Dream Girl ’s prezzie for me. They always get the best presents. My drums at Xmas being a fine example. So lots to be optimistic about & hopefully no more dreary moaning. Having said that, it’s chuffing freezing &amp; I demand that it stops. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Other than suffering some genuine tragedy I cannot imagine having a worse birthday. The only prezzie I received (for now) was some socks from  Buddy With Boobs  (bless her), though that’s not what made it bad. There was a bit of a blizzard at about 3.30ish, it was very heavy snow that settled quickly but it had stopped within an hour. So at just after 4.30 I got in the car & headed off to Crapsville to spend some quality birthday time with  The Boy  prior to starting work at 8pm. So I got in the car at 4.30 &amp; didn’t get to Crapsville until 20 past midnight! Nearly 8 fucking hours to do a trip that usually takes 25 minutes. 8 hours of stop-start-stop again traffic. The icing on the cake of all this? No fags! NO FUCKING FAGS!! Then when I finally had Crapsville in sight about a mile away…I ran out of petrol. Ace. So I never got to see  The Boy , which has really upset me (& him), I’ve lost 4 hours overtime which I’d already put in &amp; now I’ve got 5 hours work to do when I feel like I’ve already done a day’s work. Throughout this ordeal  Funny Dance  has been an absolute diamond (again!), he phoned me early on into my journey to warn me how bad the roads were. It took him 3 hours to get home. After he got in he phoned me about every half hour to make sure I was ok. Then when I finally arrived he’d made me up some sandwiches, got me some fags &amp; gave me some change for coffees. He also notified work for me, as I had no credit. I shall make a big effort to show him how much I appreciate all his help. Maybe a really lavish birthday present for  Funny Dance  this year. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I decided some hours ago that is quite simply unacceptable to be a morose motherfucker on one’s birthday. So I laugh in the face of depression &amp; do a jolly little jig on the twitching corpse of doom. Happy birthday to me! 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it’s been a while since I wrote. Nothing of any great significance since my last entry – shocker! I texted  Too Keen  last Thursday night & told her as nicely as I could that I couldn’t go on with it. I don’t know how she took it ‘cause she never replied. So I turned down a guaranteed shag from a young horny woman. I think I did the right thing, makes me a better man apparently. Better than what? I don’t know. Unfortunately today I’ve been caught in the vice like grip of doom. I feel so low, so lonely, so unloved, so unwanted &amp; worse of all; so unwelcome at home. I’m not even sure I feel liked at home anymore. They try but I have this overwhelming sense that my strongest, most needed, friendships are very slowly being diluted. In half an hour it’s officially my 34th birthday. 34 years & the only thing I have to show for it is my beautiful boy (my reason for still being here) &amp; an impressive music collection. No home, No real career, no outlet for my singing & songwriting. Like I said on page 1 – under-achieving, potential wasting lazy arsed waste of flesh &amp; bone. Still, things can only get better, right? 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not a good day. I have spent the last 2 hours feeling really low & on the edge of tears. I don’t really know why. This morning I had quite a good chat with  Dream Girl  about  Too Keen . As previously mentioned I have been uncomfortable about this whole thing so I asked  Dream Girl  for her opinion because I always value really highly, even when I don’t agree with her. It was a good chat &amp; it gave me lots of food for thought. I desperately want to be in someone’s arms, to feel wanted. To enjoy kissing & yes: to have some sex, but at what price? What kind of man will it make me if I drive for 3 hours to Somerset just to shag a young girl who I’ve never even seen &amp; who’s never seen me. What kind of girl is willing to offer sex to an older man (How much do I hate that description?!) under the same conditions? Once I’d come what other fulfilment could I expect? I had much the same conversation with  Reckless  after a paltry 5 hours sleep. He pretty much echoed  Dream Girl ’s sentiments, but it was nice that he actually talked to me about it.  Reckless  used to be the one I’d always talk to about my problems but these days he rarely seems to take an interest, “Never mind” being his stock reply to most of my woes. So it was nice to see that he can still show me he cares sometimes.   In my naivety I thought that when I left  Temper Tantrum  that my life would blossom out of the drudgery that I had let it become. That it would be an adventure. The first 6 to 9 months were but for almost a year now nothing seems to go my way. This is not how it was supposed to be, somehow I’ve managed to trade in a life where someone’s love stifled me & made me unhappy for a life where all I crave is to be loved or at least to be wanted. I’m sure  Temper Tantrum  would relish the irony of it all with gleeful joy. I remain perplexed &amp; depressed. I’m old enough to know who I am & I like to think my qualities outweigh my failings. Surely financial ineptitude, a low temptation threshold &amp; extreme laziness pale away to nothing next to being genuine, funny, warm, clever, talented, giving & having a heart full of love just waiting to be lavished on someone. Yet here I am, sitting in the boiler room at work 2 hours before I’m due to start because I have nowhere else to go &amp; no one to be with other than this little red book which is (plummeting to new uncharted depths of sadness now!) fast becoming my new best friend. How did it come to this? I have now moved into the much more luxurious surroundings of reception complete with comfy chair & hot chocolate. I’ve actually been really quite naughty, I left  The Boy ’s house at 19.30 &amp; had nowhere to go so I came to work. I clocked in just before 8 & have been successfully hiding ever since. I shall go &amp; pick up  Buddy With Boobs  in a few minutes then come back &amp; no one will be any wiser. I will have “earned” about £18 for this time period. Tut tut. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Back in the boiler room again, finding a little solitude to write. Had a lovely day with  The Boy  earlier. He’s just gained a healthy interest in star wars; so today we watched “A new hope” together. He loved it. Then I gave him a bath & read him a bedtime story. Dead nice. Since I left  Temper Tantrum  I have been fiercely determined to not let my relationship with  The Boy  be affected too much. And it really hasn’t been. It’s been a little harder since he started school but I see lots of him &amp; I’m sure (through gritted teeth) that  Temper Tantrum  would have to admit that I’ve been the model example of an estranged dad. A rare case of me succeeding in something. My e-bay addiction has shown no signs of abating. I’ve bid for a further 5 or 6 items in the last hour or so. Still, I’m banging in the overtime so it’s not like I can’t afford it. Spoke to  Too Keen  earlier & gave her the talk. How I’m not looking for a girlfriend or a relationship, just a bit of fun. She was cool about it &amp; I feel no guilt even though I probably wouldn’t mind a girlfriend, just not one who’s 19 & lives in chuffing Somerset. Think I’m gonna go on Friday, though I’m quite nervous about it for a few reasons. I’m going on my own to a strange town where I’ll be meeting people I don’t know then I’ll (hopefully) be having sex with someone who I haven’t yet seen! It’ll all be very exciting, I’m sure. If all goes to plan she will be my 15th sexual partner (assuming that penetration is the criteria). I don’t know if it’s because I’m a sad twat or a natural listmaker or even a combo of the two but I can name all of them quite easily. In chronological order obviously! I’d really like to share the list with you but I dare not for fear of recrimination! Out of the 14 there is only one that I wish had never happened. Blackpool, say no more.        >>>>  I think that this shows that although I haven’t been getting much lately, when I have it’s been quality! Better stop now; I know what I’m like. A coloured bar chart & individual breakdowns of techniques, body parts &amp; position preferences is on the cards unless I stop now! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After reading back over last night’s drunken ramblings, I must address  Reckless .  Reckless  is my best friend & I love him dearly. Some of what I wrote last night may have belied that fact, but although true at the time, it was simply the sound of envy being voiced. Odd thing, drunkenness. Experience has taught me that people invariably say &amp; do what they really truly feel when pissed, yet use drunkenness as a disclaimer the next day. I’m not going to do that. What I wrote last night was a true reflection of how I felt last night. What actually pissed me off is that I was really enjoying the 3 of us having a laugh. Then all of a sudden it stopped & they buggered off. It’s hard to have any kind of drunken fun on your own. So that triggered the venting of my spleen. Right now I’m sitting in Zoobie Island. One of those huge indoor play areas with ballpits &amp; slides & tunnels &amp; stuff.  The Boy  is off doing his bit to contribute to the colossal noise of children enjoying themselves. Looking around the seating area where I drink my not-very-nice-at-all coffee, there are families mostly. Cheerfully chatting & proudly watching their offspring having fun. Also there are a couple of cliques of young mums all uniformed in bottle blonde &amp; miniskirts. They’re not unattractive but they are so stylised that the plainer, more natural looking women stand out more. Then there are the 3 or 4 men like me, sitting alone reading papers & drinking tea. It’s pure conjecture but I imagine they’re all estranged dads like me.The reasonably pretty lady in the red about 10 feet away has just unwittingly given me a sensational look down her top. Nice view it was &amp; it’s got me wondering if women are aware of exactly how much scrutiny their bodies are constantly under. Men (not just me) in general spend an enormous amount of time looking at breasts & bums. I would estimate that the penis controls about 30% of all eye movement &amp; there’s nothing the brain can do about it. If it could, then it would stop men from crashing their cars by making them watch the road instead of the scantily clad hotty on the pavement. It would also prevent the horror of getting caught looking up skirts &amp; down tops. On behalf of men everywhere I apologise to the fairer sex but if you had a dick thinking for you, you’d understand!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I fucking hate  Dream Girl . I fucking love  Dream Girl . She would deny it until she’s fucking blue in the fucking gorgeous flawless face but she’s the most manipulative bitch that ever walked the earth. Yet she does in with such panache you cant help but like her for it. Tonight because I’ve been getting horny texts from  Too Keen  she’s been literally all over me. When was the last time she looked at me like she has tonight? When was the last time she wrestled with me in that way that made sure her perky little breasts were pressed against me? She knows exactly what she’s doing, she’s good. Real fucking good: For here I am thinking about nothing but her when I’ve got a horny 19 year old texting me to tell me she wants to suck my cock, oh yeah  Dream Girl  is the queen of everything. I so wish I could get her out of my heart but I cant. As I write this she’s (quite rightly) fucking my best friend. I often wonder if it’s just sheer bad luck or fate’s way of punishing me that my best friend’s girl is my perfect woman. She is perfect & tonight it showed. I would gladly die for a few hours of being the love of her life. If you’re reading this  Reckless , then A) serves you right for being a nosey cunt with no respect for your friend’s privacy &amp; B) Tell me 2 good reasons why I shouldn’t have fallen in love with the most wonderful, funny, sexy, clever woman I’ve ever met! (Ha! Get out of that you lucky, lucky fucker!) In other news, the interview for the supervisor job was postponed &  Delusions Of Grandeur  got the lab job. It causes me real, tangible pain that as I write this, the girl who has fucked me up like no other is probably coming about now with  Reckless  as the provider of that pleasure. I know I’m a cunt for even thinking about that but I would defy any man to escape the pure unadulterated joy that comes in the form of  Dream Girl . Well it’s 22.28 so I’m going back upstairs to watch the footy. I’ll somehow try to ignore the sounds of their lovemaking & instead concentrate on the plight of my beloved Leeds Utd. It’s quite ironic how their rise &amp; fall has matched my own. If you hadn’t noticed I’m very drunk. As Wolves are beating Man U 1-0, I can hear  Reckless ’ vinegar strokes followed by his customary trip to the toilet to dispose of the condom. On top of everything else I cant send my horny messages to  Too Keen  because I’ve run out of credit, partially because  Reckless  used lots of it on his ultimately fruitless dope scoring calls. Nice one, mate.22.56 Just feel it’s worth mentioning that  Dream Girl  would deny all of this but time has shown that  Dream Girl  is VERY good at denial. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      D’you know what? I’m going to give it a go! So  Delusions Of Grandeur  got the lab job…mmm time will tell but I hope he changes the group dynamic for the better. It will also have a knock on effect on my chances of getting the supervisor’s job for reasons that are far too mundane to go into. If I were a betting man my money would be on  Queen Bee  to get it. I hope she does y’know. She’ll do a bloody good job. The more I think about this, the more I don’t actually want the job. I wouldn’t want to turn my back on my training work. I love that part of my job, love it! I wish I could do it all day every day. I wont let go of it. It’s my baby, I conceived it, I nurtured it, watched it grow & now I stand back in pride (never standing still though!). Did I mention I was stoned? Went round  Funny Dance ’s last night, watched Lord of the rings – return of the king. Which was very good. Had some tea, downloaded some tunes, hung out, slept on the sofa. It was cool. It’s been nice seeing the kids a bit more as well, bless ‘em. Speaking of kids, had some fun in the snow with  The Boy  yesterday, we (I) built a great snowman, he had eyebrows!  Temper Tantrum  was around too &amp; we got on quite well, both of us doing that joking-but-only-partly thing. The snow reminded me of one of the most wonderful days of my life. It was January 1993. I’d only been seeing  Temper Tantrum  for a little while & we were staying at my Mum &amp; Dad’s up in Yorkshire. We went out for the day to Haworth. It snowed quite heavily & the whole place was so beautiful &amp; enchanting. We got soaked but had a great day. I remember there was a hilarious thing with a bloke & a wheelbarrow but I’m buggered if I can remember the details. That was the day that we both truly, madly, deeply fell in love. That night we made love for the first time,  Temper Tantrum ’s very first time, and it was fantastic. At it like rabbits after that, we were! So whilst on her patio yesterday I really wanted to say “Remember Haworth?” to her but I didn’t dare in case it was misinterpreted. I’m very comfortable enjoying the lovely memories I have of our 10 years together but I wouldn’t go back. I care a lot about her but I haven’t once regretted making the decision to leave. I made a prick of myself in front of a beautiful woman today. I was at our packaging department when she arrived. Long blonde hair, tidy body &amp; an aura of class. Today I looked like a scarecrow. 4 days’ growth, hair needs cutting so it’s looking a bit stupid & on top of this I’ve got the same clothes on as yesterday (clean socks &amp; undies mind!). About as attractive as diphtheria. Still I popped in the office a couple of times & engaged in some chit chat. She said she’d seen me before while seeing my boss about something. I replied that I couldn’t have seen her because I’m sure I would not have been able to forget. She smiles widely &amp; thanks me; I did my cool smile (stop sniggering!) & walked out. I’d impressed myself! My next visit to the office saw the arrival of the gibbering, bumbling idiot part of me that is much more accustomed to talking to women. She’d been asked if she had a fella which she answered with an enigmatic “one or two”. At this point I thought one of the guys said “hey flash” in a “ get in there my son” kind of way. I now fear that event never actually occurred. What did definitely happen was me standing up &amp; saying “ Fancy looking like this (now addressing her) the next time I see you I wont look like this I’ll look great, we’ll talk then”. I hastily left the room &amp; realised with dread that I must have looked a right twat! Doh! She was out of my league anyway. Got 2 Depeche Mode DVDs off e-bay today for less than 20 quid. Result! Didn’t get any negative vibes from  Dream Girl  today, in fact she’s been quite lovely. Maybe I have been paranoid, I don’t know. Well it’s nearly midnight so I’d better turn in, not bad though considering I couldn’t be bothered an hour ago eh?Out for a few beers tomorrow, hope it’s cool.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’d quite like to do a bit &amp; tell you about the last day or two but I truly can’t be bothered. I shouldn’t get this stoned…still day off tomorrow. Yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday was un-eventful but today’s been good on the whole. I was worried at quarter past five this morning when the battery light on the car stayed lit. I knew that it meant a problem with the fanbelt & that the alternator wouldn’t be charging the battery. Ha! See the fact that I knew that was something of a revelation for I am utterly-useless-cackyhanded-man when it comes to all things practical. Can’t fix bugger all me! So I got  Funny Dance  to help me. He came through a treat as well. I would be so lost without  Funny Dance . We’ve been friends since we were 15 years old, oddly we haven’t hung out much lately but we probably converse every day or two. Favours mostly, we’re always doing each other favours. More often than not it’s me needing help.  Funny Dance  is who I call when I run out of petrol or need a tenner till Friday or when I need someone to get me White Stripes tickets off e-bay. He never seems to weary of lending a hand &amp; it’s a huge credit to him. He’s a diamond. At work I put my letter of application in for the supervisor’s job, still not convinced of everything but I’m gonna play it cool.  Buddy With Boobs  texted me tonight just to say that she’s missing me, which is a lovely warm thought to a lonely git like me. I’d love a cuddle. I think  Dream Girl  is pissed off at me about something, I truly don’t know what it could be. Perhaps just my continued presence here is irritating her. If so, I don’t blame her nor do I have any ill feeling toward her. It just saddens me to think….oh, I don’t know. Sad music waffling alert!! (If anyone gets bored skip to the next bit but hey, it’s my diary & I have to be me, right?) I have been thrown a curveball, something truly unexpected has happened. To briefly explain, I am often quite loyal &amp; sentimental about bands that I like. Even when they don’t really excite me anymore I’ll still buy their albums out of devotion (usually on the cheap though!). One case being Del Amitri. A band I used to be well into & the main bridge between the 80’s synthpop world I used to live in &amp; the indie/alternative guitar land that I now inhabit. Just before Christmas I picked up their last album, “Can you do me good?” for a fiver. It had been out for 18 months or so & I kept meaning to get it. Truth be known I had little hope for it but I thought I better give it go, so it soundtracked bathtime the other day. Now I can’t stop listening to it, it’s great! Songwriting on a par with “twisted” or “waking hours” &amp; a groovy (yes, groovy!!) new sound thing going on. Perhaps I should bits like that in another colour so that people who don’t know or care what I’m babbling on about can get through this untroubled by such musings. Well, I better go to bed.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, here I am. I know a whole week as passed by but by my standards the fact that I’ve just got out of bed to write this is some feat. I’ll perhaps recap the past week if my persistence holds out but today bears some scrutiny… I’m beginning to feel like I’ve outstayed my welcome here. Here, for the uninitiated, is the home of my bestest friends  Reckless  &  Dream Girl  &amp; their four kids:  Scared of haircuts ,  The Eavesdropper ,  Noisy but sweet  &  Cutieboy . I’m really sad about this for no other reason than I’m disappointed in myself for letting it happen. Today has been odd. Today, perhaps for the 1st time, I’ve felt isolated. I’m pretty sure that nobody has chosen to make me feel this way &amp; that any actions that have have been unwitting. At the same time though it can’t be dismissed as paranoia. It’s a strange empty feeling, kind of uncomfortable rather than painful. Other factor today:  The Boy . I have missed my 4-year-old son like crazy this week yet today he has driven me mad! He didn’t do anything wrong really. I’m concerned that he may be the loudest child ever known, even his whispers drown out the telly! Work has been very dominant in my life this week. It was nice to go back to my other “family”. There’s been a lot going on. One of our competitors has gone tits up, leading to an imminent upsurge in business. There are also job changes afoot. In the lab (where I work) we’re currently trying to recruit  Annoying, Miserable & Bald’ s replacement (or should that be improvement?). So far it’s between  Decent Sort With Bad Teeth ,  Not Right  (as if!) &amp;  Buddy with Boobs  (bless her).  Delusions Of Grandeur  will probably apply on Monday & he has to be the favourite. I would dearly love  Buddy With Boobs  to get it &amp; for all the right reasons too. She would be so happy to get it & I suspect that if she beat her nerves she could be a fine lab technician. Then of course  Wind Up Merchant’ s new position means that the main production line supervisor’s job is open. I have, after much thought, decided to apply. I don’t really want the job but I think applying could reveal where my future in the company lies &amp; it could also lead to a very welcome pay rise (I’m not going to hold my breath though, which when you think about it, is a very silly thing to do anyway…unless you’re underwater…or being gassed…erm…). Also this week I have discovered the wonder of e-bay. Earlier in the week  Buddy With Boobs , in a rather out of character moment, suggested that she’d like to come & see a band with me. I told that Easyworld were touring &amp; that The White Stripes were doing some gigs but that I was sure they’d sold out. Still I checked NME.com & sure enough they had. Then the link to e-bay caught my eye. Moments later I discovered that our tickets were in plentiful supply so the bidding ensued. The next day, with my other bestest friend  Funny Dance  doing the clicking, we got right into it! With just 3 minutes to go we put a bid in for 2 tickets to the Brixton academy show. £76. As the seconds ebbed away me &amp; my audience of  Crisp Fiend  &  They’re All Whores  watched transfixed as every time it refreshed our bid remained the highest. Refresh again, 47 seconds - still top. 23 seconds – still top. 8 seconds, click refresh, rub eyes &amp; shriek in horror as the screen reappears & some bastard has gazumped us by 2 quid! BASTARD!! I have to confess the whole thing was thoroughly exhilarating! Akin to watching a striker burst clear of the defence in the last minute, lobbing the keeper &amp; seeing the ball bounce harmlessly off the bar. With the mission left in  Funny Dance ’s capable hands the tickets were acquired so  Buddy With Boobs  & I shall go to the heart of our wondrous capitol’s seedy underbelly to see the magnificent White Stripes play in a great venue, on a Friday night, 2 days after my birthday. Ace!  Buddy With Boobs  &amp; I have a strange relationship. We are very close friends, lovers in all but deed & both kind of lonely. We’ve been this way for 4 or 5 years now. Our marriage vows have always stopped anything ever happening (just hers for the last 18 months, obviously!) but there remains an irresistible sexual energy between us. I think we both suspect that we’ll end up shagging one day. If history hadn’t educated me so well I’d swear that day was getting closer. We often talk about her poor sex life (I have none to speak of!) since her &amp;  FuckwitHusband  got camera phones (I want one SO much!!) they have getting a bit rude. So on Tuesday, I picked up her phone & started nosing, telling her I was gonna find one of these photos. She was quite alarmed at first but then relaxed, safe in the knowledge I would find nothing. Then, there it was: A grainy but clear photo of  Buddy With Boobs’  left breast being cupped for the lens. Yes!  Buddy With Boobs  was mortified! We both laughed our bloody heads off. It was a great moment (and a little bit of a turn on). My sex life has displayed some tiny green shoots of recovery this week. My mate & colleague,  Crisp Fiend , has a “fancy bit” (her words) in Somerset &amp; she has a collection of friends who would apparently be more than happy to get jiggy with me despite none of them ever having seen me or spoken to me. If I’m totally honest I’m a bit perturbed by the lack of romance involved. Anticipation is a much more potent drug than expectation. That said, any opportunity to end the longest dry spell since the day I entered into the sexual arena (15 oct 1986 with  Horny As Hell ) is going to be grasped firmly with both hands. It has now been 8 months since my last full romp. This is not an acceptable state of affairs. Anyway, all this attention to the week’s events has lifted my spirits &amp; I feel much happier than when I started 90 minutes ago. It’s like therapy! Hopefully this will galvanise me into writing more frequently. No promises though, this is ME we’re talking about.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here we are 3 days late, typical me, finally starting this journal. Different from all previous incarnations in that I’m gonna keep it up all year (yeah, right!). Then at this time next year I shall change the names of all concerned* & send it out to various publishing houses where they will be bowled over by my wit, wisdom &amp; turn of phrase to such an extent that they’ll be tripping over each other to give me buckets of cash & Flash will become the long overdue male equivalent of Bridget Jones. Of course none of this will actually happen. Not because it’s impossible but purely because I am the biggest under-achieving, potential wasting, lazy arsed waste of flesh &amp; bone that ever lived. As you will see. Well, New Year’s Eve was fun. Lots of vodka, whiskey, dope & even a little Charlie combined well with some heady emotions &amp; family fun to make a really nice way to round off the most difficult & challenging year I’ve ever had. 2003 shall cast a long shadow.   *I already have for the purpose of going “worldwide”
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Boy, do we have a lot to catch up on. On Monday morning as I got into bed I texted Miss A & Miss B. A replied straight away. We sent a couple of messages each &amp; then she suggested a quick chat. Our quick chat lasted 2 & a half hours! It was great, we got on really well &amp; I had her really laughing! She sounded cool & a little mad! I’ve always liked a touch of madness in my women. Eventually it was decided that I should go &amp; see her for lunch. I agreed despite the fact I’d had no sleep since Sunday morning and that she live a hundred miles away in Braintree, Essex. Still I thought it would be an adventure, a tonic to spruce up my life of monotony. She described herself as having a shock of blond hair, 5’8” & wearing a rainbow coloured coat &amp; rainbow jeans. So I got cleaned up & headed off to meet  Rainbow Girl . I went cross-country as opposed to the motorway &amp; arrived about 2.30. We’d arranged to meet at Sainsburys. After about 5 minutes she appeared. I couldn’t miss her; she was a resplendent splash of colour in a sea of grey. I liked that. I walked over & said, “You must be  Rainbow Girl ”. We shared an awkward hug &amp; then went to a pub on the town square. It was a nice pub & we chatted for ages, it went really well. Then we had to go &amp; pick up her car from a garage, get KFC (which I resisted) for her eldest & go to her house. We then returned to the pub on foot. By this time it was apparent that I wouldn’t be going to see Easyworld after all. She said I should have a proper drink as I’d been on cokes since I had a pint when I arrived. I explained how I couldn’t because I had to drive home. “Sleep on my sofa” – “Ok, let’s drink!” I didn’t have to be in Crapsville to see The Boy till 3 the next day so why not? As the night drew on we laughed, we flirted, we argued about Britney’s hotness &amp; we simply had lots of fun. I really liked this slightly mad woman & I fancied her too. I got the feeling this may have been mutual. We stumbled back to hers after chucking out time &amp; after a coffee she went to bed & I slept on the sofa. I was very, very tired &amp; went off almost instantaneously. She woke me at 6am! The kids would be up in a minute & she’d rather I was up. Fair enough. I liked  Rainbow Girl ’s kids even though I only spent a couple of hours around them. I’ve since been told that they liked me too, which is nice.  Rainbow Girl  left to take them to school, when she returned she said she wanted to lie down on her bed &amp; that I should join her. So we laid there for a couple of hours, chatting & laughing. The whole time I really wanted to kiss her but like the fool that I am struggled to gain the courage to make that first move. With the clock ticking towards my departure time I finally leant in &amp; gave her a kiss. And it was one hell of a kiss, soft, slow & lingering to which she responded fully. All the while my fingers were gently stroking her neck or in the back of her hair. It was a beautiful first kiss, a kiss of such quality I shall forever be proud of it. This was not all good though.  Rainbow Girl  fixed her glare on me &amp; said, “You can’t kiss a woman like  that  & then just go!” She was right, I didn’t want to go &amp; she didn’t want me to. So I phoned  Temper Tantrum  & asked her if she could pick  The Boy  up from school &amp; I’d arrive a couple of hours later. “No, I’ve made plans now” was her curt reply.  Rainbow Girl  being a single mum insisted that I shouldn’t let  The Boy  down. So I had to leave. It was desperately obvious that if I wasn’t going we’d be having sex. So we kissed goodbye & I set off for Crapsville. I was livid, absolutely fucking gutted. I’d got about 10 miles when I got a text from  Rainbow Girl  saying I’d left her confused &amp; frustrated but she wasn’t hungry anymore. When another came a minute later saying “ well not for food anyway!” I should’ve done a handbrake turn there & then. Instead I ploughed on: M11, M25, M1 all at 90mph wearing a face like thunder. I would’ve cheerfully strangled anyone who got in my way during those 2 hours. I got to Crapsville at quarter past 3 &amp; spent the next few hours with  The Boy  watching Return of the Jedi & having several lightsaber duels- all of which I had to lose!I didn’t resent  The Boy  one iota but I was full of contempt for  Temper Tantrum . However, there was no way I was going to allow her the glee of knowing she had cost me my first shag for 10 long fucking months! I went round to see  Funny Dance  for a couple of hours before work &amp; told him the tale, much to his friendly amusement. Then at work I spent another couple of hours on the phone to  Rainbow Girl . Again it was great. We talked a lot about the kiss I “should have never have given”. She told me I’d left her frustrated, throbbing & soaking wet. That’s never a bad thing to hear is it? Come 6.30 Wednesday morning when I got home I was absolutely knackered having only had 6 hours sleep since Sunday morning. I slept like the proverbial log. Yesterday passed without incident though throughout I’ve been jolly, bouncy &amp; refreshed. I shall call  Rainbow Girl  again tonight, somehow we have to find a mutually agreeable time for a second visit because as we are both very aware, we have unfinished business. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Back in the boiler house again! So I skived off work on Friday- tut tut. It allowed me to commence my blissful weekend of dossing 8 hours early. I say blissful but in fairness dull but refreshing would be a better description.  Reckless  &  Dream Girl  got engaged on Friday. He bought a ring &amp; everything, bless him. There’s no real cause for a big hoo hah because they’ve lived together like husband & wife for over 5 years &amp; I cant see them actually getting round to it for years. Still, bless ‘em. I am truly happy for them & we all got drunk on Friday, which was nice. On the dating front I have this weekend received 2 (yes 2!) messages. We’ll call them A &amp; B for now. Both sound nice though I probably favour A at present purely because B is 5 foot 10 & I’m a good 3 inches short of that! I have both of their mobile numbers so when it’s a reasonable time I shall commence my charm offensive. Hopefully at least a date should come out of it, which will be great. Just meeting someone new will be a pleasure. So much cause for optimism. Remember the Leeds result from a couple of weeks ago &amp; that our next game was Man Utd away? Well, we only came away with a very creditable point after a 1-1 draw. Go on! Football is sometimes a strange beast.  Reckless  is a Nottingham Forest supporter & for several years now he has had to endure endless goads from me &amp;  Funny Dance  about their lowly status in division 1 while my boys have been in the upper echelons of the premiership & enjoying many a European adventure (Champions league semi finals only 3 years ago). So he has been enjoying every second of our spectacular collapse (&amp; so he should) & relishing the very real prospect of Leeds being relegated to division 1. Funny thing is, Forest are firmly planted in the bottom 3 &amp; are staring into the abyss that is (Cue; thunderclaps & Vincent Price cackling) Division 2! Oh how I would laugh if we stay up &amp; they don’t. Ha ha, & he’s been waiting so long to get one over on me. I certainly don’t see myself writing a lot about football but I will have to chronicle the progress of both sides as the season draws ever closer to it’s end.All being well I should be going to see Easyworld tonight. They’re at the Soundhaus in Northampton, so it should be nice &amp; easy. Somewhat bizarrely I haven’t been able to mention it at home.  Dream girl  & the lead singer had a “flingette” last year &amp; now she doesn’t want to go & see them. If  Reckless  were to know they were in town he would be very puzzled as to why  Dream Girl  doesn’t want to go,  Dream Girl  doesn’t want to answer any awkward questions so the upshot is I have to go on my own &amp; cant talk about it. Odd. Easyworld are an exceptional band & they are intrinsically linked with the whole  Dream Girl  &amp; me thing. Lyrically, I don’t think another band has ever come so close to actually replicating my own feelings through their songs. I think he has shared the pain of not being able to let go of that special someone who cant or wont be with you. Their new album “Kill the last romantic” which came out a couple of weeks ago (although  Dream Girl  had it sent to her last summer so I’ve had it since then) could almost be a concept album about the two of us. “Til the day”, “Saddest song”, “When you come back, I wont be here”, “Goodnight” & the breathtakingly beautiful “Tonight” all could’ve come from my heart. I think Dav &amp; I are perhaps very alike. I think he’s an exceptional talent &amp; I’ll be there tonight singing along to every word. There was of course the whole London thing too but that was last year. Last year + detail = undiscussable. As I shall remind myself in 7 days time. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello. I know it’s been a while but so little of note has happened that I’ve not been inspired to report it. Still nothing has happened but I’m at work on days & I’ve nothing to do so here we are… I spent a nice few days with  The Boy . We went up to Yorkshire. It was nice but truth be told, a little dull. I feel like I’m on a plateau at the moment. Nothing bad is happening so I’m not down about anything, yet there’s nothing to be particularly happy about either. So I’m just plodding really. Spend pretty much all day yesterday with  Reckless  &amp; the multi-tracker. Frustratingly we achieved very little. Recording seems to be really amplifying our weaknesses as musicians. I did do a fantastic vocal for “My worthless friend” but that recording had to be scrapped for technical reasons. Think we really need a programmable drum machine. Still no romance on the horizon & sadly for the first time since I was 14 I didn’t get any valentines cards, nor did I send any. I was going to send one just containing the words “Hopelessly…endlessly” but I ran the idea through my what-do-you-hope-to-achieve filter &amp; had to abort the plan. I have a free weekend this week but as yet no plans. I really could do with going out but the usual obstacles of where & who with need to be overcome. Think I’ll ask  Funny Dance . Well I’ve been back at work on days for 2 hours &amp; I’m bored stupid. I don’t really know what I’m supposed to be doing anymore or indeed what my role is. On nights it’s easy for I am on my own & I know what’s expected of me, also there are ways of passing any empty time. This is just crap. Think I may have to start looking in the chronicle again. The only part of my work that I find fulfilling is the training, which only happens on rare occasions. I’d like to train full time. I’m ostrich like by nature so facing up to problems isn’t something I generally do. However something keeps looming into view. I’m 34 years old, smoke 20 fags a day, eat nothing but crap &amp; take no exercise. Yes folks, roll up roll up & see the heart attack waiting to happen! I know I have to change but I’m terribly undisciplined. I shall soon instigate a new regime! * Also coming up soon: Big Brother. I applied last year to no avail but I think I’ll try again. This will involve going to an audition day &amp; queuing up outside trying to get noticed whilst looking like a twat. Now there’s a challenge! I would dearly love to get in the house, if nothing else it would give this plodding monotonous life of mine a good shake. It would certainly increase the sales of this book, eh?   *Note from August me- As if (typing with fag in hand &amp; bacon sandwich just devoured) 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Again little to report but I’ll try nonetheless. Cocked up big time at work last night. To cut a long story short I left a valve open & subsequently poured a couple of hundred litres of paint resin (a white glue-like paste) all over the floor &amp; into the new state of the art water treatment system. Doh! Apparently the general manager –an obnoxious Geordie git for whom the term “little Hitler” was surely created – wanted to throw the book at me but my good friend & supervisor,  The Silver Fox , stuck up for me. Still likely to be disciplined though. That’ll put the kibosh on any hopes of a pay rise for a while! Bought Franz Ferdinand’s self titled debut album today &amp; after 3 listens it sounds bloody great! My e-bay addiction continues although I have stopped buying expensive stuff. It is truly fantastic for getting those long deleted CDs from days of yore & also for re-establishing my “Friends” collection, now all on DVD of course!  Temper Tantrum  had our whole collection of videos when we split up, which was fair enough as my CDs escaped pretty much unscathed. Out of the 20 she took I’ve replaced all but 2 (currently watching them both on e-bay!) No romance as yet &amp; no replies to my messages but it’s still early days. A rare occurrence last night: my beloved yet beleaguered Leeds beat Wolves 4-1! Yay! On a whim of optimism I checked the next couple of fixtures to see if it could herald the start of a run of form in our battle to stay in the premiership. Next game? Manchester united. Away. Oh bugger! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s been a few days, I know but only because there has not been much to report. The multi-tracker is ace but my bloody keyboard wont work so I’m a bit limited at the moment. “Frog” is almost complete though. Today has been a day for everyday things to be great. I had a lovely sleep, a wonderful soak in the bath &amp; a fantastic wank. On the dating front I got a message from Tracy, 34, who I wasn’t sure about but she gave me her phone number with 1 digit missing so I cant phone her anyway! I left messages for about 4 or 5 girls so it’s just a waiting game now. I hope. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I’ve just registered myself with a dating service. The local radio’s midnight matchmaker thing to be exact. Cant do any harm can it? Not sure I left a very good message though: I described my looks as being phenomenally average. They’ll surely come running! Still, nothing ventured… Today I feel quite chipper, not for any particular reason, I just do. My multi track recorder arrived today, but I must have slept through the postman’s knock so they gave it to next door…who brought it round at 7 o clock. 7 O BLOODY CLOCK!! I had to be here at work, 20 miles away, for 8. Bugger! Despite feeling sleep deprived already I foresee myself staying up for a bit in the morning so that I can “lay down” a drum track. Probably for “Frog” though “Big lover” & “My worthless friend” are in with a chance. So Valentine’s Day is hurtling towards us. I’m gonna be spending it with the one person I love above all others:  The Boy . Mummy has got a date. I have to be honest &amp; confess that I’m dying to ask her all about it. I know she’s had sex with some random men (fair play to her by the way) but I haven’t yet heard of a boyfriend as such. I hope she does get with somebody & fall in love again. I sincerely want her to be happy plus it would make our parenting relationship much easier (I think!). I hope she doesn’t hook up with a dick. I know she will not let anybody near  The Boy  who she wasn’t sure about, so I’m cool with that but I do hope new man doesn’t overtake dad in  The Boy ’s young mind. I love him so much; I adore being with him. He brings me bliss. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing to report other than the feeling that I’m sinking into a very stagnant rut of work, sleep &amp; little else. I guess I’ll have to take steps to change it. How? Haven’t figured that yet! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Better try & make some sense out of the weekend, eh? After a mini sleep on Friday I set off for Crapsville to collect  Buddy With Boobs  for our trip to London. All went well &amp; we had quite a laugh on the train. We got to Brixton a bit early for my liking & had to endure a 2-hour wait in the venue. Being an experienced gigger I very rarely get into the venue until just prior to the band coming on. The next 90 minutes or so were totally life affirming. There’s nobody else quite like The White Stripes. Jack is quite simply a god &amp; the huge sound that is created by just the 2 of them is truly awe-inspiring. And when Meg took the spotlight for “In the cold, cold night” there was no other woman in the world that mattered & man, did she look hot! The final volley of songs really cemented their place at my musical top table. Only Radiohead, Muse &amp; Depeche mode have had a similar effect on me live.  Buddy With Boobs  seemed to enjoy it but didn’t get excited or giddy or passionate. It drove the point home that despite how much I deeply care for her (which I do) I could never imagine sharing my life with her. I’ve never really known her to be passionate about anything. Passion matters to me. The journey home was uneventful & that was Friday. I woke Saturday lunchtime (at last a good quality sleep) &amp; joined  Reckless  &  Dream Girl  in the kitchen for coffee. They presented me with 2 tickets to go &amp; see Duran Duran in April. Ace! Both have already, without each other’s knowledge, quietly staked their claims for the other ticket. This could be fun. After a day of blissfully doing nothing the time came for us to hit the town. We got quite stoned prior to leaving & this set us up for a wonderful 3 or 4 hours filled with lots of smiles &amp; laughter. However by about 11 by mood started to change. The main reason for this was that nobody else came. People from work simply never bothered & even  Funny Dance  &amp;  They Used To Be Even Bigger  couldn’t make it. This was exactly the same as last year when it was just me,  Reckless  &  Dream Girl . I’m clearly nowhere near as popular as I like to think I am. It also became apparent that I’d hardly noticed a single woman in the place because I had been totally captivated &amp; bewitched by  Dream Girl . I’ve found before that going out with a view to pulling is a fruitless exercise when in  Dream Girl ’s company. I just don’t see anyone else, why would I when the woman who could’ve been scientifically designed to be my perfect partner is sitting with me. So I decided that I’d like to go home. It didn’t take long for the head-spinning drunkenness to force me to apologetically stumble towards bed. As soon as I left the living room something hit me with the ferocity of a scud missile & I started to cry. I dashed to my room, collapsed on the bed &amp; proceeded to cry like a baby. I sobbed uncontrollably for what felt hours till I must have drifted into sleep. I don’t quite know why it happened, probably a build up of recent tensions, my confidence hitting an all time low & the obvious futility of my feelings for  Dream Girl . I do know that it hurt like hell &amp; I desperately wanted to feel someone’s arms around me, telling me it was all going to be alright. Sunday passed without incident & I had a nice day with  The Boy . He really is the reason why I carry on. No matter how low I get I know that he needs me &amp; that he loves me unconditionally. As I do him. He brings joy where there is pain & one day when he’s old enough to understand I’ll tell him of all the times he got me out of the emotional mire of life.So one month into this diary &amp; you must think I’m a right miserable bastard. I don’t blame you but really I’m not! I’m probably one of the most happy-go-lucky people you could ever wish to meet but I am going through a really tough time at the moment. Don’t give up on me yet; we’ll get through this together ok? 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When is January anything other than shit? Not this year. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please note I was very drunk at time of writing…  I hate myself &amp; I want to die. Why? Because I can never imagine loving anyone as much as I hate loving my best friend’s girlfriend. I KNOW! I wish I knew how to stop it but I don’t. Fate has given me such an impossible mission. How will I ever find anyone to match  Dream Girl ? 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haven’t Monster Munch shrunk? They really have, they’re titchy! If you need to sneeze apparently all you have to do is look at the light & your sneeze will come. So says  Dream Girl .  Reckless  &amp; I agree that she is mad, a mentalist if you will. So we conducted a text survey &amp; the score was about 4-4! This does not mean that she’s right but it does mean she’s not the only mentalist about! Well my ex-wife flies off to New York tomorrow so I will be heading off to Crapsville for a 7-day intensive single parent stint. Should be great, bring it on! 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a bloody boring day. Emotionally I’ve been up &amp; down today. I really can’t think of much else I want to share at this point. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, where do I start? I’ve got a lot to cover but I’m gonna start right here right now. 10 minutes ago  Dream Girl  came into my room to show her tan off. My god she looked so fucking hot you could fry an egg on her!! Tight little black shorts, tight little white top, she looked fantastic. Anyway things have been pretty bad, I haven’t been to work for 2 weeks. I went to see my doctor last week & he signed me off for 4 weeks &amp; gave me some anti-depressants, I’ve also asked to see a counsellor. Depression, you see. I’ve felt so low lately, like there’s no hope & nothing to look forward to. I’m terrified to look forward because I dread to think how I may turn out. I fear that I’m destined to be one of life’s losers.  So what are my issues?  Work – it fills me with dread it’s so boring. It doesn’t challenge or fulfil me & I know I’m wasting myself there. Trouble is I’ve been there nearly 10 years; it’s comfortable & easy. Also I earn a fairly good wage that will be difficult to match. Home- my search for a new home goes on, most of my hopes are pinned on getting a flat in a particular block in Crapsville. I can’t afford the outlay required for private rental so I fear that if the flat doesn’t come off I’ll end up in a shitty bedsit. Women- I’m still in need of a cuddle, a kiss or failing that a couple of hours of hot, passionate sex!  Rainbow Girl  lives so far away that it’s just not practicable. Miss C in Crapsville rained off our date &amp; has ignored me ever since.  Temper Tantrum  has been really horrible lately, she keeps slagging me off for not doing enough for  The Boy . This really pisses me off because I’m devoted to my son. I spend loads of time with him. I pay my maintenance (a more than adequate amount as well!) every week without fail & most importantly I adore the little bugger! I can hear him now squealing &amp; screeching as he plays with  Cutieboy . I’ve spoke to many single mums & every one of them, without exception, is really impressed at how much I’m committed to my boy &amp; his upbringing. As far as  Temper Tantrum  is concerned I don’t do enough. It makes me want to punch her in the chops! Which of course I never would do. I’ve never hit a woman in my life & I never will. So here I am, my emotions, hopes &amp; dreams in a big messy heap. I’m lost; I don’t know what to do with myself. So I’ll plod onwards, forever trying to make things better, endeavouring to be happy.That is all I want – just to be happy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry I haven’t written. I’m very very low at the moment. I can’t be arsed to write. Can’t be arsed to live to be honest. Sorry. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I got up at 6, I drove down to London’s docklands & joined the queue. I queued for just over an hour. I was then given my chance as part of a group of 10 to plead my case. I thought I did ok; I cracked a couple of jokes & got good laughs. And then I wasn’t picked &amp; that was that. I was home by half 11. The whole thing has left me feeling dismal. I feel very sad today. Very sorry for myself, devoid of love, aching to be held in a warm soft embrace. Should’ve been a girl eh? 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a quickie (drunk, you see) to say nowt much happened over last day or two but tomorrow commencing at 06:00….it’s Big Brother audition day! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      May’ve been a bit hasty about  Rainbow girl , poor love has been a bit poorly, which is why I hadn’t heard from her. Still don’t know whether we’ll see each other again, it’s very difficult. Bad news for the guys back home. They found out yesterday that the owner of their house wants to sell it so they have 2 months to find something else. It’s knocked them for 6 & I really feel for them. Today heralds another attempt to stop smoking. I’ve struck a deal with  Buddy With Boobs  who has been clean for about 10 days. If I smoke again then she’s gonna smoke again. If I stay clean &amp; she succumbs then she has to shag me. Fair enough eh? Drum machine arrived Monday morning. It’s cool & it’s reminded me so much of my final year at school &amp; the music I made back then. I’ve so far found that 34 is the age of realisation. Realising just how bloody old I am! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well the weekend was good on the whole. I think  Reckless  had a good birthday. We didn’t go out due to cash & babysitting issues.  Funny Dance  came round; the 4 of us got very drunk & played super Mario kart (old school, but still ace!). It was a good fun night. As mentioned in the early hours there was a sparkle in the air. Maybe her hair colour really does affect how she is. Last night she was blonde, beautiful &amp; a little flirtatious. Nice. I’m fully aware that it’s just the way she is when she’s drunk but hey it’s just nice, y’know? I have got the impression that  Rainbow Girl  has lost interest, cant blame her, the distance is too great for any sort of real relationship & though I’m sure we would’ve had some fantastic sex that day if I’d acted sooner, I think now if we met up again it would just be for a shag. I don’t think she’s the kind of girl who would do that. Still, I could be wrong about it all.By the way I feel I ought to tell you: my last attempt at stopping smoking lasted about 6 hours. I know- feeble &amp; weak (sigh). 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WARNING! VERY DRUNK!! There was something there tonight. I saw it, I felt it, I know it. Despite all the set-in-stone rules that I have embedded in my head it felt truly fucking wonderful but yet still desperate &amp; yearning like a … erm… desperate yearning thing. It was there though, I swear on my boy’s life it was there.I saw it! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I’ve been quite happy & jolly today, I’ve enjoyed the day. I have decided that I will stop smoking tonight at midnight. No more. It’s a drain on my cashflow, it’s shackling my singing voice &amp; - Let’s face facts – it’s killing me. Now I’ve been here hundreds of times but I am truly determined this time. I will need to show the same level of resolution as when I refused to go back to  Temper Tantrum  & when I committed to writing this diary. I also will be striving to eat more sensibly, though this will prove extremely difficult in conjunction with not smoking. I feel a strong desire to be creative. I haven’t written a song since “Egg wielding freak” which must’ve been October or November. One thing that keeps putting me off is the number of songs that are stacking up in my head &amp; not making their way to guitar world. Since we had our creative spurt last spring nothing has really hammered home. My sincere hope is that one day these titles might mean something to someone: “Hate farm”, “My worthless friend”, “Upon the scales” & “Haunted” all came together within a month or so, but since then I’ve got “Resistance is futile”, “Jack White” &amp; “Secondbest” all fully formed in my head, they just need to be nurtured.  Reckless  needs to give them some attention which to be fair isn’t always easy. LIST ALERT!! LIST ALERT!! Here is a list of all the songs that are formed enough in my head or in guitarland that could be considered recordable: Feel free to skip ahead Frog My worthless friend Haunted Hate farm The truth about you Love of my night Big lover Upon the scales Egg wielding freak All too human Secondbest Jack White Resistance is futile I tell you what, that would make a fucking cracking album! Suppose you’ll have to take my word for it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      February was a massive improvement on dismal January. Let's hope March holds the trend &amp; gets really good. The signs are promising. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s March the first today. No acknowledgement noted or expected. Nothing. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Much to report. Been having lots of fun talking to & texting  Rainbow Girl . Some good flirting too. I do like her but the distance between us means I can’t let either of us get carried away. I have also had a couple of texts from miss B whom I fear I’m not suited to at all, this fear may be groundless though I shall continue to investigate. Another message was left for me yesterday from Miss C. I just checked it out &amp; she sounds nice enough. Her biggest draw at present is that she “lives in a small town called Crapsville”. I will phone her when I’ve mustered up the courage for such a daunting task. It’s silly but I kind of feel a bit bad regarding  Rainbow Girl , almost like I’m cheating on her, which obviously I’m not. Went out last night on a work trip to greyhound racing in Birmingham. I had a great time, got a bit drunk, lost all my pissing money & best of all got re-acquainted with my old mate  Go On Gamble . We used to be really good mates when he worked with me. We had a common love for music, football &amp; gambling (which at the time cost me dear). I never go near fruit machines these days & that’s all down to  Go On Gamble ! It was great to see him &amp; we had some real belly laughs on the bus journey home. Also fun on the bus:  Big J  & his mate  Big V .  Big J  &amp; I had established a couple of days previously that his other friend  The Portugeezer  is  Temper Tantrum ’s new boyfriend.  Big V  wasn’t aware of who I was other Flash – a bit of a character. They got onto the subject of why  The Potugeezer  didn’t come on the trip.  Big V  moaned that it was because he’s under the thumb with his new missus & that he doesn’t know what the hell he sees in her. I was smirking for England! Lovely moment. Apparently  The Boy  is set to meet  The Portugeezer  this week, which I hope goes well for both of them. It’s a good sign that  Temper Tantrum  is happy with him, which is nice. Just been very reckless on e-bay. I’d already bought a drum machine for £31 earlier today. It’s a TR505 that I used to use at school on my early “works” such as “Backlash” &amp; “State of confusion”. It’s a smashing bit of kit that I hope will move our stuttering recording “career” onwards. Anyway I digress,  Dream Girl  asked me to buy  Reckless  a camera phone for her birthday gift to him. I duly landed a rather lovely Nokia 7250 for him at £113. This was fine, within her budget & done with enough time to arrive before the big day. 20 minutes later I had paid nearly 90 quid for a camera phone of my own. A Sagem myx-6 (I think!). I have wanted one for a while but the childish little spoilt brat in me couldn’t let  Reckless  have one while I struggled on with my 3510 that incenses me everytime I have to press *. Since coffee got spilt on it around Xmas it’s been a right pain so a replacement was on the horizon, that said I shouldn’t have been so rash &amp; so envious. I’m a bad man. A bad man with a camera phone though! Yay! With that in mind I’m not gonna look on e-bay anymore this week as with P&P costs I’ve already spent £130. It may even be time to sell a thing or two. Well it only remains to be said that at this time last year (well sort of because there was no Feb 29th last year) I was blissfully unaware of how my life was gonna skew onto a very different &amp; bittersweet path within the following 24 hours. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well so far the 10 commandments of Flash have hardly shook the world but it’s early days yet. One thing that has changed though is that I remain jolly & cheerful since coming back in spite of work being shit, almost being homeless &amp; the impending doom of relegation for my beloved Leeds (Forest are safe by the way). Yay!? 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today was supposed to be the big day back at work, the arrival of Flash mark II & what happens? I bloody oversleep. Woke up at 7 &amp; I’m supposed to be there at 6, so a big fat smelly lie is required. Tyres being let down in a street wide wave of vandalism should do the trick. Truth is I’m very annoyed at myself but under the new rules I’m not allowing myself to get down about it. It is shit though. Better fill you in I suppose…  Rainbow Girl ’s was a washout; it became very obvious very quickly that just holding a conversation amongst the madness of her world would be quite a feat, never mind anything else. So I left after a couple of hours, I just told her that it was a bad idea & that I was off. I went home to watch “friends” with my friends. It was really nice to get home &amp; Flash mark II has been very well received, even brought tears to  Dream Girl ’s eyes, bless her. I’m sure that secretly they still think I’m mad! The weekend has been really nice, I spent some quality time with  The Boy  & my “family”, the sun has been beating down &amp; it’s just been nice, y’know? So today I will try &amp; sort some stuff out with my unexpected free time. Ooh, I am a tit! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Prior to leaving Porthmadog this morning I held a little private ceremony where I cast two very special cherished items into the water & said goodbye to them &amp; what they represent, in conjunction with the unspeakable law. Now I’ve just arrived in Braintree, which is one hell of a trek from Porthmadog.  Rainbow Girl  is out &amp; about at the moment but should be back soon. Any reportable incidents will have to wait until I get home as I’ve just about run out of paper. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So in a frankly bizarre turn of events it looks like I’m going to Essex tomorrow to see  Rainbow Girl . Cool, you never know I might just get laid! I only have 4 days to go to stop it from being a year with no action. That statement may belie my affection for  Rainbow Girl ; I like her a lot & feel her to be a bit of a kindred spirit. With that in mind I better outline my manifesto now as I may well be too busy tomorrow &amp; the whole point of this trip was to sort my life out. So here goes: the 10 commandments of Flash. Actually before I lay down the laws one thing must be noted.  The Boy  overrides everything.  The Boy  is & always shall be my first priority. Ok here goes 1.ACT I have fucked up so much of my life because of not acting upon things that I should have. I can no longer allow this to happen, I must act upon things. This is crucial &amp; that’s why it’s law No.1. 2.DRUGS – A TIME & A PLACE. I can’t help but think that a lot of my mental decline has been down to the amount of dope I’ve been smoking. Now I love getting stoned but from now on it shall only be consumed when it’s appropriate. So no more joints at 3 o clock on a Tuesday afternoon. 3.THE UNSPEAKABLE LAW. I know what it is &amp; I know what I have to do. I shall make a grand gesture of closure tomorrow before I leave Wales. 4.DEFINE WHAT I WANT TO DO Throughout my life I have had lots of dreams about what I want to do or who I want to be. I see the need to define these dreams & either follow them or consign them to the bin. 5.STOP BEING BONE-FUCKING-IDLE. Laziness is my nemesis. It has cost me so much in my life. I can’t allow it to cost me anything else. That’s why I pushed myself into climbing a mountain today. I have to fight laziness at every opportunity because it needs burying. 6.BE CLEAN 7.USE MY GIFTS In conjunction with laws 1, 4, &amp; 5, I clearly need to use the skills I possess because, frankly, a lot of people aren’t so lucky. I have a great singing voice, an ear for a fine melody & a way with words that can serve me as a lyricist, a writer &amp; also as a conversationalist. I must be proud of these gifts & use them accordingly. 8.WOMEN MUST NOT RULE MY LIFE As anyone who knows me well enough would tell you, all logic goes out of the window where women are concerned. This is flawed &amp; has cost me dear time & time again. The pursuit of love must not detract from or obstruct everything else in my life. 9.SET AIMS I should set aims on a regular basis &amp; try to achieve them. This can only lead to success. 10.FUCK IT! I am a big fan of spontaneity. There are times in life when you have to say “fuck it” & go with whatever feels right at the time. The fuck it law can be applied, albeit sparingly, to everything except law 3.  So that’s it, these guidelines come into force as of the moment I open my eyes tomorrow morning &amp; shall stay in place until I pop my clogs. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s St. George’s day today. I’m very patriotic & I love England &amp; being English. I hate the fact that no one makes a fuss & has a colossal party like the other nations do. However I am in Wales so I better get sorted &amp; get myself back to EN-GER-LAND!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Double bill!! Double Yay!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a lovely day I’ve had. It’s been glorious sunshine all day. Since Snowdon I’ve had another fantastic drive, this time down to Porthmadog where I’m staying tonight. And now friends is on the telly. Yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why did I do that then? “Yes, why the fuck would you want to do that to us?” scream my poor throbbing, jellified legs. Well, I walked up & down that mountain as a test of will &amp; I triumphed. The top of that mountain was never come to me was it? No, I had to put in a concerted effort to get there. It’s kinda symbolic. The things I want from life, the things I’d like to achieve aren’t gonna come to me either. I’ll have to work for them, sweat for them, ache for them. When I was at the summit I left the lazy, bone-idle part of me up there. He’ll probably die up there unless he scrounges enough money to get the train back down. Even if he does I’ll be long gone by then. The plan is that I’ll never see the useless fucker ever again! Yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YES! I sit at the summit of Snowdon. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well Bangor is quite lively on a Wednesday night. Loads of pretty girls, trouble is that all those pretty girls are in the 18-22 age range. No doubt because Bangor is a university city. Still, I’ve managed to get quite drunk, which is nice. I’m already in bed because I didn’t get much sleep last night &amp; I’ve got a mountain to climb tomorrow- weather permitting. At the risk of repeating myself, I’m so glad I did this. It feels good. Night night. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I’ve had my brekkie &amp; it’s time to move on. Where will I go? I don’t know but it looks like a lovely day out there so maybe I’ll find me a mountain! 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Time to chill at the seaside. I’m in Bangor, which for the uninitiated, is a pleasant little city on the coast of North Wales. I got here about 2ish. Since then I’ve had a wonder around, read the NME, had a couple of pints & finally found a room for the night. Oh I am going to enjoy sleeping in a proper nice double bed tonight. The plan for the rest of the day is to chill for an hour or two &amp; then see what this place has to offer on a Wednesday night. Part of my new way of living is going to be setting myself aims. Mostly short term to start with. I use the word aims as opposed to goals because not realising an aim isn’t necessarily a failure. Failure is not an option. So without further ado lets set some now, eh? Tonight’s aim is to have a conversation with at least one woman. Tomorrow I aim to eat a salad (which would be a massive achievement for me!) & I think I will walk up a mountain, seriously! Right now I’m off for a shower. A long-term aim is to be considerably less minging. With head bowed in shame I have to confess that sometimes I can be a little lax when it comes to personal hygiene (feel the need to point out that we’re not talking Bob Geldof stuff) but that stops today. D’you know what? I bet back home everyone thinks I’m a nutter for just going away like this but I already feel I have gained so much from this trip, I feel vindicated. Just looked at myself naked in the mirror &amp; I don’t think I’ve ever looked so fat. I’m not gonna get down about it because I’ve been a bit of a porker since I was about 11, but a year ago I was 2 stone lighter than this. So another aim is to lose some weight, shall we aim for 11 and a half stone by the end of May? Yup, that sounds fair. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I may have actually done something right! I am so happy just driving around all this beauty. I’m really happy that I have taken control of my own destiny. For at least a couple of days I am not being swayed or led by any outside influences & it’s a very powerful feeling. It’s enriching my very soul! So for now me, my tunes &amp; my little car are just gonna drive. Yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow! What a wonderfully nice time I’m having. I slept from roughly 4am till 9 in the car at Llangollen. When I woke I drove off again, further into Wales. I stopped & had some breakfast then went off the beaten track. I had an enchanting drive through the mountains on a tiny winding road, it was ace! Now I’m in Blaenau ffestiniog &amp; I need a poo! That’s better! I was probably a bit optimistic paying for 2 hours on the car park. The Boy would be overjoyed, as the little “dinky dooey” steam train has just puffed alongside me.  Buddy With Boobs  would be happy too as she used to live here on a farm. As beautiful & inspiring as this area undoubtedly is I could never imagine living here. Being so far removed from my idea of civilisation would freak the hell out of me &amp; everybody speaks in a bizarre foreign tongue! Right, back to the car &amp; see where I end up next. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello stranger!! Sorry I haven’t checked in for a while. I’ll try & recap the last few weeks at some point but I am here &amp; I am NOW! I’m currently sitting at Corley services on the M6. I’m going away for a few days to be on my own & to sort my head out, indeed to sort my life out. I’ve left letters for  Reckless  &amp;  Dream Girl ,  The Silver Fox  at work & for  Temper Tantrum  &amp;  The Boy . I’m not running away, far from it. I’m facing up to my self, facing up to things I need to do. Over the next few days you, my hard backed little friend, shall be my only companion. We’re gonna bury some ghosts, set some goals & maybe even draw up a manifesto. A set of personal guidelines to try &amp; live within. I’m sick of the man I’m becoming. It’s time to evolve, to become a new me. A me that still holds true to who I am, that still possesses all the good worthwhile qualities that make me special but also a me that will not be accompanied by a sackfull of shit. In essence I’m going to try & figure out a way to become a winner, a fighter. Someone who my son &amp; my friends are proud to know. The loser must be eradicated. That’s the plan. I’m sure everyone thinks I’ve finally lost the plot but that couldn’t be further from the truth. I’m doing this in an effort to not only find the plot but also to read it, understand it & then take to the stage for the second part of this performance called life. Only I can do this, only I can change this life &amp; only I can fix the mind of Flash which has been broken for far too long!So where are we going? At the moment picturesque North Wales is favourite although that is subject to change. Rest assured you’ll be the first to know. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fuck March 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      May   rocked  ! I am still a very happy chappy &amp; i can only see things getting better. Come on! 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Life is strange isn’t it? I just had sex tonight (twice), it’s been great. Yet there is still a gaping chasm within me that just can’t be filled. Still, beats having that hole &amp; no sex, eh? 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don’t half write some shite when I’m drunk, eh? Yesterday was a cool day. I had another shag (Yay!) but the evening was simply divine.  Reckless ,  Dream Girl  & myself laughed so much! Of course there was also “Friends”, oh it was a great end to a marvellous 10 years. I proper cried, bawling my eyes out like a girl. I can honestly say I’ve never been so moved by a TV show. Ross &amp; Rachel got back together, bless ‘em! Inside somewhere it all became a metaphor for a dream that I know will never come true. My Rachel will never come to me. Big Brother on first impression is full of norberts! 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Talk more tomorrow but now I know how sweet pain can be; I think (I’m probably as insane as I’m drunk) I have maybe for a few precious minutes taken the upper hand in this whole malarkey. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s a whole new kind of sexual frustration that I’m suffering with now!  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  & I are both gagging for a repeat of the other day but her mum’s always too close for comfort. Man, we had some serious text sex last night! If we do half of what we spoke of then we are assured an awesome time. We may have a small window of opportunity this afternoon, I do hope so…I’m as horny as hell. The beast within as been awakened! (I hope your laughing as much as I am!). Tonight  The Boy  &amp; I are off to Northampton to stay with the guys. It’s the final episode of “Friends” & the first of this year’s Big Brother. Plenty to drink &amp; plenty to smoke should make it a cracking night. From then on the weekend is kind of fuzzy. We may go up to Wakefield to see the folks but I’m not sure yet, time will tell. Right now it’s time for some sleep & the gazillionth listen to Keane’s “Hopes &amp; fears”. It’s a fine album, it really is. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay! Yay! Yay! Fucking Yay! Today I had sex. Yay! For the first time in 13 long months I had sex & it was great. It was with  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  &amp; to be honest after Saturday I thought it was on the cards. I’d actually forgotten how blissful the afterglow is, how sweet that cigarette tastes. After the cuddles & stuff I went back to my room to get dressed. Once the door was firmly shut I silently exhaulted to myself. I imagine I must have looked like Stuart “psycho” Pearce after he scored that penalty in euro 96! Then I needed a tune. “Let’s build a home” by The White Stripes (Listen to it &amp; you’ll understand) was my choice & it was perfect. I am considering writing to my MP to see if it can be made law that all sexually active women have their tongues pierced. I only experienced being given head by a girl with one for the 2nd time today. OH MY GOD! It’s all the joy of a regular BJ but with an occasional feeling of… I don’t know, it’s like being electrocuted! So much pleasure that it feels like pain. Anyway subsequently I have been uplifted. As well as the physical sensations &amp; joys I also feel like a huge millstone has been lifted from my neck. I am no longer a bloke who hasn’t had sex for over a year. No more psychological damage can be caused by that statistic because today it became a thing of the past. Yay! Although nothing else seems to matter right now, I have to tell you about “friends” I watched the pen-ultimate episode yesterday. God I laughed. At one point I was simultaneously laughing &amp; crying. I am SO gonna miss those guys. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Phew! That was a mad weekend. Friday was cool, nothing of any great note happened yet it was a good night. I only found out last night though that I pissed off  Buddy With Boobs  big style. Apparently in my drunken state I had told  Major T  about the whole photo-of-breast incident from back in January. She told me last night that she was very angry with me. At first I was really sad that I’d let her down & subsequently gave her a full genuine apology, she still sulked with me all night. Now though, I can’t help thinking that it’s not a big deal really is it? I also think that I’ve put a lot of time in lately, making sure I’m there for her. I think I’ve been a rock for her of late, I’ve listened to all her woes &amp; I given her support & advice (as any good friend would). I think she could’ve taken that into account before lashing out at me. Anyway I went home about midnight so I wouldn’t be late for work on Saturday. Work was great. I love doing my training. I was at Desford with a group of 14 &amp; it was really cool. I was on top form & we had a lot of fun while still achieving all that we had to. From there I had a lovely tune assisted drive back to Crapsville. I arrived at  Funny Dance ’s at 2 &amp; we headed straight up town to watch the cup final (Manchester united beat Millwall). It turned out to be a great day, I obviously got steaming drunk but as often the case with all day drinking by around 8ish I’d reached that blissful state where no matter how much more you drink, you stay at the same level of drunkenness. The whole day was spent with a posse of guys who I know but rarely hang with (other than  Funny Dance  obviously, who left about 7) & it turned out to be a very bloky day. I had been wearing trainers all day having not anticipated going clubbing. However, last orders were called so now the club was the only option. On the recommendation of a girl who was dishing out flyers I put my black socks over my trainers. My god it so nearly worked! I got past 2 bouncers &amp; the 3rd & final one only got me at the last second. Fair cop, guv. I really didn’t mind as I’d had a wonderful day full of fun &amp; laughter. So I happily got myself a burger & walked back to the Bronx &amp; that was the end of Saturday…or so I thought. As I got upstairs  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth ’s door was open & she said hello. Her friends’ 2 kids were there too. She said they were just about to watch a film: The Ring &amp; did I want to join them? Now as  Reckless  &  Dream Girl  had bigged this movie up to me in the past I thought why not? So I sat next to  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  on the bed &amp; started watching. It wasn’t long until it was decided that it was too scary for the kids (which was bloody obvious anyway!) so she then put on “heartbreakers”, a bloody awful film which was only redeemed by Jennifer Love Hewitt looking hotter than the sun throughout it. Anyway the kids fell asleep & slowly  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  &amp; I got closer to each other, the “accidental” touches became more frequent & before long we were kissing, this was followed by some mild fumbling about. Obviously due to the presence of the kids this was as far as it went. I finally got into my own bed at 04:00. To be honest the whole thing with  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  took me totally by surprise. I suspect that wont be the last time either. Though I will have to tell her clearly that I’m not in the market for a girlfriend. Sunday came along all too quickly &amp; it was time for  Smiler ’s christening. The whole thing was lovely. I’ve always got on very well with  Funny Dance ’s family so it was nice to see them.  Reckless  &  Dream Girl  came over with their brood &amp; it was cool to see everybody together. It was also nice to see that  It’s A London Thing  didn’t seem to be holding any grudges, not that he’d have any right to! It was much more comfortable than anticipated, so that was cool. After 2 or 3 hours,  The Boy  & I followed the guys over to Northampton. We had a lovely few hours over there just hanging out in their lovely garden.  Dream Girl  actually showed some sparkles of what is never said &amp; even confessed to feeling pangs of jealousy at my recent dalliances with girls, she did also say that she was genuinely happy for me & that she was pleased to see me with a spring in my step. She also told me that she always tells the truth when she’s drunk. She was drunk. So again, with no intent on her part I’m sure, the cruel hand that fate has dealt me is brought to the forefront of my mind. I may’ve actually come to the conclusion that the pursuit of sex will be fun but the pursuit of love is a waste of time for my heart belongs to  Dream Girl  &amp; I suspect it always will. None of this made me unhappy though & we all had a thoroughly nice afternoon.  The Boy  had a lovely time too; he &  Cutieboy  are just like a mini-me &amp; a mini- Reckless . If they forge a friendship as strong & as durable as that of their fathers then they won’t go far wrong. On the way home we ran out of petrol (Doh!) &amp;  Temper Tantrum  had to come & rescue us, which she did with good grace. I got home with just enough time to have a quick shower &amp; a little flirt with  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  before I had to go to work, I was dead on my feet. Still, during work I wrote a song. I’ve not picked a title for it yet but I think it’s a good un’! I bought 3 (yes 3!) brand new albums on Friday. Ash, Keane & Morrissey. All sound good but Keane are leading by a nose at this early stage. Today my audition date arrived for my great leap into the cheesy world of TV talent shows. The X factor is the brainchild of Simon Cowell &amp; is basically pop idol with no upper age limit. So on Monday 7th June I shall drag my arse down to London again, prepared for rejection having learned my lesson from Big Brother. I am totally prepared to have nothing come of it. That said, I do have a genuine talent as a singer so who knows? I have to sing a verse & a chorus a capella. I really don’t know what I’ll sing yet but I have some ideas. Blimey, it’s all go y’know! I haven’t even told you about my flat yet!  Temper Tantrum  texted me on Friday &amp; said that her sources had told her that someone had done a moonlight flit from one of the flats in my building. Armed with this info, I phoned the housing association &amp; said flat should be mine in 3 weeks at the most. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello! Just a quick word to say I may have to neglect you over the weekend in the interests of time. Here’s the plan: Now- Beer, pub, girls. Tomorrow- work in the morning (Training at Desford) then cup final in the pub, which traditionally means drinking until collapse & on Sunday-  Smiler ’s christening,  The Boy  time &amp; then back to work. Bring it on! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’m feeling very introspective. I’m having one of those moments where loads of different thoughts & ideas are flashing through my head, like cars on a motorway; you can only focus on each one for an instant until you have to turn your attention to the next & so on. I’ve been out in the yard in the darkness singing to the stars, facing east as always &amp; I had a little blast of Easyworld. Each song overtaking me & then me overtaking it. Each one becoming my song, my thoughts, my emotions. I’ve said before no one has impacted their lyrics onto my heart like Mr. Ford has, we really must have had some similar experiences. Started with “Saddest song”- felt every word, then “Bleach”. “Bleach” was the first song I ever heard by Easyworld, tonight I seemed to really feel it not just get it- “make me feel I’m alive”. Then “A stain to never fade”, “Drive” &amp; “Goodnight” were simply fantastic, a short turbulent trip through the parts of my heart that only I know. I have never found any more potent way of expressing my emotions than with song. I’ve had some wonderfully spiritual moments here &amp; there in my life where I have been able to perform a song to the person it was written for. It’s the purest form of communication I’ve ever shared with the exception of the odd bout of proper love-fuelled emotionally charged lovemaking. Unless I’m unluckier than I already suspect, that kind of lovemaking doesn’t happen all that often, even in the strongest long-term relationship.Hey ‘ark at me waffle on! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’m at a bit of a loose end. I usually sleep all day on Mondays when I’m on nights but I had a kip yesterday & work finished early so I was in bed by 03:30 this morning. Subsequently I got up at midday &amp; now I’m a bit lost. I spent all my money over the weekend so I cant go shopping or to the pub. All my stuff for projects is all in storage. So what shall I do? Work isn’t till 10. I’m just going to conduct a little experiment, back in a mo….. Ok, done. Between January 3rd (when I started this journal) & April 21st (When I set off for Wales) there are 5 “Yay”s written in that timeframe. Since April 21st's grand decision to go off &amp; find my own cure for depression there have been 9 “Yay”s in less than a month. If anyone has any doubts about how important that trip was for my sanity surely the statistical analysis of the Yay factor must dispel them all. Point is I’m a happy bunny &amp; so it shall remain. Yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went over to  Reckless  &  Dream Girl ’s new place on Saturday &amp; it’s lovely. It has a beautiful huge garden. I got the impression that  Dream Girl  had really missed me. I have missed them all, particularly  Dream Girl  but if I’m honest it hasn’t crippled me like I thought it would. The whole weekend went so fast &amp; it’s been really, really good. Yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Was I on fire last night or what? It started as a fairly routine night out. I was looking good (for me), new haircut, best clothes ironed.  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  & her friends all said I was looking fine before I went out. After a few beers in pub No.1 &amp; a rather uncomfortable blast from the past in the form of  She Who Changed Everything , we (that’s  Buddy With Boobs ,  Namesake ,  Major T , myself & a couple of  Namesake ’s mates) went to pub No.2 &amp; then No. 3. Here I met up with  Funny Dance . I then started talking to some girls, one of which seemed quite keen. I said I’d see her in the club. Later in the club while I was searching for her I got chatting to another girl, whose name I don’t think I ever got. I’m not sure what was said between us but I do remember her saying we could “go up an alleyway”, oh yes! So it was agreed but then at the last minute her mate put the kibosh on that & off she went without me, never mind. So then I went back in &amp; had a chops with various people then I ran into the girl from earlier whom I shall call  Impressive Cleavage . After some dancing & getting to know her a bit better (wink!) it was decided that I would walk her home. We said our goodbyes to our respective friends &amp; walked out into the night. We soon discovered that we had nowhere to go so we hung out on the basketball court near her house just outside town. That’s when things started really hotting up. There was a hell of a lot of kissing, which was wonderful. Then it was established that “the decorators were in” so we wouldn’t be having sex. She had beautiful full & firm breasts which I lavished attention on &amp; without going into too much detail I used my finely honed skills as a loverman (tongue in cheek) & took her to heaven several times &amp; she returned the favour in my favourite way. We then kissed, talked &amp; kissed until sunrise. It was great. Eventually I did walk her home then I kinda skipped back to the Bronx feeling very pleased with myself. Very pleased indeed. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So out of 20 girls I sent messages to I had 2 favourites. One of those has replied, Yay!Becky is 23 & lives in Loughborough. She appealed because she loves her tunes, does a bit of writing &amp; sings in a band. She looks pretty too. Haven’t been able to do much about though ‘cos the fuckers at work have slapped “access denied” on that site. Bastards!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, life in the 21st century…I have just watched “friends” (which you must know by now is SO my favourite program ever!). I spent the entire episode standing up holding the poxy aerial above my head. Now my arm hurts. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Although my job leaves me unfulfilled & it’s not what I want to be doing with my life, where else would I be able to spend half of my ten hour shift sending messages to lovely ladies on the internet? I’ve sent out 20 messages to 20 girls. 2 in particular I really like- Becky P in Loughborough &amp; Smiler2U in Birmingham. Ironically the other 18 are not so far away. So lets hope the replies come flooding in. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What’s new? Well I’ve joined another dating service & in less than 24 hours I’ve had 3 messages already! Can’t read them yet because you have to pay for that, but I’m working on it. I’m really missing the guys over in Northampton but I have to confess that being in Crapsville makes life a lot easier. I haven’t been stoned for days &amp;  Reckless  &  Dream Girl ’s theory that dope suppresses dreaming may hold water. This morning I had my 2nd really vivid dream in 3 days. As always most of it is forgotten now, I do remember a trip to London via Bristol (!) with loads of friends &amp; I also remember being fellated in an alcove next to a restaurant by either Jordan or Jodie Marsh (neither of whom I particularly fancy). I remember a lot more actually which I did chronicle in the diary but I don’t think the world needs the gory details of my dirty little mind nor do I have any desire to write porn. Enjoyed a lovely couple of hours with  The Boy  this afternoon. We did a couple of paintings, played Thomas the tank engine frustration (which oddly enough he found very frustrating) & of course we had the obligatory lightsaber battle. If there really was such a thing as The Force &amp; Jedis then I fear the dark side would consume my son. Put a lightsaber in his hand &amp; he becomes a ruthless, snarling fighting machine! I’ve only just realised but perhaps his Star Wars obsession was fated. He was born on 16th July 1999, the very same day that episode 1- The Phantom Menace opened in UK cinemas. I wanted to call him Obi Wan to mark the occasion but  Temper Tantrum  vetoed it, which let’s be honest he’ll probably thank her for. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing to report really but I’m very aware that there are a couple of things from pre-Snowdonia that I never told you about. Can’t remember the date but it was FA cup semi-final weekend.  The Boy  & I went up to Yorkshire for the weekend. I went out on the Saturday night with  The Duke Of Jokes  &amp;  Gentle Giant , my old school friends. Despite all day drinking induced sickness, I had a great time. Funny that even with a void of over 10 years with no contact we all still get on really well, I look forward to my next visit. On the Monday before I went to Wales  Reckless  & I went to see Duran Duran at the NEC in Birmingham. It was blinding! Our seats were about 4 miles away from the stage but we didn’t care for we never sat in them. Just before they came on we were having a fag prior to taking our seats when this bloke gave these 2 women special wristbands &amp; told them to go up to the stage.  Reckless  went over to said bloke & duly acquired wristbands for us too, top man. We legged it down the side of the arena right to the side of the stage where we were admitted to an exclusive little platform with only about 20 people on it, right at the side of the stage!!! In an arena the size of a small town we were only feet away from the band. Fan-fucking-tastic! They gave a thrilling performance, absolutely top class. “Careless memories” being the highlight for both  Reckless  &amp; myself. During “Save a prayer” we witnessed a spectacle of beauty that was very much a 21st century event. Instead of waving lighters, the crowd held their mobile phones aloft; from our vantage point it really was a wondrous sight, like 20000 stars dancing in the night sky. Suffice to say we had a great night. Also should point out that I’ve had no contact with  Rainbow Girl  since I drove away from Braintree 2 & a half weeks ago.  I think I’ll leave it that way, as much as I like her I can’t see anything coming from it for either of us. So maybe the whole thing is best being filed as an entertaining adventure. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I cried as I drove away on Saturday. My little car, full of stuff following  Funny Dance ’s bus thingy out of  “memory lane” for the last time, may have even shed a tear. I had a hug with everyone & had a walk to the shop with  Reckless  before going. That was nice, gave us a chance just to be mates having a natter. So what happened next?  Funny Dance  bought me a KFC on the way over to Crapsville, bless him. Then we arrived at the area of Crapsville known locally as “the Bronx”, where I have found lodgings. I’m in a room in the home of  Wears Pyjamas All Day  &amp; her 28-year old daughter  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth . They’ve been very nice & welcoming but it still feels odd. It’s not a home y’know? Still that’s where I am for now. The state of play is that I’m homeless as far as the housing association are concerned, so I’m top of their list with maximum points. The upshot of that is when anyone leaves one of their very nice flats in town it becomes mine. Mine! It will be my home, where I do what I want when I want. I am itching to get in though for now I’ll have to make do with this room. Which is ok, for now. On Saturday night I babysat for  Smiler ,  Funny dance  &amp;  They Used To Be Even Bigger ’s baby daughter. More to the point I tried.  Buddy With Boobs  came to join me too as she’s getting really sad on her own. Sadly, little  Smiler  hadn’t read the script & within 10 minutes of Mum &amp; Dad going she started screaming & didn’t stop no matter what we tried until with heavy heart I had to ring  Funny Dance  who with  They Used To Be Even Bigger  (obviously!) came home. I then went down to  Buddy With Boobs ’ &amp; got drunk with her till the early hours. We talked & laughed a lot. Strange bloody relationship we have, she &amp; I are each other’s special friends. Though I’d quite like us to be friends who shag each other, we both know that it could lead to a relationship neither of us really wants. Sunday I got up about half past 10 & just festered in my room for a bit before going to see  The Boy . We went to the canal &amp; watched the boats going up & down the locks. It was a lovely couple of hours. Then we went to  Funny Dance ’s where we spent the rest of the day. I downloaded some new tunes with mixed success. I thought I’d got most of the Ash &amp; Keane albums but when I played them back later they had been garbled to stop people like me nicking them, I suppose. (Feel the need to point out that while I may occasionally download albums prior to release- I ALWAYS buy the damn thing when it comes out, ok music piracy types who may just be reading?). I did get a few bits I wanted though including a sensational cover of Beyonce’s “Crazy in love” by my new darlings: Snow Patrol. I have been for some weeks now addicted to their “Final straw” album. It’s sheer class & without doubt my favourite album of 2004 so far (Apologies to Franz Ferdinand). Then last night I went to work, twas great to be back on nights with lots of mates, a lighter workload &amp; tunes as I work. Ace. Then this morning at about 08:30 I was woken by the phone. It was  Dream Girl . Anyone else would’ve got a right gobfull for waking me, but not her. I was delighted. Sadly her fucking pathetic ex-husband had turned up yesterday to see the kids. First contact he’d made in over a year, wanker. So she was upset & I comforted her. She then said it was horrible at home without me there, I felt my weary battered heart glow for a moment, and it made me feel very nice. Then I had a very bizarre dream involving me as “DS Flash” on the bill trying to get Billy Mitchell bang to rights. It was mad, there was even a matrix style fight on a dodgy London train station! Best dream I’ve had in ages &amp; no women involved. Now I’m just whiling away the hours till work time but I guess I’m reasonably happy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’m moving out today. In a couple of hours I’ll be leaving this house for the last time. I’ll tell all the details later but right now I’m so very sad. I’ve been on the edge of tears all morning. Maybe this was the last time that  Dream Girl  & I will spend some quality time, just the two of us. I still love her more than I’ve ever loved anybody, and in an hour or two I have to leave her. I should also point out that I’m gutted about leaving  Reckless  &amp; the kids too, really gutted, but is always the case with  Dream Girl  my heart is breaking. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As much as I’m trying to remain cheery & upbeat since Wales I cannot sit through syrupy bollocks like “Pearl harbour”, all those people all in love &amp; snogging & shagging…. I don’t need a reminder of what I’m missing.Poor old  Buddy With Boobs  is having a hard time. She’s left  FuckwitHusband  but still has to live with him &amp; it’s hard for her. I wish I could send her a hug. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well that’s it. Leeds have just lost 4-1 at Bolton &amp; that means they’ve been relegated. Oh woe is me! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s been my last Saturday night here at “memory lane” with the guys & it’s been fucking beautiful; full of joy, laughter & love. I gave them the gift of song with a great performance of “Coming home” a song penned especially for the occasion. I’m now very drunk &amp; blissfully happy but also secretly very sad. I know that when I try to sleep I will have to strongly enforce the unspeakable law. Night. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      April, I hope will be remembered as when I took my life by the scruff of the neck &amp; started a new era. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fair play to June, can't knock it. Everything seems to be getting better & better.  C'mon July, are you up for it? 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      London baby was great as always & a mighty fine time was had. Saturday started with the full posse of 12 converging on the station to get the train. The full 12 were: Me,  Funny Dance ,  It’s A London Thing  (a London native who introduced me to the wonders of a weekend “in town” some 4 or 5 years back),  Namesake ,  In The Same Boat  ( Funny Dance ’s brother-in-law),  Big Laugh Brummie ,  If The Wife Caught Me Smoking ,  Sound But Spitty ,  Fountain Dweller  &amp;  50%  (all who I’ve come to know since  Funny Dance ’s Blackpool stag weekender & last year’s London baby- all decent sorts) &amp; finally 2 newcomers  Babyface  &  Older Than Me . The fact that  Older Than Me  is emigrating to Australia in a couple of weeks became the unofficial “reason” for the whole shebang. After dropping the bags at the hotel the drinking began. Couple of pints &amp; an all day breakfast, great start. Then we all went down to Clapham; an old haunt of  It’s A London Thing . As we had our first pint down there  Funny Dance  suggested that we should pop a pill, fine by me! I took mine 10 minutes after him who already was hugging everyone around him & telling me how much he loves me, bless him. He always gets like that &amp; it’s quite endearing. I started to buzz as we moved on to the next pub; we’d only been there a couple of minutes when Wonder Woman arrived! I bounded straight over to her & had my photo taken with her in exchange for a drink. Fair enough I thought until it cost me 4 quid! Much to the amusement of the posse. And, not wanting to be too much of a bloky arsehole here but surely it’s a pre-requisite for wearing a wonder woman costume to have some sort of bust? After a few more beers we headed back on the tube to the hotel where we all got changed in readiness for the big night out. Myself,  Funny Dance ,  Namesake  &amp;  In The Same Boat  were sharing a room & we also shared out the wiz so at least us 4 would be up for it! Most of the guys wanted a feed before we hit Soho but  Funny Dance ,  Namesake ,  50%  &amp; I elected not to & went to the pub instead.  Funny Dance  &amp; I started chatting to some girls down from Manchester on a hen night. One of them was very nice & I was getting on really well with her. I was reluctant to leave but by now the others were on route to Soho so off we toddled. From then a great time was had by all except poor  In The Same Boat . At about 11 the posse split into 2 groups, one bunch going to a strip club &amp; the rest going clubbing.  In The Same Boat  inexplicably lost both groups & his phone had just run out of charge! So he spent 4 hours wandering around Soho on his own whilst wizzing his tits off! I went clubbing (Going to the same strip club for the 4th year running just didn’t appeal) where many more drinks were consumed &amp; many dances were danced. Maybe drugs give  Funny Dance  some much needed rhythm because his dancing was uncharacteristically not funny, or maybe the drugs I’d ingested altered my mind  that  much! On the way back to the hotel we went past the Astoria (ah so many memories of so many fine gigs, I did my first ever crowdsurf there) as we did Girls Aloud were being driven out of the back (sadly not out of the country). I could only see Sarah in the front as the others were (I assume) in the back behind tinted glass. As they waited to join the main road I tapped on the window next to Sarah & told her she was very hot. She smiled but for some reason that I still haven’t fathomed out, she didn’t ask me back to hers for a shag. Odd. So that was Saturday. Ooh, actually that’s not quite it. Whilst grooving away in the club fuelled by a dubious mix of vodka, cranberry juice, wiz &amp; ecstasy there was a buzz in my pocket as well as my head. Text from  Impressive Cleavage ! Remember her? She simply put Hello so I replied with the same. She then asked me where I was & I told her I was in London. It would seem she didn’t quite understand that as her next message read &amp; I quote “I’m in the club, come up, I will shag you”. FUCKING TYPICAL!! I could not believe it, believe it or not but I don’t often (i.e. Never) have girls offering sex out of the blue. It felt good to actually be desired by someone but did it have to be while I was 70 miles away in London? Anyway some further texting ensued & it was arranged that we’d meet on Monday. We didn’t &amp; I haven’t heard a peep since, just like last time. Not that I’m bothered, she’ll be back! Woke about 9 on Sunday, went down for breakfast (which was yummy this year, quite a surprise after last year’s barely edible effort) & sniggered at  Funny Dance  &amp; his pounding head. The off to  urlLink The Church . Yay! Pills were swallowed just before going in which was a masterstroke! I just started really rushing just as the tunes started & the tunes were absolutely sublime. First up was Reef’s “Place your hands”. Ace. Not far behind was Jet’s “Are you gonna be my girl?” during which of course I did find a hot girl to sing “now you don’t need no money with a face like that, do ya honey?” to. When “7 nation army” came on my head exploded like I had swallowed a 100 mega-ton bliss grenade! I looked round the place in my chemically fuelled state &amp; soaked up the vibe of this absolutely perfect place, totally life-affirming. After Church we went to the backpacker, which is kinda the law, & continued to be happy, happy, happy! To my utter shock at about 5 o clock  Funny Dance  comes round to the dancefloor where  In The Same Boat  &amp; I are grooving away & announces that everyone has had enough &amp; that they’re all going home! Are we coming? Are we fuck!  Namesake ,  In the Same Boat  (who was making friends with a girl) & I were staying. So the other 9 went home. I would’ve normally been well annoyed that no one other than  Funny Dance  came &amp; said goodbye but in my loved up state I really could not give a shit. Bloody lightweights!! Anyway the 3 of us continued to drink, dance, & in  In The Same Boat ’s case, snog until we had to go for the last train. We stopped in another pub on the way back to the hotel to collect the bags &amp; then had a final drink at Euston station. Train home was a bit of a blur but I do know that over the weekend & particularly those last few hours  Namesake ,  In The Same Boat  &amp; myself bonded quite a bit. We’ve said since that we’ll be doing the whole thing again soon with or without the lightweights!  Namesake ’s mum (god bless her!) picked us up at the station & dropped me right outside the flat. It was a fantastic weekend; I enjoyed every minute from start to finish. And that’s the whole idea. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Same old story… last night in the company of  Reckless  &  Dream Girl  I had to endure the pain of watching England get knocked out of yet another major tournament on penalties. Bastard! This time seemed even worse because we were good enough to win it. I phoned that girl from the other night as arranged &amp; her phone was turned off. I left a message & my number but no reply so I reckon that’s dead in the water. Her loss! So I never told you about last Friday night did I? I went out with the usual crowd. When  Czechmate  arrived she totally blanked me, however a little while later she pulled me to one side &amp; demanded to know what I was doing with “that minger” the other week. I told her that I was really pissed off that she’d seen me with  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  that night. Within a couple of hours we were getting very close on the dancefloor. Everytime  Vodka For Breakfast  turned his back my hands were all over her very, very lovely arse.  Ah & the eyes. You know that look when you just stare into each others eyes, when you’re just saying to each other “I want you now”. It was also said by our mouths &amp; if we could’ve ditched  Vodka For Breakfast  we’d have been having a very good time, of that I’m certain. Anyway I managed to slip her my phone number & she assured me she’d text me &amp; we’d meet up before she flew out to the Czech Republic for a month on Tuesday. She didn’t & now she’s gone for a whole month, which is probably a good thing considering  Vodka For Breakfast  &amp; all that. So when she gets back I don’t think I’ll be pursuing her, though she does possess a mighty fine ass! Tomorrow sees the annual “London baby!” event & I’m very excited. The drugs have been acquired (3 pills each for me &amp;  Funny Dance  & a wrap of wiz to share). I think I have got adequate dosh; all my good clothes are clean &amp; ironed. So LET’S ‘AVE IT!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As you may’ve gathered last night was cool. The downside was a fucking bitch of a hangover which left me with no choice but to go back to bed instead of going to work. I’ve just come in from a lovely walk, yes I know that sounds mad coming from me but my I-pod & I thoroughly enjoyed it. We went round the country park. I had to smile when the teenage couple walking toward me swiftly hid their joint upon seeing me. I also observed that Muse’s “Bliss” is THE most euphoric piece of music I’ve ever heard, it makes me rush &amp; it actually sounds like bliss. I’ve been pleasantly surprised by the volume & crystal clear sound quality of the I-pod. Oddly despite all the true happiness &amp; sense of well being I feel since Wales my thoughts still turn to  Dream Girl  more than anyone or anything else. It doesn’t bring me down anymore though perhaps I’m just in remission. That said, I would still gladly give up everything (bar  The Boy  of course) to be her man. Or at least I would were it not for  Reckless . Bless him, I wouldn’t want him to know how life without her feels &amp; I’m glad that he’s been lucky enough to find true happiness. If you’re gonna envy someone I guess it’s good if it’s someone whose joys you can’t begrudge (well, not often!). 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Again I’ve had a smashing day. Work was a doddle as I spent most of the day out on the road away from the dullness of the factory. I had  The Boy ’s company for a lovely couple of hours. I had a walk with my I-pod then I went to the pub to watch England stuff Croatia 4 – 2 & therefore make it to the quarter finals of Euro 2004. Then to top it all off I got talking to a very nice girl whose phone number I acquired. I shall be calling her in a couple of days with a view to a date. She said I was like Chandler; I so totally can’t think of any higher praise. Yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let me tell you about my lovely day. I woke from my very very lovely bed at 13:45. Had a bubble bath, coffee & corn flakes. Then I walked up to the school in the sunshine to pick  The Boy  up. Walked back with an indignant little boy who couldn’t believe I hadn’t brought the car, he moaned all the way back (only 10 minutes) but I didn’t get narked by it, I just took the mickey out of him &amp; it was quite fun. We then hung out for a bit in the flat; playing on the computer together, watching “Attack of the clones” & messing about. It were reet smashing I tell thee!I had a call from  Dream Girl , she sounded fed up but assured me she was ok, bless her. Then had more corn flakes…. Whoa, I just drifted off into a strange world where Alanis Morissette sounded  really  good!… yeah, um, corn flakes. I then watched Spain vs. Greece (draw). Then I carried on with my new song, I made the drum track last night so today I got the four-track out. I put some bass on it &amp; what I think is a great keyboard track. Its working title is “piano song” but very oddly for me I haven’t got a melody or a lyric yet. It’ll come soon. Then I did the mixing while watching Russia vs. Portugal (0-2) then off to work. When I got there I received the payslip for my quarterly bonus – over £400- nice! On Friday with this cash I shall finally getting an I-pod. Yay!! I shall also be putting aside a wedge for next weekend’s annual weekend of debauchery in London, officially referred to as London Baby! This will be my 5th time, it’s awesome. Me & a bunch of geezers, beer, strippers, drugs, girls, the church, more beer &amp; probably some footy! There’s always a tale or two to tell. Past events have included losing my wedding ring & replacing it without getting caught, snogging a hot lesbian, jumping into fountains with other like- minded souls &amp; many, many more! (in the style of a cheesy voice over “artist”). Anyway I’m off for a fag but just to recap, it’s been a bloody nice day! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello. Well I’m pretty much settled into my pad now &amp; it’s great. I’ve just done my ironing! Other than sorting the flat out not much of note has happened. I think  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  is slowly getting the message, poor love. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally I have my own home. I received the keys at 10 this morning. I’m in the process of opening boxes &amp; sorting stuff out. Yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah well, another day, another wasted trip to London. I’m stunned, I know I sang damn well but sadly I didn’t get through. I reckon my looks must have had a lot to do with it. Simon Cowell was not there nor was anybody else. Just sang to one producer sitting behind a desk. I didn’t even get in front of a camera! Still on the plus side I got to meet some nice people &amp; it was an experience. I’m resolutely not going to let this get me down. I’m enjoying life too much at present. So let’s hope I get the flat sorted out today. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, much to report. Friday night I went out in Crapsville. I had a good night & I spent a lot of time talking to  Czechmate  who is the wife of one of my colleagues,  Vodka For Breakfast .  Vodka For Breakfast  is 58; a good old boy & I suspect an alcoholic.  Czechmate  is 26, very attractive, smart, funny &amp; a native of the Czech republic. I’ve admired her from afar for some time. Anyway during our chat she confided in me that things with her &  Vodka For Breakfast  were pretty grim &amp; that her sex life was abysmal. I, ever the shit, told her that I fancied her & that I’d “watch developments”. She then surprised me by basically telling me that she fancies me &amp; that she would be “up for it”! The evening ended soon afterwards & the situation was left tantalisingly open. It is a big dilemma for me as I have a little bit of history in being the “other man”. Being the selfish git that I am I’m quite worried about getting a reputation for such things – “flash, he’s a good bloke but don’t leave him with your missus”- I don’t really want that said about me. On the other hand I do really fancy  Czechmate  &amp; I’m sure it would be a thrilling experience. So, left open. Prior to going out  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  had been upset, so I had given her a cuddle & tried to cheer her up. As part of this I asked if she was upset because of me, she said no &amp; why would it be? This gave me a chance to gently remind her that “flash doesn’t want a girlfriend” & I also told her I was worried that she wanted something I couldn’t give her. She said all was fine &amp; that was that. I didn’t believe her. Saturday I woke quite early, watched a Harry Potter film on the telly & then went to collect  The Boy . We headed over to Northampton.  Dream Girl  &amp; I had arranged to go shopping ahead of my audition.  The Boy  stayed with  Reckless  who took him to the fair with the girls.  Dream Girl  & I had a lovely couple of hours together. We spent most of it in the pub, we had a really good chat &amp; it was nice. My love for her as obviously been mentioned many times but I do feel I’ve reached a point of comfortable acceptance of the way things are. I have a strong inkling that  Dream Girl  may be struggling a little with her emotions. There have been many subtle signs that her feelings for me may be trying to break down the door that she locked them behind all that time ago. It is also not inconceivable that I am simply a spaz! Either way it warms my spirits without hurting anybody so it can only be a good thing, right? After spending 20 minutes or so actually shopping, I left her to shop some more while I went back to their house where  Reckless  & I thoroughly enjoyed watching England stuff Iceland 6-1. Then it was back to Crapsville where  The Boy  went back to his mum &amp; I went to  Funny Dance ’s to baby-sit for  Smiler . Though not as traumatic as last time it was still far from easy.  Smiler  woke at about quarter to 10 & stayed up till half past 11 when  Funny Dance  &amp;  They Used To Be Even Bigger  came in. the difference this time was  Lulu  who also got up & kept  Smiler  pacified. It makes one feel quite hopeless to be indebted to a 12 year old, but indebted I am.  Lulu  was a star. I then went home.  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  was out so I just sat in front of the telly. It’s actually quite surprising how many satellite channels screen nothing but naked breasts late on a Saturday night. The phone soon shattered my voyeuristic tranquillity. It was  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth . Would I drive over to Northampton to pick her &amp; her friend up? Mug that I am I said yes. It has to be said that she looked quite hot in her little skirt & red top. Within seconds of her getting in the car it became very clear that my old chap was gonna be pressed into action for the first time since the “banjo incident”. As we drove back to Crapsville it was decided that we should go up the club for a drink. I was very reluctant. It’s fucking shitty of me I know but I don’t want to be seen out around town with  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth . I made sure she couldn’t hold my hand as we walked in. once in I felt very uncomfortable, even more so when I spied  Czechmate  &amp; no  Vodka For Breakfast . This was not good,  Czechmate  looked well pissed off as  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  dragged me off to the other side of the dancefloor. I tried mouthing “help” to her but I don’t think she got it, which was the final straw. I gulped down my drink & lied to  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  that there was a woman who I’d once had an affair with &amp; her husband & left, dignity (?!) intact.  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  &amp;  Vulgar The Hutt  followed & we went to  Vulgar The Hutt ’s house (for house read tip) for a quick spliff. Whilst  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  was in the loo,  Vulgar The Hutt  told me that  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  was in love with me, that’s she never seen her so happy &amp; that we made a lovely couple! This was not good & I told her quite clearly that I need to be on my own &amp; I don’t need a girlfriend. I hoped that  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  had overheard. We then went back & had a couple of hours of good sex. Well she did. As seems to have become routine frighteningly quickly, sex seems to consist of me pleasing her for an hour &amp; then her pleasing me for 5 minutes (truth be known this time it was a fucking great 5 minutes!). And in case you’re curious, my penis held up admirably after it’s recent trauma! Today I didn’t rise until 1pm, which partially explains why I’m still up at 2 in the morning. I dashed to get  The Boy  & again we went over to see the guys. Today being the dress rehearsal for my audition. I could see in  Dream Girl ’s eyes that she thought I looked good! Then I sang “summertime” &amp; I sang it bloody well. The “judges” were suitably impressed & I progressed to the next stage. All too soon it was time to take  The Boy  home, good luck was wished &amp; off we went. Then I nipped home for a shower & shave, packed my bag &amp; got back in the car this time heading for Watford. As my audition is in Wembley at 8 in the morning I asked  Oh Gawd  (still officially my mother-in-law) if I could crash at hers. Being the diamond that she is she said no problem. People moan about their mother-in-laws but mine is great, as are the rest of my in-laws & it’s a real shame that I rarely see them. After a short while I went out for a beer &amp; a curry with  Big Bro  & his wife (another Czech bride!) &amp; their friend  The Bodyguard . It was a nice couple of hours & a welcome distraction. I settled into my airbed just after midnight &amp; here I am. I can’t sleep. Like a child on Xmas eve I’m just too excited. In a matter of hours I will have to stand in front of TV cameras & a panel of judges (presumably including Simon Cowell) &amp; sing for my future. I know I’ll be nervous but I have enough confidence in my ability to think that I’ll get through this first round. That said I’m not going to be complacent. I will go in there & sing my very best. I’ve been trying to keep my feet on the ground but I cant help wondering where it  could  all lead. All I’ve ever wanted to do since I was a child is sing. I adore singing &amp; it’s my dream to be able to make a living by singing. This cheesy TV talent show could just lead to that dream coming true. When I was a kid I just assumed that I would become a famous singer. Ever since I sang the lead in “Joseph & the technicolour dreamcoat” when I was 8, I knew I wanted to be on a stage with a microphone. Things seem to be going really well for me at present but if this goes well things could really take off. I really don’t think I’m gonna win the thing but If I could get to the latter stages &amp; gain some recognition then who knows?It’s now nearly 3am & I dare not even try to go to sleep. I set my alarm for 05:30 so I think sleeping now would be a big risk. So more coffee &amp; maybe a fag. Wish me luck. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OW! I had a quickie with  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  this afternoon. On completion of the deed I withdrew (as you do) to be confronted by blood & quite a bit of it. I asked if she had started her period; she hadn't. Then in horror I realised the blood was coming from my nob! Around this time the euphoria of orgasm faded & the pain kicked in, like I said:OW! After a tentative examination it appeared that I'd torn the little bit of skin between the foreskin &amp; the shaft. I later found out that this is known as "snapping one's banjo". Soon afterwards I phoned  Reckless  - who else would I turn to at a time like this than my best mate- I'm not sure what wisdom I expected him to have on the subject. He was a comfort though as you can imagine it was a cause for much hilarity. I later told  Funny Dance  too. Then tonight  The Duke Of Jokes  called me out of the blue, which was great. It's a source of great happiness to me that  The Duke Of Jokes  is back on the radar. I discussed it with him (amid much laughter) & he said that it had happened to him once. He said that I shouldn't worry too much but to "give it a week". Absolutely fucking typical, eh? I haven't needed the bloody thing for a year &amp; it goes &amp; breaks now! Poor  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth , bless, was quite worried. She feared it was somehow her fault. Joking aside the whole thing was quite a sobering experience to us both. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      News on the flat - a 2 bedroomed flat has become available & it's (touch wood) mine! If the housing association are to be believed I could even be in by the weekend, ace!  Do You Kiss Your Mum With That Mouth  is getting a bit full on, which is scary. so moving on would be a good thing although I have to say that my stay here has been a breeze. I'm starting to get quite excited about my audition on Monday. I think I'm gonna sing "Summertime", I know it'll impress &amp; it's not something I could cock up. Hopefully at the weekend I can get  Dream Girl  to help me with my "look". Had a bit of an e-bay relapse last night, bought 5 new tops. This is on top of the 8 tops i got from Temper Tantrum's Next catalogue. So I guess I'm alright for tops, eh? 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, here's the plan. I like to have a plan, sadly I rarely adhere to it, but I like to have a plan. In January of this year I started a diary/ journal. I'd been meaning to do it for years. This year though I have actually done it & I've stuck to it. So the plan is to post all of what has occured so far this year &amp; then take it day by day. However at the moment I'm a teeny bit drunk. It's Friday evening so I have to go & spend a considerable amount of time in the bathroom trying to make myself look presentable for the evening of drink &amp; debauchery ahead. Here's hoping it's gonna be a good un'!   Cheers.   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In fact it was so simple that now I sit a little perplexed. I assumed (a recurring failing) that it would take hours to get sorted & i could use that time to come up with some dazzlingly witty &amp; clever opening post that would instantly show me to be a total "geezer". Sadly, I now feel a bit silly. Welcome to my world. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>