<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Heyy! i almost didnt have time to ryte today but i did so it dunt matter ryte!?! well ne ways today i woke up n talked to Matt til my dad got home from golf then we went out to eat @ Steak and Shake and went to do a lil more skool shoppin since skool starts bac on friday :( but ne ways i got sum ne shoes! and a CD and 2 dvds and a couple outfits... then i got home n called Lauren and she came back over b*c she had to go and drop off wat she got shoppin!.. then we went and played sum "goofy" golf lol member Lauren those dudes told us thats wat we looked like we were playin lol! then we watched Cheech and Chong up in smoke THE BEST MOVIE EVER! lol... then we went to take a lil nap! and now were goin to watch secrete window...soo g2g Luv Yawl! Bye*Bye!   
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          Last nyte was cool i think me n my best friend kinda resolved our prolems which is really really good...but then i woke up the next morning and it totally sucked! 4 one my mom found sumthin of my brothers that myte get him in alot of trouble...actually it will and im not sure wat is gunna happen...then Jesse got mad @ me and i felt sooo bad..by the way if Jesse is reading this...i love yah and im sooo sorry...then i was supposed to go do sumthin with Matt but got in alot of trouble 4 a cell fone bill so im not doin nething tonyte...then i found out my brother isnt aloud to talk to his g/f ne more and i felt sooo bad for him...? but i guess i cant do ne thing about it...but ryte now im havin to be my dads lil slave b*c of the bill he got today he said i have to repay him $135 which is crap b*c i wasnt the only one who used it but oh well...but i g2g b*c my dad says i gotta go clean the pool table?? Luv Yawl...well most of yawl! Bye*Bye     
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey!..wat happened today?? well my lil cousin came over like a week ago n finally left today hes cool and everything but he was makin it so that i couldnt ever talk to Matt!! lol not his fault but.. yah know? then when he left i called matt! i finally got to have a good talk with him!! well i guess you could call it a good talk? but all we did was argue and yell @ each other...once we got past all that tho and kinda made me feel a lil better...but i dunno? i dunt think its gunna work out..? then i finally got to talk to Lacey! i was happy cuz i havent gotten to talk to her in a while n now im bout to go golf...augh i hate golf but we do live on a golf course so i gues si gotta get used to it? but ne ways g2g Luv Yawl...well most of yawl lol! Bye*Bye   
      
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       OKAY well to start off NOTHINGS goin on Saturday so STOP askin me i had nothing to do with ne of that and i dont want nething to do with it ne ways..! the whole things of cuz Matt told Nathan forget it.. cuz of Po Pos! lol.. and b*c hes not thickheaded like my dumbass brother lol but ne ways today was okay juss like ne other day... went to skool like every day.. it was gay other than the fights and everyone comin up to me sayin wats happenin Saturday and i juss kept sayin NOTHING! augh i have nothing to do with all that shit and i dont want nething to do with it.. but ne ways... when i got home from skool Jessica and Jane came over for a lil bit and hung out we had fun then we went over to there house to chill there and make plans for nothing... lol but ne ways i have to go and get some HW done b*4 its too late and finish talkin to Matt cuz i love him more than i love yawl! haha j*p but really i g2g Luv Yawl! Bye*Bye  
      
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey yawl all i can say about today is WOW lol long day i guess... THA WHOLE CAR PROBLEM ASHLEYS POS! lol haha it broke down! like 30 times lol.. o well i got from point A to point B finally juss took a LONG time lol then i came home from "skool" and chilled out for a lil and talked to Jesse and he doesnt love ne one ne more so.. oh well!?! i dont get that but hey w*e floats his boat! haha but ne ways then i talked to a few other ppl... Holly for a sec then Stefy! i love her! lol and miss her tonz! and tonz! .. sorry if this is gay but im so hyped up ryte now u juss dont understand! lol but ne ways.. then wetback (James for some of yawl who will prolly be like who wtf ) lol and Tyler came over and hung out and started stuff with matt and matt got all his "boys" which i dont get and got all mad @ me when i didnt even start tha stuff and nathan and Tyler start callin up boys and my rents heard them all gettin mad and told Nathan he wasnt leavin tha house and that if he did they would call the po pos so we couldnt do it tonyte.. but Saturday we will!... if yawl wanna come its Saturday in T-Town! my home town haha Tyrone for those of yawl who dont get it.. but yah @ the NEW baseball feilds... over there by.. uh i dunno kinda by Publics in Tyrone.. yawl can come if yah want.. its gunne be off tha chain! haha... but ne ways i gotta go call up a few ppl so i g2g! Luv Yawl..   
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey yawl wat to say bout today lets juss say it totally sucked and i felt like crap all day till i got home cuz then Allison (Mallory haha luv yah Allison!) and Mandy came over and we hung out then like 2 min after they showed up Matt came over and he hung out for a while and we had alot of fun we played pool and went to see Trey and then he had to leave... i love Matt and all but today wat he did was wrong.. Amanda agreed !... i wont go into details but juss belive me!.. Amanda thankz 4 talkin to me bout it.. luv yah girl... and now im juss sittin her talkin to Jerett and Amanda!... so i g2g Luv Yawl Bye*Bye  
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey! today was pretty fun i got to see Kara finally after all the screamin and yallin and cry we went through and we hang out all last night and juss watched movies and stuff then tha medicine i have to take makes me a lil.. i dunno fune so i was ready to go to bed so guess wat we went to bed lol then we woke up @ 2 lol then we hung out with Dustin (FUNE) long story but it was so fun then we made dinner for everyone and left to go to tha car show... @ tha car show there was a pink car that was sooo awesome u juss dont understand lol then we went in home depot and acted like idiots (Kara and tha choclate bar and tha toliet! haha then we went to khols and Ross and waited for Toni who never showed up then we met up with Becca and went to tha bowlin alley with her and Matt and met up with Whitney and went to Tonis and yelled @ him for a lil then 6 of us piled into a lil civic and rode back to tha bowlin alley and i saw Lauren!!! i was so happy i love her! then i got mad @ toni cuz he was ignorin me so we left.. forget that im not gunna put up with that! then i met my rents @ Eka and it was soo fune my dad and everyone but my mom we wasted and they were singin kareoke it was pretty fune my dad sung girls jus wanna have fun! then we came home and here i am talkin to my Best Bud In Tha Whole World!! Javeair so i g2g cuz i love him and miss him and i havent talked to him in FOREVER so Bye*Bye Luv Yawl.. oh yah Luv Yah Lori well get KK sooner or later!! thankz!  
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Heyy sorry again for not rytein yesterday but i was out of it the whole day i had to go to tha doc for those migranes i was havin and i had to get a shot of demeral and then i got two diff kinds of pain pills... i was out... then i came home and went str8 to sleep and woke up @ 10 and called back Tony and Zach and Kara then i went back to sleep and woke up this mornin and went to skool BLAH it was horrible i dunno know y maybe juss cuz i didnt feel good and i juss was down and were talkin bout skool i mean lol.. yah know and now im talkin to Jesse and Stef wat could be better? NOTHING lol cuz i love them so very much!!! but im gunna go b*c i want to go find plans for tonyte... LUV YAWL.. OH AND BY THA WAY HAPPY FRIDAY THA 13TH keep it real but be safe! Bye*Bye  
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey! sorry i didnt get a chance to ryte yesterday but i slept the minute i got home until 10 then i talked to Tony for and hour.... then i went back to sleep lol i didnt wake up til this mornin then i went to skool and it sucked soooo bad cuz i didnt feel good and i had to sing in first block and it sounded like crap cuz i didnt feel good and my troat hurts.. but ne ways then i went into my next class and i told coach i was like dont even ask me to do nething cuz im not doin it then i saw Tony and i was like yay and ryte now im waitin on my brother to get home hes in sooo much trouble b*c he hasnt been home yet or nething and my mom and dad are home and omg hes in so much trouble but thats okay more time on tha fone for me lol.. ne ways and im tryin to get this migrane to go away and chillin talkin to Tonye soo i g2g but i luv yawl!.. Bye*Bye   
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       OMG im soo scared but not really at tha same time cuz this gang is all out for me n shit but Jesse told me it would be okay so i guess it will be... thankz Jesse i luv yah!... but ne ways today was so PIMP i finally told Zach str8 up that i was sick of his shit and that i was tired of him grabbin me n shit it was so fune but then i went into chorus and it was pretty fune i fell off tha raisers then in home ec i was talkin to choach Flavin bout everything and he told me that he would talk to KK that man is soo cool then i saw Zach Waters i was soo happy! then i got home and it made my day even better cuz i got to talk to Jesse finally but i have to go if i want to talk to him Luv Yawl.. MOST!.. blah blah blah  
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey! sorry i didnt ryte yesterday me n Ashley and Holly were BZ all day! first they showed up and we went to get sumthin 4 lunch we had Arbys! then we came home to eat left again and went to drop off the other ashleys purse... and went to walmart to get a couple more things we needed for skool... then we went home and hung out n drew pics and then we left and we told my mom we were goin to get her some pepsi @ tha gas station which is only 5 min away from my house and we were gone for 2 hours we went to Fayetteville and i got to see stefanie then we went to tha pool hall so i could see wat was up with Matt and all cuz he hung up on me AGAIN! then i showed holly n Ashley where we recked.. ooo scary! then we came back here for like 20 min and we left again and god it was a LONG nyte we did everything we went and followed this girl around cuz Lori wanted to beat her ass then she tooks us to the projects of newnan (tha girl we were following) and she was meetin up with ppl that were gunna kill us and truit... i have no idea how to spell his name told us to get tha hell outta there so we did lol i dont think we stoped @ all and i think we ran like 4 stop signs lol then we went and called that girls cell and told her to meet up some where and we waited for like an hour so we left to look for her and went to wally world again and hung out for a lil bit and then ashley tru coke all over this girls car and keyed it OMG.... then we came back her and Ashley Ashley and Holly me n Nathan all left and went and rode around @ like 2 in tha mornin we went to waffle house and the play ground then we came back here and went to sleep but ri have to do chores cuz i got in trouble for bein up so late n wakin up my dad so g2g Bye*bye  
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey yawl! today was PiMp i mean i got to see al my friends which way really cool and i found out i have sum classes with a bunch of uperclassmen and my first block was pretty fune cuz theres alot of FreshMen and i was all messin with them about how tha class was so hard... were talkin bout mix chorus i mean comon lol but it was fune and another cool thing is its not like last year when my classes went from one side of tha skool to tha other there all like 4 rooms away from each other... but dang my skool is poor we dont even have agendas lol but my schedule is first block mix chorus 2nd block home ec...well its called nutrition and wellness but its really home ec all we do is cook... i didnt pick that class tho but i guess its cool? 3rd block i have World History and i have 2nd lunch and 4th block i have Algebra II... so its really gunna b easy.. but ne ways i juss got back from eatin @ Texas Road House n i saw Mal i wanted to see her sooooo bad today but i didnt then i saw her @ work lol it was kool and i saw Ashley and Holly! it was fun but there gunna be here in a min so im gunna go! Luv Yawl... MOST OF YAWL lol Bye*Bye  
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Today has been the worse day omg... first off i havent gotten to talk things out @ all with Matt and i hate doin that with ne @ all i dunno long story of y i juss do... then im juss i dunno wat i am bout this who Holly thingy that girl used to be my best friend.. wat went tru her head? b*c when i knew her she was the sweetest girl! ne ways then sum test came back not so good i would juss rather not talk bout it... so DONT ASK lol jp but really there not my test dont worry bout it lol and the thing that made today the worst was ITS MY LAST DAY OF SUMMER :( oh no! skool starts back tmrw and that sucks soo freekin bad but oh well but i have to go n str8in my hair so im ready to go tmrw... soo i g2g Luv Yawl...and yah know wat i say n those who i dont love know who they r lol Bye*Bye  
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey! sorry i havent been able to tell yawl was goin on but ive been in Tyrone 4 3 days with mah gurl KT and juss been hangin out yah know same ol same ol lol  AND IT WAS MIKES B*DAY!! YAYA HAPPY 18TH BIRTHDAY SWEEETY! but ne wats i came over Monday nyte and we stayed up til 5 in tha mornin and 6 guys came over to her window total that nyte we had fun and i got to see my b*f (well he was when i saw him @ least) and Mike and Erick and Joe and Randall and Josh rode by... then that nyte Matt called me and we broke up :( but oh well cuz wat i did was wrong but i guess all i can do is say im sorry...so Matt if your reading this i still love u and im sorry... but ne ways then the next day we woke up and Mike and Matt came over for a lil and all it was was a nother fight about NO HUGS!! lol but oh well then they showed us sum pics we didnt want to see.... but then they left w*o ne hugs! lol and me n Kate rode tha go cart lol haha that was fune! then Mike came back over to see us cuz he luvs us lol and he made up for not giving us hugs! lol then  KT was supose to come over and we were gunna go hang out with Mike but her daddy said NO! but oh well we went to her color gaurd practice...BOO NOO FUN! lol but i did get to see sum ppl from SC that i missed! so that was cool then we left there @ like 9:30 10... and got to her house n looked tru year books that was fun and went to sleep and woke up round like 11 and i felt like it was freekin 1 or sumthin cuyz i had soo many dreams haha member KT fightin that bitch! haha but ne ways lol thats sooo fune then here we r now up @ tha library and ill be @ KT til like 6:30 or so.. but i g2g! Luv Yawl.... well most of yawl yah know tha story lol Bye*Bye  
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        WOW its been a nother long day today sucked soo bad...Matt im soo sorry i didnt mean it that way but the way things were goin i dunt know nvm...ill talk to u when u call me tonyte...all i did all day was clean for a punishment cuz of that cell fone bill and then i tried to talk to Enjoli today but her dad answered and was like yeah ill tell he ru called n juss hung up...WTF?? but ne ways ryte now im waitin on Jesse to get on tha net cuz i really really need to talk to him... and waitin on matt to call and the fone juss rang soo g2g Luv Yawl! Bye*Bye   
      
</post>


</Blog>