<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i feel pretty damn proactive. i made a blog magiger. plus its not even past 12 yet. so yeah go me. i dont really know how much i'll write in it but we'll see. so if my limited amount of friends who know about this read it, well it'll rpobably be post midnight rants. wich is when (all of you should know by now) i go crazy.....or sew. i cant spell i can already ssee a million mistakes but guess what im too lazy to fix em.... so yeah that's it, ig otta do laundry.....damnit!  I HATE COMPUTERSSS I JSUT DELELTED TEH WHOLE HALF OF MY BBLOG FUCKERERER!!!!!!!!!  figures i'd start the my blog with something angry.....      
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i found out today that one of the horses i ride at lackshmis is being put down tomorow. she has melenoma. she's the biggest sweetest horse there, and though i've never been able to put her bridle on myself(cause she lifts her head up so high that u cant reach it) and even thouhg she's stomped on my feet a million times she's ma favorite. she's a brute but seh doesnt mean to be she's jsut HUGE. and she's soo amazing to ride becasue she's so responsive. when u sratch her lower belly she sticks her head up and her lip starts to quiver. adn if you give her a bath she'll drink right from the hose. she'll also half break down her door if you dont give her grain first. not to mention that she fight alots with the other horses wich can be a really nerve racking experience wehn your riding her. i think she's even kicked emily in teh leg before because she missed the horse emily was riding. of course it was my fault casue i wasnt watching her... every animal has their own personality, you just have to look for it, but with horses they usually make it pretty obvious what their like. Tory is big beutiful witch and was also very loving in her own way. if you stand next to her she'll almost knock you over by scratching her head on your back. anyways these are the things i think about most when i think of tory. i really love her adn i'll miss her alot. but she's in pain now so its not like its a pointless death. she had a wonderful life with lackshmi too. i'm going to see her tonight. 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      POEPLE SUCK yeah thats right YOU! u know what i despise on top of everything? MSN not that i have the willpower to stop signing on. just poeple are WIERD on msn there all shifty adn distorted if that makes any sense. plus its next to impossible to figure out weither their joking or not. i cant count number of conversations i've had that turnedinto unpleasant things becasue of misinterpretation. or maybe my friends jsut dont knwo me adn i dont know them... hmm nah i blame msn ANYWAYS yes teh amazing thing thast really been making me smile for the past week, more then any plans wiht friends at all, is.... (corny drum role pleasse) my new mic and acid music cd! HAHAHAHHA oh the joy. this is teh part wehre i go a bit psycho out of antisipation. see the mic is a mic(wich i proudly installed myself even with my computer illiteracy(is that a word?)heh i jsut put bracekts in brackets... yeah um yeah before i sound ireversibly stupid wich i think is ahrd ot avoid at the moment(even if i ahve a backspace key!) ahh enough with teh brackets... ok breathe calm. ok what im trying to say in my many fumbled words is that i can now record guitar playing on the computer and make a cd. wich is amazingly exciting becasue i LOVE guitar. now im jsut waiting for one day of empty house ness and i can start. hurray for me yeah i think ill rethink the whole going psycho next to a computer thing next time casue i dont think the majority of that made sense, but oh well! 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      toaday i wandered around aylmer with a group of friends. we went bowling and spent at least 2 minutes fiddling with the computer to put our names in. we ended up having the most childish names ever, but it felt great to be laughing at something simple. it was also cool to actually be bowling for once. i mean bowling is usually my coverup story. i only really go bowling about once or twice a year, i guess cause i've never actually enjoyed it that much. toaday we had alot of fun though. there was a fair amount of throwing slush around and name calling. the kind of stff that u would feel like a child doing in front of an arena full of retiered bowlers. but there wasnt anyone but us there toaday, not that i think it would have made us stop if there was. i think my favorite part was that we were there for about an hour laughing about stupid shit, but not one of teh jokes revolved around some hung over story or some day of being stonned. we were jsut being stupid and it was fine at that. it msut seem pretty dumb really but i cant remember a better bowling outing. after that we wandered around aylmer and sat in this littel kiddys park for awhile. we didint really have anything to do but it was nice to jsut sit there and veg. later on we decided it would be fun to go to mike's and make him kraft dinner for wehn he finally woke up(it was around 4 by then) unfortuantely he woke up before we were done and we had to try and hide in the side room beside the kitchen. though he wasnt really pissed to find 6 people randomly in his house cause we promised to clean his kitchen adn make him food. then we had our little tea party adn half of us had to go home. i ended up sepnding the rest of the night wandering around with sam adn gladys. overall it was really relaxing day.but as much as my day was fun i cant help but feel upset now. it pisses me off cusae i wanna jsut be able to leave a fucking happy entry without feeling like im leaving anything substanciel out. but whatever if i'm not in a good mood im not gonna pretend i am on my own fucking blog. i had alot of fun yeah, but near the end we started talking about more serious crap and it got me thinking about things. we were tlaking about how people that went threw hard times in their lives either turned out to be really amazing people or jsut plain fucked up. wich i think is completly true but i dont think its really that simple. i mean u can become an amazing person after a hard childhood, but those scares stick with u and they often end up tainting your life. and though it seems unfair that alot fo teh great people we've met have suffered i kinda wonder weither they would be great people without that suffering. somehow i dought it. i mean do you think that they cuold apreciate life as much as you need to to be kind and respectful to others if they have never seen the bad parts of life? i would consider myself a good person but i dont think i've necesarily been threw alot. but then again that in itself is questionable because my life compaired to some of my friends would leave em feeling pretty lucky but still the hard parts i have gone threw at the time were a big deal to me. i dont really think you can compaire your hardships becasue each persons problems affect them differently. i'm not saying you have to go threw hell to be a good person, i jsut mean that i think its alot easier for someone who has at least seen and learnt from hard experiences to appreciate how great life can be then it is for someone who has had everything handed to them on a golden platter. but on the other hand its also easier for the people who have suffered to see jsut how terrible life can be. i guess if you think about it in that way, its the saddest people who have teh most potential happyness. but then again maybe im jsut over complecating things. becasue i do find that in the end everyone is going to think what they want about life, weither good or bad and weither becasue of good or bad experiences. i guess it just has to do with how open you are to life and how you choose to interpret things. well thats my little blurble. goodnight 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      YES! i started off my day pretty pissed cause i was gonna have to do chores and thast all i'd be doing all day but now thnigs are lookign up! i guess i must sound jsut a bit psycho to be accited over sewing but whatever i like it. it calms me down for some reason and it feels great to be making something. so anyways i talked to gladys and she's coming over and im gonna sew all day. i mean i still have to do my chores..... but at least i ahve soemthing to look forward to. fuck im starting to dout that chores everyday if worth teh money im making cause i think  staying at home is making me really miserable. its not that i hate my parents or anything like that its jsut that theys tart to get to me. or at least my mom does.. not that she means to. anyways she's off holidays now so i get to be the only one cleaning the hosue, wich is alot easier. my dad starts his holidays tomorow though. seems kinda odd that he'd take holidays right when my mom's were done but whatever. my dad is easier to get along with lately though so chores will be easier. but anyways that wasnt the point! my point was that im gonna sew all day. i really wanna make this amazing purple shag coat. it'll be great everyone i know will end up walking 2 metres behind me to avoid being seen with THE COAT. not that i think my friends will acutually do this but thast how amazingly ugly the coat is gonna be. there gets to a point were somthing is just SO ugly thast its great.  i love it when that happens with clothes. when ur shopping for fabric but u dont know what u wanna make its alwasy teh best idea to look for the cheapest nasty colors, like teh green and yellow plaid bits. ok i think tis unhealthy how im going on and on about this, and gladys is gonna be here any minute probably so i guess i should start chores. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      events of the day: 1) waking up and disecting a mango 2) cleaning spice jars with crusty yellow shit on them 3) cleaned bird cages, wich includes being hissed at and shat on 4) weeded the garden while listening to randow cd i got from leahs mom 5) sat at computer  overall sentiment of the day: cranky and somewhat feeling like a bad person..  solution: eating complete container of humus and disgusting amounts of organic chocoalte sauce HURRAY!!! have a good day:)   
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      im starting off writting this blog not really knowing what i wanna say. i mean i could jstu write about the past few days and stuff, but somehow i dont really feel like it. well thast not really true i gues i jsut dont feel like writting all teh details. but teh basics are that i slept over at leahs house wiht her and drew. what made it memeborable is two things, first of all i dont see leah as much as most other of my friends so wehn i do see her its always a good thing, but second of all cause its the first time i really jsut hung out wiht her and drew. he's a very important part of her life, and i can tell he's an awesome person so it was good to be able to ahng out without things being awkward, especially since we all had alot of fun. anyway, though i dought u'll be reading this leah thanks to both of u for an awesome time.  i'm cooking this egg plant thingy in teh fire, n im guessing tis gonna turn into a yucky sludge as msot of my vegan concoctions do soooooooooo i better go check on it. WELL the foods not cooking at all, so im giving up adn eating chips. adn a mago, thanks to maya... 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      right now im sitting in teh living room basically dreading the inevitable wich is my unability to sleep. but over in the hall my sis is laughing, well its not really laughing its like laugh talking. it's hard to explain unless u know jaz, her voice gets more high pitchy n u can tell she's really enjoying herself. if u dont know her it could almost sound like she's upset. anyways, my point to this is that i love it wehn my sister does that. i dunno it always makes me smile. its defenitly my favorite part of having her home with her friends. i was reading my cousin emi's blog and she was talking about how she's glad she is working with jaz at cinnabon, n i dunno i thought i kinda wanted to write about my family for a bit. i really havea  great family. lately i've been hangning out with jaz n em more and i've been thinking about how its not really everyday that people can get along so well with their family like that. their honestly some of the best friends i have. i dont wanna sound all sappy and shit, i jsut apreciate the fact that their great people.    
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      aint it great when ur talkign to people on msn late at night to ahve something to do and tehn all the convos hit a dry spell and ur just sitting there wondering why your not sleeping, but you know its cause u cant sleep and ur trying to avoid boredome that'll drive you insane, wich doesnt relly matter casue that wholea ttempt was in vain anyways cause here u are bored adn insaen writting in ur blog.....  the funny thing about boredome is that its teh only time my mind is clear. but i guess in this case thats not a good thing, casue a clear mind mixed with tierdness only measn that im gonna be thinking about shit i dont really wanna think about and i lsot my train of thought. there u have it. 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      you wanna hear something really funny? well of course you do, ok well wehn i wasmaking my blog i decided to not be a looser with an unimaginative user name n stuff, so i decdied to use the dictionary. right now my username is the omnisciently brainless wich is a contradiction casue omnisciently means to know all, but the thing is as u probably have already figured out if ur ready my stupid blogs is that i cant spell so each time i decided to sign on i ahve to either spend 10 minutes tryign to write that stupid word or get the damn dictinary. so much for my intelegence. yeha u know what medulla means? something aobut the inside of a vein or somethig. so i was reading my sisters livejournal and she was saying how our mothers music wasnt allowing her to write, which was the whole point to this post cause i completly agreeded wiht her adn im bored so i thouhg i'd write about that unintersting fact, but then i spent 10 minutes trying to sign in and i ended up having to go into my account where teh music does not play to get inot my blog becaseu i have the remember me thingy. so now theres no music for me to comment one, which leaves me nothing to comment on except my own stupiddity adn teh fact that while iw as dooing all this zahra signed off of msn so now i cant talk to her.... moral of the storymy mothers "sade lover rock" cd, does not allow me to spell. and to further prove to u how dumb i am i jsut took the cd out of the computer to figure out what cd it was and put it back in causing it to play....adn haunt me some more. 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      it seems to be becoming a tradition that every time i write a long post the computer fucks up and i loose it..... but instead of getting amd and pitching a rock threw the monitor i decdied to stay calm and to  rewrite it all.. sooo......  i just got back from joannas three day party at her farm. it was great, though i am now stinky and full of shit n itchy bumps. i played this 4 hour long truth or dare game with gladys, gavin and warwick wich was pretty haalrious especially wehn we found out warwick would rather fuck a sheep then fuck gavin.... i dunno if that says someting about gavin or the sheep.. but anyways. now i really want a turkey even though my aunt says there loud and obnoxious not to mention humongous when they grow up. befreo teh farm i had this girls ngith out with a bunch of ym firends i havent seen for a while. it was great, i got free food at tuckers market cause all i could eat was plate full of vegetables and pickles(wich beleive me i took advantage of) and those little red chemicaly cherries that take three days to digest. anawys after hanging out for a while teh last few of us headed b ack to my hosue cause it was raining. my horseback riding teacher was over for a barbecue, so i went outside to say hi. when i got outside all teh adults seemed surprisingly mellow and shit so i kinda figured out what they ahd been doing all ngiht(and why my mom ahd told me to not come home) the ash tray of rollies and crumbs didint really make it hard to guess either. HAHA it was all really funny espicially casue i asked my mom about it later and she went on about how it as home grown and mild and shit. i dont think that she gets that i dont really care as long as she's not lying about it. well now i'm off to see a movie so its time to wash the turckey stench away 
      
</post>


</Blog>