<Blog>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       My day started out nice with me waking up early and finally checking out that church on Main street. The pastor was Korean and the congregation composed of eh, non Koreans, mainly elderly people (black, white, whatever). Yes, an interesting and rare combination. He had organized the sermon to the best of his abilities and he seemed really sincere. And I can tell that he's a praying man but Dr. Keller is still worth traveling to the city.
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       So, no e-mail from dave-o. He sucks! That's right! You suck, man! There must be tons of guys out there who would so~ wanna go out with me! Eh, I curse you to end up with a mean, mean biotch!
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       After confirming from Joe Tieng that Dave definitely did not write a reply that sounded inviting, I felt depressed and extremely rejected. I mean, it's not like I was head-over-heels or love-at-first-sight with this guy. In fact, I thought he was pretty funny-looking. But his profuse apologies of not being a good host or something, gave me the impression that he liked me. Otherwise, why on earth would he apologize that many times? And, he seeked me out via Friendster! Well, it ain't even back to "square-one" because I gave up on the male gender ever since I was afflicted with E.     
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is literally freezing in the factory office. If the outside temperature is 21 degrees, it's at least a good 15 degrees less in the concrete structure. So yes, I am typing away with my reluctant fingers. And despite the small heater they have provided me, it doesn't warm me up too much. Come summer, this concrete building will turn into an oven, hotter than the outside temperature.     I hope I'll be able to work full-time at the firm instead or maybe dear grandma will send me to skool. There's so many things I want to do. Blogging reguarly is one of 'em.     I started on this book called "Women's Lives" and last night, I fell asleep wishing I had more time to at least finish the chapter I was working on. This book has been eyeopener in the sense that there were examples of women who were experiencing the very same things I was. The most intriguing of 'em all was about being a single woman. As a Christian, sex is out of the question because it belongs to the marriage bed. However, it's so tempting because I had a taste of it. Wish it wasn't like this.   
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Around noon Tony immed me and the conversation lasted for nearly 3 hours.  I so regret not copying the dialogue but here's the gist of it:    It started off with what our individual plans for the weekend would be.  He was going to hit the mall again with his buddies for a movie and I was planning to work since it was crunch time for the Expo.  Then he suggested that I work more on him.  So I asked how.    Him: You really wanna know?  Me: Start talking.  Him: Start off with a kiss...   ...  
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To the woman who is otherwise known as my mother:    Bitch, you have managed to screw up my life yet again.  How do you live with yourself knowing that you botch your children's life like this ALL the time.  Thanks to you, unless we find an accountant willing to help us out, I'll never get that extension on my visa.  Do you  even realize what this means?  Eventually, I won't be even able to drive!    I hate you so much that I'm at the office at two in the morning, just to get away from you and your miserable shit.  You're nothing but a selfish troublemaker.  I'm just sick and tired of taking care of all the shit you put me through.    And for God's sake, stop dealing with all those ShinKwang poop heads.  We've been burned enough.  Do you have to drag me into it too?  You and your "Godly" ways.   
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know if it's because my period is coming up but I've been so horny all week.  I am literally starving for sex -- the raunchy kind.    If Tony does follow me to Vegas here's what I plan to do:  I'm gonna check-in first into the hotel and take a hot shower prepping myself to be surveyed by his tongue.  Since it's gonna be MGM, I'll just put on the hotel bathrobe when he's about to arrive at the door.  As soon as I open the door, my arms brazenly thrown around his neck, I press myself against him and whisper, "Hey babe."  And immediately I pull him inside and lock the door.  With the door behind my back, I approach him slowly and he's probably smiling nervously.  My hands quickly go to work in unbuttoning his polo shirt and I help him take it off.  Bewildered, he'll comply; I doubt he'll say no.  The boy's been trapped in Oklahoma training for the army for almost half a year albeit sexually repressed.  He probably can't get any privacy in the rooms or the showers even if he wanted to masturbate.    Once the shirt's off, my lips latch onto one of his hardened nipples and he moans in delight.  Then I trail my tongue upwards toward his neck and suck and lick until he moans again.  Meanwhile Tony unties my robe and cups my breasts and one hand starts to trail towards my ass.  As he finally fondles my ass, I unzip his cargo shorts and let 'em drop on the floor all the while making my marks on his well-defined chest.  I then quickly pull his boxers down and feel his warm penis poking my stomach.  At this point, I get on my knees and pull the shorts all the way down and lick the tip of the head.  He gasps and before he can relish that moment, I take his thick penis into my mouth and start sucking the dripping precum.  Licking his penis as if it was some lollipop, he's in ecstasy.  By this time, Tony's hands are cupping my face and he starts thrusting himself  into my mouth.  I take his penis in as far as I can.  But I don't want him to come just yet.  So I withdraw my mouth and get on my feet and push him on the bed.  Though Tony is six feet and 195 pounds of manliness, he's easily knocked off from his stance.    I get on top of him and start planting kisses from his forehead but never his lips.  The kisses trail down to his manhood and I reach for the condom near the bedside table.  I carefully tear the packaging and quickly encase his penis and force myself onto him.  The initial entrance is painful but in no time, I start straddling him.  His hands reach for my breasts and from there one of his hands makes way to my neck and eventually a finger starts tracing my lips as I pounce on him.  I then hungrily suck that finger and just then he positions me on my stomach with his weight fully pressing against me, his limbs immobilzing mine, he starts sucking my neck from behind.  When he reachers my ear, he pants, "I want to fuck you from behind."  I melt, somewhat touched that he knew I wanted to be fucked like that without me saying a word of it.  So I lift my ass and he starts pounding me and I moan in delight.  As I relish the pleasure, I only pray that it doesn't stop.  Eventually I call out his name and beg him to don't stop and fuck my brains out.  And Tony, the man that he is, stays hard until I come shuddering.  Then he releases himself and comes as well.    We both collapse on the bed; him on top of me and I am in bliss feeling the aftershocks.  Shortly thereafter, Tony regains his erection and penetrates me from a missionary position without a condomn.  My vaginia doesn't protest and clings to his penis, never wanting to let go of that rod.  He says he's about to come again citing that he can feel me grabbing onto him.  "But not yet, babe.   Kneel again."  Soon he's banging me doggy style and I'm loving every moment of it.  My juices are flowing and I just want his penis to stay hard forever.  Finally Tony pulls his penis out and comes on my back.  I collapse on my stomach and Tony despite being tired takes a towel nearby and wipes the come off my back.  I stroke his hair lovingly because of the said subtle gesture.  Soon we embrace and my lips slightly brush against his.  Shortly after I trace his lips with my tongue and I feel him shudder in pleasure.  I then press my lips full on against his and that's when he invades my mouth with his tongue.  His tongue explores the cavity of my mouth and soon our tongues are wrestling and our bodies are grinding against one another.     ...  
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been thinking all day, trying to analyze boy and the role he plays or has been playing for the last two weeks.  urlLink Good radio station , hormones settling down, and mentally comparing his behavior with my platonic male friends helped clairfy the situation.  I'm afraid I'll have to admit that the boy has very little interest in getting to know me as he claims. I believe he only wants me to reveal my desire for him, not necessarily everything about me. Yes, I may be getting ahead of myself. However, even without confirmation, instinct tells me that whatever we have will be short-lived. Not that there's anything wrong with him; we're just not compatible. We have similar interests or tastes but the end result will be just like my previous relationships: he's not the type to stand by and support me. Rather, he needs somone who will play the supportive role.  I understand that he requested vacation and it's been almost a month since application. However, brooding incessantly only exacerbates his "inane" state. And I can empathize that monotonous work and isolation can drive one crazy. However, I don't have the energy to attend to his "needs," and I wonder if tables were to be turned if he'd even considering reciprocating the same.  The conclusion is that though we want to gratify our repressed sexual desires, we don't and can't think beyond that. And that, eventually, can only lead to trouble.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      him: so, what are you wearing today? me: a dress me: long one though him: i bet you look nice in it me: that's what i try to tell myself him: what's underneath the dress? him: hehe me: no bra me: i don't like wearing bras me: unless it's absolutely necessary him: hehe him: will you wear one when we meet? me: depends me: if i wear a dress, most likely no him: i see him: are you wearing panties though? me: o yea me: it's a must him: is it sexy panties? me: no... me: cotton pack from bj's him: woohoo him: you don't like wearing thongs? me: never tried him: do you own any? me: plus my butt doesn't look that great me: nope him: haha him: we'll have to go to Victoria's Secret get some him: you can try them on for me in the dressing room me: or we can make-out in the dressing room him: i like your thinking him: we cna do more than make out in the dressing room me: i can get pretty creative him: i bet you're a wild one in the sack me: or a wannabe me: u be the judge him: hehe him: so, is that an invitation? me: ah u know want me him: that's good English there me: typo me: well at least i know i want to get to know u him: hehe him: true that  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Signed into msn messenger, hoping to talk to boy. I missed talking to him. But Boy wasn't on. Not a second later, boy signs in. Or rather, I think, he makes himself visible.  Would have pasted the dialogue but it was no arousing material.  I asked him how he spent his Sunday and he hardly paid any attention to the question. I wanted to subsequently ask him why he didn't call but I figured since he didn't hit the malls yesterday as he usually would, it's either because (a) he's saving his money or (b) he started losing interest in me. So for conversation's sake, I rambled on about my newfound love -- stretchercise. And that got him to come back to earth commence an exchange of our thoughts on oral sex.  Yes, Christian guys like oral sex too. Duh. They're just not as outspoken as others. But they have no problem at all doing the nasty with me. Morals are put on hold while they fuck me.  Speaking of which... I'll be going home to pleasure myself very shortly... Can't wait to pinch my nipples and finger-fuck. I so wanna experience that oozing come but it has yet to happen. Perhaps with diligent practice, it wil materialize and shoot forth.  Anyhoo, I'm not as intensely into him as before. But if he's around, we'd definitley fuck. But then again, sex is always better if u're really into him. I feel lonely now...  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's something about Ritz peanut butter sandwiches. I finished half of the box. Yes, the no-no for the health-conscious or rather weight-conscious. It's worse than rat poisoning, they say.  The consumption took place while viewing an exercise video:     Instead of following the well-conditioned instructor, I decided to look for and catch any editing mistakes. And guess what? I found one! Most likely inadvertently she got ahead of herself and did the wrong move. And the  urlLink GAIAM  editors probably thought nobody would notice! Well, take that,  urlLink GAIAM ! Otherwise, and overall, it's a good stretchercise. I'm serious. I highly recommend it. It's gonna help me be limber in case Tony and I do the nasty.  Speaking of which... The boy didn't call. Since we met online, I'm starting to think I'm setting myself up for disappointment. I have tried to rationalize that  urlLink Friendster  is just like any meet market -- e.g. a bar. But upon examing my personal history with online dating, it's been proven again and again to be a bust.  No worries. I'm not treading new territory here. Loneliness is ingrained to my inner core and we get along just fine. My other friend Masturbation is always there to cheer me up.  Speaking of which... I always had my panties on. Yes, weird. But that's how it's been. I have used it as a barrier to keep my fingers relatively clean or dry.  After seeing the instructor swaying her pelvis to-and-fro, I got horny. Not only did she look amazing for a mother of two, but I wanted to try those moves myself -- in a more pleasureable way.  Ever since  urlLink the bathroom incident , I have finally started to experiment with touching my sex with bare fingers! And it has been fantastic! Of course, bare finger-fucking ensued and for the first time in my life, I think I had the sort of orgasm where you're trying to catch your breath. I was well spent.  I know, I know. The other day I said I wasn't horny anymore. Well, I lied. Or rather, my body did.  Anyhoo, I didn't think of anyone while doing the deed. I was just enjoying the new sensation and came to a calm conclusion afterwards to just see the affair without much expectation.  In other news, I'm starting to develop some serious interest in  urlLink Barack Obama . I so~ wanna read his memoir but not the republished ones. I want the first edition printed back in '95. But Amazon isn't much of help in procuring the gem.  Anywayz, he's handsome and what really makes him hot is that he's very intelligent. I love a man who knows how to talk and really values transcendentalism. I think transcendentalism is the key to unlock anyone's potential. And Obama mastered it. I think he will be the first black President. Hopefully I'll be eligible to vote by then.  In related news, Mother has managed to get an accountant from Shinkwang or Moses' dad to do the dirty deed. Looks like I won't have to get married. Relief yet I know that this will cost me somehow. It looks like as though I will never escape the grasps of Shinkwang. Hopefully everything will turn out well and I'll be granted the extension.  Though I haven't been doing much productive work, for the first time in my life, I'm starting to feel like I'm accomplishing something. I'm excited about the  urlLink Expo  and about the endless possibilites  urlLink the company  can tread. I just need to get off my butt now...  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As of today and now, desire has subsided. The only thing I want now is some sleep.  Tony read the excerpt but didn't say much about it over the phone. I was mentioning how I felt the piece needed more tweaking. "Well, you're not going to publish it or anything, right?" His response then undermined my confidence and of what little interest left of writing such material in the future. Perhaps the change in chemistry of the hormones is to blame but I started to wonder if it was a mistake to share it with him. This also made me realize that I may not be not good at taking criticism. In addition, I started to evaluate the viability of our relationship -- if there even was one to begin with.  I'm sure we'll hang out a lot in the beginning but after he gets stationed in Korea, I doubt that he'll be diligent in keeping in touch. A lot can happen within a year and I may eventually lose interest as well. But for the record, I did relish in the thought of being Mrs. Park. Moments like this are fleeting. A crush can easily turn into loathing.  But whlle I was in my lovey dovey crush mode, I thought about getting hitched in Vegas with Tony. Though I wouldn't mind  urlLink Little Church of the West , since it's Vegas I want some pizzazz! Don't know about him but I think the  urlLink Stratosphere  would be ideal. Especially their Thrill Ride Weddings. Afterwards we'd dine at Top of the World. For dessert, our entourage will be treated to this luscious cake made by  urlLink Freeds Bakery :     I think it reflects me very well...  Then we'd have to hit Crazy Armadillo for some oysters and drinks or any clubs would do. I think our guests would be itching to imbibe large quantities of alcohol. And I love~ playing a good hostess; I think I'm also getting good at playing "house."  I thought about having my friend deputized or obtain a temporary certificate to perform the ceremony but I wasn't sure he'd do it. Beside the fact that it isn't a breezy procedure -- although  urlLink obtaining the marriage license  is -- Chang would probably protest it. Chang is studying to be ordained in California and he might actually frown on Vegas weddings citing that it's unbiblical in the sense that it's a sacred union that shouldn't be handled so lightly.  But I'm serious about marriage. I just want it to be fun and memorable and enjoy the moment with people I hold dear. Not with some random strangers which will be the case if I let my mother run the show. It would end up being a boring big-fat-Korean church wedding where anybody is invited to partake in the so-called "sacred" ceremony. And why on earth would I wanna invite hundreds of strangers and foot the bill?  Funny how I can whip up stuff like this from a crush. It might even be just lust. But it feels a bit different this time. *cough* I promise.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>