<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Being a woman is pretty difficult, I think. I have centuries of stereotypes weighing down on me – preconceived notions that women are emotional and crazy and needy and weak. Being an intelligent woman is even harder, though, because I know that women are emotional and crazy and needy and weak. It’s a daily battle for me to balance my rational thoughts against my God-endowed ability to let emotion rule my every action.  I think in most cases I do a pretty good job. But emotion tends to win over more often than not if alcohol is involved.  Now, because I work at a bar and date a rum enthusiast, the battle is even tougher.  One night Christopher and I walked down the street to a recently opened bar where a friend of his was bartending. This place was not my usual type of hang-out. The featured music was tinny European techno spun by a dj and there was a $7 cover at the door. Not to mention the fact that I was not particularly fond of this female friend of his.  At this point, we hadn’t been dating very long, and, as is my usual rule, I was pretty open about letting him do whatever he wanted and keeping a safe distant from any sort of controlling behavior on my part. The rational side of me likes to just try and have a good time enjoying a new boyfriend’s company as opposed to being all uptight and clingy, at least until the boundaries of the relationship are set. Usually, with luck, I can continue being laid back as the relationship progresses. And I’m normally not a jealous person. I have no problem, for example, that he subscribes to an adult DVD rental program and that I regularly find titles like “Cum Swapping Sluts” in his DVD player. I am not stupid and I realize I am not the first girlfriend he has, so I generally don’t get upset when he mentions previous indiscretions. And most of my close friends are men, so I take it in stride that several of his close friends are women.  So here is how my internal dialogue was going on this particular night:   Emotional me : “I really do not like Christopher’s friend. They seem too close. Plus, she’s very cute and she’s, like, a size 2.”   Rational me : “God, don’t be so insecure. You spend practically every night at his house. Don’t you think you’d know if he was fucking around on you? Besides, even if he wanted to, when would he have the time? He spends all his free time with you, happily.”   Emotional me : “I know, but I don’t trust her. One time, he was wearing this really cool shirt, and when I told him I liked it he said she’d bought it for him. That  bitch .”  This conversation continued as I continued to down Myers’ and cokes. Pretty soon, I was very intoxicated and my rational voice was being drowned out by my emotional voice. I got up and walked through the ridiculously crowded dance hall to find him.  “Hi hon,” he said. “You’ll never guess what happened. This girl just walked up to me and offered me some pussy.”  Already emotionally tattered, that comment opened my drunken floodgates.  “Why do you say things like that to me?” I asked, tears starting to stream down my face. “Don’t you realize how inconsiderate that is? Don’t you think about things before you say them. “Hi hon,” he said. “You’ll never guess what happened. This girl just walked up to me and offered me some pussy.”  Already emotionally tattered, that comment opened my drunken floodgates.  “Why do you say things like that to me?” I asked, tears starting to stream down my face. “Don’t you realize how inconsiderate that is? Don’t you think about things before you say them? You always say shit like that to hurt my feelings.”  Before he could respond I turned around and hurried to the ladies room, already feeling like I’d made a scene but happy that I’d stood up for myself. As I wiped my face and tried to regain my composure, another girl walked into the restroom.  “Would you like a free sample of this energy drink we’re promoting,” she asked me, clearly not aware that I was in the middle of a self-imposed crisis. Still, eager for a distraction, I turned to her and said yes. She handed me a class bottle with a twist top.  I looked down at it. The bottle was decorated with a drawing of a modern-styled pin-up, this buxom girl with an impossibly tiny waist. Then I turned the bottle over and looked at the label.   urlLink “Sum Poosie,”  it said. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I remember as a kid living in Oklahoma, all I’d ever think about was traveling. My great-grandparents lived on this spacious ranch in the panhandle of Texas, and when my family would go visit, I always wanted to go, not because I wanted to see the ranch, necessarily, but just because I wanted to travel.  I used to fantasize about seeing the ocean. The first time I saw it was when I was 13, and my family reunion was in Orange, Texas. After the reunion, my dad and uncle and aunt and cousins and I drove to the Gulf, and I remember, going over a hill, seeing the ocean for the first time and gasping with delight. In Houston now, other people always laugh at me and my love of Galveston and the Gulf, calling the town and the water nasty and polluted and stagnant. But as a kids growing up in landlocked Oklahoma, any salt water is still an ocean.  When I lived in Oklahoma I used to dream about leaving all the time. I used to think that one day I would escape and live on some unpopulated island with no electricity and spend all my free time at the beach. I’m a simple gal - I don’t need lots of material possessions. Just a hammock, sarong, swimsuit and shelter. I knew a guy who worked at a newspaper in the Virgin Islands, and entertained ideas of joining him. But I spent 23 years in Oklahoma, paralyzed by my family, a co-dependent mother who always made me believe I could never survive without her. Everything I had ever known existed in Oklahoma, and I was afraid to leave my cozy little shell.  Now don’t get me wrong. I was by no means sheltered. I knew life existed beyond the Red River, and I desperately wanted to see it. When I was 16, I spent a few weeks in England and France, the first time I’d ever left the United States. The following summer I went to Greece and Italy, and in college I returned to England for a semester, spending my free time traveling the continent. I even tried to join the Peace Corps to help broaden my horizons, but, worried about my increasingly sick mother, I chickened out of applying.  I never gave any real thought to traveling because I didn’t know anyone else to travel with. That is the mentality of Oklahoma. “Everything you need is right here.” Some of the most interesting and brightest people I knew there were seemingly trapped, like I was, and sadly, still are.  What this all boils down to is that one day everything snapped. I was heartbroken and poor and lonely and sad and worrying about my Mom, who in turn was sucking every bit of emotion out of me. So I just left. I don’t know why I chose Houston, but for some reason it worked, and the past year of my life has been filled with more happiness and adventure than the previous 10, I think.  To celebrate this, I recently did something I’ve always wanted to do – I got certified to  urlLink scuba  dive. Now, next weekend, I’ll be taking my very first dive trip, to a place called the  urlLink Flower Gardens . It’s the northernmost reef in the Caribbean, and it’s only 100 miles or so off the coast of Freeport, Texas.  I can’t possibly describe how excited I am about this. I’ll sleep on the boat and dive about four dives a day. For a few short days I’ll be living this nautical life I’ve always fantasized about but never thought would ever be a possibility. There is a whole new world out there, and I’m about to explore it… 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’m a journalist who has worked at suburban newspapers for three years. I gradually began to realize that journalists, or writers for that matter, don’t make much money. So about a year ago I took a job as a bartender.  The bar I work at is in the  urlLink Rice Village  area of Houston, so a lot of our clientele consists of college students from  urlLink U of H  and  urlLink Rice . During the day, there are a lot of regulars and older business people. At night, it’s frat city. Especially in the summer, since college kids who attend Rice have even more discretionary income and usually don’t work.  The bar is called  urlLink Under the Volcano  and is named after a  urlLink book . The owners are  urlLink Argentinean . I took the job because I knew I could make fast and easy money. I also thought working there would expose me to a lot of interesting people that could later become characters for my stories. But I was already a little  urlLink misanthropic  to begin with. And after working in a bar full of assholes on my weekend nights, I’m even more so.  When I first started bartending, I remember telling myself, “Wow! These people act like idiots. I’m never going to drink again.”  Of course, that was a lie, but I’ve never learned more about how not to behave than I’ve learned from my customers.  I’ve often though that I should write a book about how to be a good customer at the bar. My short stint as a restaurant waitress also influenced that idea. Think about it. It’s simple supply and demand. I control the booze supply, and you want to get drunk. Be nice to me, and I’ll hook you up. Get on my nerves, and I’ll make you miserable. It’s like Curtis Mayfield said: “I’m your pusha man.”  Here is your guide to bar etiquette. Don’t piss me off.   Ten percent is minimum. Fifteen percent is great. Twenty percent is much appreciated. Anything above that says, “You did a good job, barkeep.”  Don’t give me random pocket change. Pennies may spend the same, but I hate them. Cheapass.  Tip according to the difficulty of the drink. I work at a bar where all our drinks are made from fresh squeezed juice and fresh ingredients. We make things like  urlLink mojitos , with fresh mint that has to be crushed in the glass, lime juice squeezed by hand with a press, and pure sugar. It takes about two hours to make a mojito, but about .5 second to pop the top off a Bud Light. A mojito would be 20 percent. A beer would be 10.  Round up. If you’re paying with a credit card and your tab is, say, $33, and you want to tip 20 percent, don’t give me $39.6. Just round it up to $40. What’s that extra .40 to you?  Don’t hit on me. Let’s settle the score here. Me: sober. You: drunk. Me: 1 point. You: zero. Besides, I don’t care how funny your drunk friends think you are, I’m sure whatever you have come up with I’ve already heard before. Now go away.  If you want to get my attention, please don’t wave your money in my face. I’m not a stripper.  On that same subject, when you tip me, please don’t fold your money  urlLink lengthwise , as though you're going to stuff it into my cleavage or down my ass crack. That’s gross. And don’t crumble your money into a tight, sweaty little wad. I don’t have to time to unwad your disgusting money because there are people behind you waiting for service.  At my bar, we get really busy on the weekends. Sometimes the bar is five or six people deep, all thirstin’ for an ice cool beverage. So, if you’re waiting in line, use your time wisely and try to decide what you want to drink before you get to the bar. Don’t stand there at the bar trying to make up your mind. If you don’t know what you want, I’m going to go on to the next person.  Order all at once. I don’t want to make three separate trips to the other side of the bar to get you three separate Bud Lights. Also, don’t change your mind mid-drink. That’s annoying.  Know how to make what you like to drink. If you want Grey Goose, for example, order Grey Goose and soda, not vodka and soda. And if you order an unusual shot or drink, knowing how to make it  includes  knowing proportions. Otherwise, I’ll just ask you what color the drink is supposed to be and make you something really nasty that’s the same color. Example:  Drunk frat boy:  “Uh, hi there hot stuff. Uh, yeah, I’ll take four Monkeys Fucking.”  Me  (bored): “I’ve never even heard of that drink. What’s in it?”  Drunk:  “I dunno, like Jager, Rumple and pineapple juice.”  Me:  “Okay, how much of each?”  Drunk  (panicky): “Uh, I’ll just take a Bud Light.”  Booze is not free. At my bar, every drink and shot is two ounces. Doubles are four. Most bars only pour 1.5 ounces. Don’t ask for “a little more” unless you want to pay for a double. And don’t ask for birthday specials. I hate this. If it’s your birthday and your friends are along, then  they  should buy you drinks, not me. I’m not your friend. When someone asks for a free birthday shot, I like to give them what I call the “Texas Ratt’ler” – Jager and our cheapest tequila mixed together.  Low carb and diet drinks are for pussies. Let me explain something to you. If you are trying to lose weight, stop drinking. Switching to Michelob Ultra will not make any difference if you still sit on your fat ass all day playing Grand Theft Auto. And alcohol – most of it is made of sugar. And sugar = carbs. So there no use in ordering a Diet coke and rum.  Drinks should not be fads. Drink what you like, not what you saw Sarah Jessica Parker drinking on television. When “Sex and the City” came out, cosmopolitans were all the rage. But guess what. Cosmos are very strong, and not very sweet. Most girls don’t even like them. Also, current fad drinks I hate include Red Bull with anything (speed freak), Michelob Ultra (homosexual) and any liquor-based wine cooler posing as something different, a la Smirnoff Ice (too girly).  I’m not a bartender to make friends with people. I’m here to make money. When we’re busy, my goal is to serve as many people as fast as possible. If you want to chit chat, come in at 3 p.m. on a Wednesday afternoon, when I’m so bored I do the TV Guide crossword. Don’t be angry that I don’t “smile” or I’m not “talkative.” I’m working. I’m busy.  Listen, Tourette’s, don’t randomly blurt your order out to me. Chances are I’m not listening because I’m serving, oh, like five other people at the moment. If I make eye contact with you, ask what you’d like or tell you I’ll be with you in a sec, then you can tell me your order. Patience is a virtue.  People who tip after they ask for water ROCK!  Don’t get belligerent if you get cut off. Our door man is a 300-pound Samoan biker. And in Texas, I can cut you off for any reason whatsoever, like, for example, because I don’t find your baby pink polo T-shirt with the collar flipped up even the most remotely funny. Not even in an ironic way. And don’t try to beg for “just one more” when you get cut off or after 2 a.m. Here’s a tip, honey. Drunk people generally don’t make the most rational arguments. And you’re not worth me losing my job and liquor license over.   Don't give me attitude when I ID you. If you are 21 and look 18, fork it over. In fact, if you're 25 and look 21, that should be a compliment.    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The beginning of August. Summer’s almost over. That’s depressing, but when I think about it, now that I live in southeast Texas, summer doesn’t really end until October. It’s actually better that way, because later in the Indian summer the weather is less humid and there are less kids at the beach. A while back, I sat on the beach sipping a rum drink Christopher had made and watching a tiny  urlLink shrimp  swim around in a tide pool I’d created. It was just the perfect moment.  A thought occurred to me that hasn’t been entirely foreign in the past year. I sat there on the beach in the sun and wondered what I’d be doing at that exact moment if I was still in Oklahoma.  I’m sure the concept is old, but I remember seeing it in the movie “ urlLink Slacker .” For every decision you make, and alternate version of you makes an alternate decision and branches off into a whole ‘nother reality. People always say you can’t run from your problems, but so far its worked out pretty well for me. Then again, I think it was other people’s problems, not my own, I was running from. I love Oklahoma, but leaving was the best decision I’ve ever made in my life. It somehow seems like this was the first decision I’ve actually made for myself. And though I’m a little restless, I’m happier than I can remember being in a long time. I’ve lived in Texas for a year now. I don’t plan on staying here forever, but haven’t decided to leave yet, either. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Other blogs:    urlLink Angry in the Morning  - by friend and fellow journalist Elwell X.   urlLink Dave's Blog  - by fellow journalist Dave Barry.   urlLink MeMo  - by fellow journalist Kyrie O'Connor. I see a pattern here.   Other links:    urlLink The Villager  - see what I get paid $8 an hour to do.   urlLink Houston Hash House Harriers  - my little drinking club with a running problem. There may be pictures of an intoxicated me on this site.   urlLink On On  - This is a better hash site by a local hasher, Roller Balls.   urlLink Deadenders Scooter Club  - classic Vespas and other toys our friends own. Look for pictures of me drunk, too.   urlLink Savage Love  - it's a dangerous and sexy world out there, folks.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>