<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       	 		 		 so, here it is. i am tempted to muse on the signifance of writing a blog or the thrill of anonymity or something, but that far too much navel gazing...  should I introduce myself?  it is a strange time for me to start something like this.  i feel like i am in a time of complete flux, stemming from a dissatisfaction that spreads like an oil slick over all aspects of my life. my work and my home lives leave me rolling eyes and counting minutes... this can not be all about the externals of work and relationship... there is something disturbed and shifting or else waking and crying out in my psyche.   maybe it is just that i can't handle stability.  so why not try something new?   well, we're just getting acquainted, lets not get so dark so soon.  HOW ARE YOU? 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink middlebeachview 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink endearinglyflawed .			 		 	  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       	 		 		 This weekend I attended my first ever big city, wet and saucy Pride Parade.  Now,  I have had my various forays into girl on girl, but for the time being, I am boyfriended.   Attending a pride event as a het couple, requires a bit of discretion.... I am all for PDA, but frankly, this is not our event and so  I would perfer to keep a low profile. J however, seemed to feel a bit uneasy at this oggle-fest. He wanted to have a hand on me at all times. I am sure that he would deny this, however.   He did say though that his favorite part was the men from Boston, of which there were about 30, who formed the most outrageous rifle twirling squad, in their tight militant outfits in time to disco, no less.  My favorite part was getting hosed down on this hot hot Sunday afternoon, but equally hot men with HUGE waterguns! I am sometimes shy about such things, but in this atmosphere, I was shouting "Me! Spray Me!"   I felt so excited to be part of something  so bold, enlivening and empowering. 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink Annual Pride Promo Cards by Local Card Printer 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink Stewart .			 		 	  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       	 		 		 I am in the grueling process of being interviewed for a job this week. I have to ask, what is the point of some of these questions?? "Can you give us an example of a time where you have helped a client with a problem?" I spend everyday helping people with their problems... that's what my work is about. What are they trying to find out... it is obvious that I have helped people, that  I do help people and that I am happy to do it, otherwise I would be in a different line of work!  Anyway, I find it difficult to be courageous in these situations. I don't have any trouble talking about myself and my strengths yada yada yada, but this power imbalance totally triggers my desire to tell people what they want to hear, even when it doesn't meet my own needs. For example, I  sensed that they want me to start very soon, so said I could be ready in two weeks, when really this would be burning my current employer a bit.  That is why I have attached this ferocious tiger to this post. I need to be more fierce and stand up for what I want.   I will negotiate in my own best interests Ggrrr. 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink Tiger 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink AKMA .			 		 	  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>