<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I LOVE ANDREW!!!!! That's really all I have to say!! He's hot and cute and smart and alot of other stuff!!! I don't care anymore about this being a secret inside myself!!! I'm letting the world know that I like him!!! INDEED!!!  
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You see, I always never looked around to see if there actually was anyone else other than Andrew. Well, today I did, and was really surprised to find that there is. I remember this kid named Caleb from one of my classes in 6th grade. I always thought he was cute, but nothing more. Of course I had a crush on this kid named Sam at the time, so you know, everyone else was like nothing to me. lol Anyways, I looked at him 2day, and he's really changed...he's no Andrew, and I know physical appearances shouldn't matter, but still, he's WAY hotter than he was b4...and then there's this other kid who's sort of a skateboarder, and has changed a whole bunch since last year in 7th grade. He's cuter ever since he cut his hair, and just the fact that he skateboards is cool lol. Uhh...I worked with him in EXPO last year, and he kept burning himself with the glue gun for fun. We all thought it was so funny. But we were all SO impressed by the way he could build houses out of like these popsicle sticks. Any ways, that's way off topic, and the point to be made is that maybe Andrew's not the only one, maybe I need to open my eyes a little more. 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OMG! I found out today that Andrew doesn't like Sponge Bob! How could anyone not!!! It's like the most awesomely awesome show ever!!! Oh yeah, he also likes to do Motocross or something like that, I couldn't understand what Griffin had said lol. And he also wants to be rich...but really, who doesn't lol. Yeah, he's in my 1st period EXPO class, and my 6th period IPC Science class...it really sux tho cuz I have to get a schedule change to be in choir cuz they messed up my scheldule, and guess what period choir is?!? 6th period, which means my whole schedule will be all switched around, which means no more classes with Andrew : ( WAHHHHHH!!! Oh well, *tear tear* I suppose I can live without the classes lol. I mean, maybe it's time to move on from him. I know it'll never work out, and why torture myself. I know this kid at my church who liked me last year and in 6th grade, I suppose I could talk to him more or something. He comes to church every Sunday and to youth, so it wouldn't be that hard! 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I only have 17 more days left till school starts! "Sigh" Summer has dragged on  so  long this year...probably cuz I didn't have a crush last year during the summer! I can't wait till I get to see him again, even though I know he won't look the same as last skool year...he never does look the same as the years pass...I mean from 6th grade to 7th grade, he grew his hair out...he was WAY hotter than in 6th grade, I couldn't believe it lol. But then he cut his hair, and made it all ugliful. You see, I like that new style, or old style as you could call it, that's sort of longish and not like plastered to their head. My brother looks so cute when he can grow his hair out, it's just that my parent make him cut it : ( But, you know, he's almost 19 and then will be able to do what he wants. Anyways, I also would like say that if any of my friends find this and regonize it as myself, please don't spread the word...you know who you are "cough cough" Yeah, so bye bye! Gotta go think about the 17 days left ^^
      
</post>


</Blog>