<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today has been one of those days that feels like it's really actually not there. A day you feel bad for sitting around, when you know you should be using every second of your life. It feels like this whole summer has been filled with days like this. I don't know, maybe I feel empty because so many things are going on in my life and I just wish I can freeze time to sort everything out. 
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A conversation I had with a friend:    friend-   blue     Me-   red 
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       There's something about my ex that I cant put a finger on. I don't know why but sometimes I feel myself caring so deeply about him, worrying about him and stuff. So much that it actually makes me upset. I don't understand, it's not like our relationship was that of a serious one. It was just a "relationship", one rushed into that it kinda felt like you weren't even in. Once we broke up I felt I hadn't even had time to know and understand him and so I wanted us to be friends. But sometimes I feel this friendship thing isn't working. Too much emotion his part and mines. 
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       today i was laying on my back thinking about my life and where its going. All the regrets that i face everyday. i just cant help but think that years from now im gonna think back and say "what if". i dont wanna look back and think "what if". i wanna be happy. happy that i used this time on earth. a few days ago they had the model search thingy. i have no doubt in my mind that i would be good for it. ask any of my friends they'll say im model material but my insecurities kept me from doing that. and before that there was this backround dancer thingy for girls my age just like in the town over but again my insecurities and my fears kept me from that. i just dont wanna miss out on things because i dont feel good about my self.
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok this is my third time writing. but i really need alot of opinions. so i can see whether they suck or not.lol. anyway. my mom just said that i have cto choice highschools. i thought i was going to chad and that was final. but my mom went on this interview and she said that we are definatly moving, and if she gets the job we can move to new brunswick. and if we move to NB then i can go to new brunswick highschool. now chad is way better than NBHS but all my friends are there and it would be cool to go there. now my mom gave me three choices.   i can go to chad and she'll just drive me there when she goes to work  i can go to nbhs  i can go to chad for a year and then nbhs   now with the last one i can be skipped and then i would go to nbhs in 10th grade instead of 9th. which might deflate the purpose of going. but i will be near my friends. i know that i want to get skipped and if i just go to nbhs then i might, no i wont be skipped. if i go to chad then i can be skipped and meet new ppl but if i move to new brunswick i will still be with my friends but that will be alot of traveling. i dont know. im not sure what i want to do. something is telling me to go to chad and if we move to new brunswick then i will be close to my friends. but then something says go to nbhs where you'll get great grades and be with your friends and stuff but i also want to do extra curicular stuff and with both it looks like i wont be doing that. im confused and i need time to think about this. but right at this time somethings saying number one.i wont be in school with my friends but my mom said we will be moving to at least one of he brunswicks but thats not definate. but there is a big chance we will move close to new brunswick so....yea somethings saying number one but still im undecided...please comment. i can use second opinions.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ....continuation  a few days ago i found myself just laying in bed crying. i hate thinking about the future. i really want to go to college in california but everything points to new york. i mean the one thing i dont want is to be near my family. i want to be independent. but when i think of it everything i want to do (theater,interior and fashion design, and or music) are all there. im afraid that i wont realize what i want to do early enough to start preparing myself for it. im afraid that im not good as i may thing in the things i like to do. yea my friends compliment me about how i can sketch out a room or whatever. but i cant help but wonder if im really good at it. im afriad that not only will i figure out too late,but that i may lose out on a great future because of how insecure i can be.  i hate what i see when i look in the mirror. no matter how many times i lie and lie to make myself feel better about myself, i just end up at square one.omg i just got distaracted by this cool song.lol.but back to the piont on hand.i just really really want to change. and i keep saying it and saying it. but it never happens. i always say "oh im gonna try to be more organized" or "im gonna try not to be so shy and try to be more social" or "im not gonna let others opinions shape my own reality". i hate that. i wish my mom had never told me that saying. it feels like the second she told me not to let others shape my reality, i started to do just that. like when you tell a child not to touch the iron cause its hot but they do anyway.  i was thinking. my days are filled with fantasies. so much that it seems so real. i dont want to call them day dreams cause i feel i  dont really do that. i fantasize. so much that its become so real. so much that i can see the people in front of me. all sprung from my own loneliness and insecurities. my own yernings for something. i fantacize about my friends being there with me just talking or dancing or something. so much that i find my self voicing my part of the conversation out loud. my way of wishing.  its ok.yea. but it comes a point where it goes from wishing my friends were here. to wishing i wasn't so alone. dreaming about being someone. not just an empty shell of a person i dont know. i find myself staring in the mirror just trying to figure out who the person in front of me is or at least trying to remember the face i see before me. i look at pictures of me when i was younger. and i smile. to see that little girl  frozen in time with a push of a button and a flash of a light. and i just wish that i could have remembered wat she looked like when i was her. ha. no wonder i cant remember how my father looks. i cant remember how i look. and i look like him.god i wish i could just stop these freakin tears from falling.they are so difiant. falling at their own will. and teasing me by only falling form one eye.lol.  i just wish i wasn't so alone. i remember when i would cry. it would stem from whatever had happened to how i was so alone. how i dont have any true friends, no one to love and care about me. feeling worthless.to think my own father didn't feel likei was worth even being in his life. just a curse to the world. a scar on its beautiful face. i put it off as depression. but now that im not in 5th grade. now that i dont have shavani or sidra or ms. demskis (whatever that god damn teachers name was), now that i dont have them to fall back on and i have the same feelings deep inside, bearly covered by a light blanket, i realize its not depression. itshow i feel. its what i have to live with. and no one can help me but myself.  my two friends have these boyfriends. people who love and devote part of themselves to them. and i cant help but wonder why no one feels that way about me. and though i dont want to blame, its just obvious to my heart. influenced by my moms constant nagging about "why dont you have a boyfriend" or my friends suggestions that they need to pair me up. i hate that. i hate the fact that i and so many others like me, feel the need to have someone there to love them just so they can find it in themselves to do so. "why is that your friends can see how beautiful you are inside and out, but you cant?" its not that simple. i guess i'm just not strong like you people.  god...why is it that we let ourselves be bohtered by what other people think and do? i read in   BODY ELECTRIC by CAMY BAKER     "as we become young adults on our way to becoming women[and men], we'll be faced with many people-friends, boyfriends, parents, teachers, actors, models, songers- who will influence and inspire us in many ways. these people will influence what we wear, how we act, and even how we feel.
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       well ive been gone for quite sometime. my computer broke down on my birthday. and that kinda sums up that day. i never have a good birthday. its the one day that is dedicated to my birth and someway i always end up feeling miserable. last year it was because i had to move to this shit hole and that basically took up the whole day. how convient for me. but this year i cant blame anyone but myself. i woke up upset because i couldn't sleep till 2 like i do everyother day. then i couldn't go on the computer and hear my friends wish me happy birthday. i didn't like the cake. it was alright but im not a cake person. cakes , expecially birthday ones (lol) with all that icing, gives me gas.lol. i like ice cream cakes but i had forgotten to ask for one. so anyway. the only thing that kept me happy was music and my constant day dreams and fantacies.  anyway. then me and my mom had a fight. i dont know what about. oh wait yeah i do. about the computer.lol. anyway. sometimes she can be really cool. i mean i can talk to her about stuff. sometimes she doesn't care and i get mad. but sometimes she does take the time to listen. though i always think that her listening skill can be better. and she always confineds in me, whether i want to hear or not, about her relationships. shes always kinda been able to talk to me about that. but sometimes she gets me so mad. and she always has a way in making me feel bad about myself. i mean she probably doesn't do it on perpuse but god. shes always done that. said things to me, not realizing how much her words mean to me. i dont know. i cant blame her completly for it. i need to stop letting peoples opinions shape my reality. anyway. obviously im not feeling as bad as i did that day.so here is an entry from something i wrote that day.  (HERES THE ENTY WORD FOR WORD. STREIGHT FROM THE PAGES) (THIS ENTRY WASN'T DATED AT THE TIME)  i hate being here. i hate crying. i hate her. its all my fault. why the computer broke. why my brother was born. why we have to live in this dump. everything. i f i wasn't born none of this would have happened. if i wasn't born, she wouldn't hate me. i cant even wish i was dead because that would only make me out to be an even bigger burden. the ony thing that would matter is that she now had to pay for my funeral. i hate being a huge disappointment. god i hate to open my eyes because all that i see is all the things that ive done to be an even bigger disappointment and i cant close them because it doesn't go away. thats all she sees and now i understand. there's no reason to be here. there's no purpose to my living. i'll never be what i was meant to be. i''ll just be more of a failure. thats all that peple see of me, a big failure. to life. she wonders why i cant tell her things. because this is what happens. she makes me feel like an even bigger failure because thats all she see of me. i feel so stupid for even feeling that i should be greatful to her for all the things we've been through and getting us out of them because what it really boils to, al throughout the situation all she was thinking about was how if i wasn't here, if we weren't here (my brohter and I), then it all wouldn't have gone that way. all throughout my life, i can be summed up to be  ONE BIG REGRET.     well that is the entry. heres another one from a different day. backround info about this is that i wouldn't wake up to do the dishes so she got mad. and called me ungreatful and said other things i dont feel like repeating.  (HERES THE ENTY WORD FOR WORD. STREIGHT FROM THE PAGES)  August 16,2004  God,my moms a miserable bitch. i sware. she thinks of everyway to make my life unbearing. she's like let me show you how its like for a mother to not care. ALREADY KNOW. let me show you what its like for me to have already eaten and not care whether you do or dont. ALREADY KNOW THAT TOO. let me show you what its like for a mother to not care whether you live or die. KNOW THAT TOO. something must have happened during her childhood to make her so evil. to make her wish that she had no children. it should be a law to keep unwanted children. ABORTION. i'm sure they had that in her day. then i owuldn't have to deal with her no. i dont know why they let ppl who hate children have children themselves. who care more about their crusty 40 y/o boyfriends then their own children. her whole life is revolved around verbal abuse and making her children feel horrible about themselves. i wouldn't have such a horrible image about myself is it wasn't for her. she thinks that because she's "here" makes her a good parent. because she works hard makes her an even better parent. and that the fact that probably only 3 times a month she spends with er children and everyother day she spends yelling and shaping their minds with bad thoughts about themselves. she rather brong a plant or a foster child home to love then her own children. its funny how once she's sick of you she can just get something else to take your place. for me it was Rah-Rah. but poor Rah-Rah got replaced with a plant. see how she thinks of us. and now that the plants have brought those bug things, now she's not gonna xcare for them and she'll probably through them away.funny,huh. if only she can do that to people.then mabey her life wouldn't be such a shit hole. ha. thats probably what she thinks about every day when she wakes up to torture us.  wll thats both of the entries. obviously i was mad during both. but i belive that when mad you say alot of things you mean or you feel that you try to stear away from when your happy.anyway. i wasn't completly sad during my time away. i was frustrated abnd mad.lol. just kidding. i was happy sometimes. but a few days ago i found myself thinking about things...
</post>


<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today i woke up thinking about my eight grade class. I had a dream that we were all in science class being our stupid selves again. I really will miss all of them. We were a really fun class to be with. Specially since we have ben with the same ppl for at least 3 yrs cuz of T.A.G (talented and gifted). Its basically a class for advanced students and they get tought above grade knowledge. We were all suppose to be getting straight A's or honor roll .....hahahahahahaha well some ppl did, i did in 7th and 6th grade but then 8th grade i got some C's so no honor roll for me:( . Not a lot of kids got honor roll. I think the ones who did were,juliet,jessica,corey,shanae,and anisa and in 6th and most of 7th grade me.. 5 outta about 19. We were all smart but some of us were just plain lazy. In some ways we were united. All the teachers with the exception of ms.buck(gym teacher) basicallly hated us. But deep inside i know they liked having us around. There wasnt a day that the class didnt have a good laugh during some class. I know i didnt, me and ester and sometimes shanae(my best friends) would always have something to laugh at ,specially during lunch time. (anisa...armando...shanae..if ur reading this u know what im talking about). I came to T.A.G in 6th grade, so i was with them for 3 yrs. To get in to TAG, u have to get good grades and then take this test if u pass then u get in. I say all were good times, there were a couple fights and some bitching in the classroom and some misunderstanding within our nitch. I will miss all of the ppl in class even those who i sometimes despised. Like for example, peter who kinda smelled and was a really weird kid, he was sometimes nice and he was very good with vocabulary(very very very good). LOL and those times that he flipped , man that was scary . Oh yeah and when he fought with corey, lol omg, wont get those images outta my mind. And Keith(did i spell it right?) who i thought was soo inoccent and came to find out that he was looking girls butts 24/7, I guess i can understand y he notice them a lot, i mean hes short enough to reach them lol. alright alright, sorry keith for calling u short. Let seee......o yeah theres corey, corey corey corey, u big mouth, always seems to have something silly to say and alwyas getting in trouble. He flirts a lot too. Armando......well i guess ur an example of "if u dont succeed try and try again", good luck with anisa, and stop saying "ok" "kk" all the time..sheesh! Aneysa(other anyesa) ashely,mahagoni(or however u spell her name) and xianne, all u guys are funny in ur own weird cruel mysterious ways. Even though sometimes u did get on my nerves. Dominique....theres only want thing to say about u and i know a lot of ppl say the same thing......BITCH i know i know, it does sound mean but after the way she acted all these past 3 yrs, tats all i got to say. Deep deep deep, very deep inside of her i know theres a nice person. Ester.... my partner in crime, we always had a fun time together, whether it was laughing our way through lunch cuz someone slipped or playing jokes on ppl and ourselves, or throwing crumbled up papers at our classmates, we always seemed to get the best outta life. LOL remeber the time in languge art class when we didnt have our homework so we handed in some other papers with a total different subject on it, and we still got a good grade for handing it in. lol, those were the times. OH and i will always remeber the times that we went to the library and looked and flirt with cute guys, lol, specially victor, the cute library guy. And i hope the teachers in high school dont have huge butts like some that we experienced. specially with MS.Paulson, she would always bend down o help someone and then her ass was on the face on whoever was behind her.Im glad were going to the same high school. Shanae, my weird crazy friend,who ppl thought was posessed by a demond,cuz of ur glowing red eyes when u got really mad. And u also know how to dance very good. You,ester and me were the like the 3 musketters......GIRL POWER,LOL W/E. Such great memories, but too bad that ur going to another high school, 3 musketeers wont be complete in high school without u. i hope we keep in touch. Juliet.....man someitmes ur a pain in the ass, and u can be very stuck up. You are a nice person sometimes, but other times i jut feel like cursing u out. Stop trying to be so god damn popular and crap, its just gonna mess with ur head, even thought its already kinda messed up right now.To tell u the truth because u acted so stuck up u lost ur best friend ester, cuz u ditched her for jessica. Jessica i kinda dont know u cuz u came kinda late, but i can tell u to make up ur mind about franklin, either u love him or u dont. And whats all those rumors about u going to juliets house and u and franklin would lock ursleves in her room, thats just freaking weird girl. Stephanie.....ur a very very good friend, ur always there for ur friends and ur a very strong person,i dont think i could go through the things u have gone through. I really hope hat we still keep in touch and keep being the nice, funny person that u r. Anisa....ur weird!!!!! and good at basketball, its cuz of u that i joined in cuz i was kinda scared, but thanx to u i got the courage to, thanx for being a good friend and for always helping me when i needed help. Hope to keep in touch. Teresa, wow ur something rnt u, but what i dont understand y u would loose a friendship over a boy, y u were mad at anisa, just cuz armando liked her. U shouldnt be like that. I also think that ur not as shy as i frist met u. im glad u finally know how to stand up for urself and not take shit from no one. And last but not least me......my goals for high school is to get my grades up again so i can get a scholarship, to be a friend to everyone and be more adventurous and risk taking. I also need to conquere my shyness, im not too shy but i want to be a little less shy. I think i will be remebered to my friend as the crazy silly girl.Im glad i met all of those ppl up there, it helped me to see that i will be dealing with different types of ppl in my life and that i need to to cope with everyone.Or at least try to. 
      
</post>


</Blog>