<Blog>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      can't deny it anymore.    urlLink http://www.zheteng.com/ttt/lifeview.htm   be a good friend, not a stupid friend, don't always trust people, but believe in yourself.  
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      People is like that, they will condemn you for the mistakes u done, but never praised u for the good things u do. It juz take 1 mistake to destroy all the good things u have done. And if u keep making mistakes, no matter how much good things u do, it will never change the fact that u did some mistakes in yur life.  So what if i have done mistakes at first? i am human, dun u ever done a mistake? so what do they do? Condemn u? ok fine nowadays people condemn u then forgive u, thats good enough, so i did do many mistakes at first, but nobody correct me, they rather condemn me then correct me. ok nevermind, condemning is a way of correcting so i understood y they condemn me so i change but its a big mistake it worsen the condemning, there r doubt in them now. Nevermind that, people doubt each other at first, so i learn through the hard way, when i got people angry, i change, they say bad things behind my back i try to fig it out and change, people frame me sabo me nevermind i change to suit them so that they won't do it again. ok its a hard work but i find it challenging. It begin to work, people r beginning to trust me and i can get along. but there's a fact that human get angry sometimes, i am human so there r times i got angry, so what if i scold? u can't take it? i didn't even shout. And the cruel reality came. U ALL want me to stop condemning people.  i felt stupid, why in the 1st place did i listen to u all? why must i put up all yur shit? why must u all brainwashed my best friend? did u all know my effort has gone to waste? and i still wanted to warn u all that there are some blacksheep in the group of friends, but come to think of it i am going to yur level by doing that. Or shall i say u all are one of a kind? Gals alike, u all knew what happen, but u all wanted to do things yur way so much u all forgets about being grace.  After reading this there will be people thinking that i am stupid, i can don't listen to u all in the 1st place, and do what i like, its yur own damn fault for being what u are today. FUCK that's what i have been doing before u all condemn me, i have been minding my own business all the time. that's a mistake u all condemn me about. u all push me into this shit hole and blame me for it. Some how i always hope that you all are happy for what u done, if not then what the meaning for all this shit? 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I minded my own business don't like to mind thier business they say i am rude and unsociable, will do things watever i like without asking. ok fine i get along, talk to them tried to be friendy, listen to them to do wat they like. fuck they say i am trying to cheat them "po lan par" etc, ok nevermind you all did it, i know wat u all want so i go, i won't bother u all, now they all say i need to talk more.  Fuck lah make up yur mind lar. what u all want from me? u think i am a toy to play ah? then chuck me aside when bored, very fun is it?
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      the prev picture was posted after i came back from stadium, damn tired after the parade, see the tv broadcast but didn't see me, haiz nevermind i dun look good on tv anyway, its the memories that count.  anyway G.O.H shift is over, its back to my duty shift, i did say something about unwilling to go back but what can i do, can't escape the cruel reality. Before that i am having a looong deserve break, from now till sat. Till then i am free from hell. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    NDP 2004 9th Aug I have finally found some happy memories to remember. urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Exicited right now, in 10 hrs time i will be marching into the 60,000 crowd. so in the mean time i must get myself ready  now till 8:30 i will go to base 8:30 till around 11am i will be heading to indoor stadium 11am till 2 or 3pm will be doing the last rehersal 5:30 to 6pm march in!  wish me luck. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      tomolo is the Big day, after all the drill rehearsal, it is finally the day to perform.  this past 3 months has been quite enriching for me, i have seen the "behind the sence" of NDP 2004, the mistakes, the fun, the sense of achievement. the girls, (heehee) all this feeling are within me and i won't forget it for the rest of my live.   see u at the national stadium....... 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2 days ago at century sq entrance oppisite the field, me and my father was crossing the road and was almost knock down, we ran across juz in time.  but this couple who saw us say: pity we didn't get knock down. it was the girl who said it and her boyfriend or husband or whatever say: yah lor.  why did u say this??? did u know it hurt me and my father? u are juz being irresponsible, passing rude remark without thinking. u think we want to cross road and want to get knock down delibrately?? theres so many people crossing the road there everyday and u didn't say anything to them? even u did don't u have yur own business to mind or did u ever jay walk b4??? if got lets hope u and yur boyfriend get knock down soon. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Picture of me taken outside the kallang indoor stadium, this is taken during the NDP2004 NE show. I can only post this picture as i have no time to take pictures during preview i wish i had the time to take photo but the RSM won't let us take, he say something about us taking photo of the girls there. whatever does that mean.....  urlLink     i know this photo is dark and u might not see my face, what the heck i don't look good, trust me u don't want to see. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One day a boy question his dad on why he is different from other people, he asked why some people has the ability to enjoys life easily and effortlessly whereas he must work very hard to enjoy life and sometimes didn't get to enjoy at all....  Dad's reply:  In the big sea there are different type of birds, one type hunt fishes by soaring up the sky and dive down into the sea bravely to catch the fish. The other stand still in the sea near the beach and peck at the fishes around the water. The day juz passes as it is and both live without starving.  i didn't understood the reply at 1st but then i finally understood this story and know that my ability is limited, i must know what i can do now and can't do, and perhaps in the future i can be that bird that can soar up the sky and dive into the sea bravely.  hope you understand. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      why am i writing all those sad memories? i should juz forget about them and write about my good memories. i shouldn't be blaming myself or people for a mistake that happen so long ago. (ok i will try not to)  Anyway, NDP 2004 is coming and i am in the AirForce Guard Of Honor contingent. this is a whole new experience for me as it a first time i can feel such a BIG crowd looking at us. I was pull out as a reserved during the NE show, it was dissapointing i guess i sux in drill, but i did manage to film some firework so its not a bad thing to be a reserved.  but i did went to the preview, felt nervous and excited, luckly i didn't screw up, i hope i won't screw up on the actual day.  
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's funny though when both of u r meant to be friends god will put u together, but if u are not meant to be, god will not, even he does, he will still seperates you eventually.  Friend A and B start off as stranger, but no matter how hard they tried to do their own things, trying to ignore each other, they still manage to find things to chat. on the other hand another Friend A can't find any thing to talk to Friend C,  A and C always offended each other. C felt uneasy and wanted to ruin A and B. but A know he has offended C so A tried to get along, but it can't be done, no matter how hard A tried, they still offended each other, in the end after a hard struggle, A managed to be friend C but it has ruin him and B's friendship.  After a few months faith put A and B together in a same place though both did not talk much and was seperated later.  A and C didn't get to be best friend, as months after A quarrel with B and tried to be friend C, they still can't find things to talk. In the end faith put A to place R  and C was put to place C, place C has a mission to put down place R and place R has to stop place C (was never put together and even it does they will destroy each other)  A and B remain stranger A and C remains plain friend and on job enermies. A lost a best friend. A wonder if B and C are meant to be together.. ???  This story tell us that A and B are meant to be if C leaves them alone, if C comes to A, B has to go and also the other way round. C and A takes more effort to be together then B and A. when A and B has the will to be friends GOD kept them together. When A and B lost his will to be friends, GOD seperates them. (meant to be together and meant to be sperated). when A and C are together, something bad will happen. (Not meant to be together).  A will never know if B and C are meant to be together as he was FUCKING STUPID. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate that place, its dark, cold, smelly and chaotic. but i need to go back on wed night., and soon i will be living there for 2 night straight. i am very afraid and lonely there, i don't know when will i get beaten. it so chaotic. people fighting, quarralling, stealing each other's stuff. i don't trust anyone there, they r sooo fake when they smile at u.  i don't have much friend there, even i have they r starting to doubt me, i can feel it, their eyes is cold, the job there is killing me very very slowly, i dun have enough sleep and the people there dun let me.  some try to please the higher ranks, getting all the good job themselves leaving the shit job 4 us who juz follow orders when given.  some will use force to settle problem, they dun know pain or regret, they juz beat you up when they like it, nobody will know if u got beaten.  I am brave, things will be alright, i will juz take it slowly step by step, everthing will be alright after this one. i will not fall.  319 days left.... 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A stupid mistake done years ago, and its haunting me, i felt helpless, i can't be a good friend then, i don't understand life, who does? trying to change, but its soooo difficult.  i felt something is wrong in me, but i can't express it, even i do, no one understand me... yet. what shall i do that is correct? what shall i not do if its wrong.   whatever shit happens life still goes on... Life does not sux, it juz ain't EZ/fair... 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    30th july Fri night, around 2330hrs - 0030hrs, an accident has happened below my block, seem like a van and a cyclist collided, heard a loud crash n some commotion. saw a person crawl out under the van with the aid of a passer by b4 the ambulance arrived, he was sent to hospital by the paramedic. (well thats what i saw, might not be the case.) Cycling can be dangerous at night, i think i need to gear up properly and take proper route if i ever want to cycle at night again.  urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    There goes another one.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    NDP 2004 NE Show Firework, it was soooo beautiful. Life should be like that, full of colours and energy.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i believe everyone needs a place to voice out your feeling or else you will go insane, i tried to voice to some friends but it seems to fustrate them, well nevermind not their fault, who wants to listen to me nag about my problem all day. Thats life....., here you are reading my blog and if u find it offending i guess it can't be help, thats the life i am having. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    I Loved this anime&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>


</Blog>