<Blog>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love History. Both military and cultural history. My favorite subjects are Ancient Greece, Rome, Mesopotamia, Egypt. Byzantine Empire, Dark Ages, Crusades. WW II. I have many books and magazines for the above subjects and read them many times. If i wasn't a Comic designer or a Civil Engineer then i would definately be a historian. I find history fascinating and a good source for stories and drawings. Living in Greece is helpfull since a lot of very interesting archeological sites are near. I have been to Delphi, Knossos in Crete, Akrotiri in Santorini, Akropolis in Athens, Ancient Olympia and many others.  But according to many people again i am a fascist. Because i read about Ancient Greece and war. A very close friend of mine said "Military History? Fascists read that man!". Someone can be and IS called a fascist if he hangs a Greek flag on his balcony for no reason (if showing that you love your country and are proud to live in it is not a reason). I cannot explain it. It is a Greek thing. It's like i was raised to believe that through secret subconcious messages.  And so in 2004 comes the Eurovision Song contest. For those who don't know it is a contest for European countries. In my opinion it is something overrated but people here have taken it a bit too seriously (if we don't win they hace sabotaged us). Anyway this year we selected our local SUPERSTAR Sakis Rouvas to represent us with a really "cool" song (in English heaven forbid if we honour our native language). Sakis performs with....... a T-Shirt with the Greek flag on it!  And suddendly EVERYONE is proud to be Greek and wears the same t-shirt. And all that fascist stuff are forgotten! Magicaly! It took only one Contest, one Singer, a tea spoon of Greek flag and suddendly you are not a fascist! What do you get? A national symbol treated as a fashion statement.  I have a headache......... 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like heavy metal. I like the fact that most (if not all) heavy metal bands write their own music and lyrics giving it their personall signature trying to give us a view of their world show us their feelings. I respect them for what they do and will always listen to this music.  But why in God's name doesn't anyone here respect this? My personal opinion and taste? Why do i have to be an asshole or stupid or a punk because i don't listen to Greek mainstream "music"? Because that's how everyone else is handling this here. You don't have a taste in music if you don't listen to Greek mainstream "music". You don't have taste in music if you don't listen to a bunch of women and men bitching about how they lost the love of their life and want it back or how they spent their vacations with their love of their life or what they want to do to the love of their life when they are alone.They don't even write their songs. They are performers and nothing more. And people worship them. Gather like ants to see them perform and pay 150euro a bottle of whiskey per 2 people.  And because i listen to Metal i am a bad person and they are better than me. I wear my favorite Metal T-shirts (only have 4 of them) and i'm a punk. When i wear my "normal" clothes i am ok until i say "Yeah i listen to metal!" then i become a immature. "When are you gonna get serious?" many people ask me. Never. If serious means listening to all the mainstream music they listen too, showing off my car (which my father would have bought), showing off my girlfriend as sexy as possible so anyone would see her.  Please....worry about yourselves and listen to something before you judge it. If you don't like it thats fine. Just say "I don't like it i like better listening to other Greek music" but don't say "It's a bunch of people screaming! Listen to some real music!(Greek mainstream blah blah)". Respect someone else's taste and opinion.  But knowing Greeks (hell i'm one of them) i wouldn't count on it....... 
    
</post>


</Blog>