<Blog>


<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so yeah...I have come to the realization that I just might be an alcoholic or something of the sort..I don't know.  Or is it social drinking or could it be boredom? More than likely boredom. Freaking school registration is on Friday :( Its going to be cool because its my last year, but yeah, it is still another long ass year of juvenile people to deal with. Why not move to Canada?  ..that had nothing to do with the immature students at school, I just want to move to Canada. 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate traveling if you do not know how to get home....no more comments.  But Six Flags was actually kind of cool because I had money Meaning that I was able to get on rides     of my choice with the FAST LANE PASS. It was so awesome because people were all...     "ooh..they have fast lane passes." and i was like shyeah. But it was cool. And Junior actually called me. It has been FOREVER since HEs called ME. It was sweet really. yeah... 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just recently got in a serious argument with a supposed good friend. Wtf seriously. How exactly would I justify being a feminist if I let a friend have someone walk all over them? I just don't get people sometimes, and she actually let him too, thats what pisses me off. All for love? Bullshit dude, mabye an obssession to sex because in the end, it is all about the sex. But whatever, don't let me help or give advice. Fucking dumbasses. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You have a surprise kiss! Your partner is always pleasantly pleased to have you jump outta no where to dote them with a fun peck on the cheek or more passionate embrace. super markets and work places are your favorite places to attack your loved one with all your love =p   urlLink  What kind of kiss are you?    brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla       
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      suck it 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Allah I feel so much better.  I was very much depressed yesterday night because I found out that my boyfriend's family pretty much hates me and they honestly don't even know me. They have never once sat me down to talk to me, find out what I do, find out how much I love their son but ook. I'm certainly not going to bend over backwards for people who act nice when I'm around and then talk shitty about me when I'm not. There is no point, and I'm not going to cry about it again. Fuck them. Anyways, I just got off of work from the fabulous Pretzel Time and I feel like shit. It was so hot and I pretty much walked home in 100 degree weather. Bloody bastards. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude it sucks so very badly coming on the rag. I am always depressed. There is this really awesome party that is tonight and I feel to shitty to even go but I'm going anyway...I might feel better eventually I suppose. But yeah...
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm sitting at home and decided to let people hear my voice because no one ever really does...plus it is really freaking boring and that always has a lot to do with my life choices.    So yea, much to everyone's disbelief, I am still dating Junior and I'm happy about it, now anyways. A couple of things were..settled last night and were okay. I am supposed to see him tonight and I more than likely will because I'm over there with his brother, one of my good friends, all the time. Literally, I think I've gone maybe two days without seeing him this summer. Sad I know but hey, is there anything else to do in Bloomington, Illinois?      
    
</post>


</Blog>