<Blog>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
                     Lord,      &nbsp;    I praise you for all the freedom you've given us in  Australia. Thank you for letting us worship and live our lives for you freely,  without major persecution.      &nbsp;    I pray for our brothers and sisters overseas who  are facing suffering because they are your children, Lord. Help them in times of  trouble, encourage and strengthen them. As Ramadan approaches, I pray that those  believers who will go through even more persecution are surrounded by your love,  and they stand firm in their faith.       &nbsp;    Father I pray for Daniel, who's not feeling well,  and anybody else who is sick. May you place your healing hand upon us, and help  us to recover quickly, so that we use our gift of health to serve you  fully.      &nbsp;    For those of us at school, I pray that we still  make time for you. I pray that we see you as our Father in Heaven who will  always be there for us, when we're upset, stressed, tired and just sick of it  all. And you'll never get sick of listening to us. How amazing you are, God!!! :  )      &nbsp;    in Jesus' name,  Amen   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i'm praying for your friend von!   Heavenly Father,                  Thankyou that when we need help you are there for us and care for us. Thankyou that you help us and guide us and give us all that we need and keep on showing us the way to live better lives for You so that we may be cleansed and ready for what You have for us in Heaven. "Who shall I compare to You, who can reach so deep into my soul, like You my Lord." Lord You know us inside and out and You know what's best for us beacuse You created us. Thankyou for this and that You are in control.   You are eternal, You will never change and your love will never fade, nor will You leave your people.   Please keep us fresh in You and willing to go wherever your path may take us, however challenging it may be - because You were willing to pay the price for us, even if it meant your Son.  Please help us  not  to live for our  own  glory, but for  yours    Your will be done in Jesus' name, Amen  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      if u guys remember, i have a friend who's promised to be married. she's not gonna be married until she's 18, but he's really awful. there are other things i can't tell u but please could u continue to pray for her?  thanx guys,  von 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      please come and carry me, i need Your love to carry me  Lord,  help us to remember that when we feel that the world is against us and we're having trouble being happy, that you are always there for us, that we can come to you and you will lift us up. help us shine a light in our friends' lives, christian or non-christian. so that "they may see our good deeds and praise your Father in heaven". i pray for our prayer group(s) on wed. that you may work your will for our schools through us and other prayer groups throughout the world.  in Jesus' name i pray,  Amen 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Jesus You are Lord forever  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      God,  We're young and we want to use the gift of energy you've given us to serve you :D  Thank you for being a sanctuary that we can go to when life gets tough. You were there before friends, boyfriends/girlfriends, enemies, teachers, parents, siblings etc. etc. came along, and you'll be there if they ever go. So we ask that you help us see that now we're in your family, our future is ETERNAL!!!!  EVERYBODY'S SINGING NOW 'COS WE'RE SO HAPPY EVERYBODY'S DANCING NOW 'COS WE'RE SO HAPPY IF ONLY WE COULD SEE YOUR FACE AND SEE YOU SMILING OVER US AND UNSEEN ANGELS CELEBRATE FOR JOY IS IN THIS PLACE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!   sing it with me :D  *oh i could sing unending songs of how you saved my soul well i could dance a thousand miles because of your great love*   :D :D :D :D   In Jesus' name, Amen.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dear Lord,  I pray for those of us who are having trouble at school, pray that you'll help them concentrate on their work and most importantly on YOU. Help us to do everything we do for your glory. Help us not get distracted by MSN, this blog and others, tv, stuff... I pray that as we get older, and have more work, that our focus in life will never change.  in Jesus' most precious name,  Amen 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Our Father in Heaven,   Thank you for the trials and tribulations in life. Strengthen us; encourage us; and give us the ability to endure. Let our faith remain strong through every challenge. Generous and gracious God, we ask that when we need help, we will not hesitate to come to you in prayer.       Lord, remove every doubt in our minds, and let us be certain and decided. Do not let us become like a wave in the sea that is blown about by the wind. We pray all these things that we might better serve You, mighty God.      In Jesus' most precious name, Amen         [Read James 1:2-8 for encouragement in hard times ^-^]  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        { Do not be anxious about anything, but in evrything, by prayer and petition, with thanksgiving, present your requests to God. And the peace of God which  transcends all understanding, will guard your hearts and minds in Christ Jesus }           Philippians 4:6-7      
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Heavenly Father,  we thank you for giving us such a close knit group like the one we have. Lord we ask that you guide and lead us and help us grow closer to each other and help us to encourage each other in our faith.   For everyone who's tired, either physically or spiritually, may you renew their mind so that we are fresh to serve You :D  We thank you for being the God who always loves us, even if we don't deserve your awesome love. May we learn to serve and bring you glory :)  In Jesus' name, Amen.
     
    
</post>


<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      But despite her best efforts. Marion was soon surrounded by a cloud that burnt like fire. Marion screamed as the flesh melted from her bones and fell to the untouched ground. Soon, Marion was nothing but a pile of ragged bone fragments. 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Marion raged against the glowing green walls of her prison. Nothing she did helped, and she was weakening fast. Marion sat down, despairing. "Hello?" Marion turned around and saw someone sitting down a short distance away. Hope rose within her. "Hello?" Marion's hope vanished as she gazed on the source of the voice. A small child. Rising past her disapointment and despair, Marion moved closer. "Hello, little boy, what's your name?" "Joshua, I feed on despair." "My name's Marion. I feed on death." "Then you will fade. Everyone except me does, because I feed on their despair as they fade." Marion raised her dagger, once Tittanya's, and struck. "Then your death should bring me lots of strength.  Tittanya jumped as the green stone suddenly dimmed. Damien cursed and threw the stone away. "RUN!!! If she has done what I think, she will have released a force that cannot be matched even by her!"  Marion jumped from the stone and ran from the cloud behind her. "SHIT!!!" 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tittanya started to run towards the sound. "I'll be buggered before I let somebody else kill her!" She wispered to herself. When she reached Marion, she was huddled among the forms, wimpering as the prodded her with their shard talons. "Get away from her!" She screamed, "She's  mine !" Still running forward, Tittanya pointed the strange green stone at the group of creatures surrounding her enemy. They all collapsed. "What a fucking anti-climax, huh?" Said Damien from behind her. "No shit." She replied as she bent down to check on Marion. "She won't get up again, she's utterly dead. That's what the stone was for. "Oh, right. Well, can we get out of here?" And they walked towards the setting sun. 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "What were those... things ?" Tittanya asked when she had regained the energy to speak. Damien hushed her. "Promise me to relax and try to recover, and I'll explain everything. You must rest." Tittanya nodded gently in reply. Though she disagreed with his logic, she dared not object. Her curiousity silenced her. "Tittanya," Damien began, "you once said that your vendetta with Marion must cease- that only one could survive." He paused to allow Tittanya time to drink it in. "In the bar..." "Yes. It is not a simple matter," he continued, sighing. "Everything has spiralled out of control because I intervened. Do not ask how, but you and Marion  must  have a   Final Fight, else anarchy ensue. One of you- and I sincerely hope it to be Marion- must die in the hands of the other." These words reminded Tittanya, who shot up like a bolt of lightning. "Marion's still in danger!" she exclaimed. "She will not die yet." Damien's words were so plain and emotionless, raising a slight fury in Tittanya. "what's that supposed to mean?" she questioned. "We need to rescue her now! You said yourself that she musn't die yet." "I only want you to be fresh for your battle against her. I will save her when she is nearing death," he promised. "Then you can finish her off easily." "Can you really risk that? What if you're too late?" At that exact moment, Marion's shrill voice could be heard worlds away. It was a cry fer help. 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Marion was scared. Just because she could not die did not mean she didn't feel pain. The creatures that surrounded her in her corner made her blood as ice. Moving Tittanya's dagger in front of her, Marion desperately tried to think of a plan.  Tittanya fared little better than Marion, having no weapon other than the stone. it held them off, but only when directed straight at one. "Damien." Tittanya's voice was barely a wisper. As one of the creatures managed to circle her and grab the back of her neck, Tittanya screamed to the only other person she could think of: "MARION!!!"  Marion heard the cry and hesitated long enough that she was disarmed. "TITTANYA!!!"  Damien raised his head as he heard the exchange. "Damn it all!" He passed through the worlds and grabed Tittanya. She was weak, but he heard her: "Got to save Marion, got to fight creatures." "Shhh..." Damien said tenderly, "Yes, we'll help her and get her help against these creatures, because none must interfere with your Final Fight." 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Meanwhile, Tittanya stood still like an ice sculpture, the green gem glowing in her hand. She did not move. She simply stared vacantly. The night was coming to an end as the sun peeped up from the clouds. Tittanya was roused by the rooster crow.   "Damien, what did I do?" she sighed, crompling to the ground. A glistening tear slid down her pale cheek.   The sight of a long lost friend had invoked so many memeories. It was all bittersweet. He had died to save her life, but he had not realised at the time that she couldn't live without him.   Drying her eyes, she felt her own being warming. It was as if she had been frozen, unfeeling, for so long. Too long.   Again, Tittanya fingered the crystal. There was no doubt that Damien had wanted to help her in her battle against Marion. And she had been given the green stone.   "Why?" she wondered. "How will this thing save me?"   Suddenly, Tittanya felt a burning need to see Damien again. She had been stupid to turn him away and think that she could handle this on her own. What would he be doing right now, thinking right now?      A cold hand rested on Tittanya's shoulder, and her blood froze to icicles.  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Fuzzy Rememberance Scene!   Damien ran along the golden sands, the boys hard on his heels, Tittanya just ahead of him. "Come on Damien, we've already started, why not let us finish with her?" The leader of the boys yelled. Damien was about to reply when a sudden weight from behind brought him to his knees. "Run Tittanya! Don't let them catch you!" As he said this, he rolled over, pushing himself into the path of the other two boys. "Bastard!" Swore the one who had tackled him. "You're gonna pay for that!" The two others pulled daggers from within their jackets. "Slice him, we don't want him to inspire others to delay us, do we?" The leader gave Damien a nasty smile as a blade was drawn across his throat.  In his own time, Damien stood and moved off to find Tittanya and set things right. 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Damien was angry as he left Tittanya. He had been her friend all along. Sure, he had helped Marion once, but that didn't mean he wasn't helping Tittanya. And now, when he finally had the power to help her diectly, she spurns him.  Damien's anger boiled out of him and into the surrounding landscape. Lightning flashed and earth rumbled. "How is she meant to kill a vampire who is alive, not even undead, without the power of the dead behind her? Doesn't she realize what she's up against? Marion is a vampire who endures sunlight, who feeds on death, is fuelled by Death and is protected from death by Death. Can't she abandon her pride long enough to realize that she needs the help of one of the dead, to accept her weaknesses long enough to stay alive?" Damien's anger suddenly turned to grief and a river of salty water surrounded him. "Tittanya, I'm sorry." His voice was a bare wisper. "I shouldn't have let them do it, but I died because of it and now you won't let me repay the debt. Can't you trust me enough to let me bring you here, so you can learn how to rid the world of Marion? I'm sorry." Damien stayed on his island surrounded by the river of his grief, remembering what he did to warrent such a strong rejection from Tittanya. 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tittanya stood in his path. She would not budge. "Come on, Tittanya, let's go, " he coerced. But she was adament. "No, Damien. Not until you tell me what is going on here!" she demanded. "Well, a vampiress is after you and trying to kill you with your own dagger. Satisfied?" he replied curtly. "I know that!" she cried. "But what I don't know is why you're here and what you intend to do to me." "I'm here to take your soul to a better place- where you can find peace." "Why?" she interupted. "Why do you bother to show up after so long and expect a friendly welcome?" He placed a firm hand on her shoulder. "Tittanya- I died but returned for the sole reason of saving your life. Had I not intervened, Marion would have claimed it. Please understand this, and stop looking on me as an enemy. I'm your friend."   She waved his smile away. "No, Damien," she replied, "I have no friends because I don't  need  anyone's help."   "Tittanya..."   "I don't need you!" she screamed. The surreal setting melted away, along with Damien. Before he disappeared, he handed her her a radiating green stone.      And Tittanya was left outside the pub again.    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn, stabbed twice in the chest in as many hours. At least this time she didn't have a heart to stab. Marion stopped, panting and confused. Why was the person who had helped her before helping Tittanya now? Marion looked at Tittanya's dagger, hers now. She would have to learn how to use it. Then she realised she had left her heart back there.  Damien picked up Marion's heart and smiled. Her greatest strength was her greatest weakness. He had her greatest strength. "Come, Tittanya, let us find Marion." 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I am here to take your soul to a place of peace." Damien reached out to Tittanya. "No, Iwant to stay." Tittanya's lip trembled. "Of course you do." Marion's voice came from behind her. "No, she will be coming with me." Damien lunged at Marion, a dagger appearing in his hand. Marion backed up, slashig the air with her own dagger. Suddenly she felt a cold something between her ribs. Startled, she looked down, and saw the ornate handle of Damien's dagger quivering in her chest. "Bastard!" She screamed as he stepped away. "Well yes, but that's beside the point." Damien sighed, "I've always wanted to say that." Marion turned away from his smiling face, and ran as fast as she could. 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It seemed as though Marion would avenge her sister's death after the wild persuit. The persuer landed on the roof, following her prey. Tittanya now seemed so weak. So futile.   "You can'e escape me," Marion called. There was a heavy silence, disturbed only by the howling wind.   Tittanya pushed her vibrant hair behind her face. "What are you going to do, Marion? Kill me? Tell me, girl- what good will it do?"   "You always questioned everything... Why ask questions? Why not simply accept things as they are?" Marion was shoked to find the words of the man in white coming from her own lips.   Even more astonished was Tittanya. It was eerie to hear the exact words of her late friend. Eerie like a phantom of the past finally catching up to her.   "Damien..." she coughed, before dropping backwards off the roof.      Tittanya had no recollection of falling. She awoke to find a long-haired youth looking over her. Damien.   She supressed the emotions flooding her mind, and said passively, "What are you doing back again?"   "You've changed, Tittanya," the man replied. "Three years ago you would have greeted a friend with a smile if not an embrace. I see the world has hardened you. Where's the Tittanya I knew?"   "Yon  were  my friend. Not anymore. How can you be?- you're dead!" Tittanya cried, her eyes betraying her feelings. "The world has not altered me. I changed the day you left me in this world. Damien, why are you here?"  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Soon she heardfootsteps, slow and steady like a heart beat. She turned, and her own heart beat sped up to twice the speed of the footsteps. With tensed muscles, she raised one of her arms. Just as the sound turned the corner, Tittanya threw the tiny stud. The police man she had just hit in the jugular screamed, and she absorbed the wash of fear he released. "Your aim is impressive, but you made the mistake of giving me his death. Though an unintentional gift, I thank you."  Tittanya had spun at the first word, throwing arm poised. The sight that greeted her made her hesitate. Marion leant against the wall, holding her own heart with Tittanya's knife sheathed in it. Marion found the direction of Tittanya's gaze and commented, "An Interesting symbol, the pierced heart. A symbol of love, of a broken heart." At that, Tittanya threw remaining stud. Her trembling body betrayed her, making her miss the jugular. Marion removed the silver jewelery from her cheek and inspected it curiously. then she laughed. "Ah, Tittanya. Silver does not affect me, for I am not dead. If I were, why do you think I would need the death of those such as the policeman? I am protected from death by Death, and Death has power over everything.” “Exept Immortals.” “You are not Immortal, Tittanya.” As she once again harrnessed her terror, preparing to jump, Tittanya wondered how Marion and her own positions and personalities had become so confused. Didn’t she used to be the implacable one? She thought she heard a soft whisper as she landed on the roof, a whisper that sent a shiver down her spine.  “For my sister.” It was then that Tittanya realised she should have killed Marion first.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tittanya's heart pounded. Marion was dead, that explained a lot. After a while, Tittanya slowed. She heard no footsteps, only silence. "How do I stop her?" Tittanya searched her mind. Then it came to her. Silver. That killed supernatural creatures. Pulling out her earings, Tittanya sat down to wait. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Your right, Tittanya, hearts are stupid, and weak. Why else do you think that your pittiful dagger could pemetrate mine?" Tittanya shreiked, jumped up and began to run. After only a few steps, she stopped and turned around. In her eyes was the bane of Marion's own life. Curiosity. "You needn't ask, I'll tell you anyway." Marion stood up, gracious even past the gaping hole in her chest. "You didn't realize, did you, that when you killed my sister, you killed my heart. It was dead, lifeless, before you stabbed it." Tittanya dropped the knife she was still holding, the clattering of metal against concrete drowning out the dull thud of meat landing. Marion laughed and picked up the heart that had left a bloody smear to her feet. "Are you hungry, or just terrified? Heart meat is considered a delicassy in some parts." The evil in Tittanya's eyes was somehow muted, making her more alluring than before, more human, more accessible. Then she spoke, breaking one spell while weaving a new one. "You don't understand what this terror means, Marion. You may be fuelled by death, but I am fuelled by fear. Yours may be the more powerful, but ti is also the most erratic. A sudden burst, then a fading away. Mine is ever constant and not only present in those around. I can use my own as you never will, for you are immune to your power." And with that, Tittanya harnessed the terror and ran faster than Marion ever could in her hungry state. Marion didn't try, she just picked up the knife. An instument of fear. An instrument of Death. And Tittanya's. The owner traceable through the object. "For my sister." The chase began.   
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Marion launched herself from the rickety stool and followed Tittanya into the night. Tittanya ran ahead, frantic for a way out of thismess. Marion felt like she could float away. Her sisters murderer was within reach. Just a little further. Almost. Not quite. Got her! Marion and Tittanya tumbled to the ground, growling and scratching. Then Tittanya was on top, her dagger plunging towards Marions heart.  Tittanya pulled the knife from the Marions chest. "I never thought you stupid." Tittanya whispered to the lifeless heart. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      " So, you've finally come..." Tittanya pale, thin lips curled into a sinister smile. But it was her green eyes that were the most terrifying- cold and reeking of pure evil. When Marion did not reply, Tittanya beckoned her over to the stool beside her. She held up a drink, "Let us drink to the end of a wonderful... adventure." "The end?" Marion asked, hesitantly raising the glass. "Marion, Marion." Tittanya crowed, "You know as well as I do that this pursuit cannot go on much longer. Only one of us can survive. Let us enjoy our last moments." "Why should I accept your poison?" Tittanya shrugged and sipped from her own glass. "Suit yourself." Marion eyed her nemesis suspiciously. "What are you up to this time?" "I don't understand what you mean," she said quickly, taking another drink. "You're staling, aren't you?" Marion searched Tittanya with one sweeping look from head to toe. Tittanya's glass smashed against the floor. Marion continued, having successfully intimidated Tittanya, "Stop your games, Tittanya. It all stops now! Face me like any honourable person would." To Marion's great surprise, Tittanya fled out of the bar into the dark of night 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       That night Marion began to feel hungry. She had been wandering the city, talking to her sister.As she wandered, Marion had felt something was missing. She still didn't know what, and she still had no idea where Tittanya was.Noting a bar across the road, Marion made a bee-line for it.Once in, she stopped dead. There, right in the middle of the room, was Tittanya. Her sister's murderer...  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       She looked down with surprise at the blood that soaked into the gauze to meet her own. Then she looked at the young man at her feet, the vacant expression in his eyes and the smile on his lips.   "For my sister!" Her voice had become breathless with passion. "In her death, she became my life. And now she has yours. Why do you smile? Is death so good? I wouldn't know, and you cannot tell me. Will I ever find out?" These questions flowed from her with the ease of practice. Somehow she seemed to feel an affinity with Death. She was her instrument.   Marion stopped, unsure of where this certainty the Death was female came from. Maybe it was because Death was so beautiful.   She was her instrument. A double edged expression. Just as death was the instrument of Marion, Marion was the instrument of Death.   It was a while before Marion realised that she was no longer cold in the chill breeze. She was not cold, but she was alive, so gloriously alive, and free from death. Yet she was fuelled by Death.   "Thank you."   The corpse did not respond.   "My sister is dead, but I am not. And neither is her killer. For my sister."   With the picture of Marions dying/dead sister held firmly in her mind, Marion began the long and epic quest for Tittanya.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Marion stepped out onto the road. The sunlight stabbed at her eyes, threatening to blind her.    Quickly, she looked down at the wet pavement. Seeing her reflection in the puddle at her feet, Marion thought she looked unusually pale. Then she realised that blood loss did that to you.    Shuffling along, Marion realised she was rather hungry. Thinking about where to get a good meal, she bumped into a young man.    Mumbling her apologies, Marion noticed that the young man smelt very good. Good enough to eat.    Before she could stop herself, Marion reached up and pulled the young man's head down, tasting the salty sweetness flowing in his veins.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       But she had not fainted again. It was simply that Tittanya had left her, abandoned her withput another soul in sight.   Marion played several theories around in her mind. How did she get here? How was it possible that she still lived? And it was at that moment Marion realised what the stranger in her dream had meant. It was irrelevent how all these events came to take place - the important thing was to sort out this whole mess.    Already the icy water half-filled the tub. Marion shivered involuntarily as if glacier daggers sliced through her body. She made a move to turn off the water, but her hands were weak from the wounds/ her head light from blood loss. Unable to even stand and get up, Marion reached for the gauze Tittanya had left on a nearby bench. With much splashing nd difficulty, she too managed to cover the wounds and cease the flow of blood.    Fuelled by the wild fires of revenge, Marion ignored the pain and stepped out of the bath. "For my sister," she repeated over and over lie a mantra spurring her on.     The air wa stale and surprisingly colder than the bath, but Marion took no notice. All that mattered to her was to avenge her sister's death .       To find and stop Tittanya.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Awakening from the brief dream, Marion felt light, she was lying on her back in a pool of crimson blood.   Tittanya was standing over her, her face like carved marble, expressionless.   "Why won't you die?" tittanya sounded interested, not angry.   Picking Marion up, she carried her over to a bathtub in the next room. Placing Marion in the bathtub as a mother would put her child to bed, Tittanya began to run a bath.   Bending over Marion, Tittanya slashed open her own wrist. After letting herself bleed for a couple of seconds, Tittanya picked up a roll of guaze and wrapped her wrists to stop the bleeding, then moved out of the room.   "Now to destroy the evidence." Those were the last words Marion would ever hear.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        When Marion eventually awoke, light flooded into her head. Suddenly remembering the events prior to her fainting, she selfconciously felt her wrists. No blood, no cut, no wound, nothing. Not even a scratch.   "Marion." A resonant voice came from behind her.   "W-whaa...?" She asked. Confused, she turned.   The man standing behind her looked kindly down on her. Marion felt no breeze, but his hair flickered, beams of sunlight bounced off.   "Marion." He repeated, smiling.   "I-I don't understand. What happened? Where am I? Who are you? Why are you here?" She stammered.   "You always questioned everything. I mean, thats what got you into this mess in the first place. Tittanya tried to kill you, but you're still alive. You challenged death, yet you still breathe. Why ask questions? Why not simply accept things the way they are?"      The dream faded as abruptly as it had come.    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hmm, watch out. This story has been written by 3 different people.    Marion looked into the cold, green eyes of her murderer. She saw no remorse, no triumph, no pleasure, nothing.   Shuddering, she grasped her wrist to slow the bleeding, only to have the dagger flick out again and open a vien on the exposed wrist.   "Too bad you only wrote of me as the 'Imaginary Fiend' in your diary. Now I'll get away without a mark." Tittanya's smile sent a shiver racing down Marion's spine.   Darkness crept around the edges of her vision, almost welcoming. Sighing, Marion closed her eyes and slept.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello, I am new. Therefore ignorant.  Be afraid. Be very afraid. These stories may scare the weak minded.  There are none here yet, but there will be some soon.  Kisses and wishes, Aunty fiend. 
    
</post>


<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      no, actually, her name's Jasmine... dad didn't like waffle :)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      waffle!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       yes, nay got a puppy.    let me clarify, ur.. cleaner's dog had puppies and one of them really liked it @ ur place so decided to stay there? *looks hopeful*       with the whole "year 10s moving up", i agree with mark [for once] and i think u guys should move up cos of all of the above points. "what she said" [the 'she' refers 2 our lil dorkus here]      umm.. and yeh, i don't think i'm going to the prayer rally either..      i think that's it. so.. yep, u guys have fun @ the prayer rally      cyas, dot ^_^      p.s. danie still owes me a shiny yellow star from the first sleepova :D  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      SLEEP is good for you. you should SLEEP more. i'm SLEEPy just talking about SLEEP *yawns and nods dreamily*  sorry guys, i won't be at the prayer thing tomorrow night - von and dot, you'll probably have to organise your own transport there, since i dont think my sis is coming either.  mark, Parkes is in the middle of a sheep pen, and i had the pleasure of going there. haven't u seen The Dish before?! [well, actually, i havent either, but ssshhh]  puppy, nay? 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      man, von, u gotta start sleeping - even i've stopped staying up late  (aren't you proud aren't you proud aren't you proud?!)  mark and von u get to see my puppy ^_^
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok i'm done doing my IT assignment... i think this is the latest i've ever stayed up doing hmwk...  i'll tell u guys what the website for it is when i post it.... stoopid assignment.. have to post it on the web... it'll probably be something like  urlLink www.geocities.com/cggs_2707   h&k&amp;atms,  von 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Whats with the sheep pen..i don't get it..where was it? Hm....oh well..cya  Marky<>  P.S James says that Blog is for Newspaper related stuff and political stuff but i say..STUFF U SHOVE IT WHERE THE SUN DUN SHINE!! well not really..otherwise he woulkda beaten me up:P.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      heehee..  how was sheep pen??  i take it you got home safely...  those sheep, you should probably make sure that they're not G.M. chickens...  *meep mep mep mep*  heeheehee..i'm so crap at science, it cracks me up.  yaaaay!!! i'm leading songs on sat!!! :D :D :D :D :D :D  except some ppl haven't made up their mind whether or not they're going..certain guitarists...:P
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       honestly, guys, i go to the middle of a sheep pen for  TWO DAYS  and you guys have already written heaps [not counting the messages that were posted twice]. OK, i'm gonna try and get through this  one  by  one ...      ~ Markyfish is a   neeeerrrrrrrddddddddddddd     ~ I'm generally not too fussed about bible study groups, and I can see what point everyone's making. I really would miss u guys if i went to the college group, but since the yr12's are gonna be "university" ppl, that group WOULD be really small. Anywayz, it would be like old times in Sunday School :D *pictures James shouting at all of us telling us that we're wrong, and shudders* :S   ~ I was only half-serious about the last thing I said   ~ With Marky's #1, I didn't get it either, Von, ur not the only one. I think he's just trying to be a    neeeerrrrrrddddddddd   so just leave him alone      just a very old note, i think i AM going to the anniversary lunch this sunday      Who's the new Alex? Hmm... maybe I really   DO   have to start stretching the borders       ~ Lynn ^-^          pink !!       
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      meehee.... i posted it twice... that's the stoopid computer/internet's fault. u guys will just have to put up with it. :P  was it just me or was mark being xtra nerdy today? and i didn't get his #1... maybe it has to do with dot hitting me over the head... i know what u feel like now, nate...  ok...   with the best of both worlds thing... u KNOW we're gonna drift apart... we won't get the jokes and u guys will become closer to the rest of the hs group... i dunno maybe it's just my paranoia but...   yeah i agree with mark.. maybe we SHOULD talk to other ppl... i don't feel comfortable around new ppl, but it's time to stretch those comfort zones!   with the whole angelic lil angels thing? i'm not expecting us to be angels.. that'd be too hard... we can joke, all i'm asking is for us to shut up when ppl are talking.. cos sitting on the other end of the table, it's kinda hard to hear when someone sitting closer to u is talking... about irrevelant stuff...   keep talking guys, it'd be cool to hear ALL of ur views...  h&k&amp;atms,  von  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ooh a few more pointers to add..  1) Although there are people joining there wouldn't be a suffice amount of people who would start at the start of the yr...there may be people who join mid-way thrgouh but we don't kno that. Last yr, when they formed the new HS group i dunno if im right here..but didn't all of us (well excluding me i joined mid-yr)  join right at the start of the yr? They had a decent number of "freshmans" coming into yf so they could put another group together...hehe freshmans can't wait for uni.  2) I don't think it is a good idea for the yr10 ppl to stay with the Hs group and i do have a good reason for this. One of the reasons why we go to tehillah is to have fellowship and trying to put this in a non-harsh way..but i think that people in Y/f should learn to be more open to people. We have to stretch our borders of friendship in a way..we have to welcom the new people... I kno for one that hardly any of us have spoken to Tom or Alex  (yes the new alex..i kno who im talking about) so yup.  That way if the yr10's join the college group it would expand ur friendship boundaries. U get the best of both worlds ain't that great?:D Plus the college group is small enough it needs some people to bolster the group otherwise it'll probably end up folding...  3) Yes we all shuold concentrate but the thing is when ur in such a large group that makes it hard..the reason y sometimes we just start taling is coz the answer is at the other end of the table and we can't hear it..don't get me wrong it would be lovely for all of us to be lil' angelic angels but i for one wouldn't be able to do that for a whole bs session...dunno 'bout u guys though except for nate:P  That is it i beleive..hmm..yes..i dropped my monickle will be back..tarry on  Marky<> 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      to read a totally random story go to my blog. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      gahh!! the blogspot thing is dodgy!! it deleted my post!  whoa... we've got like 56 posts on this thing.. that's what the counting thingo said neways  dotpoints cos they're fun... :P   lynn and i haven't quite decided what we're going to do about the college group thing.. and i'm not sure about sherman and george... if we have to, then i guess we have no choice.. but i think we're more comfortable with u guys... i know that we'll be making "new friends" but seriously... i really don't wanna change groups now. also do u think it's possible if the new ppl next yr just made a bs group by themselves, that is if there are more ppl than tim and moses.. cos that's what our sunday school group did when we joined yf.   by "our group is getting a bit too big" i didn't mean split up!! we won't be us if we're in two or more groups and we wouldn't get as many ppl's opinions and stuff.. we wouldn't get as much out of it... i've got lotsa pros and cons for the splitting up bit... i dunno how to say this nicely but maybe we could get the ppl who talk a lot to split up into two different groups or next yr if there's gonna be another hs group other than us, they could move to that one...   that uncontrollable thing? it's true, we're controllable.. if we could get EVERYONE to shut up and concentrate.. but that's a bit hard with such a big group/ some ppl ... we've changed a lot since last yr and our bible studies are gettin more discussion-y... that's gd... but we need evry1 to try and concentrate so that they can get the most out of it and so that they learn more about God, which should be their purpose for coming to yf... not just to socialise.. cos they can do that after church and stuff....   by splitting up, we wouldn't be doing that to escape ppl but to give ppl the opportunity to talk... like putting half of the ppl who talk and half of the ppl who don't talk in one group and the other halves in the other group.... but nay's right... the "quiet" ppl might get more intimidated... i was like that last yr and the yr b4... and we had fairly small groups then... but u guys  know  that u can speak up anytime u want to.. just raise ur hand and wave it around a bit...   another thing... when ppl say things that we don't agree with, maybe it's completely off, but don't all start yelling at them... it's bad enough knowing that ur answer is wrong, u don't need the whole group yelling @ u... it's intimidating and it's enough to make someone not contribute to the discussion for some time... the one person speaking at a time thing....   thanx guys...  h&k&amp;atms,  von 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok.... looks like i started a whole heap of spam... aren't we glad it's not thru email? it'd be like wk 2 again... scary stuff that...  ok... dot points cos they're fun!   lynn and i haven't yet decided what we wanna do about the whole college group thingo... not sure about sherman and george. we aren't too keen on leaving u guys... don't u feel luved! :P and there was another thing which i've forgotten.. do u think that's it's a possibility that the new ppl next yr form a group of their own if there are more ppl than just tim and moses? cos that's what our sunday school class did when we joined yf...   by too big a group i wasn't suggesting that we split cos i agree that it wouldn't be as fun and as educational.. if that's the proper word to use... we wouldn't get as much out of it... but if u guys wanna say something just stick ur hand up and wave it around... we'll notice u... but mainly the ppl that i'm talking to aren't members of this blog.... that's kinda weird...   also i've found out that the area of the table where the stooges/nay/lynn/dot/tara/me are, mainly the ppl who contribute  the most  to the discussion (and i'm not saying that the others don't), is always the easiest to concentrate in... on sat i found that i really had to strain to listen and i was getting distracted a lot...   also guys, maybe we should be more accepting... if someone says something that we don't agree with, don't all start yelling @ them or arguing against them... it can be kinda intimidating especially knowing that ur answer is wrong, u don't need the whole group trying to disprove ur answer... one person @ a time thing...    :D thanks guys for responding so fast...   and after we're done doing this we could think about bible study books that we wanna do... the life together series (i think that's what they're called) sound pretty gd... kinda expensive though...  h&k&amp;atms,  von 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
                       okay, accidentally posted this to the wrong  blog..*blushes* sorry..      &nbsp;    1. There's at least 5 people leaving our group and  moving up to the college group next year. Lynn, Von, Sherman, George, and I  think Aimee?      &nbsp;    2. Let me clarify something - I don't mean that  everyone MUST always have something to say, I don't mean that you should say  something if you really don't feel comfortable with it. But we all need to  realise that that's what Bible study is about: studying the Bible together,  discussing the text! Why else would we have a Bible study GROUP if it was for  one person to talk and talk and everyone else to listen? There are times to  listen, times to talk, and we kind of have to do both, peoples : )&nbsp; Plus, I  assure you, it's much easier to talk out of your own choice rather than the  leader pick on you...      &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      if we break up it ill be kinda not as exciting... that might sound kind of dumb but yeh... but then if we do break up people might speak out more and that would be good! but i like the big group... i dunno.  hehehe the school flooded today and i went around to my friend's place and she had a karaoke machine and it was fun as! hehehe
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      if we break up it ill be kinda not as exciting... that might sound kind of dumb but yeh... but then if we do break up people might speak out more and that would be good! but i like the big group... i dunno.  hehehe the school flooded today and i went around to my friend's place and she had a karaoke machine and it was fun as! hehehe
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Heelo all...aah this is an interesting subject to talk about ain't it..its been on my mind for a very long time and time and time time time...  1. I think i was talking to nick and yeah he said no leader to lead us so it'll be leaderless...  2. I like the #2..it sounds kool but um there are alot of pros for being in smaller groups sometimes...Stronger freindship bonds are formed when in closer proximity of people...hehe proximity...nggaahhh neerrrrd!!  3. People may sometimes open up in smaller groups as there are not as many ppl there...i dunno...  Meh i don't mind whether we stick together or not for the time being except..it is gonna get bigger next yr.  Although 2 memebers are leaving moses, andrew, tim are joining.  I kno moses and tim are definites and there are probably more people coming so just bear all of this in mind people.  P.S Haha Chueck went to Yohan's birthday party...Did u go just for the food or did u go as a good friend?:P Haha one up on chueck.  Marky<> 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      a lot of people think our group is getting too big..  i think it is a bit too big, and i know some of you want to split off into groups. but there are some things we need to consider:  1. there's less to learn - you have to admit that we have some pretty interesting discussions, that's one of the pros of having a large group - there are more opinions to share.  2. if we have smaller groups, yes, the "quiet people" might speak up. or they might get even more freaked out, and like, two people are always talking, and those two people end up getting nothing out of our Bible studies..  3. think about what it's going to be like when it's you and someone you really don't like stuck in the same group. i know i shouldn't say that, but you know i have a point - i seriously do not mind being in the same group as any of the people in the group already, but just a point to consider, in the hope of "escaping" from these people, you might actually end up having to deal with them more..SO not a valid point for separating into two groups.  4. we don't have the leaders.  5. even if we did have another leader, everybody likes having evan as a leader.    I agree that the group is getting a bit too big, but i think for now we should stay as one big group. i'm not going to mention any names up here. but seriously, some of you hardly ever say anything at Bible study - you're really going to get more out of it if you do ask questions, and you do share. You should know who you are.. I think our group has some issues to deal with before we split up into another group, and the only reason I can think of that's a good enough point to split the group up is that we're "uncontrollable" - which last saturday night disproved..we CAN focus, we just have to try. So try.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i aint going to the prayer rally.  im going to a PARTY!!!!  yay  =) 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yip... youth sunday was  fantastisch!!    good work guys!! :D  i might be coming to the prayer rally on sat... depends on whether my family decides we're going to sydney or not... hmm... it's most likely a no to the sydney thing cos of transport and accomodation and stoof like that  guys? about our bs group, i think we're getting a bit big... i notice that there are ppl who say a lot and have lots to contribute to the discussion and also ppl who don't say much... i dunno whether this is cos they don't have anything to say/ don't know what to say or because they're overwhelmed... anyone got any suggestions?  tararaboomdeeay is a barney song... did u know that? gave me kinda a shock when i first heard it... and it's tararabooMdeeay or rather ta-ra-ra-boom-de-ay... but i still reckon tararaboompdeaay sounds better.. so tara can be the one with the P and the song can be the one without the p...  lynn... i'm always posting @ school because.. i have nothing to do/am slacking off and cos i don't get much time to post @ home... because of SOME ppl.... :P nah.. it's cos i always go on late neways and also it takes up a lot of our downloading megabyte-y thingos...  yeah... this is getting kinda long so i'm going now... u guys have a gr8 wk and wknd if i don't see u and remember to prepare for bs!! :P it's time and gifts.. should be interesting... specially Q1...  h&k&amp;atms,  von 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       this one's for danie...      the magician says, "i'm going to pull out a rabbit from my hat"   and u say, "that's impossible!"   and then he does it, and ur like, "wow, that's amazing!"      i'll be in the middle of a sheep pen [dont laugh, nay] for the next two days, but i'll probably be at the prayer rally if i can ^-^  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. i remember lydia's win...that was when i wasn't in their section, mwahahahahahahahaha :P plus raymond was performing, so i pretty much had no competition. that's so sad. :( +++  :P +++ don't worry cheuk, they're both beatable. you just gotta find where your strong spots are and make sure you flaunt them.  2. battle of the bands? :P hehehehehehehehehe  3. and you should be happy i can still sing *lalalalalallalalalalalalalala.*  4. how many of you are going to the prayer rally nxt sat night?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah..but highly competent at what? Being a drum nerd and an idiot?hmm....must be one of the 2 there...i can't see him getting a highly competent for anything else:P. Hehe..ahh ooh are u going into a battle of the bands? Oh can i come can i come? Then i could be like security backstage and have glasses on and have that macho voice:D. Aahhh..anywayz..nothing to worry about peoples! I found my pencil under the computer desk..so its all good now.  Marky<> 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        *hums quietly to herself and pretends to understand all this piano talk*       nate...   NOBODY CARES   btw, mark, 'hc' means 'highly competent' and considering there are only two other levels, hc isnt that great [at least there were only three when i did it last year]      yf tonite... and im really nervous about youth sunday tomorrow and   nay  , how can u lose ur voice  now ?! oh yeah, im not sure if ne of my friends from skool r coming tomorrow, but in case they do,   pls   dont scare them       and how come von's always posting from skool? von,   brisbane is  AFTER  the uk; sometime in october i think...       one last thing - for all the muso ppl reading this, are any of u going in   battle of the bands  ? coz i think its being held at my skool and if it is  dont laugh at me and my friends . yep, i think thats about it      ~ lynn ^-^  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Nah..i reckon Lydia is gonna win. 2 yrs ago at the battison Lydia came 1st and Luke came 2nd..but...i dunno how this yr is gonna turn out.. Anyway what is "hc" and y is nate braggin about it? That just means we have a new resdent nerd...Nggaahhhh nerd..*sigh* i guess im just trying to throw off the reputation of being a nerd which im not!!:P hehe...aah..where did my pencil go?..i swear i saw it a minute ago..better go look for it now.  Marky<> 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      1. yeah, i've told those jokes a million times. though i couldn't help it, it's all nate's fault.  2. i reckon luke allerton's gonna win. but that's depending on what the set piece is...cheuky you better get it memorised...  3. shut up nate, you show-off. and slacker. *rolls eyes* the rest of us did good too, you don't hear us bragging about our results.  4. don't worry cheuk. don't stress out about science and stuff. you got 101 or 104 or something on your science test.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      u noe, i actually like this spam stuff. i agree with mark soz von, lydia is a piano freak i hope im not versing her or luke Allerton. hey mark if u didnt get in the battison *points and does the haha thing that Nelson does* my sister beat u she made reserve! nah jk its not ur fault u stuffed up on the day.   
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hahahahaha exhibitions  i got hc for EVERYTHING! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey mark! watch what u say! :P lydia dobson goes to my school... yip i'm @ school... and we're doing a IT assign. and we've got a free rein... so von does her own thing now and then panics the day b4... always works like that...    yf tomorrow!! :D i don't really know why i miss u guys so much.. it's kinda weird...   h&k&atms,   von     { When you need me, I'll always be there }   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Aah well..congrats on making it to the Battison chueck did ur sis' make it as well and do ya kno who ur v.s? Haha..good luck when if ur versing Lydia Dobson and Luke Allerton..the'yre kinda like piano freaks so bests to avoid them. OH and whos going to the Church aniversary lunch thingo? Am i like the only one whos going to lunch? PLS SAY ITS NOT SO!!!! I don't wanna be the only youngen tye're going like "oh...yup the rest of em' ditched me so i'm just sitting next to my rents who are talking about the typical asian stuff i.e  study, grades and future jobs for thier children"...Ahh...the oylmpics have started!!:D I can't beleive that Iraq beat Portugal haha but then again it is funny..:P And Greece drew with South Korea..mmm...veeery interesting. CYa guys at y/f  Marky<> 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i think sometimes he surfs doesnt he?  and is it just me or did this blog thing change? liek you can change font colurs and stuff now. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      cheuk sounds stressed... glad i didn't have to do exhibitions... :P although, i don't remember lynn complaining... maybe it's just u, cheuk...  lynn's going to brisbane?! is this b4 or after england?  tara had a dream about robbing nay's house? ^o) ok then...  i'm so sleepy but i've gotta do so many things.. not hmwk, finished for this wk!! :D well, until tomorrow anyway...  youth sunday's on sunday!! :D excited!! hopefully i'll be able to sing free in tune this time... keep praying about it, guys... and invite ur friends!! :D  meehee i like this spam thing.. don't have to worry about how long the email is/ if ppl really don't wanna know and we're blocking up their inbox for less important things...:P  i'm happy.. got my science comp results back... and our german teacher gave us a freddo today... i LIKE freddos... they're yummy... cept that freddo was skiing on my wrapper... was freddo ALWAYS skiing before?  h&k&amp;atms,  von 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i hate exhibitions its so gay and its useless for my future. I have sooooo much work 2 i got science, english, health, spanish and maths which hasnt bin given yet i hope they 4get. oh man i hav 2 hand in a minimum 10 pg assignment 4 science and a stupid model of a house by tuesday. On top of all that i have stupid battison and stupid eistedfodd and stupid miles franklin. im all stressed out. I think they should ban exhibitions 4 life 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       ...in about two months, but meh *shrugs*       yeah, that's about all i had to say ^-^ [well, this IS a spam site after all]  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i had this cool dream last night... it was early in the morning before the sun rose, and i was jogging and there was this big oval with all this yellow canola and i was like 'cool' and then i jogged over to this house and I broke in and I was like 'oh i could steal some stuff' so I started taking things and then Nay's mum walked in and I found out I was robbing nay's house. It was funny [not that i would rob you nay]. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      huh? wasn't the pilot a loaf of bread and that's why the plane crashed? ah well breadstick sounda better. haha sounda. that was a typo but it sounds kinda cool. im tired. i have no school tomorrow. i have to do homework. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ur weird... all weird...  i don't think it's northside... just nay and nate... they're crazy... :P  yes, mark, moderation day is all on the same day. for those of us who have it, that is! *evil cackle* hehe poor public school ppl/dot's school which doesn't have a college... nevermind guys, two years from now we'll all be having moderation day... although we're all supposed to be studying then... hmm... at least none of us are boys grammar ppl... they don't get moderation day... meehee...  i'm thinking of going for chapel vice captain next year... what d'you guys think? i know, my time management skills will have to improve drastically... considering i'm the only one out of u guys who's on @ the moment doing hmwk.. nay would be on, but she's @ camp... : i'm lonely...  lynn was supposed to call me about prayer group tomorrow... or maybe she called when i was having my piano lesson... hmmm oh well, i think it's too late to call now...  ooh this is a looooong one...  h&k&amp;atms,  von  ps: nate? fools never differ 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hehe...  Ripped!!:P Ripped to the ground. Anywayz...dum dum de dum...nuthing else to say really.  Marky<>  P.S Do all schools have moderation day on the same day or not? 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok, i'm with marky on this one     *whispers* i think there's just something really wrong with north-side humour  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      read the title ...  ISNT THAT RITE NAY !!!!!!!!  mark u gotta be stoned to get them. thus  'stoner'  jokes. duh. stick to what you know nay make mark make my dinner!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Is it just me or are the jokes meant to be funny..? 'Coz i don't find them remotely funny at all...Especially the stoner jokes...are they jokes only for stoner's or are they jokes told by stoners...wats going on?!?!? Oh well..i think we've seen enough of those so called *ahem ahem* jokes...Haver a good week at skool ppl's and cya at y/f!:D  Marky<> 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      why did the boy fall off his bike?                because someone threw a fridge at him. why did the boy fall off the swingset??                because he had no arms.  why did bob fall off the swingset?               because he's a breadstick.  why did the bus crash?                bob was driving  BAHAHAHAHA! :D
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      why can't a cat milk itself?                    because it has no face. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      what did one cow say to the other cow?               "we're cows" 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      what do you get if you water a cloud?                    a sheep!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hi my bloggy thing works now ur free 2 go on it 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      actually, nay's les miserables song isn't quite that bad... kinda weird, but not bad.. i found my mum's cd(s) and then dot stole it off me cos she didn't like the song... some songs sound familiar... why is that? and that guy's voice on track 8 is REALLY high...  hmm... what was i gonna say?  oh yes, for those guys who saw me crying @ church, i'm ok... just a bit high-strung @ the moment... i'll get over it... :D  love you all... and thanx for being there for me always always always  h&k&amp;atms,  von 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      and you probably don't want to hear tomorrow's another day but i promise you you'll see the sun again and you're asking me why pain's the only way to happiness and i promise you you'll see the sun again   :) loving you always, God's always there for you. :) 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      tara with her hair out reminds me of a christmas tree.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Geez...wats with nay..shes gone a bit kooko-clock..whacko for schmakos...a bit of a blistering barncales if u kno wat i mean..but u probs don't so..i dunno..ask james to see wat im taking about im not even sure if he knos wat im saying.  Marky<> 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      *In love in love...* i think im gonna be sick.  its nay for crying out loud! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      nay's in love nay's in love nay's in love... with...   the song "a little fall of rain" from les miserables...*sigh* (yes, she rediscovered her 2CD set...hehe von..does this bring back memories..... one day more! another day another destiny :P  it's so sad *bursts into tears* such a bittersweet ending... :( :) :( :) ? gaah it's so sweet   *in trying to return to the barricade to give marius news from cosette, eponine is shot and fatally injured.*  eponine:  don't you fret, m'sieur marius, i don't feel any pain a little fall of rain can hardly hurt me now. you're here, that's all i need to know and you will keep me safe and you will keep me close and rain will make the flowers grow.  marius: but you will live, 'ponine - dear God above, if i could close your wounds with words of love.  eponine: just hold me now, and let it be. shelter me, comfort me.  marius: you would live a hundred years if i could show you how i won't desert you now...  eponine: the rain can't hurt me now.. this rain will wash away what's past and you will keep me safe and you will keep me close i'll sleep in yrou embrace at last. the rain that brings you here is heaven blessed the skies begin to clear and i'm at rest a breath away from where you are i've come home, from so far  eponine:  so don't you fret, m'sieur marius  i don't feel any pain a little fall of rain can hardly hurt me now.  marius (interjections) : hushabye, dear eponine you won't feel any pain a little fall of rain can hardly hurt you now. i'm here.  eponine: that's all i need to know and you will keep me safe and you will keep me close  marius (interjections): i will stay with you till you are sleeping.  eponine: and rain  marius: and rain   eponine:  will make the flowers... *begins to die*  marius: will make the flowers.. grow.   *everyone bursts into tears* 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      apologies to cheuk on the comment for the pants-on rule from nate.   i should stop paying you out so much...i'm getting really tight.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      happys birthdays taras :D 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       actually, it's not that bad.. i just feel like complaining.    but spam was definetely easier ;)   anyways, how was school ppl?      cyas, dot ^_^   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yut yee sam...testing testing...one two three hi every1 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      if we're not supposed to have pre maritial *oomph* how does a pants on rule sound? 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      helloooooooo guys!! :D i'm @ school, i can read all ur blogs, but can't reply...     someone tell dan the words to the song.   and i'll figure out the website for tara's blog   luv y'all   h&k&atms,   von   { When you need me, I'll always be there }   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hehe...3 days and now we also have a prayer blog:  http://hsprayers.blogspot.com  you've all been sent invites. Let me know if your invite doesn't work - the only two people yet to set up accounts are Sherman and George. (Although we do have to wait until Cheuk figures out how to actually use his.)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well you see i wanted to start my own post thingy... so you all have to reply so it is cool. this blog thing is kinda classy... well it's my birthday in two days! im pumped. i gotta go to bed though. ciao now...  tara xxx 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      okay, cheuk says spam without him...i can't explain to him how to work everything...and somebody please confirm to me that   http://cheukycheungy.blogspot.com  does not work??
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      couple of things:  - the posts should be appearing in chronological order now, it's just that before the time zone for the spam blog was if we were in LA.  - we shouldn't need to worry too much about the colours, cos I'm not going to bother...something's wrong with my comp. But considering I'm using my rgwcb account, it should read "nay" in my signature. Nate's is "nay", mark's is "stooge 2", dan's is "the FLY", von's is "viciousdurian" ...we should be right.  - how is it possible that this whole blogging thing started like, 2 days ago.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
                     urlLink      urlLink    urlLink   
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ooh thats good does this mean we can spam here to our hearts content? Yay..yippe... spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam spam..ahh i think i've got it out of my system^_^  Thanks von and nay for setting it up:D  Signing out marky<> 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       LOOK at me i need some attention   attention   thats what im looking for   turn around and look at me cause i need some attenshun    like right now   please?   hey! you stop stealing my attention   i need a pension   does that even make sense son?   give me more attention cause i need some    please?      =))))))-fat smiley with lots of chins  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Testing...  *meuh*  luv, nay xoxo
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      we've made it so that you can contribute here, like write entries, on your own accounts. you just have to accept our invite that we sent you.  for those who don't have your own accounts, set 'em up. nay
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        we should all have colours so that we don't have to even read the spam to know who it's frm... it's all font/colour coded      and btw, guys, this is the only time i'm gonna encourage u to SPAM AWAY!!!! mega coolness!!      h&k&amp;atms,      von   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      nay:  http://viciouspear.blogspot.com  von: http://magelet89.blogspot.com  dan: http://stooge_1.blogspot.com  mark: http://stooge_2.blogspot.com  nate: http://stooge_3.blogspot.com  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>