<Blog>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          It's so unfair,   
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         HAPPY NATIONAL DAY TO EVERYONE!!  
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Baptised today....it was way cool...Too bad my closest friend didn't come..sigh..but it has past i can't possibly turn back time...oh well..my pastor asked the three of the people getting baptised to share a testimony to the whole church..i got a shock to hear that we needed to share a testimony..i whispered t my pastor..and he told me that no one informed him too..so..bravely, i went up to the so called stage..and just said every single thing that came to my mind about what God has done in my life..and every one laughed..and i became embarrassed..(obviously)well...a great experience today..first person in the family to really and truly get baptised...everybody cheered..thanks for my supporters..if they read this post..hee!Well..i shaked so many people's hand...but i'm sick..haha!everyone said i did i great job....hehe!okay..i'll stop here..greatest moment in my twelve years..hee!bye..    
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey there!book and music week was held on the 4th and 5th of august..and the school really had a fun time watching concerts..4th of August,the first performance was performed by the dance girls (my cca) It rocks!everybody loved the dance..so proud of my cca..hehe..well..i'm so totally sick...i dun feel good..back to the point..today..erm...i perfomed as a kc idol..well...everyone looked so pretty and elegant..put so much make up on must be..i can't even say my lines properly cause i was sick...not fair!hmph!hehe..so childish..ok..stop here... 
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Well....it was pastor ben's birthday..and we actually saboed him on that particular love feast..i didn't expect him to bring a big water gun..while we only saboed him using our own water bottles. It was so fun!Ienjoyed myself very much...well...i got wet somehow..because of some crazy people!(innocent party!)And the most unfortunate thing is that...I DIDNT BRING CLOTHES!!This guy from my church called Xing wen..he brought baby powder?he put a whole bunch of powder on my head..my hair was like grey?!And my church friends actually teased me by saying "oh..!!you grew so old in such a short time..."(something like that)And called me a grandma or ah ma(chinese saying)really enjoy my church..this crazy guy from vs...named..*should not specify*saboed me just because...blah blah blah!such a irritating person...stopping here...toodl3s!   
      
</post>


</Blog>