<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am actually updating my blog through my hp haha. technology makes me powerful!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Coffee! Sounds great...this week i got job offers  from an IT company looking for freelance web designers.  SO IM LOOKING FOR ONE NOW.  If you happen to be one, please post your comment here and insert your homepage link. Anyway im starting work tomorrow  hope everything is gonna be alright. And i got my new phone! urlLink      
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi,  hasnt been blogging for quite a while. Well i found a job and hope everything is going smoothly on tuesday for the interview. Ha, but what the hell that is not a great job, I find it lame but i don have a choice for now just hang on for as long as i can till i get another better job. I need the money as well, to get my business going with my buddies like geraldine and marieanne. Hopefully things can turn out well and when the profit comes in, i can quit my job... 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The "decisive" moment  urlLink    He was my mentor, my teacher, who taught me to use my heart instead of my equipment. Thank you so much for everything.Henri Cartier-Bresson, who used his tiny, hand-held 35-millimeter Leica camera to bear humane witness to many of the 20th century's biggest events, from the Spanish Civil War to the German occupation of France to the partition of India to the Chinese revolution to the French student uprisings of 1968, died on Tuesday at his home in Southwest France. He was 95.A private funeral was held yesterday, according to a statement from his family and Magnum, the photo agency he helped establish. Mr. Cartier-Bresson seemed to know everyone and to see everything of importance throughout the middle decades of the last century. Even in his later years, when he more or less abandoned photography to draw, he remained an astonishing live wire who liked to say that his approach to life had been shaped by Buddhism. His wife, the photographer Martine Franck, described him to the Dalai Lama as "a Buddhist in turbulence."He photographed dozens of luminaries: his pictures of a convalescent Matisse during World War II, of Sartre as a boulevardier and of Mahatma Gandhi minutes before he was killed have become icons of photographic portraiture. But he was also the archetype of the itinerant photojournalist during the heyday of photojournalism immediately after the war, before television became widespread, when millions of people still learned what was happening in the world through the pictures that ran in magazines like Life and Paris-Match. His photographs, later collected in numerous books, were always considered remarkable for their empathy; Lincoln Kirstein called Mr. Cartier-Bresson "a responsible artist, responsible to his craft and to his society."It was Mr. Cartier-Bresson's prestige, along with that of Robert Capa, George Rodger and David Seymour, known as Chim, that established Magnum Photos, which they founded in 1947, as the world's premier photo agency. Under its aegis, Mr. Cartier-Bresson went to China, India, Indonesia, Egypt, Cuba, the Soviet Union.But he was far more than a gifted photojournalist. He combined a Rabelaisian appetite for the world with a clarity of vision and intellectual rigor that linked him to French masters like Poussin. His wit, lyricism and ability to see the geometry of a fleeting image and capture it in the blink of an eye reshaped and created a new standard for the art of photography. If in later years a certain sentimentality crept into some of his pictures, his best photographs, many of them from the 1930's, when he most strongly bore the imprint of Surrealism, are simply among the best works of 20th-century art.In 1932, he stuck his camera between the slats of a fence near the St.-Lazare railway station in Paris at precisely the right instant and captured a picture of the watery lot behind the station, strewn with debris. A man has propelled himself from a ladder that lies in the water. Photographs of puddle jumpers were clichés then, but Mr. Cartier-Bresson brings to his image layer on layer of fresh and uncanny detail: the figure of a leaping dancer on a pair of posters on a wall behind the man mirrors him and his reflection in the water; the rippling circles made by the ladder echo circular bands of discarded metal debris; another poster, advertising a performer named Railowsky, puns with the railway station and the ladder, which, flat, resembles a railroad track.No wonder other photographers couldn't believe Mr. Cartier-Bresson's luck, much less his skill. The term that has come to be associated with him is "the decisive moment," the English title of "Images à la Sauvette" ("Images on the Run" might be a closer translation), a book of his photographs published in 1952. Mr. Cartier-Bresson described "the simultaneous recognition in a fraction of a second of the significance of an event, as well as the precise organization of forms that give that event its proper expression." Content plus geometry.Walker Evans reviewed "The Decisive Moment" when it was published. "What Cartier-Bresson has is a more or less dependable ability to snap a picture," he wrote, "just when a child takes off into an ecstatic state of being as he skips beside a wall that is covered with an unearthly design of some lunarlike patina." The photograph to which Evans referred shows a boy in Valencia, Spain, in 1933, his upturned face giving him the surreal look of someone in a trance, a look akin to divine rapture. In reality the boy was waiting to catch a ball he had tossed in the air. It was Mr. Cartier-Bresson's genius to see instantaneously how the child's expression would take on new meaning if the ball were not visible in the picture. Nicolas Nabokov, the composer and writer, once described Mr. Cartier-Bresson as having a "blond and pink head" and "gently mocking smile." (In Mexico, where Mr. Cartier-Bresson lived in 1934, he was called the man with cheeks "the color of shrimp.") His eyes, Nabokov said, were "like darts, sharp and clever, limpidly blue and infinitely agile." Later in life those eyes were behind thick lenses when he drew. His hair thinned. Tall, wiry, studiously unostentatious, with patrician bearing, he retained a boyish, Gallic charm and a kind of loping gait. He was a proud and mischievous man, thoroughly French, though Dan Hofstadter, writing in The New Yorker some years ago, compared Mr. Cartier-Bresson's appearance to that of "a Scandinavian socialist schoolmaster en route to a May Day parade."Degas once said, "It's wonderful to be famous as long as you remain unknown." Mr. Cartier-Bresson loved that remark and carried the photojournalistic penchant for invisibility to such attention-getting lengths as to shield his face while receiving an honorary degree at Oxford. In the United States he sometimes traveled under an alias, Hank Carter. "I'm not an actor," he insisted. "What does it mean, 'celebrity'? I call myself an artisan. Anyone with sensitivity is potentially an artist. But then you must have concentration besides sensitivity."He tried to immerse himself in places before photographing them, to blend into and learn about their cultures. "I'm not interested in my photographs, nor other people's," he once said.Photographers and others who saw him work talked about his swift and nimble ability to snap a picture undetected. (Sometimes he even masked the shiny metal parts of his camera with black tape.) They also admired his coolness under pressure. The director Louis Malle remembered that despite all the turmoil at the peak of the student protests in Paris in May 1968, Mr. Cartier-Bresson took photographs at the rate of only about four an hour.He insisted that his works not be cropped but otherwise disdained the technical side of photography; the Leica was all he ever wanted to use; he wasn't interested in developing his own pictures."My contact sheets may be compared to the way you drive a nail in a plank," he said. "First you give several light taps to build up a rhythm and align the nail with the wood. Then, much more quickly, and with as few strokes as possible, you hit the nail forcefully on the head and drive it in."Henri Cartier-Bresson was born in Chanteloup, not far from Paris, on August 22, 1908, the oldest of five children in a wealthy family so puritanically frugal, he once said, that as a small boy he thought he was poor. He was a descendant of Charlotte Corday, Marat's assassin, a fact he liked to point out. His father was a textile manufacturer; at one time almost every French sewing kit was stocked with Cartier-Bresson thread. On his mother's side were cotton merchants and landowners in Normandy, where he spent part of his childhood.He was educated in Paris. "I went to the École Fénelon, a Catholic school that prepared you for the Lycée Condorcet, and one day the proctor there caught me reading a volume of Rimbaud or Mallarmé, right at the start of the school year, in the lower sixth. He said to me: 'Let's have no disorder in your studies!' He used the informal 'tu' - which usually meant you were about to get a good thrashing. But he went on: 'You're going to read in my office.' Well, that wasn't an offer he had to repeat."He read, among other things, Proust, Dostoyevsky, Nietzsche and a book on Schopenhauer that he said led him to Romain Rolland and to Eastern philosophy. "That had a huge effect on me,'' he said. "I had never been a Christian believer. My mother once said: 'Poor dear, if only you had a good Dominican confessor, you wouldn't be in such a fix!"'He recalled being struck, while still a teenager, by several of Martin Munkacsi's photographs. "I said to myself: 'How can one do that?' - that combination of plastic beauty and vitality. When I saw those photographs, I said to myself: 'Now here's something to do.' " ...  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The day i thrashed Yao Ming  urlLink     Yao wasnt my match, as we approached to double hill scores my no. 34 Shaq came and gave him the "Shaq-Attack"...he just stood there helplessly watching him dunk. Then came Kobe Bryant...doing all the Alle Hoops and his moves on power dribbling, oh boy he is such a brilliant player...and Karl Malone, fantastic. Payton was the underdog....silent but deadly. Eat socks Phoenix Suns. La Lakers Rules. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Just came back from JB. Had supper there. Bought 2 "original" vcds....i was thinking will it be difficult to sell off the Leica body. Hopefully not, cause i want my new Sony Ericsson P910i&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    His my brother...this little chap is actually a monkey that climb trees. Havent been seeing him for a year or so. Last time i saw him his head was as big as ever.And still so hyper-active.  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My sister  urlLink     Dats my sis. My real younger sis. She can be a bitch sometimes, always thinking of how much she has grown ....we always fought while we are younger almost over everything. Glad dat she has become more independent and getting married soon. FINALLY SOMEONE WANTS HER.  She can be so petty at certain times, i wonder wad she will say after reading this.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Walking back home...  urlLink     Finally, after days of putting some extra stuff in my portfolio and getting it printed out, i tot it was mission accomplished but fuck. My translink card went missing and i had to walk from home to the post office... 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bye Bye my Summicron lens  urlLink     Hi Leica, Its been fun having you. I took great care of you and u showed me a different world. I really appreciate all the wonderful moments we had together and i wished we had longer time. It was a diffcult decision for me to sell u off and now what i left is your body. But what can i do? Sigh. Neverthless i will never forget you.  Take care my friend.  Guys, my Leica body is still for sale at $2200. M6 Chrome classic and non TTL. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me, myself & Leica  urlLink    Its been like 7 mths since i graduate and i havent got a job. Ermm i did found some but i quit. Maybe i was too choosy but i didnt see myself getting far staying in there for long...I sent in "free Coupons" to Advertising agencies. Sent in 10 but i got 1 reply. Sigh..Well better than nothing, so i went for the interview at DDB. Anyone knows what DDB stands for? I did my research and it stands for "Dane Doyle Bernbach". Didnt turn out well, guess they didnt like my work. My plans now are to try again and again. Never give up.Today is really a bad bad day...lost my translink card, my prints got errors and my handphone charger was spoilt. Damn it! Im so stressed now about my career and my financial problems...sooner or later i gotta sell backside.Oh Yea...TO THAT BASTARD WHO PICKED UP A TRANSLINK CARD AT TOA PAYOH I KNOW WHO U ARE...MILLION CURSES TO YOUR FAMILY AND YOUR CHILDREN'S CHILDREN 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Batam1  urlLink    Hi guys,How are ya? I just came back from a trip to Batam...really hot day. Well, i didnt go there for fun cause i don play golf. Shopping? We have Orchard road or i rather travel all der way to KL...which i think i will be going within 2 more weeks....I was at Batam for a charity. My friend from his church and called me to join them. Well, i cant be bothered whether church or not thing...ya know. Woke up at 6.30 am in der morning and had to put poor milow up in his cage the whole day. Reached Harbour Front at 8 plus and saw the rest of the ppl, i think almost 40 of us, some of them had luggages. At first i tot " wah lau, go there for holiday meh?"Took the ferry and reached Batam and of all things of all things...believe it or not i dropped my departure card on der ferry ride and the custom officier kept on asking me to search my pockets....bloody hell told him i lost it on the ferry but he keep on insisting i should search my pocket...i told him i lost in English and he reply me in Indonesian...like 5 times? 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Batam2  urlLink    In der end the chap wanted SG 2 bucks so i gave him and he made a new one within 5 minutes..champion lah. Made me freak out for nothing. Boarded a bus that looks like it survived cold war...stinking petrol smell in der bus and with air cons dat provide u spa service....soon we reached der place where everything starts...And the Sister was asking me is this the first time im in Batam in Indonesian accent...The rural side of Batam, just several kilometres aways from Singapore lives the poorest people i have ever seen or worse, Aizhen should have called u along....these people are so poor that they built their houses with wooden planks above the very very polluted swamps, i couldnt find fresh water at all....The place was called Kampong Melayu. We had to pass by this wet market, which was super stinking...no, its not the fresh fishes, its their market. People just lazying around their DIY wooden planks stalls and selling their home-grown vegetables which 90% were fucking rotten, the path was covered in total mud, cause it was raining heavily before.....the mud, the smell...The strays animals there really look like strays unlike in SG.Fill u guys in later about those strays.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Batam3 urlLink    We then crossed this God damn smelly small river by their again...DIY bridge, i wonder when will it break apart....bikes actually shared the same bridge less than a metre in width. Whole scene look like we are refugees ...carrying stuffs across that place. Heng ah i carry my camera only...And so we started and i realised wads der plan...it was to sell them those 2nd clothes at a very low price. The thing is we are not giving them cause it might not push them to find work, selling at a low price actually made them look for work even though its not much of a pay.Gals in tudung stand in 2 roles and sang songs to welcome us, reminds me of tomb raider or some movie similiar to that....The kids there dont get education, cant afford or cant be bothered, but they are really really poor. The ground was bare dat not even weeds can survive in dat place yet kids can run around without shoes cause they cant afford it...Within 2 hours we sold almost everything...and we went for lunch at their church.2nd place we went to was called 12 kitchens...Situation was much better cause the govt leased land to them to built houses 6m by 10m. It was a big big land and some of these people they had houses but was half built. I was wondering, so they told me that they had to buy brick by brick to built the walls of the houses...and some of them even had to make-do their wooden planks kitchen miix with outdoor living room and 5th hand sofas....how long are they gonna save up to finish the rest of the walls? God....We went to the church at that place...it was much better yea this time with zinc roofs. And only a small statue of Virgin Marry and discoloured pictures of Jesus...This place was much better but i see no ppl and its eerie...and it has a smell....of a dead stray dog being bbq by those ppl. When i was walking back i saw a piece of dog's jaw bone with teeth on it. This is wad happened to strays there man...fuck.As i said this land was big, like a little hill, can hear someone blasting on their 5th hand speakers children chanting away some Koran music, eerie....it feels like Iraq...no ppl left except abandoned houses (actually built halfway lah).We...or they are planning to go again this December, same thing i guess, hope u guys can come along. Next august, im joining my same friend again to Germany for a 2 1/2 weeks of hitch hiking. This time its a youth camp thing and alot of walking are involved...great to take pics for me haha...Last thing, i havent develop my roll of B&W yet. Yes, its B&amp;W, if im done, i will forward it to u guys. I only took one roll. Cause its the same sad thing over and over again. Hope u guys don mind reading my long emailCya! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>