<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, well, well.  Isn't it delightful that one little story can affect readers in so many ways?  Maggie and Jenny empathized with Kate.  Gemmak found humour in Kate's reaction.  For Terri, the tale evoked memories of a snowy mid-west winter.  And Magz's's's's anonymous friend adopted a karmic view of it and sided with me. I think that's just fabulous!  We're all different aren't we?  However ...   "I note the obvious differences   Between each sort and type,   But we are more alike my friends   Than we are un-alike."    -Maya Angelou    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Strange, isn't it, how two people can see the same thing at the same time, but view it so differently.  I worked with Katy this morning. Kate is a good soul. She's completely lost in terms of her ability to do her job and many people actually FEAR working with her, but she's rather a likeable girl. Kate's among the half dozen or so women, who work here in Toronto as locomotive engineers. (in Britain, we're called "train drivers")  We departed Hamilton two minutes late because I move with the nimble grace of a one-legged man with a sore foot and it took me forever to get upstairs to the platform with my coffee and bagel.  Yeah. You've got a sore back. You've told us that already. Get on with your story.  Right. Sorry.  So we were rolling along the track together in the cab of the engine, Kate and I. She had just lit her 47th fag and I was opening the window again. I tried to focus on operating the train, but the smell of tobacco smoke (stale and fresh) mixed with Kate's cheap perfume was beginning literally, to cloud my vision.  "Smoke bothering you?" she asked.  "Naw," I lied. "I'm alright." And I stole a glance at her.  She was sitting, staring straight ahead and puffing angrily on her cigarette. She pointed her yellow fingers at the windshield.  "Idiots."  I turned my head just as two men darted in front of our train in an insane bid to save themselves a five minutes walk over the pedestrian bridge. I blew the whistle and watched as the pair disappeared into the bushes. That happens a lot, Ms Journal.  Just then the sun appeared from behind thick clouds and everything looked so pretty. The dull trees were now bright green and yellow. Ahead of us, the rails glistened and gleamed. Suddenly, I noticed the sumac trees.  Sumac grows beside the tracks here in great proliferation. All summer, it's green. But in the late summer/early fall, sumac leaves are the first to change colour. They start out a pale yellow and then quickly turn from yellow to bright orange and finally crimson. It's absolutely resplendent, Ms J. I felt so happy then. I smiled and I very nearly chuckled out loud. How fortunate I was to be there right then to see those beautiful leaves reflecting the morning sun! I felt priviledged to be witness to autumn's first blush.  I was about to comment on it to Katy but she beat me to it.  "Holy shit," she said. "Look at the stupid leaves. They're turning colour already. We haven't even had a summer yet and it's already fall. Soon the snow will be here. I hate snow. I hate winter."  I was rather shocked by her reaction to something that to me was awesome!  "But Katy," I said. Don't you think the leaves are lovely?"  "Yeah right," she said. "They're fucking lovely."  I guess she must have witnessed her own behaviour, for she then seemed to soften a bit.  "I can't believe I've got the winter blues in August."  Nor could I believe it. She saw the fall colours not as a gift from the Almighty Himself, but as a harbinger of cold and desolate winter climes. She'd made up her mind to be negative and grumpy, so I let her have her feelings.  The sunshine was soon replaced by overcast skies and nature's glory was hidden again, but not completely, for I still had the memory of what I'd seen. I could recall it and enjoy it again anytime. Not so for poor Katy. Her experience of that moment was dire and unpleasant.  I'm thinking now of a poem by Wordsworth. "Daffodils" In it, the poet speaks of seeing a field of daffodils and then enjoying the memory of it later.   "I gazed - and gazed - but little thought What wealth the show to me had brought:  For oft when on my couch I lie In vacant or in pensive mood, They flash upon that inward eye Which is the bliss of solitude; And then my heart with pleasure fills, And dances with the daffodils."   My daffodils this morning were sumac leaves. But the garden of poor Katy's memory will be barren.   
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning began with a blue jay's shrill call. "Jay! Jay! Jay!" The bird must have been perched in the neighbour's apple tree, the great limbs of which reach nearly to my bedroom window. He was persistent in his bid to rouse me. "Jay! Jay! Jay!" I turned to see the clock display and was immediately reminded of my injured back. I closed my eyes again and cursed quietly, barely moving my lips.  Gingerly, carefully, I rolled out of bed and put my bare feet on the shiny hardwood. By placing my hands on my legs and climbing my thighs, pushing slowly upwards, I was able at last to stand erect. I looked out into the garden. Suddenly, there was a bright blue flash as the jay glided from the tree and lit on the fence below me. I envied him his carefree mobility and smiled at the thought.  "Patience, Dale. You'll be fine again soon. All things come to pass. Good and bad. Joy and pain."  The bird hopped effortlessly to the lawn and then, as though to prove my point, flew off and disappeared. I smiled again and looked at the clock. 8:00. My mates at work will soon be arriving at Union Station, Toronto's downtown transportation hub, where they'll discharge 2,500 morning commuters. I wished I were at work.  In the bathroom across the hall, I found signs that clearly indicated I was not alone here anymore. Gobs of dried toothpaste in the sink. A hair brush clogged with long brown hair. And long hairs on the floor. In the bathtub, more long hairs. Shampoo. Conditioner. I climbed into the tub and sighed.  "Daniel," I muttered quietly. "What am I going to do with you, Boy?"  I started the shower and my thoughts came to me in a torrent as the hot water stung my face. He has so much to learn. So much yet to experience. Should I push him to find a job? Or let him relax this week and adjust to his new surroundings? Even Tara the cat needs time to adjust to the change. Both she and Dan wander aimlessly about the house as if they're unable to find peace here. I feel sorry for them, really. It must be difficult for them to accept these changes. I know it's hard for me.  Both boy and cat have been diligent in staying out of my way, both trying hard not to upset or interfere with my daily routine. Tara spends most of the day in the basement, occasionally venturing into the kitchen for some food or water. And Dan, bless his heart, has been so helpful. He's done much of the cooking and cleaning up. He's gone to fetch groceries, and yes Ms J, he did mow the lawns yesterday. His mother would be amazed.  After lunch today, we went out together to return a rented video game and to run some other errands. Dan opened a newspaper-type box and availed himself of a free and current copy of Employment News. At home, he sat with the paper and a red marker and circled job ads.  "Door to door appliance sales." No Dan.  "Earn $$$ in real estate sales." No Dan.  "Up to $12,000 per month in commercial cleaning business." No Dan.  "Warehouse help wanted. $7.50 to start. Will train." Yes Dan!!  "Do you have a current resume, son?"  "No, Dad. Not really."  "OK," I said. "Go upstairs to the computer and make one. Do you know how?"  He said he had learned about resumes at school so off he went. I lay on the floor in the living room and iced my back.  In a little while, he returned looking quite proud of himself. I must say, Ms Journal, his resume is pretty brief. But it's all he's got right now and it's truthful.  We got into the car and drove out into the world of employment. I could feel Dan's nervousness. It's exciting, finding a new job. I remember well my excitement (or was it fear?) at the thought of starting to work. I was a bit younger than Dan, and yes, it was fear.  We visited a lawn care company first.  "Don't make me go in, Dad. Let's just go home and call the number in the paper. I don't feel good about this."  I cast a glance at this ... person sitting next to me in the car. He looked so big, physically. So strong. He's nearly six feet and 180 lbs. Taller than me by at least three inches. But appearances can be deceiving. His body is big and strong, Ms J. But his spirit is young and weak and frightened. I looked at him again and for a moment, he was my little boy again. His eyes begged me to help him, to protect him as I did when he was a toddler. My heart was open to him, there in the front seat. I understood my son.  "It'll be alright, Dan boy," I told him. "I'll come with you if you'd like."  There was a moment of indecision then, but at last he drew a deep breath and said, "OK, Dad. Let's go. Let's do it. Let's get 'er done."  And so it went. We stopped at three places this afternoon. Dan filled out two applications and left resumes at all three. He was in high spirits as we drove home. He had the air of a man who'd accomplished something important. I love my boy, Ms J. I'm very proud of him. I must remember to tell him that.  Change is good. Very frightening. But good.    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And it's  BRILLIANT!!  Thanks Scottie, for the moving text thingy, there at the top. It's fantastic. You're fantastic. Yeah. Isn't it brilliant? Look everyone! Well, isn't it??!! Brilliant, I mean.   So sign my sodding guest book, then!      Oh. Owwww! My back! OK. Sorry. My attitude. Sign the guest book. Please? Thank you so much.  
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good afternoon, Ms J.  Attitude, it seems, is everything. What was it I wrote a few posts ago?  "It's your attitude, not your aptitude, that determines your altitude."    It's not an original Dale-ism, but it is quite true.  I'd been slowly lowering myself into a blue funk these past two days. I was complaining about my sore back and about my long-haired son and his short-haired feline friend, both of whom have lately invaded my home.  Today, I feel better. My dear friend Frankie called this morning to check on me and ask if there was anything I needed and Dan has been incredibly helpful, God love him. He's prepared meals and gone to fetch groceries and medicine. He's agreed to cut the lawns this afternoon, (I'm not particularly optimistic about that one, Ms J) and he's quick to lend his strong arms to help dear old dad up from the floor when necessary. I chatted a while with  urlLink Magz  this morning and she was, as always, uplifting and positive. Yes. Positively uplifting.  urlLink Terri  too, sent me her best wishes for a hasty return to a vertical Life. My friend  urlLink Jenn  called from work to tell me she'd be sending her Reiki healing energy to me. I REALLY like that woman. And I received compassionate comments from my sisters in the UK,  urlLink Gemmak  and  urlLink Jenny .  And I've just returned from the Egyptian bone crusher (Cairo-practor) where I was twisted up like a New York pretzel and crunched and snapped until I was heard to cry "Enough!" Then I enjoyed a wonderful, relaxing lower back massage. It was an effective treatment. A bit aggressive, perhaps. But effective nonetheless. The best $17 I've ever spent.  My conclusion? The visit to the doctor helped, yes. But it was primarily the positive energy from people who care, that raised my spirit. And an elevated spirit always leads to better physical health.  Thank you, friends! Thank you so very much. Now, I must go and lay down again. On the floor. With ice. 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK then.  I stand corrected.  It's not WAY down near the bottom.  But it's not at the top, either.  I believe it's been somewhat migratory lately.  Just look for it and sign it for Pete's sake.  And for mine.   Thanks.  And sign my friend  urlLink Maggie's  too. 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Before I go and talk to Dan, I was wondering if I might ask a favour of you, dear reader.  I was wondering if I might entice you in some way to sign my guest book.  Please.  You can link to it down near the bottom of the page.  My hit counter tells me 235 people have visited in only five days.   Sadly, I have only about four or five entries in my guest book, which is, as you know, down the bottom of the page.  Not here at the top.  But down below.  You'll probably have to scroll downwards to find it.  My guest book I mean.  While you're there, it wouldn't take but a minute or two to sign it.  My guest book.  Down the bottom there.  I wonder if I may have my webmistress move my GUEST BOOK up to the top of the page.  Instead of at the bottom, where it is now.  In case somebody wants to sign it. 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was lying on the floor in the living room this afternoon, listening to someone make a complete idiot of themselves on a talk show, and staring dejectedly at the ceiling, when The Boy arrived. Suitcase (huge suitcase) in one hand and a cage containing a cat in the other.  "Look who's here to stay, Dad. Me and Terra, my kitty. How's yer back?"  I tried to smile, Ms J. But it felt more like a grimace. The Boy. And he's arrived with an animal. Cat hair on my clothes. Odiferous litter box and cat food. Cat hair on my bed. He'd better not even THINK of getting on my bed.  "Still pretty sore, Dan. I suppose I'll have to see a chiropractor if it doesn't feel better soon. I see you brought Terra with you."  He set his suitcase down and brushed his shoulder length hair away from his face. "Yeah Dad. I asked you about Terra yesterday and you said it'd be OK. Remember?"  "Mmm-hmm," I conceded. I had said that. But I'd hoped that he'd leave the cat with Kelly.  "Where are you going to put his food, Dan? What about his litter box? I won't be cleaning that or feeding him, you know. He's your cat. He's your responsibility."  "She, Dad. Terra's a girl cat."  I reached around and pulled the cold pack from under my back. I had to lift my bottom off the floor to do it and it hurt like hell.  "WhatEVER," I hissed.  "She'll probably stay in the basement. You won't even see her. Hardly, I bet."  Dan took the cat, an orange tabby, out of the cage and the two of them roamed the house. Upstairs, downstairs. Basement. I tried to relax but I couldn't. My back seems to have gotten worse. I feel bored and frustrated. I'm tired of looking at the ruddy ceiling.  The Boy held the cat and talked incessantly. He was nervous I guess, about starting a new Life here with me. He's visited me many times before but only for a couple of days at a time. My home has not been his home for more than a decade.  I tried to listen to him, but soon it was like listening to someone reading the telephone directory. Just words. Words upon words upon words. An idea occurred to me then for a self-help group aimed at people who talk too much. I'd call it "On and on Anon".  I longed for peace. I mourned the loss of my solitude. And I felt guilty as sin for entertaining such thoughts. He's my son, for goodness sake! But talk!! Good golly lolly day, that boy can talk. I'll bet he could talk the ear off a manikin. When he was younger, I used to fear he'd get his tongue sunburned outdoors.  And so it began. The sun is shining outside the window. It's 23C, a gorgeous day. But I'm stuck inside. I can't bloody walk. It hurts to stand. And poor Daniel must feel so unwelcome. Nice way to start it off, eh? I'd better go and talk with him. I'm going to offer him my hand and welcome him to my home.  Then I'm going to ask him when he plans on getting a job. OK. I'll be gentle. 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's amazing!  My voice on the internet.  All it took was a simple phone call.  The web site says it's a free service, but that's not completely accurate.  I'll have to pay for the long distance phone call.  It was a North American number I dialed.  And so easy!   urlLink www.audioblogger.com   Let's all do it!  Yeah.  C'mon.  Let's hear yer voice! 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was lying on the couch a while ago, watching tv and resting my back, when there came a frantic knock on the door.  Then the door opened a crack and I heard the wail of a child in great distress.  "Dale!  Dale!" cried a familiar voice.  "Are you there?"  It was the neighbour lady from across the street.  Her name is Sherry.  "Yes, Sherry.  I'm here.  What's wrong?"  The remote control and the cordless telephone both slid off my stomach onto the hardwood, spilling a cup of tepid tea.  "Gary just shoved a bead up his nose and I can't get it out.  Will you drive us over to the hospital?"  She sounded quite panic-sticken, Ms J.  The boy was wailing and I didn't hear her clearly at first.  "Gary shoved a bee up his nose?  How the hell did he do that?"  "No, no.  A bead.  He shoved a bead up his nose.  B-e-a-d."  That made more sense, although not much.  I'd rather have eaten a bowl of stones than to have gotten off that couch and into the car.  "I can't Sherry.  I've hurt my back.  It'll take me half an hour to get off this couch.  Do you want some money for a cab?"  "No," she said.  "I'll find somebody to drive us.  Thanks."   I listened as she lead the screaming boy away.  She left the door ajar.  Right away, I heard her ask another neighbour and seconds later, they were off.  I felt badly that I couldn't help her, Ms J.  But what could I do?  My back is worse now than it was earlier.  I called work and told them I won't be in tomorrow.  So that's one day's pay shot to hell.   I'll take some more Aspirin and go to bed.  I'm having a bit of a challenging evening, Ms Journal.  I hate this shite.  But I still love my Life. 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've hurt my back.  I was out with a friend this afternoon.  We were downtown by the waterfront walking through a beautiful garden and admiring the flowers.   I said, "Oh look at these ones, Linda."  And I bent to examine the blossom more closely.  I snapped a quick photo and when I stood up again, there was pain.  In my back.  Lower back.  Lower back pain.  Yes, that's what I've got now.  Lower bloody back pain.  Takes your breath away, doesn't it?  Right.  I'm off now to lie down.  Mmmmpfff.  Yes.   Where's that ice pack thingy?  I don't imagine it would be in the freezer, would it? 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bi-lingual bill. And HRH as well.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...because even God doesn't trust the British in the dark. I'm not sure where I was going with that, Ms J.  But it's amusing so I posted it.  Well I guess there is a connection here.  England.  England seems to figure prominently in my Life lately.  There's the play I hope to win a part in.  "Caught In the Net"  A British farce.  I've been reading the script for a fortnight (see that, Ms J?  I could have written "two weeks" but I wrote "fortnight" instead.)   And when I read it, I read it aloud with an English accent.   I know there are scores of different English dialects, but since the play takes place in Wimbledon and Streatham (which is not pronounced "streetam", I've learned, but rather, "strettam".  Thanks Carol) I'm practicing a kind of standard London dialect, the kind we hear most often here in Canada on BBC programmes like "Are You Being Served?" or "Fawlty Towers".  It's gotten to the point now that when I read anything, I read it aloud and with an accent.  Sometimes, even my thoughts sound like a Monty Python sketch!  Cor, blimey!  My friend Marie is moving to England.  This Carol woman with whom I met on Friday is English.   Some of my blog mates are British.  I'm thinking of  urlLink Gemmak  here and  urlLink Jenny , too.  Oh and  urlLink Crash and Donna  as well.  Although my family has been in Canada many years (Dan and Meagan make the eighth generation of Canadian born Pringles), I still feel a kind of attachment to my Scottish roots.  I hope one day to travel to the UK.  The history there fascinates me.  Compared to the UK, Canada is still a toddler.  We only declared our nationhood on July 1, 1867.  And Newfoundland, our most easterly province, didn't join confederation until 1949.  Until then, it was part of Britain.   I remember quite vividly, the day when the Union Jack was lowered from the flag pole at school and the Maple Leaf was raised.  It was 1964.  I was six years old and it seemed a very solemn and important event, although I couldn't understand how important it was at the time.  It wasn't long after that we began singing "O Canada" every morning at school.  We rarely heard "God Save the Queen" except on Remembrance Day each year, November 11.  But we still have HRH Queen Elizabeth on our twenty dollar bill and on all our coins.  I'm glad of it.  It sets us apart from our American friends to the south.  It helps give us an unique and distinctly Canadian identity.  I love my country, Ms J.  And I love my Life.  God save the queen. 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's what Meatloaf sang. Remember that album, Ms J? That was a GREAT album!  Yeah, so I attended two of three social engagements yesterday. I went first to see Marie and Ian. I met Marie a couple of years ago in an acting class. She's really nice and she's a writer by profession. Marie's written a couple of short stories and won some acclaim in local contests. She and her husband have recently adopted a child from China. Amelia is about a year and a half old and cute as a bug's ear! Marie and Ian are leaving August 30 to spend a year ("at least") in merry old England. Devon, to be exact. Ian will attend school there.  He hopes to complete an MSc in Tourism Policy and Development at the University of Exeter. I offered them hugs and best wishes but I didn't stay long. I rushed off then to a back yard barbecue with friends in another part of town.  Larry is a man who, like me, is a locomotive engineer at Canadian National. But the Fates haven't always smiled on him these past ten years or so. It was nearly a decade ago that Larry fell at work and broke his back. He's had numerous surgeries and suffered terribly. His wife, Val, has stuck by him throughout the ordeal. She's a remarkable woman.  He tried returning to work about five years ago, but I guess it was too early and poor old Larry further aggravated his condition.  He's been sitting at home, hurting and steadily gaining weight for ... way too long.  Way too much time.  And now it's weigh too much time.  Larry is massive.  I'll bet he's 200 pounds over weight.  And he's had so many health problems.  But he's been practicing some form of girth control lately and he's looking and feeling better.  Much better.  He even stood and cooked chicken and steaks on the barbie.  Mike and Sue were there as well.  Mike's another engineer like me.  Mike and Larry are brothers-in-law.  They married sisters.  Mike's a nice guy too, although I wish he'd consumed a bit less beer.  Or at least paced himself.  He was pretty drunk at the dinner table.  But he behaved himself and stayed awake.  I think we all had a brilliant time.  It was nearly 1:00 a.m. when I finally got to bed. 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Life seems to proceed in an orderly fashion most of the time.  Once in a while it gets a bit hard to manage.  And sometimes, everything seems to happen at once.  That's how it feels today.  This morning, after work, I met a lady for coffee.  Carol is her name.  I first met Carol at a writer's workshop last month.  She's an English lady, about my age.  I asked her to help me learn an English dialect for an upcoming audition this month.  So we met.  She seems quite nice.  We agreed we'd meet again soon.  There may be a relationship here, Ms J.  It's worth investigating.  Later today, I learned that another woman in whom I was interested has just split up with her boyfriend.  She's cancelled her plans to move to Transylvania (or Pennsylvania, I always get the two confused) to move in with him.  I was told that Cindy may well call me in week or so.  From no women to two women.  In a few days.  Dan wants to move here to live with me.  That's another thing.  The father part of me wants to have my boy here and to help him find a job and move forward with his Life.  The selfish, single, I've-lived-alone-4-years-now part of me doesn't want him here at all.  I don't want to hear his music, or share my computer, and I don't want to find his socks on the living room floor.  It'll be a HUGE adjustment for me.  And for him too, I suppose.  It looks like it's going to happen, and soon.  Pray for us!  My sister has been nagging me to have lunch with her.  I went today.  She has two young children who were surprisingly well-behaved.  The visit wasn't bad after all.  Actually, I was sorry to leave.  Jennefer is a friend who's invited me for dinner.  Tonight's the night.  So I'll drive an hour to Orangeville and socialize there.  I'm leaving as soon as I finish this post.  Jenn's mother has had a leg amputated recently and I've been to see her in hospital twice now.  I'm feeling a bit guilty that I don't visit more often, but honestly Ms J, I haven't had time lately.  I've accepted invitations to an open house, a farewell party and a back yard barbecue, all happening tomorrow.  On Sunday, I'm meeting with another friend for a stroll around the downtown waterfront.  I've got to learn to say no.  I'm just feeling a bit over-whelmed at the moment.  Well, buh-bye.  I'm off to O-ville for dinner with Jenn!  Thanks for listening. 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got home from work at 7:30 tonight, like always.  At 8:00, I sat down at the computer.  Read my email.  Responded to a few.  I read Gemmaks blog.  And then followed the link to ... ah, some strange person's blog.  I left a comment there.  Then I left a comment for Gemmak.  Of course, I had to read all the other comments as well.  Then I visited Maggiesfarm.  Read her posts.  Laughed my arse off.  And commented there.   And I looked in on Ally for a while, then stopped by Terri's for a bit o' the old Deep and Fuzzy.  I wanted to visit beFrank, but I plum forgot.  And now look at the time!  It's nearly 10:30 and I haven't posted anything yet in my blog.  I wanted to customize my guest book too.  Never got around to that either.  I've got to get up in six hours and I'm not even in bed yet.  I won't mention any names but someone suggested to me a week ago, that I'd be spending a lot of time here in the days to come.  You were right, Magz.  Good night, Ms J.    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Morning, Ms J.  The Boy made dinner last night. It was delicious! He prepared a Caesar salad as he'd promised, but he also made hamburg patties from raw ground beef and cooked them on the barbecue. My new barbecue. It was all ready when I got home from work. He confessed to a degree of uncertainty about how to do it, but he carried on as best he could and made a brilliant job of it.  "I tried calling mom, like, 20 times to ask her what spices to use and all that, but she was probably on the internet. I don't know why she doesn't get a cable connection like the rest of the world. I was starting to get really freakin' pissed off."  "Well, you've done really well without Mom's help, Dan," I told him. "You know, we never really learn until we have to do things on our own. I discovered that when Donna kicked me out. Then I  had  to learn."  As we ate, he told me more about Carly, and about his desire to visit her in Wisconsin. I let him talk while I chewed and nodded and grunted acknowledgement.  "I'm thinking about maybe coming to live here in Toronto, Dad. With you. I could probably get a job here easier than I could in Acton. I could get a job in a factory or something. Yeah. I need a job where I can make about ... um ..." (he was trying to do the math here, Ms J) "... a thousand bucks in a couple of months."  "I've told you you're welcome here, Dan," I said. "But you'd have to pay for your room and board. And you'd have to help out with the chores here, just like at Mom's."  The Boy has become adept at telling his mother and me what we want to hear. We'll see if he means what he said.  "Sure, Dad. That's no problem. But I'm not working at a fast food place and I'm not working for minimum wage either."  In case you're wondering, the minimum wage allowed by law varies a little from province to province, but here in Ontario, it's currently ... are you ready for this?  $7.10 per hour  It seems a lot to me. When I got my first job, (at a local gas station) minimum wage was $1.90. I got paid $2.25 and I was elated at that. But that was exactly (Gulp!) thirty years ago. Prices have gone up since then.  "Well, Dan," I said. "It's not what you earn, but what you save that's important. Even a minimum wage job would give you nearly $800 a month."  He seemed astonished at the amount.  "Really? Holy crap! I'd only have to work a couple of months, then I could quit and I'd have enough to see Carly."  I smiled weakly in reply. Dan has so much to learn, hasn't he? So much yet to discover. Why do I feel so afraid for him? I didn't learn much after Dan's mother threw me out, that's true. But when it happened the second time, the pain was too much to risk repeating it. I'm bloody-well learning now, aren't I?  It's been a fantastic ride, these past four years. I've grown so much, discovered so much about the world and my place in it. Don't I always say I love my Life? By worrying about my son, and sheltering him from the bumps and bruises Life sometimes metes out, won't I only keep him from growing and discovering Life as I have?  The answer is yes. So I must give Dan enough space to grow without abandoning him entirely. Offer him a bit of necessary pruning without too much fatherly "fertilizer".  But how?  We'll both grow here, won't we? I suppose we'll grow together in this. Or we'll grow apart. I feel excited for my son, Ms Journal. Excited and frightened.  "You know, we never really learn until we have to do things on our own."  Suddenly, I want to cry.    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... I thought I'd share a few thoughts I've had this morning.  It's 10:00 am.  Dan is still in bed.  He may sleep til 1:00 or later.  Should I get him up?  I'm rather enjoying my solitude right now, but I would like to see The Boy before I have to return to work.  He asked to come here.  I believe he wants to spend time with dear ol' dad.  So I shouldn't be selfish and squander that opportunity.  Of course, it is possible that he just wanted a change of scenery.  Maybe his mom was getting on his nerves.  OK. I've convinced myself.  It's the right thing to do.  I'm going now to wake him.  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Alright.  I'm back.  Dan got out of bed without much prodding.  He just staggered off to the shower as though he were drugged or feeling his way in the dark.  I asked him if he'd like to come with me to the supermarket to choose the ingredients for a Caesar salad and he said he'd like to prepare it.  "I make a mean Caesar salad, Dad.  Mom even says so.  I might put some chicken in there, too.  Yeah.  How would that be?"  "Fantastic Dan," I told him. "You have your shower, then we'll go out and get some groceries."  Off he went then and closed the bathroom door.  A minute later, he called to me through the closed door.  "Dad?"  I was tidying my bed and I stopped to listen.  "Yeah, Dan?"  "My birthday's coming up, eh?"  "Yeah I know, Dan.  September 12, right?  Have you thought about what you'd like?"  I heard him open the door a little and he stood quietly for a second.  "Well, I wouldn't mind a two-way ticket to Wisconsin."  I smoothed the duvet as best I could and replaced the pillows.  Then I walked to the window and looked into the back yard.  Wisconsin?  What the hell does he want to go there for?  Wisconsin.  I'd seen the license plates. "America's Dairy Land"  Milwaukee.  The home of ... some brewing company.  Where is Wisconsin, anyway?  "Wisconsin, eh Dan?  Why would you want to go there?"  "'Cuz that's where Carly lives."  I continued to stare out the window, Ms J.  I took comfort somehow in the familiar sight of the yard.  It was windy outside and I watched the trees bend.  The Venetian blind rattled.  "Who's Carly?" I called to the black squirrel in the vegetable garden.  "My girlfriend, Dad.  She lives in Wisconsin.  I met her a couple of months ago on MSN.  I call her my girlfriend, and she considers me her 'boyfriend'," he answered matter-of-factly.  "Yeah. I wouldn't mind going to see her."  Fantasies.  Dreams and fantasies.  But who am I to judge him?  I once spent an entire year in pursuit of a married woman.  I really believed she'd be mine one day - once she'd left her husband.  That day never came.  Eventually, my broken heart forced my eyes open and I don't see Kathy anymore.  Kathy was just as unavailable to me as Carly is to Dan.  Remember that Bruce Springstein song, "Everybody's Got a Hungry Heart"?  It's so true, isn't it?  Every heart hungers for Love.  And yearns to give it.  But why can't The Boy find someone who lives a bit closer? Like in the same country, possibly.  And why did I choose to pursue a woman who was unavailable?  Well, that's a topic for another day.  "I don't think you'll be getting any plane tickets for your birthday, son," I said. "What about a CD, or a DVD?"  "But Dad ..."  "No, Dan. If you really want to see Carly, get a job and save up for the trip."  "Yeah. I guess so. Whatever." He sounded neither surprised nor disappointed in my answer.  "Go on then.  Get in the shower.  Then we'll go get the fixin's for a salad. OK?"  I love my son too, Ms J. And I love my Life.     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My Boy&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Meagan came home with me from  urlLink Teen Ranch  on Saturday. Kelly and Tim went back to Acton. Scott returned to his home in Fergus. Clearly, my girl had an absolutely brilliant time at camp.  "Next year, I want to go for two weeks, Dad. Can I?"  She has talked non-stop today about camp. She's told me the names of all the horses. And all her cabin mates. And she's prattled on about one particular leader. An Aussie named Ben. Ben Brown.  "Oh Dad!" Meagan gushed. "He's like, so hot! He plays the guitar, like really well. And he has this like, really awesome singing voice."  Like, yes, Ms J. That's like, what she like, said. 'Cuz that's how she like, talks. It like, drives me crazy.  But she truly enjoyed the experience and can't wait to return next summer. Her smile today was radiant and I enjoyed being near her to bask in it.  Alas, she says she wants to go home to tell Mom all about her adventures so I'm taking her home tomorrow. Acton is about a 45 minute drive from here. Meagan's brother, Dan, phoned today. He wants to come for a visit.  "Yeah, Dad. Me and Meagan can just trade places."  I agreed to the swap and so I'll drop Scout off tomorrow after lunch and pick up The Boy. He'll stay with me until Thursday or so. My son and I don't share the same easy relationship that Meagan and I do. Don't misunderstand me, Ms J. I love Daniel. It's just that lately, we seem so far apart.  He'll be 18 next month. He has no job. No girlfriend. No direction in his Life. He fantasizes about being rich one day or about moving to Louisiana or Japan to marry some girl he met on MSN chat. Dan's a dreamer. I hope he wakes up one day.  Meanwhile, I'll keep loving him. I'll try to be patient and wait for him to cross the rickety old bridge that spans the chasm between boyhood and manhood.  Breathe, Dale. All will be well.  "Don't stay up too late, Scout," I holler down the stairs. "Please don't stay up past midnight."  "I won't, Daddy. "  Good night, Ms J. 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Meagan at Camp&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Morning, Ms J. It's Sunday morning. Around 9:00. I've been up since 7:00, folding laundry, attending to email, and drinking coffee. I just thought I'd share my Saturday with you. Here's how it went:  I drove to  urlLink Teen Ranch  yesterday morning. Meagan has been there all week. Meagan's my daughter. She just turned twelve. I call her "Scout." She loves horses but she's pretty inexperienced. She rode for the first and only time, about 6 years ago, at my uncle's farm. She's never forgotten that experience. So this year, I thought "What the hay?" And I registered her for a week at a riding camp. $675.  I asked for some help from her mother and her stepfather. I was completely astounded when they both not only agreed, but actually paid up! So $225 for each of us. That's affordable.  Saturday morning marked the last day at camp and parents were invited to attend a "rodeo" and watch the kids on horseback. I wasn't terribly impressed with the rodeo, Ms J. Understandably, it was fairly tame. How much can one expect of a child after one week of riding, one hour per day?  What I found most impressive, was the fact that we were  all  there to support Meagan. Kelly was there of course. She's my ex, my first ex-wife, and Meagan's mom. Scott was there. Scott is the man Kelly took up with and eventually married when she left me. Scott became Meagan's stepdad. He was part of her Life and watched Meagan and her older brother grow for ten years. Tim was there too, with baby Emily.  Are you following this, Ms J? Stay with me please.  Tim is Kelly's new boyfriend. And baby Emily is ... well, the new baby. A year and a half ago, Kelly and Scott parted company. Scott found a new lover from ... Cleveland, I think it was, and Kelly began a "friendship" with Scott's best friend. In February of this year, Emily was born. Feel free to condemn Kelly for her neediness. I've been strolling that path for a decade and frankly, it's gotten wearisome.  I arrived first at the ranch. Scott wasn't far behind me. We chatted a while in the parking lot and soon Tim and Kelly and Emily arrived. We sat on the grass together and watched "our girl" ride her horse. I took a few photos. So did Tim and Kelly.  I must tell you, Ms J, it felt rather strange to be there in the company of Kelly's lovers, past and present. She was my first wife and I, her first husband. The marriage to Scott was the second for both of them. And Tim? Well, I don't really know about Tim, other than to tell you he's respectful of Kelly and kind to my kids. And he's quite taken with his daughter. Emily will be six months old on the 18th of August.  Kelly and I remain united as the parents of Dan and Scout. Tim and Scott respect that relationship. She and I still have our differences but we realized early on that the kids' welfare must always be our prime objective. When we act to hurt each other, we hurt the kids.  After the rodeo, we all went and enjoyed barbecued hamburgers and sausages and watermelon on the property. It's really lovely there! I think Meagan was pleased that we all attended. Personally, I wouldn't have missed it for the world.  She made lots of new friends and proudly introduced us.  "This is my dad. This is my stepdad. And this is ... well, this is Tim. And Emily, my sister."  Sometimes, Ms Journal, I really struggle with it all. But most of the time, I'm able to focus on what's really important. Scout has three men who all figure prominently in her Life. All three offer Love and support. None are violent, or disrespectful of her or her mother. How can this be unhealthy?  I love my girl. I love my Life. 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess I must have been dreaming last night. My day started out - shall we say? - on the wrong foot. It was quite bizarre, actually.  I was in my bed, and I was awake. T'was still dark outside. Quiet. I rolled over and looked at the clock. 4:20. The alarm was set for 4:15 and I wondered why it hadn't gone off. I checked the switch and, yes, it had been properly set. Oh well. I turned it off and got up. I was really tired, but that's normal for me. I stood with my eyes closed before the toilet, and peed by ear. The sound of water splashing in water is good. Water splashing anywhere else, is cause for concern. I was hitting the mark perfectly. I wished that I'd gone to bed before 11:00 last night. My eyes felt as though they were full of sand.  I washed and shaved and brushed my teeth and staggered back to the bedroom to get dressed. I chose clean socks and underwear from the drawer and a clean t-shirt. There was a cool breeze wafting through the window, so I pulled on a sweatshirt as well. The jeans I wore yesterday were still clean so I put them on and fastened my belt.  Downstairs, I had a swallow of apple juice from the fridge and checked the clock on the microwave. 4:30. Plenty of time yet. I turned on the Weather Channel on TV and learned it was 13C at the airport. (Who the hell cares what the temperature is at the airport, Ms J? Nobody lives there.) We Canadians have been metricized now for twenty years. So I can't tell you how cool it was in degrees Fahrenheit. I know 10C is 50F. So it was bloody cool outside.  I took the garbage out to the road. The raccoon, of course, went without protest.  "Too cold to ride my bike," I thought. "Besides, I'm too sleepy still."  So off I went in the car. I arrived at work in about four minutes.  The parking lot, normally full before 5:00 a.m., was nearly empty. I glanced in the office as I drove by, and there wasn't a soul to be seen. I furrowed my brow and considered the possibility that it was not Friday, but Saturday. It was a short week for us here in Canada, due to the holiday on Monday. I glanced at the clock in the car.  2:42.  I brought the car to a stop then and looked again at the clock. It still read 2:42. I stared at my watch. 2:44. Something was wrong here. Terribly wrong. I pulled the car up in front of the office and peered through the glass doors at the large railway clock on the wall inside. The correct time, evidently, was 2:44.  But how? What was going on here? Had I made a wrong turn somewhere and somehow entered a parallel (nearly) universe? I looked again at my watch. Then at the office clock. And the one on the CD player in the car. I yawned and shook my head. I was precisely two hours early for work.  "I guess that would explain why I'm so sleepy," I said out loud. I smiled at the absurdity of it, and at my own silly mistake. I felt the first little spasms of laughter and allowed myself a muted chuckle.  "Oh well. Back to bed then. I'm glad I live nearby."  I pulled off my sweatshirt and climbed back into bed. I reset the alarm. I don't know how I could have made such a mistake, Ms Journal. It was really quite strange. Although I was keen to start the day, I suppose the day wasn't yet ready for me.        
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Epiblogue:  I had lunch with a friend today.  Jenn.  She convinced me I was courting disaster by refusing to wear the safety vest.  "Can you afford a week off without pay, Dale?  Can you afford to get fired?  Think about it.  Please.  You've worked so hard to get your own home.  Why risk losing it over a silly orange safety vest?"  And she urged me to take the moral high road where it comes to dealing with Bob.  So this afternoon, I put on my stupid safety vest.  Bob quietly slunk away (slunk? Is that actually a word?) without saying anything to me at the start of the shift.  I chatted with the other guys as we rode together downtown.  Bob hid in another coach. (carriage)  I sat as I always do, with my GO girls on the ride out to Oakville.  They encouraged me to ignore Angry Bob's puerile behaviour and instead buy him a cup of coffee and pretend all is well.  Rosie even gave me some  money for coffee!  Gosh those women are good to me.  An hour later, we prepared the train for eastward movement and Bob joined me on the engine.  I walked over to his side of the cab, and placed a styrofoam cup on the little table in front of him.   "Cheers, Bobby."  He looked up from the book he was reading and said, "Here. I've got something I want to show you."  He began leafing through the book to find the right page.  In a moment, he handed me the book.  It was a small paperback book called "Settle It.  How To Resolve Disputes."  I read the paragraph he indicated.  I don't remember what it said, but I was glad to know that he was reading it.  He wouldn't admit he was reading it to help himself though.  "Yeah," he mumbled.  "My boys fight all the time.  It drives me crazy.  Maybe this book'll help them learn to resolve their differences."  "I hope so, Bob.  For your sake."  I wasn't referring to his kids and I got the feeling that he understood that.  So he talked.  We talked.  He asked me if I was still angry with Donna.  I said not very often anymore.  He told me there were still so many unresolved issues with his ex, that he could see no way to move beyond hurt and resentment.  "It just eats at me, you know?  I'm still so pissed at her for what she did... I guess my temper gets the better of me and I take it out on people who don't deserve it.  I can't even talk to that bitch without fighting with her.  I wish there were something I could do to wipe that slate clean."  I pulled the throttle out another notch and rang the bell for a crossing.  I picked up my coffee, took a sip and waited for him to continue.  "What did you do to forget about Donna?" he asked.  "How did you get over it?"  I didn't really know what to say, Ms Journal.  How could I answer that question?  Hell, I don't understand spiritual processes.  I know they exist.  I know time is the ultimate healer.  Certainly, in my case, I found friends and family who helped a great deal.  And I discovered my passion for acting and writing.  I went to church and prayed.  I learned and practiced a simple form of meditation.  I believe in a higher power.  Mighty hands, as it were, that help me and guide me.   All of it helped.  And I told him that.   But Bob rejected nearly everything I said.  He found some way to counter each of my suggestions.  "Well I don't believe in God.  My parents are both institutionalized with advanced Alzheimers and my sister has her own problems.  I already know how to meditate.  I read a book about it once.  I don't see what good that would do.  How would that get my ex to listen to me?"  I shrugged my shoulders.  Shook my head.  The poor man is lost and I cannot help him find his way home.  Only he can do that.  And he'll have to walk that path alone.  Bon Voyage, Bobby.  Good luck!       
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good morning.  It's 9:45 in the morning. The sun is shining here in Mimico. But my heart is troubled. Sigh.... Where shall I begin? Gosh, I feel like I have so much to say today. I wish I could type more quickly. I'm a one-finger man, myself. Middle finger. Right hand. Whatever. Who cares, Dale? Get to your point, please. What's on your mind today? What's "troubling your heart"?  OK. Well, I'm sure you're all curious about today's title. Dead Raccoon and Angry Bob. They could be related stories. But they're not. Let's start with the raccoon.  I exited the house this morning at 4:45 and spotted a raccoon lying on the street in front of my driveway. No wait. It was yesterday morning. Yeah. Anyway, I walked over to the little bugger to determine his condition and I was thinking "Gosh, I sure hope he's dead. I hope he's not suffering. What will I do if he's not dead? Will I have to end his misery? How? Rock? Brick? Stick? What if it wakes up and attacks me?"  You see how my mind works sometimes? It just latches on to a thought - any silly little thought - and runs completely berserk. I'm shaking my head here. So much worry. So much fret. And for what?  But it was drizzling rain. Dark. The nearby street light cast a pinkish hue on the road, empty and deserted now in the quiet of night. Somewhere, far away, thunder rolled. And lightning flashed weakly over the lake to the south.  I approached the animal. Cautiously. It was lying on its side with its tail pointed in my direction. I walked around to the front and gasped softly at the mess. There was no doubt now. This creature was clearly dead. The rain began to fall then in earnest.  What now, I thought. I couldn't just leave him there in the middle of the road. In the middle of the night. In the middle of a rain storm. I poked him with the toe of my work boot and rolled him onto his back. His legs were already becoming stiff and they stuck out from his belly in all four directions. The rain was falling in his eyes, which were still open. He (she?) looked so ignominious, lying there spread eagle like that.  Lightning crackled somewhere above me and briefly lit us like a macabre scene from an Alfred Hitchcock thriller. I stood there another few moments, staring down at this soaking, bloody, broken corpse and feeling both repulsion and fascination at the same time.  But I was getting wet. And I had to get to work. I rushed into the shed and grabbed a garbage bag and a pair of gloves. I hurried back into the street, collected the raccoon and deposited him into the trash bag. The bag I then stored in the shed. Until ... what? Garbage day? Garbage?  Is that all he is now, Ms Journal? Garbage? In an instant, a speeding car had taken this animal's Life and turned his body to trash. Think of it. There's some clear message there for those open to receive it.  In this minute, a Life. In that, garbage. How swift the transition!  The funeral will be on Friday; the hearse, a noisy truck. Two garbage men will be the only ones in attendance.  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Angry Bob works with me. He's the other engineer on my train. I see him every day. Bob sits beside me in the cab of the locomotive. I don't care much for Angry Bob. Here's a bit of background:  Bob's wife cast him out six months after Donna (her name was Donna) ended our marriage. So I had a bit of a head start on ol' AB when it came time to mourn and to recover. But Bob has not recovered. He is absolutely filled with rage at his ex-wife. Come to think of it, Angry Bob is filled with rage at nearly everyone. And everything.  He's often preachy and pedantic. He often offers bits of advice or pearls of wisdom that are not original, although he acts as though he's the first to think of it. Sometimes, he's quite ignorant of the facts and simply regurgitates words or concepts he's heard elsewhere. I've even heard him share things with me that I've told him myself months or even years earlier. He fancies himself as quite a soothsayer. I often feel as though he's talking down to me.  Am I that way? Do I do that too? Caution.  "There's something about that guy I can't stand about myself."   Stay awake, Dale. Stay conscious. Witness your own behaviour.  Angry Bob is intelligent, eloquent (when he wants to be) and he tries very hard to be helpful. Bob has a good sense of humour. He dresses nicely. He is tall and handsome.  But AB's a selfish, bigoted, violent man. He doesn't like himself at all. He almost never refers to himself in a respectful way, often using self-deprecating humour which to me, is not the least bit amusing. Bob tries so hard to be perfect. Perfectly acceptable to others. Pure and righteous. He talks the talk, Ms J, but he doesn't walk the walk.  Despite a mighty effort, Bob falls far short of his goal. In the end, he's so transparent, that I feel uncomfortable around him. I've spent the past few weeks trying to understand why I feel so prickly when I'm with him. Now I know.  I don't engage Bob in conversation much anymore. I've tried gently to offer him alternate ways of looking at things, alternate ways of behaviour. I've hinted at the difference between response and reaction and suggested the former as wiser and more acceptable. But he doesn't hear me. Or if he does hear, he doesn't or can't understand. So I nod my head a lot nowadays and smile rather than attempt a verbal response.  Bob speaks in absolute terms. He often uses hyperbole to emphasize a point he's making. His feelings are nearly always expressed in the strongest way possible. Bob doesn't simply dislike things. He "HATES them with a passion." He rarely enjoys things. Instead, he "FUCKIN' LOVES" them. He doesn't get irked or annoyed or frustrated. He gets "FUCKIN' FURIOUS!"  When he refers to someone he doesn't like, he always uses the same description: "Fuckin' piece of shit." He doesn't describe the person as lazy, or selfish, or ignorant, or as possessing any negative attribute other than being a "fuckin' piece of shit." I guess, for Bob, that's an accurate characterization of anyone at all whom he "HATES with a passion" or who makes him "FUCKIN' FURIOUS!"  I've often thought Bob is a wonderful teacher for me, although he doesn't know it. It wasn't so long ago that I behaved much like him. Over the past few years, a tiny spark of knowledge in me has gradually grown brighter. I am able now to see that behaviour and manner of speaking as ugly and demeaning. In the end, only the speaker looks bad. It sounds horrible!  Last week, Bob overheard someone referring to him as "Angry Bob." He didn't like it.  "I'm not angry," he said. "Why do they call me Angry Bob? Fuckin' pieces of shit!!"  That was one of the times, Ms J, when I could only nod and smile.  I've recently discovered something else about this man. He pouts (on a good day), like a spoiled child, when things don't go his way. He dispenses advice and gets quite perturbed when it's not heeded.  This afternoon, he spotted me standing in the train yard as I waited for a train. Two full crews ride downtown every afternoon, where we pick up our own trains to operate for the rush hour crowds. Anyway, Bob saw me without a safety vest. We're supposed to wear safety vests now. You know, like the ones worn by traffic cops and crossing guards. I hate wearing a vest. Ever since an American took the helm here, we've been ordered to wear these ridiculous-looking vests. Bug-eyed safety glasses too.  The CEO of Canadian National Railway is American. Can you believe it? One of the most readily identifiable and well-know Canadian companies - indeed a Canadian icon - is now headed by an American. And the employees are VERY resentful of this fact. EXTREMELY unhappy, we are.  This clown doesn't care about employees or their families or even long-standing traditions or labour agreements. Profit is all that matters to E. Hunter Harrison. The man, and his new rules, are despised. I refuse to wear a vest. Or glasses. It's stupid. It's pointless. Clearly, I have a problem with authority. I know. But the vests are stupid. They're demeaning. They make us look like geriatric, school crossing guards. I don't wear it. I'm among the very few who doesn't. I'll get caught one day and disciplined. Maybe they'll take me out of service and make me stay home for a week without pay. (Seems a bit harsh, doesn't it? But these Yanks are really throwing their weight around up here. They're going to get us "pointed in the raht direction, bah Gawd." I don't care. I'm not wearing a stupid vest. Til I get caught.  It's stupid of me, I know. But I'm serious about this. I know I'll lose the fight.  So Bob says, "Where's yer vest?"  And I say, "In my bag here in my hand."  And Bob gets all preachy and starts telling me how I should be wearing a vest because if I get caught .... blah, blah, blah.  "Whatever, Bobby," I tell him. "Don't worry about me and my vest. You worry about your own vest. I'll be fine."  And so ... (I'm finally coming to the point. Thank you so much for your patience.)  ...now he's not talking to me. Bob sits over on his side of the engine and pretty much ignores me. I've tried to make small talk, but he offers mono-syllabic answers. I'm disturbed by it. If it goes on much longer, I'm going to ask him point blank what his problem is. I'm going to ask him to stop behaving like a child and tell me what's bothering him. Correct me if I'm wrong here, but do I not have the right to reject his criticisms and refuse his advice?  I'll be returning to work in a few hours. I'll post again tonight when I get home.  This post is way too long to bother proofreading. If it sounds like a bunch of mindless drivel, so be it.  Whew! The End.  PS Sorry about the language earlier. I don't normally speak like that.    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Besides me, of course. I'm referring here to this blog, this journally sort of thing about which I spend an inordinate amount of time worrying. Well, not worrying per se (Did I actually use the term "per se"?), but thinking and pondering and wondering.  Does anyone really care about my Life? About my thoughts and deeds? I find it quite fascinating, but I suspect only because it's  my  Life. I wouldn't be very content, I don't think, if I perceived my own Life as boring. But what leads me to believe that others might not find it so? Why do I think others might be interested?  "Who is this guy?" Maybe that's your question, and a darn good one at that. I'm still discovering who I am. And that is extremely exciting!  OK then. Some background. My Truth. I was married once. OK, twice. My first wife gave me two children. They are very important to me. My second wife taught me many lessons. She introduced me to cocaine and methamphetamines. She showed me the incredible beauty of Canada's east coast. Nova Scotia, in general. Cape Breton Island, specifically. We were together six years.  In May of 2000, she expelled me from our home in Toronto and ended our marriage. I guess she'd had enough of my crap. She met a Dutchman on the internet, and moved to Holland to marry him. As far as I know, she's still there.  She doesn't know it, but by divorcing me and breaking my heart, she forced me to really look at myself and see where I was headed. It wasn't a very choice destination, let me tell you.  After living like a nomad for a month or two, I found an apartment. My own space. I'd never had my own place before. I'd always lived with somebody. Family. First wife. My sister for a while. Then with my second wife. Her name was ... well, I'm not sure what the protocol here is. Is it OK to use names in such a public place? Maybe someone can offer me guidance here.  I lived in that basement apartment here in the community of Mimico for 3 years and 4 months. I quit drugs. I quit cigarettes. I quit hiding from the world. And I cried and cried for the Life I'd lost. Can you imagine it? I didn't know what delights awaited me in the months and years ahead. If I had only known, dear reader, I would have suffered it gladly. Spending time alone has been the best gift I've ever given myself. My Self. I highly recommend it. It has really helped me discover my Self.  My Life today is infinitely more satisfying, more rewarding than the one I was forced to abandon. I lacked the strength to move away from a marriage that was itself pernicious and so The Universe intervened on my behalf. God stepped in.  I go to church now, most Sundays. There's a United church only a few blocks away. I've made lots of new friends at church. A few very special ones have helped me move through some recent emotional miasma. I'm grateful for their counsel.  Last December, I bought a house. Very exciting! My first. It's only a block away from my apartment. Moving day was interesting. I led a parade of friends down the street, all walking and carrying my things. The neighbours were amused, I think. Some even helped.  So here I am. In my little house in Mimico. It's only a few hundred yards to the lake. Lake Ontario. I ride my bike to work. I walk to buy groceries. I am quite happy here in my new home. In my new Life. I've learned to cook. I've done some acting in local community theatre. I've discovered that acting is my passion. I adore being on stage before a crowd. I've even won some acclaim and a couple of trophies. Isn't that fantastic?!! I've never won anything in my Life before. And I have lots of theatre friends who encourage me to limit my drama to the stage. Mostly, I do.  Sigh ...  But sometimes, just sometimes, I get lonely. I don't miss  her,  but I miss ... someone .   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... some people just have no regard at all for others.  There was a fatality at work today. A suicide. It happens. Someone jumped in front of a speeding commuter train. Obviously, he wanted to die.  He'd had all he could stand of this Life.  I can't even imagine the kind of emotional pain that would drive a person to take his or her own Life.  I feel sorry, not for the person who was turned to a fine mist by an 80 mph, 2000 ton missile, but for the loved ones who are now left to mourn, and perhaps to spend forever asking "why?"  But here's where my compassion really fades:  This person chose to kill himself in front of a train, at the height of the afternoon rush hour.  Of course, no train movements were permitted in either direction for five hours while the police and others collected widely scattered body parts and hosed the gore off the front of the locomotive.  Tens of thousands of homebound commuters were stranded downtown.  Some trains were diverted to alternate destinations, but the accident - and I use that word in a general sense, for it was clearly no accident - occured on the busiest route in Toronto.  It may well be the busiest commuter rail corridor in Canada.  So you've had enough, have you?  And you want to die?  Then why not take a bottle of pills and crawl into a closet somewhere?  Why cause such a great inconvenience to people whose only concern is getting home to their families after work?  You inconsiderate, selfish, son-of-a-bitch!!  And what of the engine crew who had to witness it?  Two men suffered the horror of sitting, watching helplessly as the train they were operating struck and killed a human being.  I know.  I've been in their place. The sound of it - a kind of dull thud and then a rattle as skull and bones pass beneath the floor of the locomotive - is one I will never forget.  It happened about six years ago.  It was dreadful!  But you're dead.  It doesn't matter to you, does it?  Thousands of people were affected.  Thousands!  And your poor family!  They will have to go on somehow.  Oh, how they must hate you for what you've done.    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      August 1, 2004    Sunday.  New week.  New month.  Good-bye July.  See you next year!  I didnt feel like going to church this morning.  I sat around here and had breakfast and drank copious amounts of coffee.  Read the script again.  The script?  Caught In The Net.  Auditions are this month in Caledon.  Maybe Ill be off book for the audition.  Bet that doesnt happen often.  LOL!  Did some laundry.  Pretty boring morning, actually.  I called Andra but she wasnt home.  I called Mom and Dad but they werent home either.  I got an email from Cathy.  Shes one of my GO girls.  I scanned some photos of Cathy and her beau that I took at my birthday barbecue last Saturday, and sent them to her yesterday.    thanks for the pics Dale........ it will be good to see everyone on Tues ! that train accident on Fri evening where they hit a  pedestrian - that wasn't your train was it ? God I hope not... Rose and I heard it on the radio and we were trying to figure out and hoping it wasn't your train.....  If you have nothing planned for today - why dont you drop in and bring your shorts and join us on patio beach !!  give me a call if you like ..........  thanks again for the pics  Cathy :)    So I called her and drove out to Oakville to spend the afternoon with Cathy and her sister, Rose.  I took a salad and some fresh corn for dinner. DJ arrived later and bbqd some steaks.  We ate til we were stuffed.  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~   I took my leave of them around 9:00 and drove to Acton.  I had to have a talk with my boy.  Dan answered the door when  I knocked.  I wanted to hug him, hold him, as soon as I saw him.  But instead I said hello as coolly as I could.   Youre kinda late, Dan said rather tentatively.  We were just relaxing here.  Having a quiet evening.  His eyes never met mine.  He was nervous and unsure of what to expect.  He knew I was angry for his recent behaviour.  I entered his mothers home and found her sitting on the couch with Tim.  Baby Emily played on a blanket on the floor.  I came immediately to the point.  What do you think we should do, Kel? I asked.  Should I take him out and speak with him privately or do you want to have some input in the discussion?  Quite honestly, I think this involves Tim as well.  He should be included.  Kelly smiled nervously.  Well, we were just er  relaxing, you know?  Winding down for the evening.  We didnt really expect youd call tonight.  Dan walked around me and sat in the big arm chair.  I remained standing.  Everythings pretty good now, she continued.  Do you want something to drink?  No.  Thank you.  Ive come to talk with The Boy.  I want to do that.  And so it began.  I told Dan I would not, COULD NOT countenance his aggressive and violent behaviour.  I told him hed better learn somehow to keep his temper in check or hed surely come to a bad end.  Kelly offered her thoughts and described her feelings.  Tim too, added his opinion, which was more than welcome and quite appropriate given the fact that Dan had been disrespectful of the woman Tim loves.  I told Dan Im sick to death of his lies and his empty promises.  I know hes struggling right now.  I know its hard to find a job.  I know its a daunting prospect.  But hes got to try.  At least try.  I suggested that if hed like to live with me, he might more easily find employment.  (Torontos a big city.  Acton is a culturally and economically depressed little pimple of a town on the arse of Halton Region.)  But The Boy seemed averse to relocating.  Hell be eighteen years old next month.  He hasnt finished high school yet.  He has no plan whatsoever for the future.  I believe that if he found a job, hed be a much happier young man.  Hed have a purpose to his Life.  Direction.  Motivation.  His mother agrees.  So does Tim.  It was nearly 11:00 when I left to come home.  I hugged my son at the door.  I hugged him for a long time.  Gosh, hes big!  Tall.  Strong.  He held me snuggly and rubbed my back.  He smelled of shampoo.  I love you, Daniel, I said.   I love you too, Dad.  My wish for you, Dan, is that you might come to love yourself as much as I love you.  I pray those words find their way to his heart.     August 2, 2004    Monday.  Holiday Monday.  No work today.  The trains will operate on a Saturday schedule.  Its a civic holiday.  No reason for it, really.  Theres nothing to celebrate, other than the fact that we dont have to work today.  Nearly everyone gets to enjoy a long weekend.  Its been a muggy day here in Mimico.  Disgustingly hot and humid.  30C.  The humidex makes it feel like 39C.  So says Environment Canada.  I went out to do some yard work this afternoon and nearly perished in the heat.  I pulled weeds and generally surveyed my domain for an hour or more until I could bear it no longer.  My shirt was soaked with sweat.  Even my glasses were steaming over.  I came in the house, and went straight upstairs to shower.  I let the water run as cool as I could stand it.  When I finished, I dried off a little then stood naked in front of the fan for ten minutes.  Golly that felt good!  I wear glasses now, Ms J.  Theyre drugstore glasses.   I call them my cheaters.  Soon  very soon, Ill have to see an optometrist and get a prescription for proper glasses.  Ive put it off as long as possible.  But honestly, whats the difference whether I wear cheap, ill-fitting drugstore glasses or good quality, prescription glasses?  If I must wear them, why not get a pair that fit?  And that feel comfortable.  My employee benefits cover up to $150 of the cost of glasses.  Meagans gone to camp.  Kelly took her yesterday afternoon to Teen Ranch in the rolling hills of Caledon.  The camp is midway between Caledon and Orangeville, about an hour north-west of her home in Acton.  My little girl gets a week at camp while her brother gets reprimanded and ragged on.  The poor guy really needs to get away from the television and get himself a job.  Hed be happier and so would his mom.  I just want the boy to grow.  I want him to become a man, in every sense of the word.  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  I barbecued some hamburgers for dinner tonight.  It was delicious!  I had fresh salad and corn on the cob too.  Mmmmm!!  Tastes like summer!  Its still pretty warm upstairs here.  Ill turn on the ceiling fan in the bedroom and point the other fan toward the bed.  Better put my toes up, as Dad would say.  Ill be up, as usual, at 4:15 for work.  Good night. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Live. Love. Laugh.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm ... OK. So I'm a blogger now, eh? Fantastic!  Could be I have something to say that may be of interest to you, dear reader. Or maybe not. But the main thing for me is sharing my thoughts with you. I welcome your comments, unless you can't be civil. Rude, slanderous, or obscene comments are decidedly unwelcome. Please keep your trash to yourself.  Let me start by sharing some of my writing with you:  This is copied and pasted from my Personal Journal - July 13, 2004   I'm really enjoying the colours of summer. Every morning at work, I marvel at the beauty of the plants and trees that line the railway right-of-way:  Soft, mauve clouds of nettles seem to float among the various shades of green on both sides of our train as we roar past at 80 miles per hour. Spikes of mullein stand at attention, proudly displaying their brilliant yellow flowers. Happy-faced daisies bow and nod approvingly while Queen Anne's lace and Scotch thistle seem to bid us slow down as they twist and twirl and hiss angrily in our wake. Fallow fields surprise and please me with their sunny dandelions and slender golden rod. The grain is beginning to ripen and the browns and yellows delight me. Around a curve, the scenery changes as vibrant orange lilies grace the banks on either side of us. I smile quietly to myself, feeling as though I've been privy to something wonderful and hitherto unknown.  The trees show their colours too. Silver birch. Verdant copses of pine - Scotch, red and white, laden with cones. On this side, a hemlock. Blue spruce on the other. Nova Scotia blue spruce. And over there, a lithesome poplar displays yellow leaves. It grows so straight and tall, it's magnificent! It's all magnificent, isn't it? Sometimes, when the sun's light is just right, and the sky is blue with the promise of good things yet to come, I'm nearly overcome with joy. A smile creases my face and my eyes fill with tears.  Mom told me once, that her minister, Donna Mann, said that when you see something truly awe-inspiring, and it leaves you breathless, it's a gift from God. Directly from the Lord to you. Custom made. Isn't that wonderful??!!  When I was up at Pat's Land with Dad and Daniel in May, Dad and I were sitting together on a log back in the bush. We were taking a break. I looked up at the tree tops and noted how perfect they appeared against the clear blue sky.  "You know, Dad," I confided, "I really like trees. It seems as I get older, I like them more and more. Flowers too. I seem to notice them more. Appreciate them more."  Dad smiled and nodded his head. It was clear he understood my sentiment.  "Shit," he chuckled. "I even enjoy looking at a weed."  I felt happy for my dad. And in that moment, I looked forward to growing old.      So anyway, that's all I feel like writing at the moment. I suppose if the mood strikes me, I'll post again later. Posting. Hmm. That's what it's called, eh? If you're in a hurry to do it, is it called post haste? Sorry. Can't resist a pun.      I'm off now in the heat the day to deposit a cheque in the bank. And to buy some hamburger for dinner. I have a new barbecue, dear reader. I'll tell you about it later.       Bye.  
    
</post>


</Blog>