<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      About Eraserhead :       urlLink IMDB :  Eraserhead        urlLink  In heaven everything is fine, David Lynch`s  Eraserhead .         urlLink Google : Eraserhead           About David Lynch :          urlLink DAVIDLYNCH.COM         urlLink davidlynch.de         urlLink On Lynch  (french)        urlLink lynchnet.com         urlLink Google : David Lynch            
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Pimp-no-sis : The word refers to a dark and powerful science. The science of the player -- the attitude, the way of life, the manner of speech.  The intent is not to glorify, nor is it to judge. It is to walk under the red lights and into the smoky taverns of a secretive world, to take snapshots, to listen to hushed whispers, to simply observe.  Two years ago, award-winning photographer Tracy Funches and award-winning journalist Rob Marriott set out to capture the pimp lifestyle in all its pomp and posture -- and to bring it into the light as has never been done before. Funches's powerful images depict the raw and intimate truth behind the glamour, while Marriott's text brings the characters and voices to life. Here is an unsentimental look at the underground world of pimps. The tattoos. The clothes. The icy stare of a hardened hustler. Uncensored.  Your guide through this netherworld is a composite character called Mississippi Twilight. Born of the many interviews conducted with real-life players, Twilight takes you on an all-access tour through pimp life: his beginnings, his women, his peers, and his enemies. Finally, he takes you to: a Players' Ball -- the underground gathering where the game is laid down and true players are recognized.  Some of your notions of pimps will be dispelled, others reinforced, but one thing will remain certain: You'll never look at pimps the same way again.   www.pimpnosis.com     urlLink    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink     
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      See more of Kinsey at  Kinseyvisual.com     urlLink     Life around Us - 2004     urlLink     Rethink on wood - 2000     urlLink     Collage Series 31 - 2003  
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A full-color quarterly art & design publication established to seek out those who depend on their creativity to survive.  In this issue:         The Girl Art Dump  (responsible for some of the best skate-related design ever)     urlLink David Choe    Michael & Laura Leon    urlLink Ryan McGinness    ... and more.        artprostitute.com              © urlLink turntablelab    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Invicid  is a line of men’s and women’s urban t-shirts, polos, hoodies and sweatshirts.   urlLink    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      About  urlLink  La Spirale   :   urlLink " La Spirale   is the continuation of a photocopied cyberpunk information flyer distributed free in Paris from 1993 to 1995. Since its initial foray onto the net in 1995  La Spirale    has been continually enriched and updated, settling into a regular weekly cadence by September 1999.  A baroque treasure-house of contemporary Counter Cultures and their myriad and diverse forms of expression,  La Spirale  has accumulated a wealth of bilingual content (French and English) in the course of it's five-year existence. Digital design, computer piracy, guerilla media tactics, body modifications and other significant deviancies and aberrant manifestations of our time."     urlLink    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fav' books :    urlLink  Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas   ,      urlLink Hell's Angels  ,      urlLink The Rum Diary   .  All about Hunter :  Gonzo.org      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Fav' song  : Hallelujah      Links :   urlLink Nick Cave Online   urlLink nickcaveandthebadseeds.com   urlLink Nick Cave / Bad-Seed.org   urlLink [mute] Nick Cave &amp; The Bad Seeds   urlLink Google : Nick Cave  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         "If you've ever asked yourself, "Why aren't I famous?" this is the place to find out. This site highlights the relationship between success and family and how coming from the right one almost always guarantees success (or at least Celebrity)."   urlLink     
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Beautiful, perfect and extraordinary ...    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This sumptuous and exclusive limited edition brings  urlLink Industrial Records ' original Boxed 24 cassette edition into the 21st Century. The new release consists of 24 individually packaged CDs which encompass the majority of  urlLink TG 's live output sensitively remastered by  urlLink Chris Carter . The box set also includes a sealed file containing a myriad of new and unique artifacts, such as buttons, patches & postcards, as well as commentary provided by all four members of  urlLink Throbbing Gristle .   Click here  to order online  
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Born in 1958 in Vienna, Austria. Lived in Berlin 1979-84. Studied philosophy. Doctoral thesis: "Film as Art. Towards a Critical Aesthetics of Cinematography" (1985/86). Teaches film making at the Academies of Applied Arts in Linz and Vienna. Founding member of Sixpack Film. Organized several international avant-garde film festivals in Vienna and film tours abroad. Since 1984 numerous publications and lectures on the history and theory of avant-garde film. 1993 and 1994 artistic director of the annual Austrian film festival "Diagonale". Editor of the book "Peter Kubelka" (1995, together with G. Jutz). Films since 1979. 								 "With more than 20 films since 1979,  urlLink Peter Tscherkassky  is one of Austria's most productive film-makers. What is remarkable, however, is not so much the quantity as the consistent quality of his work.  urlLink Tscherkassky  never allows himself to fall back on certainties, rather, with each film, he is sizing up new territory.  urlLink Tscherkassky 's films are exceptional because he knows how to pair his strict concepts and his consistent exploration of a subject with a visual richness, revealing new, surprising facets of sensuality with every film he makes." (Alexander Horwath)    "A confrontation with the codes of narrative-representational cinema is one of  urlLink Peter Tscherkassky 's constant concerns. If one attempts to distill a constant from his films, then this must surely be the oscillation between the abstract and the concrete, between the dry and the sensual, which is the source of energy of his work. The question of belly or brain is one which  urlLink Tscherkassky  stopped asking long ago — for ultimately sobriety is the route to ecstasy."   (Gabriele Jutz)    urlLink  Peter Tscherkassky - Official website     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fav' song :  Non-Stop Dancing   All about The Jam :  urlLink  thejam.org      About "In The City" : "Funneling the punk Spirit of '77 through the grooves of old Mod and Motown records, Jam frontman Paul Weller created a sound and vision that took Britain by storm but never made much noise in the USA. That's a shame because at the band's best, as on this album's furious, Who-meets-The-Pistols title track, The Jam played nothing less than great rock and roll. Their explosive cover of "Slow Down" destroys The Beatles', and "Non-stop Dancing," which sounds like a cover of an old R&amp;B hit but is actually a Weller original, has a charm and desperate energy that more than makes up for its derivative qualities."  David Cantwell,  urlLink Super70s.com   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The  CUBEX Pack  is produced by  Rebel One ,  Readymade Projects ,  Delta  and  Ambush . The pack countains a t-shirt and a vinyl sticker sheet packaged in an industrial tote bag exclusively designed by  Delta . Each t-shirt is silkscreened in random colour variations on white t-shirt, no two t-shirts are the same. Price : US$50.00. Includes shipping worldwide. Buy it at  www.rebelone.net      © Rebel One 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink BLK/MRKT Gallery  is a contemporary arts gallery located in Culver City, CA.     "Mono" by  urlLink Evan Hecox  .  © BLK/MRKT &amp; Evan Hecox.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
                         Trailer    [.MOV - 10 MO]        All about George Lucas' first feature film,  urlLink  THX - 1138  .       imdb :  urlLink  THX-1138          urlLink  thx1138  movie.com     Classic Science Fiction Reviews:  THX-1138         Google :  urlLink  TX-1138      
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fav Song : Spider      urlLink Herbie Hancock - Official Web Site 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Googlism.com  will find out what  urlLink Google.com  thinks of you, your friends or anything.  Hu ,  hu  ...  Googlism for :  Absinthe  :  absinthe is temporarily closed absinthe is divine absinthe is back in france absinthe is information available absinthe is making a comeback absinthe is a must in every well absinthe is very rare today absinthe is that it is a drug absinthe is divine absinthe by assassin absinthe is illegal to sell for human consumption because it contains the chemical thujone which is banned by the fda for use in foods absinthe is back in france culture/society news source absinthe is the most sought after drink in the web today absinthe is for collectable & entertainment purposes only absinthe is a liquer absinthe is distilled according to its original processes and derives its name from an extract of wormwood absinthe is pronounced ab absinthe is wormwood and its derivative essence thujone absinthe is becoming the drink du jour of victorian era enthusiasts absinthe is an anise absinthe is legal in some countries but there is also a limitation on the amount of essence of wormwood presented in it and it absinthe is made from a spirit high in alcohol absinthe is art absinthe is flavoured absinthe is rapidly regaining a wide following absinthe is back absinthe is the illegal absinthe is not offered; same story as blowfish absinthe is an emerald green color absinthe is stteped in history and lore absinthe is a potent herbal spirit whose popularity peaked with 19th century cafe society in europe absinthe is a semi absinthe is a pale vivid absinthe is available in larger tesco stores in the uk absinthe is poured into a glass absinthe is a drink that contains a high absinthe is a strong absinthe is poured into the glass place the absinthe spoon atop the glass absinthe is a bitter green liquor containing large amounts of anise and wormwood absinthe is absinthe is toxic true? yes and no absinthe is banned in the us absinthe is bitter absinthe is distilled solely from plants anyway absinthe is the most poetical thing in the world absinthe is a symbol of inspiration and daring absinthe is made from a distillate of wormwood absinthe is now available absinthe is a greenish absinthe is derived from the greek absinthion absinthe is still available in some countries absinthe is illegal here in the us absinthe is a absinthe is a potent absinthe is still legal in spain absinthe is an alcoholic drink made with an extract from wormwood absinthe is the liqueur of absinthe is strongly connected with the bohemian era of paris absinthe is a bright green drink made from the hallucinogenic extract from the wormwood plant combined with anise absinthe is still legally absinthe is still legally available is spain absinthe is an emerald green alcoholic drink made with an extract from wormwood absinthe is the opposite absinthe is a strong alcoholic liqueur made from herbal extracts absinthe is that it is similar to drinking few shots absinthe is an aromatic absinthe is the main source of wormwood's notoriety absinthe is posted on north avenue absinthe is derived from the wormwood leaves in the preparation of the liquor absinthe is the alcohol/drug from the 1800's that has been banned in just about every country absinthe is legal in spain absinthe is a strong alcoholic beverage absinthe is about to be reborn at the turn of another century in san francisco absinthe is still produced in spain and andorra absinthe is not hallucinogenic and should not be drunk with any expectations of getting 'high' absinthe is the ritual absinthe is composed of wormwood absinthe is illegal in most places now absinthe is closely identified with counterculture absinthe is the aphrodiasiac of the self absinthe is also know as the `green fairy' absinthe is a liqour    urlLink Googlism 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      About Clarissa Tossin :  "Clarissa Tossin is an artist running a one_woman_design_studio concept based in São Paulo, Brazil, since 2002, exploring the possibilities of the graphic design's creative world in its most embracing meaning, not always commercial. "   Experimental Magazine.    Check out  urlLink a-linha.org  to know more about the "one_woman_design_studio" concept.     Fav' stuff : "The Man" and "The city" posters. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Fav' song : Song For Che'    urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      That's one of my favorite samplers/synths. 8 bit, 27,777 khz and 128kb memory, but the sound is simply ... hum ...  terrific. And his look is perfect :)  Check out urlLink www.emulatorarchvie.com  for mo' pics and infos.    urlLink      8 bits rulezzz !  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My blog is now on my own server. imperialj.blogspot.com is dead, viva  urlLink www.imperialj.com/blog  :p  J 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
             The world of photography is mourning one of its giants, Henri Cartier-Bresson, who's died yesterday, at the age of 95.  Here is a list of links about his work.   urlLink Fondation Henri Cartier-Bresson   urlLink Magnum Photos   urlLink Bibliothèque Nationale De France   urlLink National Portrait Gallery   urlLink Peter Fetterman Gallery   urlLink Photology   urlLink Tête à Tête : Portraits by Henri Cartier-Bresson   urlLink Les Maîtres De La Photo (french website) : Biography, Gallery & Links   urlLink Artcyclopedia : Henri Cartier-Bresson   More Links :  urlLink Google   
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fav Songs : All !  urlLink    Johnny Cash - Unearthed
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      An Obscene Pang was a Belgian band headed by Pascale Tempels &amp; Pascal Lacroix. Both are now  urlLink 48 Cameras ' members. "Hyper E.P" was recorded in 1997 and published by Besides. What can I say about this record ? ... I like it, I really like it.   urlLink You can buy it here   Fav songs : Hypersex, Be My Guide. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fav song : These Are The Ghosts.  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dear friends and foes, Dear You,  Welcome to /// Imperial J >> Blog ///  It will be a place where i'll share my love about various stuffs ( records, books, movies, ...).  If you are here to know more about my outrageous sexual life, my drugs addiction or my stamps collection, you aren't at the right place ;)  Anyway, I hope that you will have fun.  A lot of fun.  Imperial J 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>