<Blog>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So this is the blogspot eh? not half bad for a journal. lots less confusing than it could be i assume. Well here's a bit about me, I'm just going to post the basics. Not "basix" or any other stupid internet chat lingo. Like "u"....HOW HARD IS IT TO TYPE THE LETTERS Y-O-U?! ok less ranting. Well here's pretty much me. I'm Missy. I'm 14. I'm a Leo ((yes you needed to know that lol)) I have a boyfriend. Though I wish I didn't I guess. He's nice. Too nice....I don't know. I like him. I'm just really confused. In other news....I have a few friends I guess. Alot of them I wouldn't consider friends. I've barely talked to any of them since summer started. I talked to Megan today, and it wasn't the same. it wasn't like old times, but it was still cool. It's not the same anymore. Nothing's the same anymore. Shes been hangin out with my other friend lydia which is cool. I just feel shut off from the world now. I mean, I love my friends dearly but I just don't feel like they want to hang out with me anymore so I've stopped trying. And on top of that no one will leave me alone. Yes I did just say I felt shut off from the world and blah blah blah. but there are certain people who always talk to me. and i prefer to be alone sometimes. in fact i prefer being alone to being with people if i truly am alone. if im sitting outside thinking i don't want someone coming up to me and making small talk. I just want to sit and think. And if I sign onto the internet and I'm in a bad mood. I don't want someone talking to me about why I'm in a bad mood unless I bring it up. If I bring it up fine. If not, then it's none of your damn business. I hate this. Ever since I got a boyfriend I've been feeling suffocated. I know this isn't how I'm supposed to feeling. I'm not supposed to be feeling suffocated. I'm not supposed to be feeling annoyed by talking to him. And I'm not supposed to be feeling numb. But I am. And my family is going crazy as well. I don't want to deal with them. I don't want to deal with him. And my friends are off in lala land somewhere. So I guess I don't want to deal with them either. I'm isolating myself again. YAY! Sounds like fun huh? My whole life feels like it's spinning out of control. I think I'm going to go take some random medication to make myself sleep. How am I ill you ask? I'm not. I haven't been able to sleep without cough medicine though. Lovely eh? Addiction to something like that. Oh well. That or I'm going to get myself some alcohol and drown my problems. Sound fun? I think so too.   ~Missy.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>