<Blog>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, I  was  in a sour mood the past few days.  Not enough food, too much work, not enough sleep. Remedys have been applied, I'm feeling just hunkey-fucking-dorey today, thank-you-very-much.  Actually, I'm missing my girlfriend, and about to go make dinner. I've had another long day, and need to get in a meeting some time, but things are pretty good. I need to relax, get a little illustration done and play a video game. Get my head straight.  I'm enjoying journaling again. This is helpful. It's strange doing it online, I find myself revising it, as I don't feel like it's a private forum, which of course it isn't. Having someone comment almost immediately on my first log was a little disconcerting too. I don't want to journal for an audience, but it would be nice to feel like part of an extended community again.  I'm a gamer at heart. I played Asheron's Call for a few years, and it kept me sober through the hardest parts of staying sober by giving me a community outside myself and outside my immediate circle of friends, who were for the most part drinking and partying friends, which were dangerous to my re-developing self. I could safely lock myself away at home and still have social contact and interaction while playing through safe fantasies - as a gamer since a young kid and a lover of good RPGs, AC provided exactly that.  Now, I'm sober for three years plus, and feel like I'm in a rut again. I've gained a girlfriend and a more stable life, a good house with a decent garden, am a lot more stable in my job, am trusted and gaining respect, but don't really have a good circle of friends like I once did. I guess that having drugs and alcohol and all that shit pretty much acted as a unifying common interest, but it was a pretty shallow and fleeting pretty quickly as soon as I gave it all up. I didn't sever my ties with my old friends as was suggested by treatment centers, rehab programs, all that stuff. I just knew I couldn't trust myself to be around them as they got fucked up. I needed to stay clean, at least to prove to myself I could, because all previous attempts to do so had failed, and I was in the center of a crushing depression that would end up killing me, either through suicide, overdose or wrapping myself around a telephone pole.  I still see them once in a while, my old friends, but it's almost always me who makes the initiative to make contact and hang out. They don't really have much interest in making the effort to see me. Which is okay, it's not like we really do have a lot in common any more. Scary thought.  So, I'm here, typing neurotically into a computer, posting these pretty private thoughts into an online journal. Someone may come along and read them, for good or ill. Whatever. It's not like I hide this information. It's just what I've done, who I've been and just more cobbles on the road behind.  All I'm saying is that I feel empty still. No... purpose. No fulfillment, or any that's meaningful enough.  I know I'm not alone in feeling that, but is this just something common in people my age, or is it more universal? Am I just driving myself nuts again?  I do good work. I am a good person. I honestly make an effort and take pride in the fact that I am a  nice  person any more. Perhaps I'm trying to make up for past sins, or whatever.  I'm not religious, and don't ever plan on being. I'm agnostic, I believe that there are powers far greater than humankind, but I really really fucking doubt they care whether I attend a temple every arbitrary duration of time, or any of the bullshit baggage and misconception we get from organized religion. Fuck it all. Keep your wars, keep your judgements, keep your history of slaughter for  ideas , just keep it to yourself. Religion has already indelibly inked the surface and tarnished the history of this entire species for so long it's remarkable it hasn't been abolished, except for the fact that we're humans, with a short life span, a short history, a huge capacity for self-hatred and an overwhelming need for stories and excuses to believe that we are walking in the path of the righteous and will be given the key to everlasting paradise as long as we give blind faith in something outside of  other people.   This is why I believe that there are other things in this universe more powerful than human beings.  Gravity  for instance.  Glaciers. The tides. Volcanos. Supernovas.  But probably not God, or Gods, or whatever you want to call them. Even giving them a label and a name like that limits what they can ever become, because we've already given them identities and thus limited what they can be. Fuck that.    Holy shit. Where did all this come from?  I'm gunna go make dinner. Go read something else. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for what it's worth, here's a link to some firework photos I've taken. Turned out surprisingly cool looking, not at all what I expected.   urlLink My firework photos  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another day at work. Another day is gone. Forever. How did  that  happen?  I make graphics, in a hurry. In a tornado is more like it.  Small town retail graphic design is like like being a juggler in a windstorm. Neat trick, pretty frantic, and who  really  cares?  Screw it. I need food, I need bed, I need to get my other work done, and instead I'm watching my fingers put letters on a screen in a relatively pointless display of procrastination.  Again.   I was in a pretty bad mood last night. Not that this one is  too  much better, but at least I can appreciate the fact that yesterday sucked more than today. That's progress.   Right?    Who else am I?  Well, for one thing, I'm a 25-year-old that lists not having a drug or a drink in over 3 years as an accomplishment.  I take a strange pride in the fact that I can grow tomato plants successfully. So far.  I used to dream of animating cartoons, but haven't drawn a picture for the sake of really  drawing  a picture in a couple years, I think. I used to consider art as sacred as masturbation.  I was 15 at that time, if that tells you anything.   Today... I'm at another crossroads, just like every day. I can choose my path and wind off into the glorious sunset of unknown tomorrow, and all that poetic crap. But instead, I feel like I'm in neutral on a slowly-sloping hill. Not gaining momentum, but just coasting in one direction. And I can't really see where I'm going.  In fact, I'm still not sure if I read the signs right on the way here. I don't think I'm lost, I jsut don't think I know where I'm ending up.   But hell, I'm 25. Fuck it. I'm young. I've got my whole life ahead of me.    Great. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nothing better to do, might as well dive headlong into the shallow pool, along with the rest of the lemmings.  God, how pessimistic.  You really wanna know about me? I'm 25, a graphic designer, lead singer of a punk band, an illustrator, a brother, a son, a boyfriend, a skinny nervous sarcastic geek, a former jailbird, a failed children's author, a gamer, a misfit, and an asshole with a knack for entertaining small crowds when necessary.  I'm too lazy to cut my hair, and it's too curly to look cool, to long to look hip, and just odd.  I pick at my cuticles until they bleed. My girlfriend thinks it's obsessive-compulsive disorder. I just think my hands get bored.  I should be asleep right now, but I'm bored and, for some reason, am posting up these strange thoughts on the internet.  I live with three other guys, members of my band. I have the big room, because... well, because.  I'm going to sleep. If I feel like writing more, I will. If not, then who cares? Go read someone elses neuroses.
    
</post>


</Blog>