<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      FEEL freee... to enter ur comments
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I still not sure how much trust is starting to develop in you     BUT  don't worry about me considering other girls okay?                                    I love you for what you Are,                             I always cherish my quality time,                             With you,                             I felt comfortable,                             although i might be really buzy sometimes                              I would still try to send an sms to you                             Well... You're truly understanding,                               haha You can say that again ...                               Is this considered as a proposer online                          Or is this a confession... ? hehe ...                                                Anyway i think you already got what i meant right ?                          so... just to say that You're very meaningful to me                                This could get a little mushy   >_                                                                                               Shy ,shy                                                                                                                  LOVE you.zy                            
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       BGR  a natural sign for people around my age to be concern about    This is all written to tell her how i felt to be living with her for  1year3months       Myths had sound though the band of my friendships   like ripple across the pond,   nobody expected it to happen,    nobody knows how it ended,&   nobody expected i was the one who    Broke away from you...   They always says that sweet moments don't last , thats what i'm emphasising   I heard rumours and thought about it    well... you're right    I'm just like a lamp post to you     The presents if me when i'm with you   Shine you through the dark,   you didn't cherish my presents,    you took it for granted,    we felt it,   I knew.   when the lamp post lost its ability to shine   what i heard was you somehow felt [lost]    Sorry  for  exposing you but if you really cherish me , i should say that you should start way-back from the start      I've tired but the result is the same      I'm living happily with my current relationship      Whether its too direct or too firm       i should say that I'm not the one for you &amp; with all your visible conditions , i've confident that you can find someone who is patient ,     understands your needs ,     &amp; Finally who  you Loves       Best wishes           
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       "THANKS" for intoducing me the girl which you MMS her my pics     well...i must say that i really hate you for this .......   she called and claimed that her name is  carol  and betrayed you by telling me its you who sent the photos , i'll not blame you for what you have done if uyou could find a way to keep her outta my inbox whenever i msg???    haha YOU r really good with this kinda joke man ...      Btw if you see this pls send my regards to Ah Kiat1 &amp; Ah kiat2  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       everything now seem so complex to me ...   Althought i can get very buzy most of the time but i won't forget 3 important things    > Friends    > Family    >& my DearDear    i've to apologised here to tell anyone that is nelgected by me for past few weeks that     I'm sorry ...........   oh i almost forgot! a special thanks to HuiHui for excusing me for the last outing to Marina South , pai sei i'm on a diet HEHE...(-_-)!   
      
</post>


</Blog>