<Blog>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       On 27 March 1968, Suharto was declared the President of Indonesia. Events leading to the inaugaration of Indonesia’s second president started with the notorious yet controversial 30th September Movement in 1965.  Suharto’s grip of power was shrouded in controversy, debating as to whether the coup overthrowing the president was inspired by communism, or the army pre-empting the coup. The coup might also have been a setup by the army, supposedly in the name of protecting the president, to eradicate the communists before overthrowing the president. Despite the controversies, Major-General Suharto, a senior army officer in his forties, was quick to seize the opportunity in establishing support from the coup. Not surprisingly, he earned kudos for his presidential bid.  Sukarno won independence for Indonesia from the Dutch and fashioned Indonesia through his notion of a Guided Democracy – a balanced power relationship between the President, the army and the PKI (Indonesian Communist Party). The 30th September coup, however, crippled this triangle and accelerated the fall of Sukarno. Before the 1965 coup, factual accounts proved that the Indonesia under Sukarno, a president whose health was ailing, had also been crippled by economic woes and sour international relations. Such mismanagement of the country saw Sukarno’s popularity plummet and hastened his fall from the presidency.  Sukarno’s leftist-slant towards communism led Indonesia’s foreign policy into making bold but preposterous moves by forcing the merger of Netherlands New Guinea into Indonesia and declaring war on Malaysia. By August 1965 Sukarno had withdrew Indonesia from the International Monetary Fund, Interpol and the World Bank, thereby isolating Indonesia from the capitalist market. Indonesia’s social, political and economic structures were in chaos. Inflation soared to 900 per cent, export trade collapsed, and shortages of food sparked riots and signalled an imminent coup. Indonesia was in economic disarray and politically tumultuous.  The PKI, whose members totalled more than three million, provided the mass support for Sukarno’s external militant campaigns, while Sukarno offered protection for the PKI against persecution by the army. Sukarno was balancing on a very fragile power triangle that was his Guided Democracy. It is likely that Sukarno’s increasing reliance on the PKI in the mid-60s made the army feel its position was threatened and this exposed the soft underbelly of the Guided Democracy. It prompted Colonel Untung to execute the 30th September movement from Halim airbase. This Movement, from which Suharto was to benefit the most, left six army generals dead, including Army Chief of Staff General Achmad Yani. General Nasution managed to escape and Suharto was left off the list due to his neutralist stance. The death of six prominent army generals left Suharto, commander of the Army Strategic Reserve (Kostrad), a heavy responsibility but along with a fortuitous luck since there were no other generals who could match his appointment.  Lieutenant Colonel Untung announced on the radio that the coup was planned by a ‘Council of Generals’ who sought to overthrow the president and the Movement was to pre-empt a coup by the army on President Sukarno. Untung assured that Sukarno was under the protection of the Movement but he did not mention that he acted in accordance to Sukarno’s orders.  Suspicions logically arise that Suharto was one of the plotters. Colonel Latief, one of the key plotters of the coup, was rumoured to have visited Suharto twice shortly before 30th September and warned Suharto about the plot, hence suggesting that Suharto was able to make ample preparation to topple and subdue the coup. When Latief was brought to trial in 1976, he admitted that he had told Suharto about the imminent coup two days earlier.  With the death of Yani and the absence of Nasution, Suharto gained recognition from the people and grabbed the opportunity to seize command of the army. Suharto proclaimed over the radio that he had taken control of the army and would make sure he crushed the 30th September Movement to ensure the safety of the President. Suharto immediately took measures to counter the coup by talking the two rebel battalions over to his side. He contacted other key army officers and secured their support for acting against Halim, where the 30th September Movement took place. On the morning of 2nd October 1965, Suharto moved his forces and took control over Halim airbase. Simultaneously, Suharto took control over the national radio station and closed down most of Indonesia’s newspapers, manipulating the event to his will.  The PKI was accused of masterminding the coup due to the killing and mutilation of the generals at Halim. An autopsy carried out several years later revealed that such mutilation never took place. Sukarno was, at this stage, still reluctant to ban PKI activities and its organisation. Suharto swiftly made his counterattack once more by inciting the military to allow the massacre of the PKI by the Muslims across Java, Bali and Sumatra, thus smashing Sukarno’s triangular relationship with the army and the PKI. The number of deaths was estimated at between 100,000 to more than one million, although a figure of between 300,000 and 500,000 is more likely. Furthermore the massacre of communists and left-wing sympathisers was supported by the US embassy, which provided logistical support to the army. Suharto’s name became known to the US through this bloodbath and with the US throwing her weight behind Suharto, his presidential bid was strengthened.  Suharto, in a bid to undermine the remaining pro-Sukarno military and civilian forces, disseminated details of Sukarno’s political, economic and moral transgression. Sukarno was subsequently coerced into signing the ‘March 11 Order’, which bestowed extensive political and military powers on Suharto in the name of preserving law and order and ‘protecting the president’. Thus, the 1966 ‘March 11 Order’ shifted the domestic balance of power in favour of Suharto and reduced Sukarno’s rights to leadership. In January 1966, with support from the student demonstrations, Suharto further flexed his political muscles.  After the ‘March 11 Order’, Suharto implemented a series of reforms for Indonesia. First, he set up a new cabinet excluding supporters of Sukarno. Following that, swift negotiations helped patch up Indonesia’s relationship with Malaysia. Steps were then taken for Indonesia to rejoin the United Nations and economic problems were tackled, particularly in areas like debt repayments, trade stimulation, controlling inflation, encouraging investment, and improving production of goods and services. By March 1966, PKI and its mass organisations were officially outlawed and suspected communists were purged from all governmental sectors. Sukarno eventually signed the transfer of power promulgated on 20 February 1967, and on March 1967, Suharto assumed the role of Acting President.  It was not until 27 March 1968 that Suharto was declared the President of Indonesia under the decision of the MPR (People’s Deliberative Congress, whose function is to choose the president and vice-president). It has been two years since the ‘March 11 Order’ before Suharto formally took the role of president. Suharto, whose power was still frail and doubtful in the months following October 1965, chose to adhere to a slow constitutional process rather than a forced eviction on Sukarno. This was centred on fear of setting a risky precedent for the future if Sukarno was ousted by force. With Sukarno officially stepping down as president, the shift from Sukarno’s Guided Democracy to Suharto’s New Order was slow but accepted by the nation.     Despite lingering controversies about the true nature and intention of the coup, Suharto reaped the most from it and occupied the presidency seat for over thirty years.  
    
</post>


</Blog>