<Blog>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I've been a fan of Peter Biskind's  Easy Riders, Raging Bulls,  for a good while now, avidly reading it as a bored suburban schoolgirl, desperate to lose myself in the glamour and creativity of such a world (it was around this time, to distract myself from the mounting terror of my A-level exams that I devoured  The Kid Stays in the Picture,  biographies of Brando and Clift and studies of Method Acting. I also became totally obsessed with  The Godfather  Parts 1&2 and  The Deer Hunter.  The year before, it had been  Hamlet.  Quite a leap, no?)    Anyway, last night, in the name of 'research' as I prepare to edit my own documentary, I sat down with the filmed version of  Easy Riders.  A selection of the bright lights of the era of American indie filmmaking, lauded by hip students and filmmakers today as the greats of cinema - Bogdonavich, Hopper, Fonda,  Scorcese, Coppola, Raefelson, De Palma, Lucas, Spielberg -of them only Hopper, Fonda and Bogdonavich spoke (the latter at great length - a full interview with him was an extra feature of the DVD). And not a flicker of humour was there among them - only briefly from a haggard-looking Margot Kidder and a prickly yet mesmerising Richard Dreyfuss. The belief in their own collective and individual genuis was powerful as ever, and now that they are, of course, the very syllabus of film schools internationally, the subjects of theses and studies and publications, they have very little reason to doubt their stature, their contribution, their brilliance.   And indeed, some of their work  is  brilliant. But it is the hard lesson to learn, as a lover of books, movies, music, drama, that those works which become such a fabric of one's inner life, that one lives and breathes and adores - it is the hard lesson to learn that the  creators  of such works, may not necessarily be as decent or illuminating or  noble  as the works they have produced. Simple and obvious. The best of the artist goes into their work. Yet endlessly disappointing. And a lesson that seems to have been quietly pushed under the rug of late, in an era in which it is  personality  that is important, above and beyond anything else.   That is why I so idolosed Bob Evans for a time - it was the sheer energy and  personality  that was captivating (though not, I imagine, for any hapless woman that would have fallen for him). It was also the strength of the masculinity, the confidence, the devil-may-care attitude to life (not to work) that was so extraordinary to me - he never seemed to worry overly about losing a wife, a friend, a lover - events that would shake the very fibre of one's being in the 'normal' course of a life - nope, no worries - there'd always be another one to fill the gap, and anyway - there was very little gap to fill, the work being all-consuming.   This I saw as a virtue, and as the way things should be - the obsessive nature of a project, the sinking of oneself into something external, the value of the work. These things I found deeply attractive and I craved them for myself. But I didn't see somehow the  ego  that made this seem so wonderful, so right and true. The ego that says 'whatever I apply myself to, will bring greatness'. Breathtaking. Impressive. American. Narrow-sighted. But awesome. And yet, what is it that makes a successful life? Is it this? A few good works at the cost of...what? None of this is new, or original or even striking, and yet, coming away from watching these middle-aged guys, still basking in a haze of self-approbation and deferential arse-licking, I am overwhelmingly struck by the insignificance of it all. And this from someone who wants nothing more than to make movies.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Or even a week for that matter. Flying back to Dublin, my home for close on six years, from London, a feeling of quiet pleasure  -  the pleasure of habit and the known - mingled with that slight sinking desperation, the viewing of one's life as a whole, a sense of stangnation and of impossibility. Self-pity, really, but an awareness that Dublin is a city of deception, and a city where the lost can stay put, drowning their sorrows and talking their talk. Insularity is the key, and this is a city that breeds it in spades.       I am strangely attracted to this place, and despise myself for it sometimes, for it is the breeding ground of PC do-gooding and middle-class liberalism that beats anything England has to offer. And that, it would appear, is the point. There is an unspoken fear about 'not keeping up with the Joneses' - in this case, the neighbouring isle - and this has resulted in a middle-class more frightful than even Dickens could have imagined. There is snobbery in the water of the South Dublin suburbs - it is the snobbery of new money and old, old grievances - tempered with a recent attempt at cosmopolitanism that falls flat on its face. Why does it never quite work, here? Why is there always something that lets the whole enterprise down?  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>