<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Servando Gonzales -- Kiss Your Internet Goodby   Interesting little article that will appeal to the conspiracy theorists amongst us... including me naturally. One of the biggest benefits of the Internet is that it gives you and I the same freedom to publish and potential to be read, as the NY Times, Washington Post or the NZ Herald.  The problem is, a lot of money has been spent to centralise the control of mainstream media and the diet of Pap we are fed every day... the media moguls don't want upstarts like us publishing the our views outside of their control, and the biggest uncontrolled tool...the Internet of course.  What to do??? WHAT to do??? it must be causing some serious sleepless nights for the powers that be. This report shows one man's prediction, and makes interesting reading.  "One of these days, out of the blue, the Internet will be used for launching a devastating terrorist attack on the United States. Somehow, this cyberattack will cost the lives of scores of American citizens. In order to avoid more damage, the government, putting to good use the recently approved anti-terrorist laws, will shut the Internet down and ban the use of the Internet as we know it."  I can't imagine a time without the Internet now...This anarchic, unregulated shouting match is the only opportunity left to find alternative viewpoints and real opinions. (remember those, before when having a minority opinion was no longer PC??)  Maybe George Orwell was less of a fiction writer, and more of a clairvoyant, just 25 years ahead of his time...   

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    What a week. Recovering from an abortive attempt at snow-boarding at Whakapapa... great weekend, if only to confirm that snow and I don't mix. Next time the crew can go shushing while I play 9 holes at the Chateau and enjoy the Après Ski.
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have no idea what to expect of this Blog. All I do know is that an idea, if not recorded or repeated... dies. Therefore this will be a record of ideas and quotes, views and philosophies, morals and ethics, all of which pertain solely and totally to me. Some would call this egotism but since I don't expect anyone else to read this, who cares.  If anyone does try to read this, good luck. My writing is atrocious, my spelling even worse. My logic is flawed and my view is warped. I make no apologies for what is contained herein because strange as it may appear, this is ME.  By the way, I'll try and put the source for everything but if I don't, it's likely to be me.  As a starter for 10, there is no such thing as an immoral, unethical or sinful person. There are only those people whose morals or ethics {their own   Life     Rules  } are so different from our own that we either don't understand them, or in the worst case, find them so abhorrent that we can't stand to associate with them.  Everyone strives for order in their life. Even the most confirmed anarchist imposes order on himself through his   Life Rules  . It's an intriguing idea to write down your own "Laws of Nature" as most people are not consciously aware of their own self-defined limits and constraints.  Some are formed by our parents, others by the society we live in, but the most interesting (and flexible) are those we create for ourselves through our own life experiences.  We can't enforce our own code on other people. At best we remove their free will (ie a Dictatorship), or at worst our code is given lip service while being used to keep others under control.  Moses tried this by giving the Jews the ten commandments {no capitals as they are someone else's rules}. Although fine in principle, most believers prefixed them all with "Thou shall not get caught..."  This brought about 2000+ years of almost pure hypocrisy on the part of the various christian religions. On one side they paid lip service to Jesus's rules...   which I have a great deal of respect for, so there.   On the other hand, the church has perpetrated atrocities that rival Hitler at his worst.  E.g. The Inquisition - used to gain power and wealth for the church while removing all rivals to the "Life Rules" of those in power, all in the name of God.  The domination and genocide of the Mayan's and Aztec's - lots of dosh scored out of that little bit of "Soul Saving".  What this has lead up to is this statement:    "No one has the right to impose his own rules on someone else and everyone has the right to defend his own freedom as long as he is prepared to face the consequences of his actions" 
</post>


</Blog>