<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Heya, what's up.... the Olympic games are on and me being Coral, Imma wishin' I was a swimmer.... Im wishing I'm everything. My road to satisfaction does not exist. So I got up, washed my face and brushed my teeth, rearranged my desktop with a collage, loaded the dishwasher, and gave my dog a bath. Now imma here to vent. 
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today was pretty busy,... no crazy... Julieanne started shit on the first damn day of school, anyway it's all good.  Highschool is fucking crazy. I can't stress that enough....  NOT A-FUCKING-NUFF! Everyone is different.... you've got the quiet one's the mean one's the sensitive one's the popular fake ones the flat out fake ones The meak wannabe preppy's flippin' their hair..... (By the way I dressed today you can just punch that stamp on my ass right now.) FUCK!   I feel so fucking dumb....... ttyl -coral  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So I just found out that Jen will be home around 10. That's cool. Her Mom doesn't know it but the "chaperones" aren't exactly going to be with them the whole time...  I hope she has a great time with luke and he doesn't make any moves on her cause she doesn't even want to kiss him on the first date. We'll that's that. Um... I don't know what to say about things lately other than that I've found it easier to stop feeling. I cried last night in bed. Something that hasn't happened in like a week truly. All I did was fight today. Chase the girls around with heavy objects. I got Joanna good with a plastic chair. Hahaha. I am so bad. Someone had to teach her. I am messed up, I know but what can I say? Jim just got home. He doesn't ask questions. Why do I not help around the house, why do I not listen to them, why do I do anything? He doesn't care why he just wants it to stop, well I say fuck him.                       Oh-So Sincerely, CORAL 
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So I was looking at Jennifers Mom's yearbook picture, wondering if she had a clue as to what was coming her way later on in life. Did she have an idea that she would go on to have one wonderful daughter and raise her single-handedly while getting her masters? That she would be a dedicated Christian? That she would work part time while doing all of this? That she would get her stomach stapled and lose about half of herself in her mid-40's? It's amazing. I never thought it possible but Teresa has more self-help books than my mother herself. The Queen of depending on others to tell her how to think and live. I'll kill myself before I live my life by books. j/k. I am just pretty against anything but winging your life by your own thoughts and standards. Maybe I will be more comfortable with self-delusion once I am 40 something. errr. I shudder at the thought. Anyway, so yeah. Maybe self help books and shit are the only way of getting through this life. Maybe for weak people. I'm not assuming anything. Teenagers think they know everything, don't they? Maybe everyone has these hopes. This sureness that we will never be like our parents no matter what. It'll probably hurt when I find out that I do need self help books. Haha. So many dreams. So little possibility. So much pain... Ah, you get used to it. Is that a bad thing? Yeah, somehow. The older I get the more pain I am dealt. The more I have a tolerance for and I might teach myself to stop dreaming, for apparent lack of foolishness. You tell me... 
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey, Just yesterday I spoke with one of my Mom's friends on the phone. He's gotten his Masters in Phycology and Law and he is just amazing. He talked my ear off for about an hour but I would have slowed it down and recorded it if possible. He's amazing. He has been a counselor before and he's just so good at pin pointing what's wrong in someone's life. Marriages, children, you name it. So he gave me some advice about... well a lot of advice about life, people, careers, college, the human mind, family life. He really helped me understand some things. 
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Heya everyone. I'm in a pretty good mood, probably because I just got Scott's comment.(Shout out to Scott!) Didn't go to the gym today, but I got a pedicure. Pretty cool. Jennifer can't paint for shit but I could care less. Hey Scott, your totally right... How can anyone go wrong with that kind of perspective? No wonder your so awesome.... Keep Rockin'... 
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I know nothing. Nothing, nothing, and more nothing. I want to always do the right thing but how can you distinguish between right and wrong when you know nothing? Just great. Ahh, my life's not that big a deal. There are thousands of people out there today abusing themselves and others with their insecurities and carelessness. What's another one? Somebody tell me that... 
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         So things have been going lately, as opposed to the last few weeks of my life. Um, things are changing. Almost no one knows this but changes are scary to me. I suppose it's because all my life I have been going through changes. And I didn't like them. Jim would do something stupid and we'd have to move in with a family member, friend, or a less expensive house. All I remember is the fighting and leaving a place once I finally felt I fit in. Listen to me bitching about my life, I hate this. 
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Alrighty, My mind is all over the place today. So many thoughts and concepts are being tossed around, I can't keep up.  This entry will be "language" free and censored if neccesary for Wade. You got a good point, I'm just not always a person that does the right thing. So Jims been here, back from the hospital and he's being a jerk. Can I say jerk? To call him a father would be a lie... To call him a worthy supervisor would be a joke. To call him anything other than a brainless ...evil person?..would be an overstatment. Or maybe you just don't know Jim. Allow me to explain... All my 15 years of life Jim has..messed...up. He has gambled away homes and vehicles of all kinds at many times. At one or two points he was abusive to my Mom and at times me. God forbid he lay a hand on his own two children. Can I say God? Now don't go stamping me an abused little child that was destined to end up in the phsyco ward... First read this. 
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Heya trusty Blog. I was just watching skinny bitch models box on T.V. The guy who put the whole disaster together said that they were going to be showing it monthly, then it hit me that by watching it I was supporting it, so I turned it off. Yes, I know. Another night of staying up. I have no discipline. Is it my fault? I think not!      I just realized that I look like every other damn white girl in America. I could pass for fucking britney Spears with some makeup and a tan. WTF? Just kidding. So my Mom told me a few days ago that Jim took all the money out of our bank account and gambled it away... I was like wtf!!! And then today she springs it on me that he got in a big-rig accident and is in the hospital... And I was like WTF !?! I'm not Aces on what it means but I do like to say wtf a lot. I hope I figure out what it means to me so I can analyze the shit out of it and find out what I've been feeling lately...Why? Because I said so! And I have nothing better to do because I am pathetic...      Am I the only one that thinks with words? Is that bad? Are their really intuitive people out there that don't? Why the fuck do I only understand words? Why the fuck must things have a name? I live my life by logic... I blame the words! There ARE no feelings. They must be described using the words provided by the English Language because I am typical and dumb. I never just think something and can't explain it.. If I can't explain it I can't think it. If I can think it I can say it because my emotions are limited to words. I am fucked up. But we all know that, right? Yeah. Who needs a reminder. I have to remind myself because if not I will forget and then I can't fix it. For some reason I think if I worry about everything that's wrong in my life I will fix it eventually. Kind of like a life to-do list that pinches me in the ass every once in a while, making me feel like shit because there's nothing I can do about the things on it. A normal person would forget about it because there is obviously nothing they can do about these things, And they know would probably be a lot happier. But noooooo. Not me. I strive for perfection and that is the reason why I will never be happy. Here's a quote for ya...   "If only we'd stop trying to be happy we'd have a pretty good time." -Edith Wharton-  
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Thanks to Wesley, Megambo, and Whit for the kind words of encouragement and for putting up with my crap. I just now read them so don't think(due to my last entry) that your advice did not change my thinking a bit. Wesley, I'm keeping tabs on your page. The Challenge... very inventive. Megambo, Thanks for your "pearls of wisdom"(for lack of another term) and you should write on your page! To Whit, Thanks for everything chika. Your awesome! To some people my thinking could be considered brash, ungrateful, and selfish. And it is, because I am weak and this is how I "vent". I don't expect anyone to put up with it and I thank you.  
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Aha. Turns out my Mom is just as pathetic as I am, wait, I knew that. But I figure it's okay for me since I am 15 and all. I'm finding out who I am and so on. Ooo and don't forget about the pressures of being in high school in this day and age and so on. SO... My Mom has been going to the bar every night and popping in around o, say 4 ish every morning. Of course I would know this because this is when I breath. So, she is sooo kidding herself. Just as I am I suppose but it's okay cause with me it's expected ; ) . She thinks she's going to find a worth-while guy at that filthy, lame ass, crooked bar where no one goes except for other desperate, pathetic middle-aged people like herself. I never want to be that way. With the way I'm talking about my Mother I don't think God is in any mood to help me so that I do not. hahaha. Sooo I'm on my own. I think that the internet is a very unhealthy place. Forming bonds with people who have never seen your damn face. Who have never looked into your eyes when your telling them something about you. This is my way of socializing hurt-free and still not feeling bad about it because I am telling myself that it is okay. Well I guess I just blew my own cover. I need to stop talking to ppl this way. This here, writing in this thing that no one reads is the only "healthy" thing I do on this computor. So everything else is over. Byeeeeee!   P.s. No more Chris either!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Another damn night of going to bed in the morning. wow. I am so fucking pathetic. I hate the internet right now. Nobody can see anybody and everyone can be anyone. It takes me away from my life and reality and puts me into a place where no one can hurt me and it's just a playground of possibility. Possiblity that grows old after a week straight of going there. I can't believe I could even find a friend in some of these people. God I'm a fucking idiot in denial. I feed myself all this bullshit about being realistic and not let myself slip away from reality by such things as popularity, drugs and alcohol(occasionally), and being someone I'm not in any way. But this is just me fooling myself. Which brings me to Chris..................... 
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So schools starting up again in a few weeks or less. Yay. That was sarcasm. I went to sleep around eight or nine this morning and woke up around 4 30 as usual. My sleeping habits are not unusual in comparison to a few of my friends but that means nothing to my Mother. Nor does she even think that it could be due to depression, or anything related to that. I'm going to have to start sleeping like a "normal person" pretty soon here. Get back in shape for school. Joy, joy. I have no knowledge of time at this point in my life, nor do I have a life. Things are pretty pathetic. It feels like winter with my Mom blasting the swamp cooler 24/7 and me being indoors the same. I miss Winter. It's nice because I love the cold. I love for by arms and face to be icy and dripping cold. I want to feel and see things on the outside that I feel deeply on the inside. It brings me to reality. Truly. I can't think of one better thing I could ask for right now. I am hoping that when school starts back up my friends will greet me warm heartedly and I will be accepted. Last year people were less than accepting. Or maybe I'm just an extremely needy person who couldn't get enough devotion from another being. God I'm bad.  Well it's about time I take responsibility for the things that go on in my life. What the fuck is stopping me? What the fuck. I used to be so full of life and possibility, now I'm just a drone. I hope I have the courage to change all of this. I do. Sincerely *Coral*  
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I told myself I wasn't going to stay up till 4 in the morning anymore but I did it again last night. I actually signed off with my friends at 2 AM, but then decided it would be nice to take a hot bath. So I ran the water, put on the only radio station we have in Berryessa, 95.3 "For lovers only", and lit some candles. A few of the songs I used to listen to as a little girl came on as I was in the bath and all of a sudden something happened that, I can't even remember the last time it happened. You often hear middle aged women talking about their inner child in self help books, well alone with my candles and some songs from way back when, sounds crazy but I felt just like the old me again. The innocent, warm spirited little girl that I thought for sure was long gone. I didn't now until last night how much I missed her. Missed  being  her. She is all I need to be in this life and I don't want to lose her. I don't know how I ever let her slip away in the first place... 
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hello people who have nothing better to do but read this, or maybe I'm forcing you. Either way I gotta tell you that every day chiclets comes up with another word that sounds dirty, only ISN'T. Today they slacked on the job and didn't change the word. Travesty! I know this because I have particularly strange sleeping habits when I have no prior arrangements for the next day, so I was on the computer around 1,2 ish. When they were supposed to change it, and they didn't. Now here I am the next day and it's still the same. I ,for one, am appalled. Maybe they couldn't come up with any new words. It's gotta end somewhere. School is starting in a few weeks. I can't imagine going back to that place with those people, so I figure it's God's plan for me to somehow die before then. But I don't want to die! Shut up. So as school goes on and everyone's getting older, I can't remain the girl that I was. No one accepted that and neither did I. But now that that part of me is gone, I miss it. I guess I never appreciated my innocence, but how can you when you know of nothing else? This brings me back to the whole "You can't be everything all at once" thing. I want to much and am too demanding of myself and others. Someone has to be at fault for this problem that I've grown accustomed to due to the fact that there's really nothing I can do, yet I blame myself. Who else is to blame?
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Everyone is imperfect . Or at least that is what I'd prefer to think. Just wait until I stumble upon someone once more who appears to be perfect in all his or her imperfections and kills me once again. Haha I don't even want to imagine it. I'd like to think that all the chicks broke out of their warm shells, out into the cold world just like me. I happen to be a semi-jealous person naturally. It's my nature. You have something I don't, I want it. You could say I want the world. Every damn thing it has to give me. Every aspect of every thing it has. I will never be content in that area until I come to peace with the fact that I can never be a sunny blonde and earthy brunette at once. I need other people in my life to fill in the puzzle. I can't be everything and it kills me no matter what I do but I always find a way to blame myself. God. Maybe even you. I hate needing other people but it's reality. I think it's a part of life and there's no way of getting around it if your going to be honest with yourself, and I must. It will be a cold day in Hell when I lose touch with reality, or "my reality". As long as I think I'm being realistic, I'm okay. It's all about what I think in my world, and yours too. We live our lives by how we perceive it to be. As long as I am in touch with reality I can never perceive wrong and therefore never be wrong with in my capabilities. You could say I am realistically fooling myself. And that's okay cause I rarely notice it. Haha. I'm such a hypocrite. Feel free to comment on the minor details I may have misjudged.
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It sucks when you realize that no one cares. Truly cares. A friend told me awhile back that "family is just people who are obligated to care about you." So I have come to the conclusion that outside of the ones who "say" they care and the one's who are obligated, I have no one. Along with many other people of course, but the mere fact that I now recognize that, with my friend's help, is worse. I hate that it is human nature to put ourselves first. I would prefer to talk of myself for a paragraph or two than anything else really. When someone recognizes something such as this, worries about it. People spend so much time worrying about things that never come. I could spend forever not only talking of myself but of my opinions. I want you to like me but I have never until now been willing to change myself to make that happen. All I can do is be there when you need me, otherwise I am alone. Not needed. I realize that I feed off of others problems. It makes me feel needed. But what happens when all is good? I am not needed. I feel alone. I want you to need me therefore it helps if you are not happy. So how selfish am I? Do I purposely drop my friends once they are content? I am sick.  Ha ha. I'm starting to hear those words of despair you see when your friends IM you poems come out of my brain. Just like everyone else. You gotta laugh. There's nothing else to do. When I was younger , and I know you can relate, Everything was so, you know. Now it's, you know. Everyone's going through it and no one knows what to do except be someone your not for momentary satisfaction in highschool. Whatever that meant. So it all depends on how much you value your individuality. Mine is running thin. How about you?  I've lost a few friends to the other side. Naturally. Sure, the grass looks greener over there but I keep trying to look into the future. Maybe the tables will be turned. Anyways I hate regretting things and I am known to worry a hell of a lot so this whole "hoping I chose the right life path, made the right choices" thing is constantly pricking my sub-conscience regaining my attention to what could've and what can't be. Are you confused yet? Me too. Just a little. So I'm done talking about how I feel because it makes me feel self-centered. That's it. Love, Coral Ann 
</post>


</Blog>