<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to make a new post.  Pizza.  We ordered pizza from Pizza Hut last night.  The sweet thing is that you can order online.  You get to choose everything.  We got the extra large for only 9.99.  What a deal.  Anyway, this was completely pointless.  I just want to feel good about this blog...
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is my disection of his pikman 2 vs half life 2 story.  The first part of every number is  his.  the part that is correctis mine.  read on   he claimed that this entire thing was filled with facts.  What a liar. a ling ling liar.   1.) Pikman is not easier to spell. In fact, when I ran pikman through my computer spell checker it said wrong, but no results were able to come up. Half Life is much easier to spell. Not that it really matters. Spelling usually doesn't affect gameplay.   2.) Wait, let me get this right. You must have innovatio. But when people go out of their way and take YEARS to make a new engine that will innovate it is bad? And yes, the gameplay is good. I had the privalege of playing the leek "demo" of HL2 and it was awesome.  3.) What?!!? I like all consoles equally with a little lean towards the xBox. Up until now I had not heard of Pikman 2. Not that you will listen but you can't say that it will sell better. you could say that you think it will sell better. But that is not a fact until both have been released. So that fact is more like crap.  4.) Bugs, powerful machine. Have you ever played a PC game? Some have bugs. Most have a few. However, I have never had to call tech support to figure out how to run a game. Even when I am modding I can figure it out. And I am running a Mac. You know how much effort they put into mac games. Not as much as the smae company would put into the same game for PC. That means less support, less patches and so on. BtW: PC games sell better than GC games. Nice factoid.  5.) Except for the fact that Hlo did innovate, and they are nothing the same you are correct. Halo innovated. Only allowing you to carry two weapons. Vehicles. Awesome graphics. That is what innovation is. Retard. And the only thing that is similar in the two is that you have guns and you shoot. Because, see, it is a first person SHOOTER. SHOOTER. YOU SHOOT. THAT IS THE IDEA. Saying that the games are the same is like calling Super Mario World the same as Castlevania. They are both sidescrolers so they are the same. LOL...LOL...  6.) Yes, half life 1 story was a little dull. However, hl2 does have story. at least I think it does. See it isn't out yet. So it better not have cutscenes, or dialogue, or any single player at all. Otherwise your "fact" is wrong. BTW: Half life came out before MP was even drempt up. That means that MP must be copying HL. You retarded monkey tail.  7.) It doesn't have zombies. Who cares about playing a game that doesn't have zombies. So, don't play MP or Mario, or zelda, or MK:DD. They don't have zombies. So they must suck too. You are a fucken retard. Just because you have some wierd fetish with zombies does not mean that a game needs zombies to be good. Also, you havent played it so maybe it does have zombies. Loser  8.) Tru, the HL2 did not look as good as Halo 2, but uhhm. See the pic from RE4 was a cutscene. Not actual gameplay. It was prerenered. The gamecube can't handle as good of graphics as the computer or the box so stop trying. You want a good looking game? Try Syberia. That is and old xBox game that oustrips the new GC games by a mile.  9.) WTF? No goombas. I refer you to the bit about zombies. Screw MP. screw Geist. screw all that. Everygame must have zombies and goombas and not have people in space suits, not use menus to start and must not use the same letters in their title. Also they must have fake innovation. Stop shooting yourself in the foot. It took me 3 hours to get good at haol pc. You have to spend a little time getting good at a game. otherswise it is boring because it is too easy. And it took me 15 minutes to install all of the sims gaes on my computers. And about 20 to install halo. After that, they ran easy as the cubes games. Ohh but wait. The option is their to mod the PC games. that makes them much more fun. Sure, you have to do a little work to get it modded corectely. But after that you have it home free. And it is much more awesome.  10.) Who cares about a "Seal of quality" You are just proving that you are fan boys. God damnit. Take your head out of the cube and play some other games with an open mind. you are not hardcore gamers. Hardcore gamers play lots and lots of games. You are loser gamers. you play only Nintendo games. get a life.  In other words, don't buy pikman 2, let Gabe newall live his own lifestyle, that is none of your business. And, buy a game that is much cooler than GCs crap. Halo 2.  specialest I think you have fact and fiction mixed up. I was able to prove all of your "facts" wrong. Go play some of the games you are dissing. Play them with an open mind. Pretend that you are play the GC port of them if you must. And than go get some counsiling. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Production" has started on our Halo Video.  We finished the script late last night.  Or early this morning.  We will start filming tommorrow and hope to have the release date on or around October 28.  With a few trailers (teaser and full) in the couple weeks before hand.  Thats all I really want to say.  But it will kick.  Go halo!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another bit of stupid from the little girls over at tendomfg.  They have been writing "Goomba saftey tips"  With a general response of "your retarded"  This was my reply to their crap.    "Because that is what kids do. And if we know anything, the main members of this blog are kids. Lay off them a little. They don't have enough intelligence to come up with good arguments for Nintendo. (I think that the might also be girls) But maybe not... Anyway, Goombas are boring, they are little triangles of brown poo. If Nintendo lives long enough to make another console hopefully they will focus on what gamers want. ie: games like Halo, Doom, KOTOR and so on and so forth. Not what kids want. ie: Cutesy games that have no violence or suggestive themes with little or no gameplay.  More than likely they will reply to this post with some incredibly stupid peice of crap. Like: At 4:07 PM, Specialist said...  "...you guys just don't know all about playing games... and yeah I'm talkiong to you DUke, GAYLO lover, and all the rest of the unhardcore dolts... you guys just aren't TRU gamers... and DOOM coming out in the 90's... it came out LAST WEEK!!!! OMFG I GOT YOU ALL ON A LOGICAL CONTRADICTION, AND YOU PROBABLY WONT ADMIT IT!!!..."  Doom 1 and Doom 2 did come out in the 90's. Obviously specialist is very special.   Also At 5:57 PM, Specialist said... "DOOM 3 is CLEARLY a ripoff of Metroid Prime! I don't care if there were other DOOM games, who cares?!! That's the most mainstream game out there!!! Mainstream games suk.."  and " is there a dark and light section of the world in DOOM 3? NO, LOL... totally boring. The only color in DOOM 3 is DARK! OMFG, can Id make any gamez where there is a different color other than DARK?!!"  First off, Dark is not a color. Dark blue is a color. Light Blue is a color. And Doom does have sections colored "light" That just shows that you have played it. Specialist , By saying that mainstream games suck you are just shooting yourself in the foot. Metroid is mainstream. Mario is mainstream. Ask any kid who Mario is and he will know. Ask any kid who John 117 is and he won't.  Doom 1 and 2 came out in the 90's so therfor MP rips off Doom. You retard. And Doom rips off Pong because both invovle moving and projectiles and have 'o' in their titles. Stupid.  So try to flame away little boys and girls. Nintendo is dieing and the DS is their last hope. " 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like the old systems quite a bit.  Mainly the SNES.  You can download emulators to play the oldSkool games on your computer, they are easy to find on google if anyone s interested. (I like Snes9x)  The only problem is that playing with the keyboard sucks.   So I got a soldering gun and a old USB cord.  I took the crappy xBox controller that I got with a Halo 2 video disc.  I used the little extenstion peice at the end and cut 'er open.  After a little while peeling I was able to expose the little wires and match them up to the same color in the USB cord.  (Any that wants to try this, yellow is extra in the xBox cord...)  So, short story long, I now can use my xBox controllers in my computer.  And let me tell you that it is awesome.  Nothing beats sitting a foot from the screen playing the old classics.  Unless you are playing Halo.  Man that game is kickin'
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just started a new blog called Octane Gaming.  It is basically a game review site.  If anyone wants to review give me a holler.  I check my posts regularaly.  What are you waiting for?  Go check it out!!  http://octanegaming.blogspot.com/  btw: no crappy fanboys please...
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am an Apple user.  So when I first heard about the iPod, of course I was drooling.  About this time last year I got a 10gb 2nd generation model.  I figured that I would write a simple post to tell how much I like it.  True, they are more expensive. True they are sexier.  True they are awesome.  The only thing I can say to people want to argue about price is: I used a Dell Jukebox.  It was junk.  It felt  cheap in my hand.  the sound quality was bad (could have been the music).  Also, it was hard to control and looked a lot like an iPod.  I would have to nor reccomend it to anyone.  Spend the extra 30$, get an iPod...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would love a chance to discuss the GC/FPS/Box/Ps2 with any of the members of 'tendomfg.  Nintaldo, I would love to get an email from you.  My address is macdjinn@spymac.com. Anyone else, feel free to email me.  I have come across some problems with some of your posts, I would like to point them out to you in person. (via a thread or email or aim)  I would urge you to stop using terms like PonyHayStation Goo and Xbomb.  They do not help your argument, they just make you look like a bunch of uninformed kids.  I doubt that you are however.  Anyone who can, direct some of the 'TendOMFG guys or gals over here.  I am not sure they will see this...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently came across Nintaldo's top ten reasens that Geist makes Halo 2 Cry  I decided to disect it and see what good it is.  Take a look  We all know about Geist, the visually amazing first-person shooter from the boys over at n-Space and today, being the #1 Nintendo fans around, we've got a run down on the top ten reasons why Geist will make Halo 2, or Gaylo as I like to call it, cry.   After reading your list I was surprised to see that you are Nintendo’s #1 fan.  You think that their biggest fan would have to be intelligent.  Oh Well.  "10. Bungie made Marathon, which is dumb "  Marathon is not dumb.  While you may claim not to like it I am sure you would if it was originally for your lover the GameCube.  It is a great game that innovated the shooter industry.  It is not Dumb.  It has a very deep story line.  But of course you like to run and shoot more than run, think, shoot.  "9. Master Chief is a boring character that never talks"  Never talks? Did you play Halo all the way through.  Sure he doesn't give lectures to a class full of pimply morons such as yourself, but he does talk. Boring!?  Did you read the books?  Of course not you were to busy having people talk to you.  After all, anything that doesn't Run shoot run shoot run shoot talk talk talk shoot.  Is boring and not fun.  "8. Halo 2 has not ghosts"   That's not even a freakin sentence.  Retard.  I think that you mean halo 2 does not have ghosts.  How do you know?  I suppose that you are making the game.  It will probably not have fake, cheesy ethereal characters.  However, does Geist have Aliens called grunts?  So I guess it is an even trade off.  Wait. Grunts are cool and funny.  How do shoot something that is already dead?  Guess Halo is cooler in that aspect to.  "6. Geist is made by the same developers that made Mary Kate & Ashlee: Magical Mystery Mall "  Which was an awesome game.  Just ask one of its literally dozens of fans.  Thanks redvsblue. Just because a company made a bad game in the past does not mean that Geist will be bad.  "5. Halo 2 is GAY"  Uhhm.  How can a game be gay?  How does it care for more games of the same gender?  And even if it did have other sexual preferences that doesn't mean that you should put it down.  Gay people have feelings too.  I know plenty of people that have other sexual preferences.  They are just the same as everybody else.  "4. Geist is a more pure first person game. Halo 2 has stupid stuff like two guns controllings and vehicles. Is it a fps or a stupid racing game? Geist is pure 100% shooter! "  If you are trying to tell us that Halo is not a shooter I will simply ask you why do they have guns?  To make the cars accelerate?  To trade cards with opponents?  It doesn't make any sense.  Also,  the best shooters are for computer.  And xBox.  I haven't played any shooters on the Cube I liked except Metroid Prime and that hardly counts.  Its more of a racing game.  Dual wielding is awesome.  The fact that Bungie took the time to write an engine that supports it is sweet.  Having vehicles elevates the discourse.  I can sort of see how having extra features that set a game apart makes it "worse".  But than you should be a Geist basher also.  Their are hardly any games that you control other people's bodies.  Therefore, to your reasoning,  Geist is a poor game.   3. Geist looks better than Halo 2   I guess that you could say that.  I personally think that games should look real.  However you are entitled to your opinion.  "2. Geist doesn't have stupid online play. Online play is just a fad, Nintendo said so themselves. I mean who wants to play online like some PC nerd? I know I don't. Plus Xbox Live has lots of lag. My friend's friend told me that his Xbox caught on fire once."  Have I said retard yet. Or that my gamecube regularly bursts into a ball of lightning that engulfs my entire apartment complex and kills everyone?  I won't stoop so low as to point out that Live has over 1.2 MILLION users.  Or that Live has virtually no lag.  (your friends using dial-up?) Or that online gaming is computer gaming's biggest market.  I won't even point out that Nintendo said that GTA "Will never catch on because of its horrible violence." Stupid. Stupid. Stupid.  Thanks Al  "1. Geist sounds cooler than Halo!"  This depends upon how one bases "cool"  If Constipated Overrated Out of style Loser is what you mean by cool than yes, geist is "Cooler" than Halo. However, If one says which is better.  Halo has giest taken.  "PonyhayStation Goo and Xbomb fans cry away, GameCube is here to stay!"  If GameCube is here to stay why did it drop down to $100 while Ps2  and the Box were still at $200?  The PS2 was out way before the GC. So it kind of looks like the Box and PS are here to stay...    Well anyway...
     

    
</post>


<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Come read the review of Halo  by: MacDjinn
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a partner Blog to my other site (http://macdjinn.blogspot.com/) I am going to review games here... If anyone wants to help out give me a holler.  My E-Mail is (macdjinn@spymac.com) I would prefer that you not be like the fanboys over at http://tendomfg.blogspot.com/ .  Anyway.
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No, no, i havent converted to Nintendoism, this is just a small listof future games that i dug up on the internet.  Let's see: Splinter Cell 3, Ratchet and Clank 3, Halo 2, Half-Life2, Fable,  Terminator 3, Tony Hawk's Underground 2,  Dynasty Warriors 4,  Star Wars Battlefront, Final Fantasy XI,  GTA San Andreas,  Call of Duty:Finest Hour,  Star Wars: Republic Commando, and the list grows with every passing day! 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You were once a scientist. Now you are a one man army. 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Review of Crimson Skies: High Road to Revenge...Cause we all have fun blowing our friends out of the sky in a friendly dogfight... 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Looking into the soul of Capcom, in Resident Evil: Outbreak for the PS2 BRAINS! (Ok, I know I said no more stupid jokes, but, um..er...READ!) 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I wil Review the Recent DDR game, DDRMAX2: 7th Mix. So, put on your sweats and read on! *Note: This game is not for the lazy and has been deemed FUN!*(Ok, I know, Bad joke, anywho, stop reading this and get to the Review!) 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seek, and ye shall find...hell 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A look into Kingdom Hearts(PS2). Read on, young Grasshopper 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read on my young padawan learner.  Okay, you are probably older than me...
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What do you get when you cross a medieval demon slayer and a crazy french guy? A great Onimusha game, that's what! Review inside!! :P 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read on for the full review for this creative addition to the Nintendo Gamecube system. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Custom Robo review inside!
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Spidey is Back.
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Anywho, Sorry I haven't posted lately, I went on vacation with some buddies of mine to visit some friends over in Cali...We threw a MASSIVE week long Halo LAN party....We basicly drank, partied, and kicked each others asses in halo..just the way god had intended, lol...But I got back yesterday, and now that I'm settled back in, I'll be going out tonight and renting a slew of games to review, I should have them up sometime tomorrow...OH! I also read that Nintaldo Played Halo and got fired from TendOMFG!! I'm glad that Nintaldo has been liberated from the fanboyism... I hope someone gives me a memo that hell has froven over next time! I froze my BALLS off! anywho, laters all.. 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not lying. Nintaldo played Halo on Legendary and got fired from TendOMFG-Mario is pissed. 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have several short reviews of old sim games....
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tell us if you play any multiplyer games on the almighty Internet. 
    
</post>


</Blog>