<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Survived Hurricane Charley all on my own, with Phoebe of course!!  Never lost power which I am very grateful for---I am definitely one of the few!  The storm was so fascinating---the sky lit up different colors of blue and green with the lightning--I found out later that those were transformers being hit.  Saw (& met!) Bobcat Goldthwait at the Improv on Saturday!  What a nice person...actually quite shy!  Gina and Duane spent the night with me.  Sunday, G and I went to see "Little Black Book" while Duane stayed in to watch Nascar.  Jim got upset with me for not inviting him over.  I've learned you can't please everyone.  Ed is home, but haven't seen him.  
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I say ... and you think ... ?  Server ...........Waitress Charlotte .................North Carolina Jackson ............Jessie Resentment ....................Negative Controlling ....................Possessive Intense .................Serious November ..................Turkey Donkey ...................Ass Weave ..................Web Satisfies................Pleases  urlLink  http://subliminal.lunanina.com   
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Interesting weekend...Ed brought me a card on Friday because he was sick and had to cancel the movies...we ended up just staying in and watching a movie at his place.  i slept there, yep just slept...he got up at 7 and got completely dressed for the day.  i asked where he was going and he said he had a golf tournament (guess he was feeling better!)...he asked for help with his ear drops and then told me i could stay as long as i wanted but he was leaving.  nosey me---i opened his bathroom cabinet and found a small supply of "girl stuff" and some hot rollers---who the heck do those belong to???  found photo of he and another girl on his desk too...maybe that's her stuff.  don't know anything about all that.  i didn't stay any longer and went home to sleep in my own bed.  he called yesterday and stopped by last night.  we went to toojays to pick up his dinner then he went to his home and i went to mine.  i walked back over to get my lighter and he was on the phone with someone (maybe curler girl) and was saying sarcastically and abruptly "i need to go, i'll call you right back...i said i'll call you right back!"  he hung up and i came in quickly to get my lighter...didn't hang around.  about 10 i remembered that he wanted to borrow my cookbook so i knocked on his door...no answer.  returned to my apt and called him--no answer. left a msg.  he never called back.  saw him this morning when i was walking phoebe around 7:15--he told me he had to leave at 6 am this morning....something's a little strange and i'm not sure what yet.  i probably shouldn't read anymore into it at this point.  he seems to like being with me so the last thing i need to do is start obsessing.  just wanted to document my thoughts to see what comes of it in the long run.  met with jim on saturday---that was exhausting.  i need to get through this and get my life back on track.  the stress is NOT good for me. 
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I say ... and you think ... ? Sting...........bite BMW ...........dream car Jeremy ..............lions Audacious .............bodacious Drag Queen ..............makeup Title ...................name Stamp ................letter Bad ....................sick Snow White ...................................dwarfs Delegate..................congress  not so interesting today...maybe i'm just not in the mood to be creative. 
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What a day!  Thank goodness tomorrow is Friday.  Didn't get much sleep last night---was wide awake until 2:00 am!!  UGH!!   Got my bloodwork results back---everything is okay---but that doesn't explain why i feel so lousy.  Went to the gyno--not so bad.  Highlight of yesterday was that Ed came over to say hello.  Going out with him Friday.  Today...notified about some trouble on the workfront with 2 employees.  have decided to suspend them both for 3 days without pay.  that's no fun and not something i enjoy doing but need to show them that their behavior is unacceptable.  so, my stress level is pretty darn high today.  not good.  i know i need to relax.  going to dinner tonight with seymour (deborah), kristen and nick.  should be interesting.  kristen and i aren't real thrilled about the deborah saga but are trying to be supportive of seymour. 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I say ... and you think ... ?  Testicles ...  Balls Ribald ... Grace---isn't that someone's name??? Auction ... Car Inch .... Mile Tony ... Award Phony ... Plastic Stool .... Sample (just had sewage overflow in one of our offices yesterday--ick!!) Coyote ...  howl Cinderella ... princess Battery... Smoke Detector---just had to change mine because it started beeping.   from    urlLink  http://subliminal.lunanina.com/   
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wednesday....hump day...almost made it to the weekend.  Going to the gyno today---who likes that??  Looking forward to the weekend and feeling better.  First day trying out this blogging thing....we'll see how it goes...better get back to work!  
      
</post>


</Blog>