<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       when we last left our unfurry friends they were forced to take a partner-to-partner vacation. We pick up from there arrival...    A: Wow, sweet home Alabama... J: We are not in Alabama....   A: ... where the skies are so blue J: We are in Florida... A:...   Sweet home Alabama J: HELLO! F-L-O-R-I-D-A!!!! A:     Lord, I'm coming home to you   J: Get in the car, we gotta get to the hotel and unpack.    in the car...oddly enough on the radio...   J: You've got to be kidding me! A: Cool! Sing it!.... J: Ah, no.  radio, and A....           In Birmingham they love the Gov'nor, hoo hoo hoo Now we all did what we could do Now Watergate does not bother me Does your conscience bother you, tell the truth       Sweet home Alabama, where the skies are so blue Sweet home Alabama, Lord, I'm coming home to you  J: ENNNNNNNNNNOUGH!!!!!! A: What, why, where!? J: Oh, Thank God we are here! A: Oh wow! Motel 6!!! I love that commercial when the guys on the bed with his dog and there like..."we'll keep the lights on for yah" This is gunna be fun! J: Or i will commit a sad gruesome suicide. A:  in his own world...    Cool! J: Hmm...thanks.  to self...  Wow, a Motel 6, the beareau is way to good to us, geesh. No Hamptons, we are in Florida...just Motel 6. Where the heck is the beach. A: Boss told me we wernt gunna be within 50 miles of the beach, something about financial reasons and water. But the zoo is within 20 miles! WHoooo-hooooo. J: Ok... Time to find my knife. A: When is our first partner-mo-partner activity!? Im ready! J: To soon. First ones at 12pm sharp. A; Oh, so we only have an hour to unpack. J: Nawwwwwwwwwwww shuckle sherlock. A: eh? J: Nothing, lets unpack....  enters motel room...  J: Whoa whoa whoa whoa flippin whooooooooooa! Where's the other bed??? A: I told you, big financial problems the boss said there buddy... winks at J  J:    shaken up is J...     Alright, wheres the nearest payphone, Lobby, yes lobby, mark set go, ok, phone...be right back.    in lobby calling the boss    Boss: F.B.I Director.... J: Its me!!!! Boss: Who? J: You know who you mungral! Boss: Excuse me, who the hell is this!! J: Oh, just the poor chick you sent away to flordia to a motel six in a single bedroom to get to know her psychotic partner better!! Boss: Oh, that. Hahaha. Um, ah, well, i figured you might be callin' 'bout that. We had some budgetary issues, the beaureau couldn't accomidate anything more than what you have. J: We're in Flordia, but nowhere near the water. Nowhere near the beach. And there is only one bed. And i am supposed to be relaxing, easing the stress, and trying to bond! And if by bonding you mean sharing a bed, you booked us the wrong bonding trip buster! Boss: Oh, just tell him to sleep on the floor, your the lady, im sure he will give you the bed. Now your first "bonding" activity is in...oh 40minutes, so stop talking to me and go get ready. And when you come back you two better be buddy, buddy! Or ELSE!  ....HANGUP...dial tone... J stares into space...phone in hand...  A: Oh hey buddy there yah are! On the phone awhile, ya'll right? J: No. No. Not at all actually. But ill tell you what im going to go take some asprin, and hopefully they ease my pain, k? A: Allllllllrighty! Meet yah in the car...we better get goin'! J:  staring at pill bottle.  Recomended dosage, 2 pills. Yup, that works.  throws 5 in mouth, drinks down with some scotch.  J: And off we go...bonding time...     to be continued...  Will J Puke Will A Go to the zoo? Will J: O.D? Will A Sleep on the floor? OR will J & A Get in on...yahhhhhhh baby yahhhhhhhhh  stay tuned...                      
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       the adventures continue....episode 2...          J, and A leave the milk mans house and are in the car....   J: Well that was just fascinating, never seen so much milk in my life. A: Boy, i tell yah, wasnt it cool when the milk shot out the shower. Man, i just wanted to jump in...grab a lil soap. Boy, what a case. J: There is no case, the case is over. You can't catch a ghost. So what. He's a milk man. It's fitting there is milk everywhere he goes. A: Oh please, i know deep down you wonder what is going on. You just don't know how to solve the case. That's why you say its over. J: Ok, its your case you do what you want with it. I want nothing to do with these cases that make me look like a royal you know what "hole". A: huh? J: A-hole. A: a? Hole? Ahole? A hole? why A hole? as in in the ground...a hole? J: What happened to you as a child. You never heard the abbreviated term of    (explitive)     hole?? A: Oh. (ackward silence) J: Well than... A: hmph J: yuh.... A: Yah know, i never knew you had that side to you. J: O c'mon you never said a swear word right? A: i say suguar, assenomber, flucker, and cruddles. J: Freak A: Potty mouth.   Arrive back at headquarters....   The Boss: How'd the case go. A: We're makin' progess sir. J: No sir we are not and i would ask immediatley for re-assignment from this dumb flucker and no more cases in which make me look like an idiot as an agent of the FBI. A: I dont know what to say. The Boss: I can not do that. A: Those peanuts look good. The Boss: I mean i am not the one who assigns departments, i just run the department you were assigned to. A:  (sayin comments quietly to self) Tasty lil' nuts... J: Well sir than i request than you talk to your superior and get me re-assigned. I am sick of looking like a fool to everyone. I work with the joke of all agents, and i hate to say that cause he was once the best we had but look at him now! A: I'll name you tigger, you nice lil' nut, and you can be slaughter, and you, corky.... J: He's naming NUTS!!!! The Boss: Get away from my nuts!!!! All F.B.I Agents through secret see through glass: AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!!!! The Boss: Peaunts! Give em' back! ......   Lord, you are insane! A: Now excuse me i may act like an idiot but know one and i mean know one has a higher success rate in the beaureau than me! Argue with that mam! J: Oh for cryin' out loud i could make some stupid thing up about a singing spider, or a man whos part devil and say "Oh, boss, i solved the case duuuuuuuuh. And duhhhhhhhhhhh im smart. And duhhhhhhhh can i have a peanut now....duuhhhhhhhhhhhhhh." oops....Braindead!!! A: Why you lil' assenomber! The Boss: Enough! You two are going to remain in this department cause you are insane, and you still attacked an old lady and cost us 10 mill so...so  thats that! A: O please somebody stop the yelling.....wahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh...the noises...stop the.....no----is---esssssss...m--y.....heeee-aaaaa---d..... J: Wow, this is like a bad movie. The Boss: I am sending you two on a paid FBI vacation. You will enter into our weekend get-a-way get to know your partner program. Its bonding time boys and girls, and when you two come back you better be naming peanuts and drinkin' milk together. J: You wouldn't! The Boss: I am! A:..... (under breath)  o and you lil' feler can be called shooter. J: I don't deserve this. A: I'm scared of airplanes and i get sea sick. J: You cant get sea sick in a plane. A: Huh? The Boss: Out OUT OUT! J: Pack up...we obviously have to do this. I'll meet you back here at 8 for airport departure. A: OK! Im excited. J:  (sarcasticly)  Ok, your a fool!! A: ...... J: I'm hitting the bar on the way home for real tonight. A: OOOOOoooo i just remebered they serve peanuts on planes!!!!! J:  (under breath)  A murder might be commited this weekend....   Will J get drunk? Will A name more nuts on the plane? And will J kill A...  tune in next episode.        SIDENOTE: Well its a start. I liked the beginning and admittely this episode wasnt as good as the 1st, to me at least. But we'll continue the adventures and hopefully they will get funnier and more entertaining as characters mold together. Till next time...        
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Boss: I got a new case for the two of you. Very interesting... J: If its like the last one with the stolen monkey, i quit. A: O, c'mon, that monkey was cute. The Boss: Enough, please. This case involves "paranormal" activities. A: You mean like pizza.  (silence for 30sec)  J: Wheres the nearest bar? The Boss: Daw gawn ya'all your FBI agents pull yourselves together!! J: How can we when you give us cases about monkeys. The Boss: It was one case!! J: Oh, how quicky we forget about the man who claimed his chicken talked to him, and told him he was gunna die by an angry parrot. That was a fun assignment. Chicken hit by F.B.I vehicle... A: We killed a chicken!!!!!!!! (tears, crys) O the nightmares!!! we're going to hell in a handbasket!! J: Oh the damn thing comminted suicide, i couldnt stand to live with the whacko either. The Boss: Excuse me, how'd you 2 get hired again?? A: We begged. The Boss: Yes, but that usually doesnt work for a federal employment job. A: yes i know, we were surprised too. J: Well, you are the most annoying person on the face of the planet, i would hire you and give you cases about monkeys and talking chickens to shut you up too if i were smart. A: (blank stare on face....deep thought)......HUH? The Boss: Wheres the nearest bar again? J: I heard they have really good margaritas.... Boss and J: MMMMMMMMMMMMMMMM A: So bout that case there boss cause im just lovin bein in the F.B.I and solvin these things. And you said this time we get to hunt ghosts, coooooool! J: Yes, another way to make a mockery of our profession and life, notice all the people  laughing at us behind this secret see-through mirror. All F.B.I employees: AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!!!! The Boss: Ya, and you know whats really sad, im your superior and have to supervise you too. J: I was once a highly respected agent and now am doing this, how did io get this demotion!! The Boss: You attacked an old lady who you "mistakenly" thought was a bank robber. She sued us for 10,000,000 and won. Thats why. All because of you. So now you get to hunt chickens, monkies and ghosts. Here's the case, i've had enough of you to for the day. See you at the bar later? J: awwwwwwww ya. A: I wanna come!!! J: Yes and if i wasnt so scared you would see a ghost and close the bar down, or play health inspector and try to shut the bar down so you can invite only your friends and play spin the bottle and strip poker, id say come on down. The Boss: Tell me he didnt do that before! J: Looooooong story. A: I would like to defend myself please. J: Oh, please try. A: Um, well i need time to think about a defense. J: Well maybe while were hunting the spirits they will come to you and tell you a reason for your insanity! F.B.I Angents, behind mirror: AHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!! The Boss: OUT PLEASE!!!!! A: Can i have one those peanuts? (J tugs A away) A: Boy o Boy it says were lookin for the ghost of a janitor who got run over by the milk man, and now milk comes outta everything the milk man does. Shower, toilet, sink, dishwasher! This could be the case that puts our names in the hall of fame if we solve it! J: This could be the case that finally gets my petition to send you to the mental ward accepted.   will A solve the Case Will J quit, or kill him Will the milk man see more milk. And will J and the boss get there freak on at the bar.  Stay tuned...  
      
</post>


</Blog>