<Blog>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's where the two cultures clash.  Not that they have to because both are strong on both sides.  It's an artificial boundary with a wall that divides the two sides that slowly shift into different sides of gray.    You can have your Cancun, your Mazatlan, give me the real stuff.  I don't want to be in a bubble, I certainly don't want to willingly give in like that.  Something about the border area captures my attention.  Let me walk around El Paso/Juarez or Laredo/Nuevo Laredo - something like that.  The resort towns?  I can show you parts of Denver that are more Mexican than those Resort Towns.  Have 'em.  Love 'em.  It keeps the ones I love more authentic.  Not a construct.   "Life is not measured by the number of breaths we take, but by the moments that take our breath away."    
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sit back and watch me shine.  Yes, Yes!  You didn't know it but my best writing comes when I am somewhere in the land between half buzzed and downright drunk.  You guessed it - I am somewhere crossing the river that divides those two kingdoms.  The grass is greener no matter what shore I look to.    Don't admire me, don't look to me.  Anyone who thinks that they perform better when liquored up should be nothing more than a cheap antic.  This is what my creativity has been reduced to.  This is the world we live in.  I was a science nerd in school, good at the maths and sciences - in college (the first time) I was a major in Economics.  I had taken art classes and I had never been told that I was good, in fact comparing myself to the people who were in my class I felt like crap.  They were so confident, so "talented", like I was in the Sciences and Maths.  Where are they now?  Fretting because they can't find a 40,000 dollar job to cover the costs of their philosophy or modern art degree.    Here [as I raise my beer] is to expectations (and lack thereof).  One day I bought a bottle of Tequilla and a canvas and passed out shortly after the painting was done.  When I came to I had discovered that it was my finest work.  I have sold a painting since - it was another drunk painting.  Those are the only ones I like.  This is my drunk writing, it's the only kind of writing I like.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Cooking for oneself isn't fun.  It's a chore, how to make a portion for one?    One of my favorite things to do when I am in a relationship is to go shopping for the ingredients together, pick up a bottle of wine and a movie and then go home and start making dinner together.  A glass of wine as the preperation starts and maybe a break between dinner and the movie.  Oh shit - it has happened before when the food burned or was out too long.   It was worth it.  Adults make more sense to me now.  When you are 7 or 8 you can only think "how could you have burned the dinner?"  Somethings are just more exciting, somethings I would just rather do.    How is it that I know of a fantastic little Bed and Breakfast down in Colorado Springs and I have no woman to take there?    It's easily the most romantic night of my life.  Top floor of a 4 story house.  The patio outside had a hot tub and the inside a steam shower.  The bed had a canopy and the establishment provided free wine (not that we didn't bring our own).  Several nice restuarants within walking distance.  Snow was falling as we sat in the hot tub, Pikes Peak's shadow grew longer and longer.    That was my reward for my hard work.  It would have been nothing if she was not there.    I love doing that kind of thing.  I want to do it again.  Damn it!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pride.    Do I have too much of it?  My car is in the shop and I need to shell out 450 dollars.  My Father has offered to help me out with it.  He knows that I am going back to University in 3 weeks and might need a little help.   I am 26 years old, I have lived on my own since I was 20.  I have not recieved any financial help from either parents since then.     It's almost a feeling of giving in, of giving up.  I know - he wants to see me be succesful.  So do I.      I am grateful.  Very grateful to have the father that I do.    I don't show it enough.  Someday I would love to take him on a trip with me.  France perhaps and walk the beaches of Normandy.  Or London.    Perhaps I should accept his help.  Make a promise to myself to pay him back in my own way.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One coworker bugs me with his attitude.  He has a job, isn't getting the number of hours that he wants, was recently booted from his apartment and says "God hates me."  "If God hated you then you would have been born in Somalia," was my response.  What is the compassionate way to respond to this?  I feel like if I help him appreciate what he has been given in life then I have done a good thing.  Being born in a wealthy nation full of oppurtunity though does not instantly make us wealthy in relation to so much of the world's population.  Some of the poorest people I know have buckets of money and have had many doors opened for them because of where they were born - I can see the poverty in their eyes.  It's in the way they don't use words like "please" and "thank you."  It's in their lack of patience.  It's in their lack of respect for what and who surrounds them.  They need our compassion as much as anyone.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ready for a trip&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         This is not one of those days.  "Those days" defined for me are the ones where I get out of bed on a rare day off and go straight to the fridge to grab a beer.  A learned lesson, taking a beer into a hot shower with you causes the beer to warm up in a hurry, so drink it quickly!    The last couple of days I have been craving a trip.  The need to travel in me is something that is hard to describe.  It's in my blood and runs deeper than anyone I have encountered.  It's a yearning, stronger than the need I feel for love, I don't feel right when I am stationary.       Gone are the times that I wallow in self-pity.  Something happened as I crawled out of those teenage angst years.  Stay busy, stay moving, try new things and set new goals.  I worry a little bit about going back to school in the fall while also managing a cafe.  Is it going to be too much to juggle in my life?  No - I have been in much busier periods during my life.  So why do I worry?  It's because I have the time to worry.  When trying situations  just "happen" we are thrown into them, discover new qualities (sink or swim?) and reach a whole new level within ourselves.      (what I would say to myself)   So don't think about it, don't worry about it.  When University starts and it hits just do what you've done in the past- push it.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>