<Blog>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Take a moment and look around.  Breathe deeply.  Turn you mind to the society you live in.  Getting depressed yet?  Wondering why even the church looks the same far too often as the world?  Think about those who will not draw breath tonight.  Think about the unborn who are having their brains ripped out of their bodies while still in their mothers womb.  Think about the homeless man getting rained on.  And about the 15 year old girl who is being raped.  Sill sad? Depressed? Angry?  Think for a moment of the hatred of Jesus.  See how irrational it is?  Think about how society rages against the church. Isnt all we want to do is love them? We have a corrupt and immoral society.  A society that is in its death throes.  It is kicking and screaming trying to hold onto life, and ironically it is raging against the only being that can give it life.  So many christians lament and do nothing.  Many others burn out and desert the cause.  What are we to do? Perhaps its time once again to agressively engage our culture.  If we have been commanded to disciple and baptize nations.  Then how can we ignore culture and society.  We have been given a mandate, a christian manifesto so to speak to take dominion.  We are like like the Israelites, the promise that where ever our feet will step He has given us.  Was Christ a liar when He cried out "It is finished"?  Was salvation accomplished for His people.  Is the arm of the Lord too short to save now?  Can He take Canada and America and change it in a day?. Christ is not a liar. Let God be true and everyman a liar.  Mission/evangelism exists because true worship dosent.  Kiss Him, worship Him, and adore Him like you've never done it before.  Just see how the world changes when the church worships Him in Spirit and truth. Psalm 2The Reign of the LORD's Anointed1Why do the nations rage[ urlLink 1 ]    and the peoples plot in vain?2The kings of the earth set themselves,   and the rulers take counsel together,   against the LORD and against his anointed, saying,3"Let us burst their bonds apart   and cast away their cords from us."4He who sits in the heavens laughs;   the Lord holds them in derision.5Then he will speak to them in his wrath,   and terrify them in his fury, saying,6"As for me, I have set my King   on Zion, my holy hill."7I will tell of the decree:The LORD said to me, "You are my Son;   today I have begotten you.8Ask of me, and I will make the nations your heritage,   and the ends of the earth your possession.9You shall break[ urlLink 2 ] them with a rod of iron   and dash them in pieces like a potter's vessel."10Now therefore, O kings, be wise;   be warned, O rulers of the earth.11Serve the LORD with fear,   and rejoice with trembling.12Kiss the Son,   lest he be angry, and you perish in the way,   for his wrath is quickly kindled.Blessed are all who take refuge in him. Take refuge in Him beloved......  Footnotes   Or nations noisily assemble   Revocalization yields (compare Septuagint) You shall rule   

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've always been somewhat of a stats man..  So here are some interesting stats done by Ipso-Reid.  Of the visible church (at least those professing) there are 3 catagories and these 3 are further divided into 4 sub-catagories.  The 3 catagories are Conservative evangelical, Mainline Protestant, and Roman Catholic.  Within these are the catagories called committed, customized, ceremonial, census. Committed refers to Christian committment within church allegiance. Customized refers to Christian committment with the individual right to pick and choose their own beliefs.  Ceremonial refers to Christian identity with self-selected special occasion involvment. Census refers to Christian identity without any church involvment (they simply denote a denomination when the gov't census people roll around). Within the Conservative Evangelical camp 23% are committed, 46% customized, 19 ceremonial, and 12% census.  Within the Mainline Protestant 9% committed, 30% customized, 37% ceremonial, and 24% census.  Within the Roman Catholic 15% committed, 28% customized, 37% ceremonial, and 20% census. What this means is a very very small percentage of "Christians" are actually committed to a message that is orthodox (Jesus is God, Jesus died, Jesus rose, exclusive claims of Christ, Trinity, etc).  Also interesting to note is that the difference of 18 between ceremonial "evangelicals" and mainliners and catholics is not very much considering these groups far outweigh the Cdn "Christian" population. The most troubling of all these stats is the catagory "customized christian" having such a huge majority within evangelical circles.  We all know it, so many of our trendy, faddish evangellyfish church which are more "seeker" sensitive than doctrinally sound.  These are the people more committed to orthopraxis and pragmitism than faithfulness to the Word of God.  What is with this?  Are these people moles in the evangelical church, sent by satan to unwilling (maybe willingly) to waterdown truth?  Rise up, Oh church of God.  The world for you doth wait.  Bring in the day of brotherhood.  Rise up and make her great.... Isa 6:8 "And I heard the voice of the Lord saying, "Whom shall I send, and who will go for us?" Then I said, "Here am I! Send me." Will you go and be committed to Mother Church and the Word of God?  Who will go?  Who will he send?  Will it be You????  

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I though that for a moment I would think about the anthropologic issuse of womanhood.  What is a biblical theology of "womaness".  Some may find this sexist, but then again most modern femma-natzi enlightenment thinkers will find the bible patriarchal and archaic.  All orthodox christians must repudiate this. What does 1 Peter 3:7 mean when it says;" Likewise, husbands, live with your wives in an understanding way, showing honour to the woman as the weaker vessel, since they are heirs with you[Some manuscripts [since you are joint heirs] ] of the grace of life, so that your prayers may not be hindered." What does weaker mean and how does one show honour to her?  Well weaker infact means weaker (well what did you expect).  It is likened to a china teacup to a tin dipper.  The china is far more delicate, it will smash if dropped.  The old tin dipper can be thrown around with impunity.  But...  the china is far more valuable and will be treasured (as it should be)> so men rather than dominating their wives and demanding submission, should instead treasure, protect and care for these special daughters of God.  That is how the male biblically honours. Feminism has tried to destroy this paradigm.  In its quest to make women equal it has only lowered woman.  The command is given for mutual submission as well as treating others as better than onself.  The quest for equality is a direct attack on these scriptures.  I am not equal to you, you are by far better than me. This degrading of woman has made our society the sexually perverted place that it is. The door was opened and all hell broke loose through. Men have their place in the kingdom of God, and so do women.  It is mans place to be the pastor/preacher and it is womans place to be the mother.  These are both valid motivations.  So when in class I vigourously deny women the right to preach I am doing it out of a desire to lift up women not to lower them.  Remember 1 Cor 12:22 "On the contrary, the parts of the body that seem to be weaker are indispensable"  The job that women play in the church are indispensable.  Men should not want womans God ordained jobs and vice versa.. Beloved fellow members of our holy mother church, let us recapture a biblical framework for the dealings with the sexes.  All of the strife between sexes are a result of the fall (it was the second seperation, man/God, man/woman).  We must go back to the regulative principal in interpersonal/ecclesiastical matters dealing with the sexes.  Guys let us love women enough to gently guide them into submission.  Girls love men enough to allow this.  People of God love Jehovah enough to submit to His ordained roles for you. Grace  

						
</post>


</Blog>