<Blog>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quite probably this is me just being bored and wanting to do something and even more probable that I'll never see or post in this ever again, but as of now, it's something to do, and for that I'm grateful.  Frankly I've no idea at all what to put in such a thing so until I've come up with something even remotely interesting to say, this will be a lone post...that is, until school starts back for me in a mere 4 days.  The summer has been a good escape, but now I find myself dreading the return to school not only because a person my age's natural distaste for school on a whole, but also due to my situation this year.  Basically, I'm 17 years old guy going into his senior year in High School.  My grades are FAR subpar, I barely try at all, let alone put in the necisary time to get good grades.  I've made up two of the three classes I failed as a sophmore(sp?). English, which I failed due to my being unimaginably bored as my teacher droned on over material I already had 'mastered' due to the test she forced us to take at the beginning of the year and basically my neglecting to complete any sort of homework or class work.  Brilliant, eh?  Then I also made up my Biology I failed due to the excessive workload, but passed quite easily the second time around due to the fact that the very thing that screwed me over the year before the teacher no longer did.  Lucky me.  But this year...everything is comming together to make a terrible year, I can feel it now.  I have to make up the last I failed, Health.  That class was mostly just writing the word and definition of 30 words, in alphabetical order, out of the index and then writing and reading an essay with the words in it.  I found it basically just annoying and stupid and ended up failing, like all the other classes, with a 59.  Not only that, but I've not taken PE in Highschool, which means I have to this year, and, while I used to be a jock and love the whole sports thing, now a days the 'phisical' stuff isnt' for me, so thats not exactly a great thing to have to take.  Then, due to the limited classes available in my small, hicksville school, I very well may be forced down into different class, seperated from the few friends I have and cast into a very hostile environment I dont wish to be in.  If that wasn't enough, I'm a senior this year, meaning after this, I have to decide what I want to do with my life, which might not seem bad to you, but it is for me.  I've no direction, no outstanding talents, no clue about how to function in the real world, and absolutely no confidance in my being able to make it after High School.   So...yeah...end of my innitial post/rant about basically the status of my life at the moment.  I've no clue what I'm supposed to put in this "Blog", so I'll have to figure it out as I go...if I continue it.  Don't hold your breath, and I'm sorry for wasting...however long it took for you to read this pitiful post. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>