<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      BRUSSELS - Forget the handshakes and wide smiles at recent high-profile summits attended by United States President George W. Bush and European leaders. Transatlantic relations remain mired in acrimony. Despite European Union (EU) declarations of support for the US, predictions that Europeans would overcome their misgivings over the Iraq war and join hands with the US to rebuild the country have been proven wrong. Increasingly, in fact, with the US presidential election only three months away, European policymakers are in no mood to come to the aid of a president whose policies they dislike. However, with fingers crossed, and impressed by Democratic presidential candidate John Kerry's talk of building partnerships with America's allies, Europeans are watching and waiting for a change of guard in Washington.  for full story:  urlLink http://straitstimes.asia1.com.sg/commentary/story/0,4386,267704,00.html  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      3 p.m. PST - Associated Press  Evidence of overwhelming and systemic fraud in the Ralph Nader for President petitions was released today by the Service Employees International Union. An analysis of the petition sheets and a direct survey of people whose names appear on the petition suggests at least two-thirds of all signatures turned in by the Nader campaign to date are fraudulent.   for full story:   urlLink http://www.polstate.com/archives/005935.html#005935  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      By TERESA HAMPTON Editor, Capitol Hill Blue Jul 28, 2004, 08:09  President George W. Bush is taking powerful anti-depressant drugs to control his erratic behavior, depression and paranoia, Capitol Hill Blue has learned.The prescription drugs, administered by Col. Richard J. Tubb, the White House physician, can impair the President’s mental faculties and decrease both his physical capabilities and his ability to respond to a crisis, administration aides admit privately.“It’s a double-edged sword,” says one aide. “We can’t have him flying off the handle at the slightest provocation but we also need a President who is alert mentally.”  for full story:   urlLink http://www.capitolhillblue.com/artman/publish/article_4921.shtml  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Esquire Magazine   September 2004, Volume 142, Issue 3  By Ron Reagan  It may have been the guy in the hood teetering on the stool, electrodes clamped to his genitals. Or smirking Lynndie England and her leash. Maybe it was the smarmy memos tapped out by soft-fingered lawyers itching to justify such barbarism. The grudging, lunatic retreat of the neocons from their long-standing assertion that Saddam was in cahoots with Osama didn't hurt. Even the Enron audiotapes and their celebration of craven sociopathy likely played a part. As a result of all these displays and countless smaller ones, you could feel, a couple of months back, as summer spread across the country, the ground shifting beneath your feet.  For full story go to:  urlLink http://www.esquire.com/cgi-bin/printtool/print.cgi?pages=5&amp;filename=%2Ffeatures%2Farticles%2F2004%2F040729_mfe_reagan.html&x=55&amp;y=7  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Surging oil prices are starting to take their toll on the global economy, key analysts and policymakers have warned.  Sunday, 8 August, 2004, BBC News  for full story:  urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/business/3546248.stm  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>