<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       o dear god. today was the most exciting but scariest day of my life..thanks to becky and my stupidness. 1st of all my stupidness:   okay i go downstairs to make kraft dinner and i plugg in the kettle cuz i am to lazy to wait for the water to boil. yes and the [here comes the stupidness] i put the kettle on the stove and turn the stove on. dumb dumb dumbass!!!jesus. so then since i have no life and because ia m stupid i leave the stove [with the kettle on it] and go  upstairs on msn. and when i come back down the fucking kettle had melted.  and there was fucking smoke everywhere. and then the fucking smoke detector goes off. great. thats just what i need for the whole stret to hear that i almost set my house on fire. yeah.. and then after that was all cleaned up. i go back on msn.and i talk to sharlit and becky[they are lovers] and they say:   sharlit and becky:we are coming over right now   me: no youre not   sharlit and becky:why the hell not?   me:cause you wont walk all the way over here and i am ugly right now[as i   am usually]   sharlit and becky:her mom is dirving us on her way to soccer..we are leaving bye!   [15 minutes later]   my dog goes crazy at the sound of the doorbell.they open the door and my fucking dog runs right on to someones porch. great.thanks guys!. and then we come back and we do nothing. talk about nothing. as becky roams my house for food. [which we have non of]. BUT then becky finds the knives and starts chasing me around my own fucking house with a knife! ahhhhhhhhhhh RUN FOR YOUR LIVES...just kidding becky i love you..even with knives in your hands..and pants aha. and thats about it...i think. oh and bye the way happy birthday kristy YOUR THIRTEEN!!! luv you girl xoxox.  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha.according to sharlit i am cool. haha. that makes me laugh. okay you want to  hear how cool i am. yes. okay  sharlit-what are you doing today? me-i think maya is coming over but i dont know you? sharlit-becky is coming over.the usual me-lol sharlit-what are you and maya going to do? me- watch pearl harbour. and you and becky will do.. sharlit[something about going to the store i didnt rrally read it sorry] me- cool. i dont think maya will be home tho. she will be doing something by now. sharlit-yeah. i wish becky would get up.jesus me-she is still sleeping? sharlit-yes. me-lol  shalrit-actually i think she might have gone to spider man 2 witrh her dad and his girlfriend. me-her dad and his girlfriend?! sharlit-yeah. sharlit-read it in her blogg. me-okay [i read] [and read] [and wonder why maya is writing in beckys blog] me- i didnt know beckys parents split up. sharlit-beckys parents split up?! me- she went to a movie with her dad and his GIRLFRIEND? shalrit- becky?! sharlit-no stupid maya. me-ooooooooooooh.wow its not even funny how  fucking blonde i am. sharlit-haha me-but why was maya writing in beckys blog? sharlit-ITS MAYAS BLOG. me- wow this is scary.how stupid i am.. sharlit-dont worry your cool cort.  hahahahahahahahahaha omfg. soooooo funny.sad how this is my life. msn blogs.msn read blogs. msn. be stupid. msn.say stupid itiotic things that makes cortney cortney. i wouldnt be the same if i wasnt stupid and blonde and dumb and just plain RETARTED. i belong in a mental sycord. i would have more of a life there. unbeliveable.  cortney
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today.started of bad.very bad.because of my faj who thought it would be a grand i dea for him to wake me up at 9:00.and it was not a grand idea because i dont like to get up at 9:00.but now i am thankful that he did. because if he didnt then i would not have been on msn at 10:00 talking to kayla who was hungry and wanted to make maccoroni and made me realize how much i love heinz ketchup.so thankyou faj.and thank you kayla. this is how my day started: i was rudely woken up by some crazy senial freak[aka my dad] pounding at the door. so i got up. i went on msn because i have a life.no one was on so i had a shower and then i came back on to msn and my friend who i miss very very much was on ...kayla. and then we talk about how she is hungry and she left me to go make her maccoroni. when she comes back she tells me that she doesnt have any heinz ketchup just the shit kinds that try to taste like heinz ketchup but they dont. and now my new hobbie is heinz ketchup ONLY!now i am bored and the rest of the day is going bad.very bad.oh shit i was suppose to call gayla. haha oops.good friend i am huh? okay well i will be off now. hugs and kisses.  cortney.
    
</post>


</Blog>