<Blog>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Buckethead is the man. He kicks ass on the guitar. YA HEARD? Former drummer for the absolutely incredible group Guns n' Roses, Buckethead is the man     Who is Buckethead? Buckethead is the masked, inverted KFC bucket wearing, "mutant guitar virtuoso" that stunned audiences during Primus's set at OzzFest '99, toured the world with Praxis and GR2, and graced many a movie soundtrack/score. His major label debut as a member of the avant-funk outfit Praxis in 1992 opened ears and minds to his unique character and musical stylings. He has since released several solo albums (under his name and Death Cube K) and participated in many group settings (most notably the Deli Creeps, Praxis, Zillatron, Giant Robot, Giant Robot 2 and Cobra Strike) and performed/recorded numerous collaborations with other adventurous musicians and artists. There has been much speculation as to the identity of Buckethead. We do know that he was raised in a chicken coop by chickens. And possibly due to the unusual circumstances surrounding his upbringing, he is a very private person. He doesn't grant many interviews, and shuns most conventional means of contact. The mask and bucket add an eerie air of mystery to his activities and serve as a harbinger for his otherworldly musical stylings and sensibilities. He would prefer that his fans accept his eccentricities, focus on his art and enjoy the wonderland of joy that is Bucketheadland. He draws inspiration from science-fiction and horror movies, musicians, artists, writers, athletes and has bizarre fixation on Disneyland. His dream is to complete his own park--Bucketheadland, "Where all your dreams and nightmares can come true." This theme runs through many of his recordings and was first introduced to the public through his Psychobuddy columns in Guitar Player magazine back in 1991   for more info on buckethead click  urlLink here  
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That is my new name on Doom 3 because I hide in the shadows and then blow your ass away when you walk by 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WORD UP!  Doom 3 online is so amazing. I played it online for the first time tonight and GOD DAMN WAS IT EVER GOOD!!!!! I'm not sure how many people were in the server, it seemed like 6 or 7 but it was incredible. THIS GAME RULES 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The "Super Freak" was found dead Today................. damn that sucks 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know by now MOST Halo fans have discovered ilovebees.com and its messages/countdown. But now a new site has surfaced http://www.ilovebeer.org/  it is similar to the design of ilovebees.com and also has a message much like ilovebees.com......  interesting.........
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      holy crap. I can't believe they could make a shooter this good. Doom 3 is hands down the best FPS that has ever been released, screw Halo, screw Half Life, Doom 3 is where it is at.  YA HEARD!? 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1998 Viper GTS/R  DAMN FINE    
    
</post>


</Blog>