<Blog>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well if it isnt another day in hell. At least thats todays attatude, tommorow may be different. Why is life shit today? Well basically because being poor (or at least not rich) sucks. At least I am an American where else can you eat steak and complain about how hard times are. I wonder if I am leaning into the hasbeen part of my life. At one time I earned more than I could spend. Now I spend more than I can earn. I search daily for that break thats going to put me back on top, it seems to be just out of reach. Why is it that most rich people dont have the sense God gave a light bulb. Yet there are smart poor people. Is it dumb luck, do they work harder, or does God keep wealth from people he fears will kill them selves with it. I think at one time I would have fell into that catagory. Excuse my spelling I just type, I dont look.Before I was twelve I understood what type of person I was. Most people go thier whole lives wondering who they are and never figure it out. (Poor dumb bastards) Yet, even though I know who I am, it doesnt keep me from making bad choices. Any way I am starting a new job/career and I think its the one that will put me back on top but I still have doubts. This is my first blog, so I have no idea what people put on these things, except for that stupid slut in D.C. who was selling her ass because her job didnt pay enough. What a bimbo... You wont be reading that kind of b.s on this page, hell most people wont even read this page. I have never had a diary before.. I think its gay. Oh did I touch a nerve well Im not sorry, I am a hardcore Republican who believes in a right to life, NO to queers getting married, and small government with NO entitlements. Sorry no check for you. I dont believe in handouts. And if Kerry beats Bush in November then I will be drinking ice water in hell. If he does win, you people will get what you deserve, double digit inflation, higher gas prices, the dow in the john if you know what I meen. Then the terrorist will get what they want, Kerry will bring our boys home and the terrorists will be right behind em. Imagine if you will... The fog drifts in off the water, its a cool morning off the coast of Charleston S.C. The mexican laborers are busy in the fields picking strawberries. Trucks are taking the freshly picked produce to the packing houses for the day laborers to sort and pack. Rigs are running forward and back from the piers, bringing in imports and taking what few exports America still has left to the dock. At the Citadel the freshmen recruits are into there third mile of the morning, the young sargent leading them isnt even winded. Little do they know but the sarge has ten miles planned for this mornings run. There will be no more slipping out to Charleston College anymore.      As the day unfolds like any other day, a Coast Guard cutter speeds out to meet an incoming oil tanker, it is twenty miles north of the unloading zone and has already breached the harbor. The cutter had just rounded the tip of Charleston, past White Point Gardens and was at full power headed toward Fort Sumter, where the first shot of the Civil War was fired. The oil tanker wore the flag of Kuwait, the harbor master had radioed the ship and requested the ship turn around, but the captian, if he was on the ship, did not reply. The oil tanker was within two miles from Shutes Folly Island when the little cutter caught up with it. A first mate took the bullhorn from its resting place and relayed the Cutter Captians commands. "Bring your ship to a full stop and prepare to be boarded." By this time three Navy helocopters had taken defensive positions around the oil tanker. There was no response from the ship. The lead copter pilot radioed the cutter."Captian Sheffield, there is no one in the pilot house that I can see." "I dont think your ship is going to stop." The Captian knew he had problems now, the way this tanker was riding in the water, he could tell it was full. The helocopter pilot moved in closer to see if there was anyone on deck. They were now within a mile from the point of Charleston. Captian Sheffield ordered his men to form a boarding party to go up to the pilot house and put that "Damn Ship" in full reverse. The first mate picked up a grappling hook and fired it at the rail. The climb would be straight up, thank God for calm seas this morning. The copter pilot radioed back, "The best I can tell sir, there is no one on board." "I am going to set this bird down on the forward deck, then your men can walk me through the steps of stopping this thing." The captian gave his approval,  the pilot could stop the tanker before even one of his men made it on board. The pilot, Major Jim Parson set his huey down with ease, the deck tilted forward to meet him. Major Parson ran to the pilot house, as he stepped inside he slipped and fell. As he gathered his bearings he realized that he was covered in blood. He pulled himself up by one of the many bars mounted around the cab. As he got his footing he looked to the controls, thats when his face turned white, his gunner walked in behind him. "Whats wrong Jim?" All the Major could do was point. There on the controls was a note, written in blood. "This tanker has four thermonuclear bombs on board Praise be to Allah" The gunner looked from the note to his commanding officer, "Dear God Jim, What in the hell are we going to do?" As the Major shook off the initial horror he radioed the cutter. "Captian, this ship is rigged with nuckes, what in the hell do we do." Captian Sheffield shot back"Put the Damn thing in reverse!" Major Parson found the lever and pulled hard, back to reverse. When he did he heard a small pop under the console, and smoke wafted from it. "Oh sh...." Those were words that took over one million people instantly to hell. The four thermonuclear bombs lit up ten thousand barrels of oil to create the largest explosion in the history of man. President Kerry was on television within 45 minutes trying to calm the American people. With the harshest tone he could gather he swore vengance on Al-quida...But now it was too late. The former President Bush watched in horror from his ranch in Crawford Texas. All over America anyone with a middle eastern complextion was in trouble. Linchings were the order of the day. Pakastanies were shot and stabbed. Children with the wrong look had thier throats cut on the playground. Within two hours marshall law was declared, yet the streets of America ran red in foriegn blood. This is where we are going people. Vote like your life depended on it.................................................................. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>