<Blog>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Madden 2005&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       F or the past few years, the player who has graced the cover of Madden NFL Football has gotten an injury, his team has done bad, or they had a horendous season. Eddie George, who was on Madden 2001 , failed to break 1000 yards and Tennessee went 7-9. The Curse came again when Daunte Culpepper, who was on Madden 2002 missed 4 games with injury, threw for 1300 less yards and 19 less TD's then in the year before. Minnesota's had its worst record since 1984, 5-11. When Marshall Faulk was on Madden 2003 he rushed for 430 less yards and had 4 less TD compared to the year before. His worst season since 1996. The Rams scored only 16 more points then their 1996 team who had Tony Banks at QB and Lawrence Phillips at RB. And last Year, when Michael Vick was on the cover of Madden 2004 he missed the first 11 games with a broken leg. His QB rating, comp pct, and yards per attempt were all down from 2002. This year with Ray Lewis on the cover of Madden 2005, the world will have to wait and see if the curse is finally over. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Larry Walker To the Cardinals? Can they Get any Better. Two MVP Candidates On one team, the best team in baseball and have a 10+ game lead in their division. It Seems The Yankees are going to have a tough series this year, right. In other New York news,   "One thing you always hear about is rookie hazing and I had to sing a few songs about three or four days into camp. They made me sing my ABCs and the Ying Yang Twins' "Get Low." I actually had a lot of fun with it and I think the veteran players enjoyed it, too." - Johnathan Vilma, LB, New York Jets  It Seems The Jets Are Going to have an ok season this year. 2-Year veteran wideout Santana Moss, last years Team MVP needs to put up some real big numbers and prove himself as an elite reciever among the leagues best if the Jets expect a playoff chance at all. Also, Chad Pennington must have a performance like 2 years ago. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Chris Rix&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       P ersonally, I think This Years Seminoles Have What It takes To Win It All. They Have e Two Bests Backs In The ACC In Lorenzo Booker And Leon washington. A Deep threat In Crophanso Thorpe. In The Offseason Thorpe Ran Track. He Was The ACC Champion In The 100 And 200 Meter Dash. And Then Theres Chris Rix.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Chris Rix, Where to get started... He  Could  be a Heisman Quarterback.  Could Be . There Isnt anyoffensive player around him that isnt good. Chris Rix this year has so many reasons he can win it. This Year The Seminoles haveone of, if not  the best  offensive lines this year, one of the top five recieving corps in the country, and two good runningbacks.  "  Rix has as much talent as any quarterback in the country, he has a loaded offense full of experience to work with, and he has 34 starts of experience to rely on. If it all comes together and he improves his decision making ability, he has all the makings of a Heisman winner and first round draft pick.   "-Collegefootballnews.com    "Rix, often a magnet for critics, also happens to possess the best raw talent of any quarterback in Seminole history. Better than Charlie Ward and better than Chris Weinke, the program’s two Heisman winners. Yet, for all his physical gifts and considerable upside, Rix is the same player, who can exasperate a coaching staff with poor reads and reckless attempts to make something out of nothing. If, however, the light suddenly goes on, and he parlays all that talent into one breakthrough year, Rix could vault to the head of the class, ala Carson Palmer two years ago. Great quarterbacks have it, that certain nebulous quality that drives them to victory and makes everyone around them better. Rix has one final opportunity to prove he’s a complete quarterback, and not just a great set of measurables."    -Collegefootballnews.com  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>