<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so me kri mussche and nicoel all hung out last night. we went to pizza king and chapple erv danny and huck met us there..... then after that us gals went to get see leah at Kmart but she wasnt there. so we didnt know what to do, the plan was to go to chases but he wasnt doing anything last night, so were goin there next weekend. anyways so the boyz called and we decided to go to danny's he was makin a bonfire and shit... mussche scarred teh hell right outta me n kir in teh back, cuz if u've ever rode with mussh on a country road, u will knwo what i mean.. shes a good driver, but ive been in 2 accidents so its easy for me to trip out over that shit. lol. so we got their and us gals took toms truck around, then we came back hung out, and Mussh was the only one to drink and it was just a beer... oh' and i quit smokin last night! yepp sure did, i smoked most of my pack last night, and gave huck my last two, i dk why i am, i just want too. cuz im sick of hidin it from my rents.. and last time my dad find out he cried, and i had nevber felt so bad in my whole life, (besides teh other time he cried when i came home drunk), and anyone and almost everyone knows my dad is my best friend. so yeah... plus i get migraines real easy, and recently everytime i have a cig. i get one, and that fuckin sux, so fuck that. anyways, so we all had to be home by 11... so kir chapple and mush got in toms truck and we go to the truck and thought they was parkin it cuz it was like 10 15 we thought we were leavin but they just said get in teh back, so what did we do? me and nicole got in teh back.. so 1/2 way there me and nic r liek where we goin, and they told us Westpoint to see randall, and i was like oh shit my rents r eatin diner there.. lol o well so worst part was mussh was flashin everyone who drove by on the way there and then they said lay down, cop is behidn us, so we thought, o fuck, were screwed cuz me in nick were in the back sittin it n shit..... so we layed down all the way there and shit, and we didnt get pulled  over, we foundout they were fuckin with us! omg it was funny. so that was that, it was fun.. and we planned we r gettin drunk next weekend! at chases...fo sure. but for now im out, i got to go get jd's shirt made and go to teh game tonight and babysit....im out xoxo  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wsup? so today, boring as hell. its the same as tues and yesterday lol.  ive had this migraine since about 7 days and my mom wont take me to st.e to get the shot, she usually does wtf? but its straight, ive been takin my moms vicadin she had for pain from, her mouth surgery.... it actually helps cuz im calm and shit then i pass out. so i think im gunna stick on the vicadin:) so Friday me kir kayla mussche and nic r prolly goin out to Chase's.. cuz i told Cydney i would, plus hopefully i'll get to drink. god i havent actually got hammered forever, it sux... but its straight, cuz i have plenty of time, hopefully. i mean ya never know when ur times comin. but anyways,  im about to pass out so im out.... updates later pry o and my schedule blows.. o well its ight i got my bestest friend ashley in 2 classes! XoXo  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so im home early, liek 3 days early why? cuz fuckin hurricane CHARLEY was headed towards the condo we was stayin at in FL. so im home, and fuck charley. it pisses me off, cuz i love to vacate, and plus i was plannin on visiting Shane down there but we couldnt cuz we had to leave. o well anyways, so the short time i was there was good.. it was really hott. i got sunburned on my back and it hurts like a motha fucka'. when we was there i got up early in the mornin, and went down 2 teh beach and just got in teh water got shells for skylar, and when i was by myself i just kinda set on the beach and thought about shit. i dk why, but lately ive been thinkin bout tyler and nate alot. like my emotions r mixed up. liek i will be fien for a long time then i will get in these moods for like a couple weeks where i think about thats shit and get alll depressed, but i think its b/c my mom took em off zoloft 4 months ago and ever since then its been hell off and on. it wasnt as bad when i was on it, the only reason she took me off was b/c she thought i was an addict,and i needed to cope with my feelings myself,not from the pills. i think its just cuz when my dad was sick he got addicted to narcotics easily and she thinks i will end that way. its stupid shit. anyways, so we went to seaworld one day too. Pat really wanted to go, and i had never been so i was cool wit it. and it wasnt that bad, i was really lookin forward to swimin with teh dolphins cuz in teh brochure it advertised that u could. and we got there and found out u had to make fuckin reservations and the soonest open was next month, so i didnt swim with teh dolpins.. i was pissed lol. o well.. i did see shamu tho! lol. thats a big son of a bitch when u sit in teh 3rd row~damn... oh and i was feeding the seals fish, and a fuckin bird liek attacked me! i hate birds. anyways, so we didnt get caught in any bad weather since we left early. i talked to shane almost every night, and im lookin forward to seein him for xmas. break. i miss him. the only person i missed while i was gone, was my dad and dog. lol. me and my dad r close, well we dont talk much or do anything anymore cuz he is always working now. but he still is my best friend. my mom and me didnt fight very much in FL. so thats a plus. and Pat was cool liek usual, but everytime she lit up a cig. i like wanted to take teh damn thing away from her, god it killed me. i think my mom knows i smoke again, i dk tho'. my dad said he wouldnt care if i didnt have asthma, but i dont think i have it anymore so w/e. tommrow im goin skool shoppin with shanna and skylar. i missed them too i forgot to mention. shit skool starts soon, that sux but i really got to try this yr and make sum decent grades to make up for frosh and soph. yr. cuz i did bad. cydney and danny just called theyre at chase's partyin' they told me to come out, but im soo damn tired, so im gunna go next weekend with cyd pry. well i took liek 4 dramamine so im about o pass out. nighty night ppl. much love 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so its almost midnight and i just came home...... what a night....im feelin pissed off and exuasted right now.. okay so it was fun and all, im glad i got to see some friends b4 i leave tommrow. so it started out slow but worked its way up, just like the lil party in her ditch!except we were drunk! anyways, so ppl came on and off, i had mussche and nic cum to see me, i wanted to talk to mush cuz i havent for a while, by the way i am sooo proud of you baby! fuck what ppl say, let them talk if they aint got nuffin better to do then fuck 'em . ashley and jasey was there, and shes my best friend so im glad they came, i never know when jasey is reallay pissed tho' like if i say summthin i shouldn't cuz he fucks with me, and i get confused... o well. so anyways, damien,kevin,dustin,kyle and them stopped b/c of aj right? well im glad i saw damien he tried to teach me how to play the guitar, but lets face it i can't. i miss damien but he even know it, its time he grows up. and i dont talk to kevin n dustin really no more, mainly cuz i got away from done shit they do, and if i get caught @kev's crib or nething i get shit from my mom, cuz she knows what goes on there. but that wouldnt stop me, but she says she'd take my car away! anywayss..... so yeah, im pissed at aj b/c in my eyes we r like posta be best friends and shit, but he acts like we are only bff when its convienent for him. and thats bullshit. so thing is he wasnt even fo sho he was cumin to cassies, and i asked him to come for me,since im leavin right? well 1st off we plan were gunan go to the mall together and shit and then right to get derrick and go to the party, and so i told him i would call when i was ready for him to get me.. well cum to find out , NOT FROM HIM, the mothafucka already went to the mall, got derrick and was at cassies and didnt even call me, and he got his cell taken away so how was i posta fuckin now he wasnt cumin, he didnt even call, the lil shit like that pisses me off, cuz he does it all the time..damn. so that aint all......so okay we didnt even hang out or talk barely, he was too busy runnin round to country view and shit with all the guys, which is cool but i mean, he was doin that all night, and he copped out on damien when they were in c.v. and left him after swerain he wouldnt' which is also shitty as hell.. so damien was ready to kick ajs' ass and no doubt in my midn he would, but they settleled it... okay, so anways i dont think aj even knows im pissed at him but i am, he puts ppl off, and liek i said HIS PRIORITIES R FUICKED UP. so i told aj b4 he left for good, to tell me bye cuz im leavin for a week and he is liek fo sho. well he cums back to get damien and kyle, and then leaves drives by again, and just yells from the corner " i love you", okay what a fuck. i said......" k.." i dont know if i want to be best friends with sumone like that,i cant trust him. i mean i would take a bullet b4 it hit him anyday, and thats how it should be, but he pry wouldnt take one for me.o well enuf bout him, why right about someone who pry wouldnt write about you right????? so anyways, yeah .... no liquor.... but jasey gave me sum cigs. to get by. speakin up i need ot get up early to 2mar. and go buy some packs for FL. so yeah, damien and kyle and this other dude got a 1/2 right? and damien offered me up on it, and i was soo close to bein hell yea im goin to the pit! but i said no. i havent got blazed since spring break with leah, and i wanted to but i dint at the same time, i have friends who ask me not to do it, and my friends respect means more to me then trippin; even tho its nice. the shits bad fo ru , i have seen how its changed soo many ppl im close with, and how it controls their likfe, and i dont want that. im not against it, cuz i cant promise i wouldnt do it again, i kno i will.. but i wouldnt make it a continuous habit. hell i dont have the $. lol. the thing is if i had to choose alci. over weed, id pry say weed, only cuz the whole point of drinkin,smokin,poppin,sniffin, any thing...... is to get fucked up right? and hell once u hit that shit ur gone, or a couple times, and drinkin, at least for me it takes sum time and some real shit to get me trashed. and the quicker the better right? i dk. and another thing is, sometimes, i feel like such a bitch to drink b.c thats how my best friend(tyler) died,killed by a drunk motha fucka. and its like why would i practice what killed my baby? i dk ..... but it helps the pain go away, sumtimes thats all that matters. cuz that pain will eat u alive no joke. im worried about leah she is my gurl, and means alot to me, she knows that, and i kno she is goin thro sum shit right now, and i cant do ne thing bout, shit im still on zoloft, how can i help her ya kno.. i want to, but i cant say nething that will change how she feels. shes a strong girl mentally and physically, but inside i know shes hurtin, and i will do what ever i can to help her thro it. she was there for me, im here for her.k im out like a fat kid in dodgeball(i got that from kev d) mofo's! lov yall and i will be in FL. for 9 days call my cell if u wanna talk or ne thing. i'll miss yall, but i'll be glad im not here! 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this will be short and sweet......So its like 12 30, and skylar is doin my hair, cuz we are gunna head over to cassie's to start decorating for her party tonight. im not sure how its gunan turn out, robbie from b.c. is bringing beer, but i dont know if we will get to drink her dad has alreayd threatened her bout no drinkin, see last yr. ppl stole vodka from her rents and they were irrate! so i dk. so were havin liek a b0nfire and swimin and shit and kareoke, so it should be fun.. i wanna have fun and see my close buddies since im leavin tommrow for FL. its gunna be me mom her best friend and her son, i was gunan bring ashley but it didnt work out, and then i was guna bring aj, but since steven isnt havin a buddy , i cant. so i promised aj he could go with me next yr. for yall who dont alreayd know, aj is my best guy friend, we used to date like 6th thro 8 and froshi think, but we are way better as friends. my moms bein a bitch again today whats new?.>? skylar is now trying to put my hair in a bun, lol shes a dork. well im out for now, i'll be back tonight and update u with the latest shit. peace out shawty'z~! 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       same routine as any other day, skylar gets to my crib at 7:00 and crawls in bed with me and we sleep until we decide its time for breakfast, which is usually leftovers from last nights dinner. SO we usually get up around 11 or 12. FYI skylar is a youngin i babysitt for, she is more like a lil sister, she was Nate Faulkners lil sis;who passed last sept.... anyways, so we get up and do w/e then i get a shower and decide we need to go to the mall. my best friend ashley called while i was walkin out the door, and she decided she wanted to go...so we go and i buy Cassie her bday present, which is a vibrater with lotion and shit, and this heller card, says,"where is dildo?" and u have to find it... shes a perv like that, not me lol.  then we were gettin a slushy from snoBiz and mikey( the mall midgett) came runnin up and asked ashley to play tag, she rjected the idea, but Mikey insisted she played. so he chased after her around teh fuckin mall for like 20 mins. i was rollin on the ground laughin my ass off with skylar.   i just got home from Cassie's like an hour ago, we made signs for her bday, "rock out with your cock out" nice huh? we went to dollar general and got accused of stealing fuckin poster boards, truth was the old bitch behind the counter was on crack, we didnt steal....this time. so i hung out at cassies and read this sex tips book its pretty intresting! then i called my mom to see if i could just crash at cassies crib and of course, she said no... then we fought a lil and i said fuck it.   me and mom always fight, its like we enjoy it in a sick way. its over some gay shit most of the time too. i seriously just think she hates me most of teh time, how can u bitch at someone u love soo much? i guess its a retorical ? to me too.. i am a bitch i know it.. o well.   so...... my dads sick again and it really sucks b/c there is no shit i can do for him, for you ppl that dont know, my dad is a hydro-sa-folic? its like he has a brain tumor kinda.. and he has had it his whole life.. he is alot better these days and not living in a hospital or charter. i love my dad more than anything. he is the best person i know. and i dont think he knows that, and i wish i could tell him, but im really bad at bein affectionate w/ ppl, mostly my rents. i dk why?    i reallly want a cig. i so called "quit" like a month ago, but why give up something you like? im soo cheap tho' i hate wastin my money on them, but yet there a so called necessity.   so tommrow is cassies bday and it will be heller... i dk if we wil be drinkin or not tho' cuz her rents, and i cant get hammered, cuz i have to go home, only b/c im leavn for FL. sat at lik 5 in the morn. damn. i would love to get drunk...hell smokin the reefer dont sound bad either, but the last time i did that was spring break with my gurl Leah.    Well im out, tired.                             
     

    
</post>


</Blog>