<Blog>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Selectica!! This word has a special meaning in this heart and certainly in many of the ones like me. It certainly is more than a place to work. Why it should be is a question.I wonder if I can put it in words. It was no more than a month when we, the fresh bloods, as all of them call us, came here with many aspirations in our heart. We were just out of our cozy cocoons to face this PROFESSIONAL world about which we only had heard. With us we brought in all the hopes of our near and dear ones. It was an entry into a different world as we could see it. Professionally they call it as time to put in all the knowledge we have on a practical podium. All set to display our abilities and create a mark of our work. I know this special moment is part of everyone's life, only if someone pens it down.  More than fear, it was anxiety to explore the culture at work place.The free birds were put to work. As it starts for everyone, it did for me too. The exuberance and enthusiasm would never fall short any morning to wake up and rush to office. I still remember the pride associated with little words like "I am going to office." It was not only I, but all my crew had the same thing in mind. As days passed, college friends got distant and a new set of people got introduced, reformation of family, is what I prefer calling it, as all the like minded and like hearted people got together sharing their experinces of the golden age of life, the college life. We were like soft clays willing to get moulded according to the new cast. Small little meets at breakfast, lunch, afternoon tea and snacks brought us closer, tigtining the bond of family. Our seniors here laid all the rules of family. We are one of the best in the market were the words which would fill us with a great esteem. Dreams were really coming true when the eyes of near and dear ones started filling with satisfaction. Slowly and steadily everyone started creating a place for himself and occupy a seat loaded with responsibilities. The hazy professional world was slowly brightening up and we could find ourselves part of not only our small cliché but a bigger family, the Selectica family. Design is more crucial than implementation is what we hear everyday, and a good design always leads to a stable product is what we have by hearted. If I put it in words of my heart, Selectica has done exactly the same for all of us. It has not only moulded the fresh clay in an attractive package but also made it strong enough to withstand the forces of this world. It has taught us values of life. No matter people say "You have changed drastically in past year!!". Its small little family and friendly culture teach us the better way of living life. Small little things starting from the daily thought on the notice board at reception, the smiling and blissful faces of people, the roars of laughter at terrace, our pantry, the breath taking TT games, the treks, the long hours of work, the concern on seniors face for their juniors everything inculcates the feeling of strength in all the buds who join this blossomed garden. The interaction with old college buddies, the talks about work, the cribbing over matters as we see them would all tell us that there always is a better way of doing things than what tradition says. What more can I say, we owe foundation blocks of our lives to Selectica.   
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello all, This is the first blog of my life. Motto behind creating it is nothing but to stay in touch of technology. May be I would come to know its advantages as I start to use it. Pen and paper  always being  close companions of mine, I would definetely love to be a part of something like this. Hope all of us enjoy the stay here , today tommorrow and forever. Tushar   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>