<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I really cant believe 3 people that I thought were my friends only think of me as annoying. But o well that's life I guess, cant be friends with everyone. Shit happens, life goes on.  

						
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Aki, the only reason I was mad was because you said you didn't care about something very important to me that I wanted to share with you as friend, not as a CLOSE friend.  I didn't know this board was secret, if I did I wouldn't have posted the link on my website.  Now that I know, I WILL take it off.  I don't think I'm the most important person in the world, generally I try to make my friends happy.  I'm really confused why everyone thinks I'm a jerk.  I don't try to make people mad.  I only want to have friends.  What I wrote on my web journal was just what my thoughts were at that moment and at that moment I was just venting, without naming you in particular.  I never called you a B****, I just felt that you were acting like one at that moment.  I didn't mean to ever annoy anyone or make them mad.  If I did, I am truely sorry.  The reason why I use my computer so much, maybe some of you know and some of you don't, is because I am in a wheelchair and I can't do very many things.  Chatting is one thing i CAN do and I enjoy very much.  Most of you can do many other things, but the options for me are very, very limited.  If none of you ever want to talk to me again, I understand and it is okay. Thank you so much for chatting with me for so long and I'm sorry if I upset anyone.  

						
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I wont stay mad, but my first feelings were just lots of hurting. She might have had her reasons why, but in just disappointed in her. Maybe a friendship in my mind is different than hers. I just think a friend should care about what friends want to say when its important to them.     

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   GOD DAMN IT!!!!!!!!! How can a friend be so heartless. I just try to share some thing that is important to me and they say "o I don't really care about your personality". Well, fuck that. That's not a friend. Friends actually give a damn about their friends. And DON'T ACT LIKE FUCKING BITCHES when you try to share something important with them. I hate it so much. IM glad I have good friends like m***, k****, h*****, and k**** and everyone else. They actually have hearts.  

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   well, she said she cant change yet.she doesn't know when she can ever love someone, and she doesn't want me to wait for her. she really thinks i willbe dissapointed in her. she is afraid of rejection and and hurting someoneby dissapointing them. i said i wouldnever reject her and i want all of her,good and bad. she said how could i saythat, we have never met. i can just feel it she wants me to still be her friend, cuzshe really likes to talk to me. she justneeds to move at her own pace, slowly.she said she will always remember i wasthe first person to say i loved her.i said to her i am always there for herif she ever changes her mind, and i willnever reject her. she said she will remember that  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    jeez, mika is always in my mind. Has she considered being my gf at all? I guess not, because she is busy. What will happen if she says yes? I haven't thought about that. I guess just keep loving her and try to talk as much as possible. in the mean time i'll just wait and hope. *sigh*   

						
</post>


</Blog>