<Blog>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      7/7 I’m stucked. 1st, its btwn iris n d rest. Both of us r in d women’s team, nt 2 4gt clara, n we r nw seen s diff frm d res. Its juz a diff feel 4 d res I supp. Its like, yea, we’re a team, initially ( mayb nw in sum ppl’s opinion, we r nt exactly one… ) but y onli dey 3, or maybe dey juz consider 2, wich is naturally mi n iris, hv d opportunity 2 be in dere instead  R dey rily pro-er den us? “dey”? nope… its juz kat… yea, I’m no gd. I’m juz a spastic fig. I dun c d diff whether I’m in dere anot. Maybe its juz a blardy name “Katherine Loh” 2 fill up d space. I duno. But my name’s in, I’m in. tts it. Well, tts d 2nd pnt la duh? “wo men gen ni men shi bu tong de”—hy . I duno. She mite be jk, bt she meant it? Or at least she tinks tt way ya? I dun blame her. But I’m hurt by tt. I finally hv a feel of wads iris life is like. Whn u gt priviledges or chances tt d res dun gt, u r seen in a negative angle. They mite c u s suckers or wadeva. Dis I duno. Or tyco? Perhaps I’m d tyco? I’m hurt tt is. But so wad? I noe if iris is 2 be in dere alone, I will hv dis kinda feeling 2wards her too. Alrite, so I slept ovr at iris hse. Cool rite? Yea tt is. But deres more 2 it. Now tt I’m clser 2 her, n uds her more, n like her more, I’m trying 2 hang out wif her s well u noe? Shes part of d team, n I duno if d res c her s 1. at least nw I can accept her, unlyk in d pas. But whn I hang out wif her, dey will be commenting at d back. I feel dis cuming. I feel d world crushing. Whr has our spirit of d previous yr gone 2? Dey say iris like me a lot? Does tt show anything abt me? Dey think iris gt anything jiu shi cum n find me 1st? Does that show anything abt me? Well, I duno if iris rily like me a lot, but I supp she has no choice too..aftr all RITE now, I’m d clsest 2 her. Hu els will she wanna hand out wif? I’m totally confident tt she dun cum 2 me 4 evrything. Tts absurb! If I can say, I wud say she dun cum 2 me at all. Sumhw I feel tt she noe I dun like her.. but nw maybe it imprv a lot a lot aftr d slp ovr. But mayb d res hv tt feeling onli 2dae? Whn she called me 2 do d pouring of water wif her? N maybe other things tt I din notice? N I dun rmb STICKING wif her, or izit she sticking wif me? D onli tym I rmb we r 2gthr is whn we r walking 2 d another 158 bus stop at d construction dere de bend. Was a few sec wif her. N tt mmt I was thinking wad d others mite think. Den d 2nd tym was she ask me 2 go along wif her 2 fill d bottles. 3rd tym was whn we drink water frm tt container thngy. Den we walk back n sit on d bench.. 4th tym was, (I tink its totally spastic 2 mention dis) whn we were juz standing 2gthr 4 a few sec during hou pai sha qiu, observing Melissa 2gthr n saying muz learn frm her.. tts it.. v long mehz??? maybe its juz tt usu I’m nt wif her, or rather, no1’s wif her, tts y whn suddenly sum1 juz be wif her, its weird? And if I go wif her, means nt gg wif mab. N I think its totally spastic 2 say tt i can onli go wif 1 of dem. i’ll have 2 choose?!? Wadde hell! Y carn d whole team (xclude amannda) juz be 2gthr? Yyy? Y muz we b so drifted? Yyy? Y muz our charac be world apart? Y carn we click? Y carn we hang out s a team? Y carn we stay back aftr sch more often 2 play ball juz like in d pas we played during recess? At least we spent sum tym 2gthr instead of juz d usual trng daes… wich is total pathetic Haiz… n heard iris suffering frm depression? On medicine de can? Shes high up in position, wif d lowest self esteem (ys’s nick) I duno.. I dun tink its lowest self esteem, juz tt no frens? N I feel abit hu lue her. D whole team’s hu-lue-ing her wad. Shes so excited ovr d slpovr gettit? N nw I dun seem tt xcited abt it? HAIZ!!!!!!!!!!!!!! SLP n its ovr… 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>