<Blog>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay, lets get down to business. I would like to comment on a crazy group of people today. They are my beloved   JUNIORS.  They range from secondary one to secondary 3.      Firstly, I shall talk about the most mature(i hope!)gang out of the 3 levels mentioned.That is, the secondary 3s. Audrina, Ying Shuang, and Hui Min entered the PRSSCO percussion group in year 2002. When they first step into the room, We(ST,HL,E,ZY,S& gang) were horrified. They gave us tis impression tt dey are very quiet, not humurous and have no enthusiam. I guess our prediction that they would make a boring group is absolutely WRONG! Come to think of it, their actions are completely opposite of what we thought of. They were an excellent group of percussionist i must say. No regrets as we leave such a well-trained group for the PRSSCO.I remember my perc. teacher told mi that they haf the potential to be the outstanding people in the CO. His views were right!Other den the sec 3 in the percussion, i've oso met other sec 3s that are oso very great people.Not forgetting to mention some of them, "Si Han, Rena, Stefphanie, Ronnale, Kevin, Stephan, Ming Li,Dixon, Esther, Yu ting, and a lot a lot more...PRSSCO is in your hands!!     oooh.. now now, the secondary two batch. They are equally good. The sec 2 percussionist ( Mei Zhen, Mei Hui, Daniel,Emily, Sing Check, Qian Hui) are extraordinary. Although we push them a lot and they suffered a lot of screams, they do not grumble. That is one of their BEST quality seniors would ask for. This lead to their sucess now. I must pick QH out as she is very outstanding and even joined us for a competition when she just join. Good job indeed.My sons,haha.. Ting Yu, Wei Jian, Daisy, Yong Xiong, and much more.. they always brighten up my days. Each equipped with their own strong points, they RAWKS!! (TY: with his "ni bu lame trademark" ang birthday every alternate days, WJ: with his habit of laughing very loudly, poking people, Daisy: with his quacks and farnie actions are scared of pokes, Yong Xiong : with his attractive body tt woo the sec 4 gals) you all nv fail to impress us. ps I'm sorry if i miss you out... i haf too mani to mention. SYF,JIA YOU!!     Lastly, the youngest in the school. The Sec ones this year is a very enthusiatic batch. The teachers say tt they are very much like us when my batch was in sec 1.Let me see, Eunice, Teri, Kok Peng, Brian, Robert, Carlo,and Lynette are my little ones. They all haf potential and will perform as good if efforts are really put into it. I believe the teachers have high hopes for you guys and please work hard. I'm waiting for you guys to share your sucess one day with us. All the BEST in your studies and CCA. Do wellwith happiness, you will enjoy wad u are doing.Try to get into the SYF next year!     ON behalf of all secondary 4s or CO graduates, I would really want to let you guys noe we appreciate ur time with us, we will surely miss you paople as we go on to separate roads and lead different lives. We may not meet each other anymore..however, i will remember tt i met a special someone tt had changed my life, &amp; I want to let you noe now: tt person is  YOU ! ...thanks a lot   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          No one ever believe the words from our primary school teacher when we were in the graduating year. They repeated by telling us how memorable sencondary school days can be. It's only until I tasted my own experience then i realised i had mistaken my teacher. Here, my life changed (  for the better  ). I had so many stories to share, so many memories to store , so little time to treasure, so little happy days to number. Entering PRSS had nv been a regret and iwill not ever regret it.  This place would share my life in secondary school...    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>