<Blog>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello and welcome to Kevin's Big Bad Blog. This blog will cover whatever I feel like talking about.    WHAT IS A BLOG?            A didn't really know what a blog was until Feburary of 2004, when one of my favortie wrestling columnists, named Mr. Tito ( urlLink http://mrtitopdc.tripod.com/ ), started taling about his 'blog'. He said it was a column about anything....but wrestling. Now, I want to be a Journalist, and writing a column has been my dream, but I am just a boy, and who   would hire me? So, I found this website threw the "I love bees" thing, I'll talk about that more below....       I LOVE BEES? NO, I HATE BEES!            OK, this is a very odd and long story. If you are bored easily, skip ahead. If you hate video games, skip ahead...but if you like an interesting read, and consipircy-type things, or is it real or fake (al la, The Blair Which Project rumors), read ahead.          In late 1999, software giant Mircosoft, annouced that they were throwing their hat into video game home console ring with the Xbox (not, X-Box, thank you very much). And, so in 2001, the Xbox came out, at the price of $300. Now, a game system is nothing without games, so Xbox had 'launch games' that came out with the system at launch (you didn't get them free, no, you had to pay another $40, just to play on your $300 game system). One of the games was Halo, it was a shooter game. It had great graphics, good gameplay, and a amazing storyline. To this day, it has sold over 3 million copies, and has only been out 3 years.           So....the story begins. Fast forward to May, 2004. E3 (or Electronic Entertainment Expo, which is a huge video game trade show), Bungie (developer for Halo) showed a teaser for Halo 2. It showed new features like, new weapons, the ability to hold two guns at once, better graphics, and other things. At the end of the teaser, it said "Nov. 11" which is the release date, then it said " urlLink http://www.bungie.net ", then the web address morfed into the address " urlLink http://www.ilovebees.com ".          Needless to say, all gamers went to the website. It was a very bizarre site about an old lady who ran a honey business, but it was hacked. There were strange messages counting down to August 24. All the pictures were disconfigured. The lady who ran the website claimed to be the niece of her aunt, the beekeeper lady. She had a blog like these one, which is where I found this website. Fans went threw channels and found the website was registered to a San Franisco phone number. People called it, and at first it was a regular message "Hey, its Dana, please leave a messgae." Fans were disappointed. Later, she posted on her blog that her aunt bought her a ticket to China for working on her website, but she couldn't leave the website while it was hacked. Soon, the website begain to show strange messages like "MAYDAY! MAYDAY! I am trapped on earth, help me, help me." Then, her voicemail changed to "Hi, this is Dana. I'm going away....for a long time. Leave a message, but I don't know when I'm coming back. Mom, I love you!" It is odd. This is the dead end. Some people say it is a ploy by Bunige/Mircosoft, to get people talking. If that is true, then it most certainly is working, because we are talking now. Also, someone named "Dan" has created a spoof of the website, called  urlLink http://www.ilovebeer.org , and he even has his blog. Its funny. I guess we'll have to wait until August 24th to see what happens. The rumor is that Offical Xbox Magazine will have a playable sample level of Halo 2.     RELATED LINKS    urlLink http://bees.netninja.com/wiki/index.php?title=Main_Page  - A web page decated to this "I love bees" fiacso.     QUICK HITS      John Kerry is a moron. The guy has no opinons. The only thing he stands agasint is President Bush. He also is a liar. I'm planning something on this topic, soon in a future blog. Stay tunned.    Former WWE Superstar, Brock Lesnar, is in trouble already. He left WWE for the NFL and he joined the Vikings, at a poor contract and only at a shot at the backup squad. During a pratice game against the Kansas City Reds, the teams were told not to hit, but Lesnar took out the Backup QB for the Reds. I think we'll have to follow his development has a NFL star, but lets look at his stats. He's 26 years old, he played high school football, but not college or pro. He won the NCAA Wrestling Championship in 2000 for Minnasoda U. He was signed only because he is a collagate sports star in Minnapolis.     Ugh....I hate hackers. I plan to have more on why they hack and more in an upcoming feature that will be in my blog.      THE FINISHER                 Oh boy, this is a bad blcomments you make. Also, I'll try to make it better. Tell me what you like and don't like.og. I need help. Also, I want to have a section where I post a comment made and respond to it. My goal is to get this done on the weekends.      Until Next time, this is Kevin reminding you that the spin stops here.....uh....good mental health.....ugh, I'm going to need a good phrase to end my blogs. Oh well, I'll think of one. Wasn't their a Frasier episode about this?          See ya latah, playah (nah, thats not it.)          
    
</post>


</Blog>