<Blog>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       HEYYYYY Im so happy today cuz its Saturday and on Monday I'm leaving this country (to bad... only for a month)!I cant wait to meet all my friends and my people there :D ! ! !I'll go everyday to the beach and then in the afternoon around 6-7 in Tirana, in The Block area becomes preety crazy there lol all those girlz and all those bars and pubs when the underage drinking is great!!! :D Its like a fashion show lol.Im going alone not with my brother as it was supposed to be :P  so maybe I'll have less fun but still anyways... I realllllytyyyy reallllyyy cant wait for Monday :D nOW LETS GET BACK TO THIS STINKING COUNTRY LOL They fired me from work cuz of a fucking fag that came to work for the company :PI tried to call Tijana from work but nobody was home I guess and Steve (tahts the fuckers name) was looking at me and said:- Hey baby r u calling your girlfriend?- Why do u care? - i replied and got away nervous!!!!!Then when the f**cing bell rung to get back to work I waz streching cuz I was tired and sooo bored to get back to that construction shit that I use ... and the little faggggg booohhhhhh while I was streching he was like 4 eyes lol and :- Awwwwwwww my goodness u have a sexy ass to be with a girl And that was it !!!! I couldnt atnd that bitch anymore!!!!!So I went on him punching and beat the hell out of that fuckingggggggg fag!!!!!I was soooooo like high that i didnt care about nothing so the boss came to separate us and I punched him too  lol :P and teh two "lovely" guys started bleedinggggg .... :D Then the police came and got me to the station but no cuffs :Pjust a few questions like "Do u have something against gay people" and "Why did u punched the boss bla bla bla ....And so i was home by 11 and my parents started scremaing as they ussualy do when im in trouble. So thats preety much the day Today Im having dinner with Tijana we'll go for sushi my favorite :D at 10.00 PM It'll be fun i guess ;D But sure im not gonna try anything ..... ;) just the simnple usual kiss of goodnight and thats it.Ok cuz im tired of writting so much so bye till next time maybe i'll write something here while Im in my paradise in Albania!!!! Byeeeeeeee   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hi :)   Today waz a nice day but as alwayz working... :(   I tried to call Tijana on lunch time there at work but nobody answered :P when i came home i also retried but the same thing! :(   So i guess my tickets for that drama show on the Second City Theatre are going to some fucking bitch that dont deserve it.... anywayz    Im only writing cuz of the e-mails taht we had. The website  urlLink www.albanian-boyz.tk  is running quite allright and i had many many visitors from all around the world. (Today somebody from Serbia & Montenegro visited though)   Im not planning anything special this weekend if i cant talk with Tijana tomorrow at least :P    I dont know why that girl made soooooo "romantic" lol and sweet (im surprised) but i only know that i like so oooo much to be with her &amp; I dont know the reason.      All day in work Ive been listening to  urlLink this song  try to hear it :)    So for now night cuz Im sooo tired       Arbri 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hi this is my first entry here :) I really dont know what to write though so ..... Bye bye just for now cuz i have to chatch a date with Tijana at 7:15 Lets see how it goes and maybe... just maybe tomorrow I'll have a new girlfriend. (lol)  Bye - Arbri 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>