<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Work For A Living
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Get A Job
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Genocide is a fulltime job!
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    No Government
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Burn Capitalism
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Greedy Hosni
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    War For Oil
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Pledge
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Toast The Rich
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    U.S. Imperialism
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Award&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Activism... It's Not just for hippies anymore!&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    You Are The Monkey Wrench...&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>


<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The rest of my family is obsessed with the once every four years snore-fest that is the Olympics, so the television is on almost 24/7. With the television comes the capititalist brainwashing technique known as the commercial. Though I try to avoid it, I sometimes watch the idiot box and so I to am unclean with the taint of consumer wants, at least for a few minutes, before I regain my common sense. There is one commercial that is pissing me off more then most lately. It is an Old Navy commercial, and it is definitely living up to the prior Old Navy comercials' annoyance levels. This one imparticular starts off in a classroom. The teacher is talking about history, when all of a sudden some girl jumps up and begans to scream about how much she loves history and about how we should all study. Scene change. Now there is a graph that tells about how Old Navy causes denim levels to rise which sets off you're savings glands or something of that sort, creating an ecstatic sensation at random moments. What the commercial doesn't tell you is that while you're buying clothing at great prices, (which you're not, if you don't know how to make your own clothing, shop at thrift stores, where there are real savings, plus, no money goes to major coroporations) you're supporting sweat shops, which is just modern slavery. Old Navy is owned by the Gap, which is one of the worst offenders of clothing workers rights I know of. Whole families, (including children) are subject to horribly dangerous working conditions, unfairly long hours, and extremely low pay, so the Gap's CEO and his associates can take long vacations and host fancy parties. Of course, the Gap makes itself look like it is the hero.      "Around the world, Gap Inc. has more than 90 employees whose sole focus is working to improve conditions in the factories that make the clothing we sell"         So, you have 90 employees who are suposed to monitor over 3,000 factories world wide? Wow, it looks like you are really trying to stop the problem. Congratulations, assholes.        Have we become so stupid that we will subject our fellow humans to horrible torturous cruelty just because we see a commercial with flashing bright colors and unoriginal pop music? Are we so brainwashed that we will continue to fatten the wallets of the heartless bosses because they tell us something is fashionable? Nothing like a large dose of capitalism and consumerism to rape the world and abuse the poor. Free yourselves and your brothers and sisters, stop supporting slavery and stop letting other people tell you what you like. Be creative, don't be part of the system. Demand change, if not for your your own benefit, then for the garment workers who are being so mistreated.       "If there is a State, then there is domination, and in turn, there is slavery."    -Mikhail Bakunin   
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, well I wrote this, its incoherent, rough, and probaly illegal. Rate it... badly if you have any sense. Just post your review, I'd appreciate it. I've written alot of songs, but I just thought this one needed some work, so any helpful hints would be gladly accepted. Thanks.                                          America The Beautiful    God bless the USA, where the rednecks beat the gays, the army kills who they desire, and the president's a liar.  God bless United States Enron, Oil, and Bill Gates. Imperialism is back in style, Our popstars are pedifiles.  God bless the corporations rich snobs and the Fox station. Gas prices on the rise, Cheap beer and freedom fries.  America the Beautiful (x3) America is FUCKED!  Music (for guitar and bass, played very fast):  Verse ||D#|Eb G Ab:|| (x4)  Chorus (acoustic only) ||Ab G|G Gb  F| Ab G|G Gb G:||                                         End ||D Eb:|| (x4)  
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       1) People who use omg!, like, lol, rofl, and so on all the fucking time.  2) Conservatives  3) Democrats  4) Nazis  5) Pop-Punk Bands (see my prior post, Punk Is Dead)  6) Rednecks  7) Jocks  8) Anyone who's wardrobe is 20% or more from Hot Topic (you aren't rebelious, you're a corporate whore)  9) Anyone who's SN contains any combination of: hot, summer, princess, cutie, girl, player, pimp, spring, sexy, lax, or pink  10) CEOs  11) Scabs (the people who go to work during a strike; quit licking the boss's ass)  12)Anyone who shops at the Gap, Nike, any sweat shop stores (you're no better then slave          drivers)  13) Homophobes & gay bashers  14) People who drive SUV's  15) Jesus Freaks (or any ultra-religious people)  16) Racists  And a hell of alot more, but I really don't want to keep typing for 5 years. If you fit into any of these categories, post a comment so I can shit in your face.  Just kidding... or am I?     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I just read this:    "Countries whose citizens believe in hell are not only less corrupt, but also more prosperous. That's the word from economists with the Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis, who were trying to figure out why some nations are so much richer than others.     In addition to looking at productivity and investment factors, they examined some unconventional ideas to explain differences in national prosperity, reports Reuters. It turned out that belief in hell was very telling.    Drawing on the research from several outside economists, the St. Louis Fed studied 35 countries, including the United States, European nations, Japan, India, and Turkey and realized that religion was a powerful economic force. "In countries where large percentages of the population believe in hell, there seems to be less corruption and a higher standard of living," the St. Louis Fed wrote in a recent quarterly review.     In the United States, a whopping 71 percent of the population believes in hell. Perhaps it's no coincidence that it also has the world's highest per capita income.    Don't believe it? Look at Ireland. As Reuters says, the Irish have a healthy fear of the nether world with 53 percent of the population acknowledging hell's existence, and the country is not far behind the United States in terms of income."        I think third world countries, where people face starvation, disease, genocide, and western explotation belive in Hell just as much as well off nations, only they know they are living it. The oppression they face is something I could never grasp. Their land is pillaged and their children are enslaved in sweatshops for our coffee shops and Gap stores. Its easy for the well off to condemn others to an eternity of torment, after all they have already condemed them to a lifetime of torment. Capitalism makes me sick. Its pure exploitation and no matter what you say about the American Dream, its total bullshit.      None of us are free while others are enslaved.     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Organized religion is not beneficial to society. It will always be a tool of the rich and powerful. The politicians pretend that they are astute, god fearing christians (or muslims, or jews, or hindus depending on area) because it keeps us peons in line. They expect their citizens to be good little cult fanatics and do what God says and to follow the rules, otherwise we will burn in hell forever. Of course, most leaders themselves don't really believe in this archaic crap, but it looks good in the public's eyes since we've had it shoved down our throats for so long. And it comes in handy for starting wars too. The now popular Jihad is one example,the crusades an older example. Bush says he does what Jesus tells him to. The anti-communist and anti-anarchist feeling in America I'm sure has as much to do with religion as it does with the political system. "What, the commies don't believe in God? Oh my, they are evil satan-loving fools!" And seperation of church and state is a joke. Homosexual marriage is boycotted because the religious right says that God hates gays.Stem cell research is eliminated because its wrong to use fetuses to save lives, because of how sacred life is, (forget the death penalty though, death row inmates arent sacred, only some people are.) "In God We Trust," the state decides for us that we believe in God. Total Bullshit. It makes me so mad, and to think that I used to be a good little Christian. Fucking depressing. I'm ranting, aren't I?     We are not good and we are not free if we do things because we are told to and because we fear. We are only good human beings when we do things out of compasion and because we want to do them. Taking orders from some supreme being is even more ridiclous then obeyeing other human beings in the form of the boss and the Government. Religion makes Government easier to swallow.     Bakunin once said,"The first revolt is against the supreme tyranny of theology, of the phantom of God. As long as we have a master in heaven, we will be slaves on earth." This more or less sums up anything I can say on the matter. We need to look for heaven on earth and we need to be our own gods and we need to follow our own, personal ideas.      No Gods, No Masters! 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           I was outside yesterday night, altering a stop sign simply by spray painting WAR under the word STOP, (for those of you with very little cognitive abilities, it now reads STOP WAR) when a man in a truck pulled up next to me and started threatening to call the pigs on me. Spying the upside down American Flag and the black and red Anarchist Flag that I had sewn onto my shirt, he told me to "get a job and trash your fucking chaos." Well, I would have stayed and debated politics with him, but I didn't feel like being arrested, so I ran. It seems that the American public has a very skewed view of Anarchist theory. Well, though I doubt the angry truck driver will read this, I hope this will clear up many people's misperceptions about Anarchy.     1) What is Anarchy?     First of all, to all those Hot Topic idiots out there with your coroporation-made Anarchy t-shirts, you're gonna be dissapointed. Anarchy is not chaos and destruction, it is not Nihilistic. Anarchy is a peaceful political philosophy based on the belief that human kind, being social animals, does not need to be ruled to function properly, and that government only serves to widen the schism between rich and poor and to make life chaotic. An Anarchist society would be a peaceful, autonomous and (most likely) small collective, which makes decisions in a purely democratic way, by the popular vote. No one's actions would be discouraged unless they were harmful to others. Property would be publicly owned, and economic barriers would be removed. Instead of a boss making production decisions, the workers would collectively make these choices. There are no police, because since all property is public, there is be no reason to steal or to kill. People would be encouraged to find ways of dealing with personal disputes on their own, but if neccessary, a public meeting is held and the matter is resolved through the popular vote. (Please keep in mind that this is very brief, and there are many different ways an Anarchist society can be structured. If you are interested, the internet has countless resources on this subject, a good starting point would be  urlLink infoshop.org  or  urlLink flag.blackened.net .)   2) But aren't Anarchists violent and brutal at  protests?   That depends whether or not you think that property destruction is violence. We Anarchists do not believe that the elimination of corporate brainwash in an attempt for peace can be considered violence or brutality. And as far as hurting innocent civilians at rallies and protests, I think you will find that it is the police (the tools of the State) who are responsible for the injuries of civilians due to the use of pepper spray, rubber bullets, billy clubs, tear gas, and tasers. Most people fail to realize that Anarchists are responsible for many peacful orginizations, such as "Food not Bombs", and "Schools not Jails".   3) Wouldn't an Anarchist society be a breeding ground for a  militant government takeover?  It is true that early human history saw the development of government, not for protection but to steal resources from more peaceful societies. However, we feel confident that such a hostile takeover would not be aloud in a modern anarchist society because human society is much more complex and human beings have become socially superior to the early man. Because of public ownership, it would be very unnecessarry to steal from another community, as one would merely need to ask and what could be spared would be gladly given him or her.  Well, I hope this sufficiently cleared up at least some of your misperceptions. If you have any questions you can research them at the websites listed above which also contain a great resource of anarchist/radical links, or you can email me @  urlLink X_AugustSpies_X@hotmail.com    Smash the State!      
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Ahhhh, sad but true, punk music has, for the most part, bit the dust. Pretty much all thats left of the once original and innovative scene is a bunch of Hot Topic look alikes who bitch about their wealthy upbringing. Fuck them, they are total bullshit. I'm sick of hearing Good Charlotte's singer whine about how he misses daddy, and about how bad his parent's divorce was. More than 1/2 of America's  married couples get a divorce, get over it. My parents are on the verge of leaving eachother, but am I trying to make some money off of their marital troubles? Hell no, because unlike these preppy posers that are so popular today, I don't make music for money. Do you think Johnny Rotten would bitch about how hard his Irish working class upbringing was? Hell no. Could you imagine Sid Vicious rummaging through Hot Topic looking for some over-produced  Simple Plan t-shirt? Hell  no. If you're gonna call yourselves a punk band, get it right guys. Make you're own clothes, be rude, be politically incorrect, be outragous, spit on people, be loud, be original and DON'T BE GENERIC.  All the great punk bands had their own special thing, The Sex Pistols couldn't play a note but had amazing stage presence and really got the fans to go crazy, the Clash were influenced by reggae, the Dead Kennedys had an awesome surfer sound, the misfits rambled on about alien invasions, rapeing mothers and killing babies. Good, original shit. And what do Simple Plan, Blink 182, Good Charlotte, Bowling for Soup, Sum 41, etc... have? The same old recycled pop shit. They harmonize about girlfriends and how being upper middle class is so hard. Fuck you  preppy bands, you got me all pissed off now. I'm gonna go spray paint all the stop signs now, just because you got me all worked up.... assholes.   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Well, I'm back, you lucky bastards. I didn't do that much today, I slept in late and then sat around reading. Reread the Communist Manifesto for the millionth time, tooks some notes on it for an essay im going to write. What many people fail to realize is that there has never been a communist country. The USSR, North Korea, China, Cuba, were never communist. Communism is defined by collectivism and ownership by the public. In these countries, the resources were managed by an elite few ruling the state. This could be defined as a socialist oligarchy, but not as marxist communism. Yeah, well thats what the essay will be about. I will probaly post the essay in my blog when I am done.      Today I realized that I am very very close to being a legal adult. In about a year, I will be 18. This means alot of things, added responsbilities, financial indepedence, possiblity of being drafted, the power to vote (... well it isnt really a power, its meaningless, all you get is a decision between the evil of two lessers), a whole bunch of stuff changes. I am afraid of getting older. Not because I'm afraid to die, but because im afraid of getting sucked into the corporate machine and giving up on my goals. I do not want to become another gear, another number. I want to be original. I do not want to be tied down with work, with tradition, with obedience. I want to be free. I sincerely hope that my life does not be about the paycheck. I hope I will be strong and resist the brainwashing techniques that we are fed everyday. I know that if I want to change the world I have to start with my self. I cannot expect others to protest for me, to fight for me, to die for me. I need to be the activist, the soldier. I cannot sit back in my comfortable suburban house with my preporccessed family and boring music and wish I had done something about the world. I need to Revolutionize myself if I want to revolutionize my world. Let the spirit and fervor of the revolution be with you.    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             Hey, this is my first post. Not too much going on right now, i'm just finishing up an article for a local newspaper, "The Voice". It's a free paper, and it will print any article that community members send in, so i suppose it's best described as a printed public forum. The article im currently working on is about the lies spread by the authorities before a large protest and the mistreatment that activists are faced with because of the police force. It will be the first I've written for The Voice and I plan on writing alot for the paper, if they will have me. Anyways, I'm going to go and e-mail my little essay to the editor, so I'll post something new tommorrow.      Solidarity, rebels.    August Spies        
    
</post>


</Blog>