<Blog>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am the fifth child in a family of six.  My father passed away when I was almost five.  At the time my oldest sister was 13.  My mom did not speak any English but somehow managed to send all of my sisters and me to college.  She did this by "cheating the system"--collecting welfare payments while working under-the-table as a seamstress.  The gunning of the sewing machine was a familiar sound in the Tran household.   My family is an island.  We keep to ourselves.  Rarely do we look outside for support.  This is a survival trick my mom has passed along to my sisters and me.  She did not have a financial/emotional support system when my father died so she learned how to rely on herself.  If you are strong internally, it does not matter if the world around you goes crazy/falls apart.  To some, this may seem like a defensive and protective outlook.  To me, it is code to live by.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm writing my story on my 23rd birthday and as i reflect on my 23 years of life many stories come to mind. For some reason three years ago, August 10, 2001, sticks out in my mind. I turned twenty and was a year away from the legal drinking age. August 10, 2001, started as out as any other birthday. I was about to embark on my junior year of college and I went home for the traditional carne asada and cake. As I walked through the door of my room at my moms house I noticed a card from my mom waiting for me atop my bed. The card said the following: "Rudy I wish you a ver happy 20th birthday, you've become a very strong, ambitious, and beautiful young man right before my eyes, your positive outlook on life has gotten you this far, although you still have a few years to go and some obsticles you might have to challenge you can count on my love and support to lean on, may you accomplish all that your heart desires in life. Keep reaching for the stars and one more thing to remember; if you want to make somebody's day flash your colgate smile, it's like sunshine on a cloudy day." I broke down in tears just like I am as i write this.  For twenty years my mom never showed me the much needed support and love that i needed, especially when it was most needed during my first year at college as a first generation college student. I thought about all the phone calls and visits home in search of love, support and validation. I've beeen through a lot, that's a whole another story. People always tell me how did become this sensitive, caring, compassionate person especially having gone through some of the things that I have been through. It was moments like the aforementioned one that have shaped me as a person who gravitates towards positions in life as nurturer and mediator. As I look back on my relationships, they number very few. But, the ones that i do have are very deep and meaningful. I consider my audience apart of those few deep and and meaningful relationships i have. Some of the teachers that I had are included as well. Mrs Hendrickson, my music teacher in middle school, introduced me to the world of music and ignited in me a passion for music. Mrs Saucedo, my Spanish teacher from high school, helped me regain the Spanish tongue that I lost along my educational trek. Mrs. Allert, my high school government teacher, was the reason I majored in history and encouraged me to seek out my history. Last but not least, there was Dr. Garcia. Dr. Garcia was my speech professor in college. He came to this country when he was 18. He was placed in special ed classed because he knew no English. He later earned a swimming scholarship to pepperdine and was the first Mexican to attend that school. He later earned a fellowship at Temple University in Philladelphia and earned his Ph.D. He was a great inspiration to me. Had it not been for his truthful, and at times painful comments my writing would have not improved. He had high expectations for me and he supported me along the way spending countless hours going over my term papers with me-word-by-word. The countless hours spent bullshiting in his office, coffee dates, and dinners, didn't hurt either.  I'm not sure if what i just wrote makes sense, but i hope you are able to connect to some part of my story and in the process able to connect with me.    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Partners,      It's good to have you here. I wanted a place where we could meet that wall all our own, a sacred space that was open all the time, somewhere where you could let down your hair (if you got any), sit down, relax, kick off your shoes and put up your feet, as long as they don't stink. But even if they did I'd forgive you, as long I knew you were being yourself...whatever that is. Bring it. Here, on this tiny corner of the world, the professional meets the personal, street smarts bisect book sense, and "common" sense is all in your head, like "crazy." Sometimes you'll feel like a nut...Sorry, ain't much I can do about that. Comes with the territory. But, like Toni Morrison said, "Even crazy people got reasons." It's the ones who don't think I'm worried about.       Some people say I spend too much time in my head, that I thinktoo much, that I should get out more often. Maybe. Maybe not. I'm willing to find out at least. That's what this all about - this place. I wanted to find us somewhere where the thinking never stops, and where we can stop being ourselves...safely. Not that there's anything wrong with you and I, see, it's just good sometimes, I think, to see things from where other people sit, try on someonelse's shoes for size, see how they fit.      I wear a size fourteen and I'm clumsy as hell, so don't be surprised if I trip or fall flat on my face. I fuck up all the time. I cuss a lot too. I don't mean nobody no disrespect. How I was raised, in my family, you had to know how cuss to communicate. It was a highly useful and necessarry skill, not something somebody sat you down and showed you, something you had to pick up on your own, listening. My uncles - Hubbard, Junebug, Pete, Paul, and Larry - made art out of cussing each other out, but neither one of them was as good as their daddy, and he, I don't think, was as good as Grandma Beverly, though sometimes it was a tie. Down in the Bottom, where they stayed, they'd go toe to toe for three rounds or all day or until my grandmother called truce. They loved each other; they just couldn't stand each other. So when Grandma Beverly told him to get the hell out her house, his feelings weren't hurt at all. He gladly packed his shit up and carried the conversation and his wife and seven kids to the house across the street. Only six of them came from him, but he claimed all of them as his own. My mother was the second oldest, right after Hubbard, the bastard, though nobody call him that to his face and few knew he wasn't really Sam's son.       Besides learning the nuances inherent in language (like the diference betwen saying, "Shit!" and "Shiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiit"), another thing I picked up and passed on was my mother's stories. I am the sum of the stories, heir to their passions and beliefs and the dreams they speak. I am my family's Dreamkeeper.One of the criteria on which your performance as a Partner will be assessed is how well you "Engage[s] others in a way that creates dialogues and promotes mutual understanding." Here, and all year, we're going to explore, among other things, what it means to be a "Dreamkeeper" and to do this work - how to do this work. Unlike the home language I learned, some of it I'll tell you how to do. The rest of the shit we'll co-construct together. I'll make you promise. I'll watch my mouth as long as you promise to open yours. I want to know what you're thinking. What's on your mind matters most, as long as it's connected to the work. Crossing the intersection of personal and professional, though necessary to get where we're going, is a fine line to walk, and can be hazardous at times. But if you - I mean we - follow the rules of the road (speak your truth, stay engaged, assume good intent, and our other collective agreements), it'll be alright and we'll get to where we're headed. That's not to say that we won't get lost along the way (and if you riding with me and Melissa its apt to occur a few times, no matter how hard The Black Man and The Black Woman try.)      I told you I was crazy, or did I? Either way that's me. Now, who you?             Please complete the following tasks. (All future tasks can be found in the posting titled, "Tasks.")         Task #1   Create a username and profile. (Follow the online instructions at  urlLink http://www.blogger.com/ ) Use the following format to create your username:  FirstNamePartner . (For example, my first name is Corey, so my username is CoreyPartner, no space between your first name and the word Partner.) Complete your profile. (Fill in or leave out what you choose.)        Task #2   Create a  new posting  titled   FirstNameStory  . (Follow the online instructions for posting. Rememebr, for this task you are creating a new posting (not making a comment or a new blog.) For your first post, I want you to tell me a story. The story may or may not be about you, but it has to be real, meaning 1) it has to be true and 2) it must say something about you, whether we get it or not. Right now, the point is just to listen. Please publish your story by Friday, 5:00PM August 13.      Task #3   Read your team members' story, and post a  comment  in the form of a question about something that strikes you about the story. (For examples of the different kinds of questions to ask, see this website:  urlLink http://www.kn.pacbell.com/wired/21stcent/lgener.html ) Ask 1-3 questions. It is up to each individual Partner whether or not to respond to anyone's questions.  It is not an expectation to respond to anyone's story  (and please, make no assumptions if someone does or does not respond to your inquiry). The point is for us to "sit" and "be" with the question. Again, you are only required to read and post to your team members' story. Reading and responding to anyone else's story, including minr, is optional. In the future, you wil be expected to engage in an online dialogue, by repsonding to each others posts. (Details on this process are forthcoming.) If you have any question, please email me or see me in person. I look forward to hearing your truth, and doing this work together.      
    
</post>


</Blog>