<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them.   Walt Disney   Being that said, just make sure the vehicle you choose to get there is right. If you are an IBO or some one who is approached by Quixtar / Amway, let me very humbly suggest you to visit the following websites. It may help you to understand it a little better. It's good to do some homework!   urlLink amquix.info   urlLink mlmsurvivor.com   urlLink formerdiamond.com   urlLink webraw.com/quixtar  and a forum  urlLink webraw.com/quixtar/forum/index.php   I have been an IBO in Quixtar. I won't say anything pro or anti Quixtar here, I just think that it's your right to have necessary facts to make an informed decision.   Don't let any body steal your dream. Don't let anybody fool ya as well! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Bush (Jason) - Failed to protect his citizens, despite the clear warning.  - Bloodshed in Afghanistan, Changed their government who was never a threat to US security. - Disaster in Iraq, over nothing. - Hundreds of dead U.S. troops since the "end of combat operations" in Iraq. - Like Jason, IQ of 70  Kerry (Freddy) - Supports Israel, who has occupied Palestine and has done unspeakable crimes against humanity. - Voted for war in Iraq - Voted for Patriot Act  - Above two implies that like Freddy, he needed Jason to do some killing for him. - Like Freddy, Kerry can talk, and articulate a plan  Imran Aziz at Tuesday, July 27, 2004 3:29 PM  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         A life spent making mistakes is not only more honorable, but more useful than a life spent doing nothing.    urlLink George Bernard Shaw    Quixtar critics are usually called losers who just can't make it and now they are trying to stop every body else. Let me tell you my another  "failure  " .  We started a vending machine business in year 2000. We bought a franchise for $30, 000 CAD including 17 vending machines and got them installed in different malls. Our parent franchise went bankrupt, left us with no marketing etc. This business generated $100 / month on average for 2 years, and then we took the machines off. We lost $30,000.     We joined Quixtar; quit it in less than a year, lost around $10k in it.    But I am not angry about 30, 000 we lost in vending machines business. Not at all. Sure, loss is 3 times than Quixtar. And I am fiercely angry at Quixtar. I’ll try to explain the reasons.    1) There’s still hope we can sell that business. Because we OWN it. That was a franchise, so is Quixtar, as they say it is. Can we sell our Quixtar business?   2) We were never told in the vending machine business that we can make millions. Just some extra hundreds. In Quixtar promises were simply outrageous that now I am wondering how people get fooled into it? Well! Humans tend to trust each other.    3) Our first and only expense on the vending machine business was CAD $30,000. We had to buy material, but its price was very nominal. And we knew about it! In Quixtar, a person signs up thinking $350 (CAD) is the only cost but monthly expenses reaches around $1000. And this is  excluding  redirection from Food basic / Wal-mart.    $60 STO $24 opens $100 / month (6 trips to US, one trip cost AT LEAST $200) 300 PV => $650 extra (300 PV is actually $750 but I subtracted $100 I saved by avoiding Wal-Mart) Shipment, GST + PST on product = $50 $100 extra fuel $21 Kate $10 website -------------------- = $1015 / month (extra)     Are prospects told this is the running cost of quixtar business, assholes?     4) When the vending machines business was dying, our expenses reduced. Less material sold means less material need to be bought. Same goes with time required. In Quixtar, both remains the same, rather increase since SOBs (Sons of bitches) push more tapes on you.  5) We didn’t have to cash-in our relationships to make profit in vending machine business. In Quixtar, family and friends are the first one for STP.    6) We didn’t think about vending machines  all the time . We, however missed no opportunity to talk to the strangers for Quixtar, and were busy listening / talking to upline / downline for rest of the time.    7) We never felt guilty in vending machine business for not making enough sales, and no one tried to make us. No body neither insulted us, nor begged us. We were not supposed to do these things as well.    8) There was no fucking quota to meet.    9) We didn’t have to go to any association in our or other country to  'learn the business' . And don’t get me started on those damn associations. I’ve written about them in my previous posts.    10)   For vending machine franchise,  I don’t have to worry that there are other people out there loosing money in this scam. It was just a business which, for some genuine reasons did not work. Maybe if I sell it to some body that has enough resources, this might work.     I'll try to summarize it. I don’t feel bad if I didn’t succeed in a legal business. I do feel guilty, angry and embarrassed when I’m been scammed, and I am used to scam other people.    Let me know if I should think differently. Should I be angry at my failure at vending machine business as well? Should I feel ok with Quixtar? And why?   It seems to me that loss of time and money is not that big a deal. $30K / 10 hours a week for 2 years vs $10K / 25 hours a week for less then a year. Both are losses, yet I'm quite ok with one and so not with the other.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       As long as the world shall last there will be wrongs, and if no man objected and no man rebelled, those wrongs would last forever.     urlLink Clarence Darrow     They said: You build this business with accountability. Stay accountable to your group. If you promise your upline that you’re going 1000 PV, do it. If you promise your downline to STP for them, do it.  Translation: Ok I’m back from puking. First these weasels tell you the power of spoken word and make you commit to a promise. They say it won’t happen until you say it. Now when you say it, you have to do it. And doing it means beg, rob or steal, do the required PV.   Didn’t we deserve any accountability, assholes?   We were told that you’ll go platinum via 6-4-2 in 4-6 months. We were told your friends or family definitely gonna join this; it would be either you or some other IBO who approached them first so we better hurry. We were told it’s a very simple business and any body can do it in spare time. We were told it’s a joke to do 300 PV.  Yeah right! $800 is a joke. How can you see yourself in mirror? What are you feeding your kids? Blood sucked out of people who were methodologically deceived  into trusting you ?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, you heard it; Imran can prove Quixtar doesn’t suck, contradicting every thing that Quixtar critics have said. Pack up your bags, commie liberals.  Imran has received numerous unanimous emails, some he read when he was awake, and some when he was not. Also, Jesus, Moses and God have directly spoken to Imran and Imran has enough facts that he can prove  Quixtar does not suck .  So all red commie liberals, blue ex-IBOs, green tree huggers, white radical fundamentalists, black urak hais, dark ringwraiths, yellow journalists, stupid fat hobbits and dumbass IBOs, behold! Imran is going to reveal the truth upon earth.   urlLink Click here  for a proof that  Quixtar doesn’t suck .  If you don't have a javascript browser, go Diamond so you can afford a non-amish machine. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I have never killed a man, but I have read many obituaries with great pleasure.        urlLink Clarence Darrow     They Say:  In these seminars, all diamonds get together to teach the IBOs. These seminars are very important as you’ll get a boost in your business after attending them. If you don’t then you’ll never grow.   Translation:  Let’s say 20,000 IBOs attended FED. And Lets say they pay ticket of $85 / head. This equals to $1,650,000. This will be distributed in 20 or so diamonds, every one taking a hefty share.  Diamonds give you a code to book the hotel room. They buy rooms at cheaper price and sell you, some times more than the regular rent. Every diamond has their own code used by their team. I’ll quote a buddy of mine DMM from  urlLink quixtarblog  here who has done some convention work:  I've done some convention work, and you would be surprised what kind of deals you can make, especially if you are willing to go in the off-season. If you can guarantee and deliver just 10 hotel rooms, most hotels will give you a 25% discount per room and a free suite. If you can guarantee 100 rooms, you are talking about 50% off advertised rates and several free suites. At 4 people/room, we are only talking about a convention of 400 people. If a room is advertised at $120/night, even at a discounted price of $75/night, if a diamond charges each participant $50/night, he is getting $200/night for a room that only costs him $75. Multiply by one hundred rooms, and it can add up to a nice chuck of change, not to mention, the diamond gets his room for free!  And yes, many facilities will waive rental costs, including hotels and other venues. Simply, more money can be made with concessions (why do you think you can't take your own food in with you) and/or parking. Some cities might even waive a fee for a cut of what is sold on the property during the convention (tools and other crap sold at functions).  I suggest next time you hear of a function and of the costs, call up the hotel where they are staying and ask what the advertised rates are for the same time period (or do some web searching on Expedia/Travelocity/etc.) and see what rate you can get. Also ask how much the rooms would cost if were going to get 10 rooms? 25 rooms? 100 rooms? Just say you are doing some convention research. You will find that the diamonds charge outrageous room prices. At similar hotels, IBO's are paying for a weekend, what I used to get for a full week (including weekend) for a room. The difference? I was working with a non-profit that did not overcharge and keep the difference, whereas the big pins are.  Also, there are many times when the city will allow you to use their convention center or stadium for free because of all the business generated through the functions (hotels/car rentals/food, etc). Many people confirmed this. Which means, whatever we are paying, hotel + seminar ticket, most of it is going straight in diamonds pocket, as they hardly have to pay for any expense.  And now, what is in these seminars any way? Same hype? You pay so much money to hear the same crap over and over again? They compare it to college, BULL CRAP. In college you study new thing EVERY day.  You go ealry, sleep late. If you are eagle, you gotta skip one night sleep. Rush for the seat. Laugh at same old stupid jokes. Stand up, clap and hear same stories again. And the numbers, how mnay people who go to these seminars make it up on stage? Most of them are not there next time any way. And here is a big secret. Many people on stage are not currently qualified diamonds either. A Big whoop!  urlLink Click here to find out the truth.   I have a better idea. Instead of going to a seminar, take your girlfriend / wife out for camping. If you are young and healthy, canoe up to an Island if you can. Leave computers, movies and books all distractions behind. Take enough food for 2,3 days and just be with her. Talk to her. Re-connect. Enjoy what you have and realize you have something so precious. You'll feel better than a diamond on your way back. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know I have to complete the Quixtar info series I started but I am getting the revelation now ... what can I do?  So here is the most honest Quixtar plan. I challenge you to find a more honest Quixtar plan on earth! And it’s brief too. Trust me! I had seen 2 hours long plans. As much as I hate you, I would never do that to you.  So here it goes:   The Plan   Hello guys. My name doesn't matter, so is yours. I'm here to explain you the Quixtar plan. That’s right, Q-U-I-X-T-A-R, the same shitty company, illegitimate child of pimpish Amway.    I won't waste your time in a ridiculous dream building mumbo jumbo. I know you’re greedy all right. Here is a circle, that’s you.  Now all you have to do is pimp out your friends and family. When you run out of them you gotta find the other suckers. Y'all know this world is full of suckers who are as greedy as you are and will come running when they’ll hear money. Now you find some losers and bring them to the meeting. Some morons will join you, some won't. How many jackasses do you know?   A List:  Ok let’s start how to pimp out your friends and family first. This is easy stuff as you already know their weaknesses. What about your sister who just got divorced and looking for an opportunity to meet people? And your uncle Joe, who talks to himself since his wife died? How about your mom and dad who are way too lonely since you don't give a shit about them anymore? They'll do anything to have your company won't they? Just get their butts on the seat and any moron will be happy to kiss their asses and sell them this shit. You follow up with them and there is your pimping out part. Harass, beg or yell, get those retards sign up.   B List:  How about your colleagues who just got laid off? They’ve got some good severance shit and very eager to invest it wisely. Get them! Tell them to bring their portfolios etc. They'll come running! Invite them to the conference. You know they got the money to go there. After the conference those idiots will have no choice since they’ve spent most of their severance. Now they got to screw other people to get their money back. Sweet eh! And remember these seminars are where the gold is hidden! Seminars, books and tapes.   C List:  By the time you have screwed these people, you'll be a real tough sunuvabitch ready for the fresh meat. Go to the mall. Look out for the snobs wearing good dresses and fat wallets. Find an excuse to chat with them. Aim is to get their phone number. Hide if you have to, and corner them when you can so they have to talk to you. Don't let them go until they give you their phone numbers. Then call them. Don't EVER put the phone down until they agree to meet you. Now show them the plan!   Training:  How to further squeeze these ass holes? Simple! Same cycle again, pimp em out till they order! Beg, harass or yell and beat the PV out of them! Keep selling seminars, tapes and book. Those are shitty alright, but they'll keep the suckers longer.  Smart ones of these morons will start doing what you are doing, i.e. pimping other ppl out and squeezing their wallets by beating the PV out of them.  You got to have a real tough skin, be a stubborn sunnuvabitch and teach other people to be the same.  I won't waste your time in showing you the numbers, as they all are in that stupid looking file I gave ya. As much as I doubt your intelligence, I know you can understand those numbers. It's a pyramid, idiot! As simple as that. And if you haven't figured out yet, products are just a decoy. Tapes, book and seminars are the real money maker. You need to move enough products to qualify for that(tool) money. Get more ppl to go on top, and suck their blood as long as you can. Be a Dracula, go Diamond. Don't EVER tell any body about the return policy of the tools! It's just to keep the feds away.  Now, sign up, pah-lease! Else I won't let ya go......
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        As long as the world shall last there will be wrongs, and if no man objected and no man rebelled, those wrongs would last forever.         urlLink Clarence Darrow     They say:  Books make you a better person. The moment you stop learning, you stop growing. Not all the readers are leaders, but all the leaders and readers. Tapes: There are conferences all over the North America all the time. One can’t be at all conferences, so BWW releases tapes so every one can benefit from them. Be on standing order, one book a month and one tape a week program. This is an eagle step and it will help you a lot to build this business.              Translations:  SCAM! Cost of production of a tape, $1 CAD MAX! They charge $10. They get books at discount from Amazon as they order in bulk, and sell you at retail.  Try ordering 1000 books from Amazon, and see how much discount you get! They charge you much more than that price. Standing order is $50 - $70 CAD / month. FTC said any product which has no end customers should not be sold to the participants. I’d venture to say 70 – 80 % of diamond income come from the tools.  When I was in the business, none of the weasels told me the return policy of this dumb shit. I didn’t know so I didn’t tell my downline. After I joined  urlLink http://www.quixtarblog.com  then I learned BSMAA return policy. Many poor people are forced to sell these items on eBay. Scroll down  urlLink http://amquix.info/  and see the tapes on sale in eBay. It reflects the hard earned income, lesser kids meals and missed husband wife fun. Help your business, my ass.  Many IBOs, who are still in, says that these books make you a better person etc. Listen dumb ass, who the fuck is criticizing books? It’s the push and rip-off I am talking about. If those blood suckers want the best for you, why on earth they are charging you retail on the books which they get in discount?   And tapes: What they do: Promote system / products and demote EVERY thing else. They bash jobs, outside business friends and family, other businesses, every thing. How are they helping on any thing other than the business?  Oh and are they helping in the business? Tell me the numbers. Tell me, how many people who are listening to tapes make profit? Or even break even. Tell me how according to their tax returns. Not the net income box, the profit box. Are they in red or above it? Back it up with solid numbers.       Fact:  Majority, I’d say 99% have lost time and money on them.      Fact:  Millions have lost Billions because of this scam.      Fact:  People profiting for tool business are sick blood suckers who’ll not hesitate to steal your kids meal if it ‘need to be done’ and will screw their own mother by pushing tapes on her.    To be continued... 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am writing three part ‘info’ what is required by an IBO. First one will explain the  9 core steps . Second will explain the  time required to be an IBO , 3rd one will explain the  expenses of an IBO .  Nine core steps are being taught to every IBO. Any one serious building this business should do these steps. This involve time, and money! Nobody has earned any money from Quixtar without having a team following these steps, or most of these steps. I haven't seen any body being able to get enough bonus by avoiding them. People who are following these core steps are called  CORE . Whatever your targets are, either to make millions or just have a second income, these core steps are a must.    You won't make any money if you don't have a downline doing most of these steps. And to have your downline doing it, you have to do them.    So here are the 9 core steps. I’ll divide them in two entries.    1) STP (Show the plan, share the plan)    They say:  To show the plan 3-5 times a week. This STP could be either to your prospects or to your downline’s prospect. Unless you start showing the plan yourself, not many people will join you. Your worst plan is the one you did not show and your best plan gonna be the next one. Showing the plan is done by 3 ways: Invite prospects to the open, one-on one or home meeting.   Translation:  At least 4 evenings of your week are gone. These 3-5 plans mean ‘your’ prospect, your downline prospects are after that. Those are also very important as you won’t retain any downline if they don't have any further downline. To show 3-5 plans, you have to QI as well, which will take further 1 or 2 evenings. You have to prospect people in Mall / Church / Mosque to add people to your ‘List’. I’ll describe the time required later in  time required to be an IBO.    2) 300 Personal PV.     They say:  Any one serious in doing the business should do 300 PV. Eat 100, use 100 and sell 100.  Translation:  You GOT to do 300 PV. Upline won’t care if you have sold 100 PV or not. Good luck selling these overpriced items. A friendly suggestion: use SAM, or master retailing eSpring. One eSpring every month is a must! It will bring 270 PV and $200 ish retail profit if you are able to sell it at retail price. Good luck with retailing $900 product as well.    3) Have 10 customers    They say:  Having a customer will finance you expenses in the business.  Translation:  Nobody in your upline will EVER ask you if you have any customers. They will NEVER help you to find them. You are on your own. This rule was enforced just to save Amway from the IRE of law!   4) Association:     They say:  To build this business, you have to associate with people who are building this business. This means: -  A weekly open meeting  where they show the plan in a hotel. Every IBO pays $6 CAD to attend it and bring their prospects. -  QUEST : Quixtar User Education and System Training. QUEST is usually held at some core IBO, higher the better. These are local associations.  Translation:  Same thing is repeated over and over again from different angles,  urlLink cult type mind control.  Books and Tapes are promoted in both, and Products in QUEST only.   To be continued.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       A business that makes nothing but money is a poor business.        urlLink Henry Ford    I dunno, is this business  exploding  or  dying  a slow, painful death? Just surfed in this site  urlLink http://formerdiamond.typepad.com/formerdiamond/  and it said:   In the mid 90’s the company said the “business” had about 7 billion dollars in retail sales. If I am not mistaken that figure, which today  includes all of the Alticor business , is in the $4.5 billion range.      Well, maybe!  One can make some people fool all the times, and all people fool some of the times, but nobody can make all people fool all the times!"  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       A market is never saturated with a good product, but it is very quickly saturated with a bad one.    urlLink Henry Ford   I have seen many critic sites about Quixtar. Almost all of them criticize the  urlLink tool scam ,  urlLink lies told to public , vulture type prospect hunting, invitation to secret….err… open meetings, upline push for volume and tools, overpriced products etc. Oh boy, just type in the word  urlLink Quixtar  in google.com and it will open a can of worms! Don’t forget to visit the second link, its more important than first one ;) First one is behind the password so you can’t do much there. :)     Even some of the critics said that products are good. Overpriced, but good. When I was in the business, I religiously believed so. Like the majority of IBOs does. I’ve left the business, but I’m still in good terms with my sponsor. I was there this Sunday night to return some things (yeah! tapes). I really like that couple. I doubt if they are making any money though, as they go to US for conferences every other month. I really wanted to help them. I heard about XS a lot. I am their client for 2 products (Glister toothpaste, Fuel Freedom) and they give me IBO price. Cool eh!     I asked for XS and bought a Cranberry XS for 2.5 CAD bucks. I was thinking that in office, I have to chug down crapy coffee with a lot of sugar, XS will be cool. Sweet, low in carbs and stuffed with vitamins. I’ll be more healthy and I might be able to help this good couple by promoting it to some of my fat colleagues :)     I tried it when I came home. I wanna sing “Nausea heartburn upset stomach indigestion diarrhea, yea pepto-bismol". Yeah! It tasted so much like it! Pepto-bismol + cough medicine! I asked my sister to taste it. Her taste buds always work opposite than mine. She said the same thing!  And it gets better, after two hours my belly starts speaking “Thump thump thump”. Has any one seen that cute ad?  I don’t know if my stomach got fired up because of XS or not. But taste was crapy for sure. I’m not gonna try another brand, and forget about promoting it! My friends would kill me!  And I remember the products I tried because of the “promotion” of upline. Strawberry shake, vanilla shake, protein bars. A big YUCK! These damn shakes are allergic to water, they doesn’t mix! I bought a Trim advantage shaker glass for 15 bucks, (which should be 3 bucks max) to mix them. Mixing is another story. After some use, it start smelling so bad! Washed it with LOC dish drops, than with name brands. Smell won’t go! And protein bars, don’t get me started! I only liked chocolate coconut food bar.  Also tried Dry-cleaner secret. It DOESN’T clean! Just kills the smell of sweat.  I remember trying ginseng. I was 25 year old and boy! My mojo was un-necessarily high! I’m scared to even name that vitamin now.  Sure, some products are good. I won’t compare them with other name brands. One thing I know, in my self consumption of 300 PV, I was spending $650 extra. Here’s the math.   300 PV = 300 * 2.5 = $750   Redirection saving from wal-mart = $100   Extra money spent   on products     every month    = $750 - $100   = $650   Retail, what retail? We were sponsored by saying that "there is no sales! Just buy for yourself and tell others to do the same". Retail was scorned in every quest by saying that it will not be a repeat business.  Even if you do the recommended retail of 50 PV using client cost it will be:   Retail Revenue = 50 * 3 = 150  I am using $3 / PV as it's client cost.  Extra money spent = $650  - $150 = $500   Good lucks selling Quixtar items at client cost! It's hard enough to sell at IBO cost!   Also, how many people have been in and out of Amway | Quixtar since 1959? According to  urlLink http://amquix.info  it is 40 million. Many of them would have tried some of these products. If products were THAT good and concentrated, won’t they be buying from Quixtar? If they are, than why sales are decreasing from $7B to $4.5 B since 1997? (Source:  urlLink http://amquix.info , Quixtar public releases)  A final note: NO McDonalds owner always eats only from McDonalds! Talk about loyal to your own business! And who is pictured in every secret…err.. open meeting? McDonalds! Founder of franchising! Mr. Ray Crok.   He was a genius, but IBOs are Idiots! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We visited  urlLink Algonquin Provincial Park  last month. It was wonderful! Algonquin has breath taking beauty of Canada, and one can see nature at its purest there. Every time we visit there, we always see a  urlLink Moose . So many activities, so few people. We just love it.  We did make a mistake though. After covering some short trails easily, we took on an 11 km trail. Mainly because this trail had wildlife sighting. First problem we faced was mud! Ground was muddy because of the rain last night and our speed was very slow! My sister was with us, who is not very skilled in such activities. Another problem was mosquitoes. As soon as we started sweating, mosquitoes attacked us. As my 12 year old brother, Bumpi said, "We are all-you-can-eat buffet for mosquitoes".      Bumpi  
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       If you want to make your dreams come true, the first thing  you have to do is wake up.   J. M. Power   Hello all IBOs out there. You guys have some faith! I mean some real serious faith. Can you prove Quixtar works? Can you prove this “Motivational Business” is not a scam? I dare ya! Come to this Forum  urlLink  http://www.quixtarblog.com/forum  and defend the “System”. Invite your diamonds to come there as well. After all, they have all the time in the world don’t they? Ask them to do all IBOs a favor and defend their scam….err business. That is an open forum, and as far as I’ve experienced, no one deletes any post unless it contains profane language. Express yourself there. Prove the critics wrong. Prove Quixtar is not ripping people off. Prove majority of people succeed in Quixtar. I dare ya!     At any give time, 99.9 % of you are losing money. That’s right! I am not talking about those little cheques you are receiving from Quixtar. I’m talking about those cheques – system costs – cost of buying all those expensive products. That’s right, a simple business formula.      Profit = Gross profit – expenses     Don’t tell me you are at this pin level or that ping level. Tell me, how much profit you are making? Calculate all your expenses honestly and tell me, are you making any money? I’ll make it simple. Don’t tell me, tell yourself.     I read in a standing order book: “Definition of insanity is  doing same thing over and over again expecting different result”.     Here is other news! Just one in every 342 IBOs qualified as a  Q12 platinum.      Source: Quixtar reported 1461 Q12's.      Here is what I’ve found in this site:  Can Any Amway/Quixtar’s cult explain any of the following:      Quote from the above site: (Amquix.info)    Chance of becoming a millionaire from Quixtar: 0.022% Total number of Millionaire households in America: 4-6%      Amquix.info Quote: Quixtar seems to be for the people with IQ less than 70 or 60. Otherwise why would the percentage of IBOs who are millionaire is lower than that of the entire US as a whole? One would be much better off by being just another person in the crowd of 270 million people of the US than being an IBO of Amway/Quixtar.    Source:  urlLink http://www.amquix.info   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello guys! As you have seen that I am doing some research on these sneaky MLMs for a while, especially mother of all ...... MLMs, Quixtar. I have came across with some sites which are, or at least claim to be,  Neutral . These websites says that they research mostly neutral people, get an outsider perspective or at least hear from the people who saw the plan first time. Many critics start writing that “I am not a bitter, failed IBO. However…”  What’s wrong with being bitter? Bitter means some one who had a bad experience and now s/he feels he was tricked into something not worthy of time and money. So? For me a bitter or failed person is a much better source of information than any oh-so-precious outsiders, who don’t know jack about Quixtar. Please understand, Quixtar and its AMQOs (BWW etc.) are very secretive. Chances for outsiders knowing something are pretty slim. In their outsider analysis, they skip many things that they never knew and make some blunders.     I am not saying that a bitter person should be the only source of information. However he should not be dismissed altogether. Who would you talk to about suffering of war? A war victim / veteran or some bubbly celebrity who can’t even spell war. (Or at least pretend they can’t)    I am also annoyed by these self righteous hypocritical sneaky fellas called journalists. I have read in many sites owned by journalist that how they dismiss ‘bitter’ IBOs and seek out only for the ‘Neutral’ information about Quixtar. So they can put ‘Neutral’ and ‘Un Biased’ information on their site / newspaper. Oh really! So journalists try real hard to be un-biased? I don’t think so! They do give news a spin. They do express their opinions. How much fucked up CNN is? They make up stories. They spread rumors. They publish whatever sells (non-profit sites are exempt). Do they do it all the time? No. Do they never do it? Nope! I am not making an anti-journalist point, all I am saying is if they can ‘express’ their opinions, what is wrong considering a   failed, bitter  IBOs opinions? I mean what the fuck! For me  Bitter   IBOs opinions value much more than   outsider opinions.     Also, they don’t seem very straight forward to me. I don’t know if they are paid for the words they write or asses they kiss or whatever (with the exemption of non-profit sites). For example, I have not heard a lot of news ppl saying that  War on Iraq was a clear aggression of a superpower against a poor, helpless country who’s dictator was appointed by America itself and he was used many times for the benefit of America!  How many American journalists have said that? All they say is, “Uh…Intelligence gave wrong report…umm Mr. President Almighty did what the report said….guards did not know about Geneva conventions, they did not know forcing prisoners to have sex with each other and taking their pictures is not right. Prison guards did a very tough job…..blah blah God bless America blah blah Long live the Queen blah blah terrorism is bad blah blah oil-ism is good.     Shut the Fuck up! Just say what you, I and the whole world know  pretty damn well! Why are you sugar quoting it?  What you are doing is putting  ketchup on a crap and forcing public to eat it, and say ‘yum’ after it!       Similarly, these same damn journalists (TV and Newspaper ones), apparently knowing the abuses done by Quixtar and it’s daddies, Motivational Organizations, keep putting news, “Quixtar products are good, XS has a new flavor, Quixtar in Spanish, blah blah. Shut the fuck up! It’s like saying  “American soldiers  killed and are still killing many innocent people, but their weapons were not  tested on animals” . If you don’t have any  testicoli , get some backbone at  least!     I know there was a recent media coverage about Quixtar / BWW in dateline. Compare it to the percentage of the ‘positive’ news about Quixtar. Millions losing Billions, press kept dildo in their mouths. Quixtar buys some team or give some charity, dildos are out and cheers are published. All I am asking is, publish the whole picture. Quixtar did something good, publish it. They fooled millions of ppl, publish it! Keep the fucking balance!  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When I look back into my entire Quixtar venture, I find out how  this all was done 'orally'. From prospecting to training, all verbal. It made me  think that why is there so much emphasizes on oral communication. Why I am not  given some written material? There are some written brochures and sites but the  total 'writing' I encountered was less than the words I have written here. And I  am just one person with a job, two cats and a 12 year old brother! BWW alone has  many employees and more than 100, 000 IBOs.  It just seems odd to me that a business who emphasis on saving  time via duplication, and calls its model 'franchising', will expect the IBOs to  do all the talking and no writing / internet. Sure one can't completely avoid  talking; specially the sales guys, but just get some balance here.  There are many advantages from an IBO point of view of keeping the business  'Oral'.           No record of outrageous claims          Intimidation           Ease to avoid hard questions          Building and manipulating friendships          Peer pressure        These tactics were used on us and many other ppl. When I talk to  my sponsor, I respect his age (he is as old as my father). I have a hard time  telling him he is involved in a scam. I also end up agreeing with him to stop  the conversation. When I told I quit, my upline kept talking to me on the phone  for 1.5 hours. I was at work! Finally I said ok I'll go to the seminar and I’ll  do whatever you want me to do. Which I didn't :) But the point is, if someone  just keeps talking, the other person will surrender with a lame excuse as s/he  would be bored as hell!    Also, after realizing I had no receipts for tapes, seminars etc.  (BSM Return policy eh!). I now understand why!! I can't even file a complaint  claiming my upline said this. I have no proof!     I love email and written material. I can copy | paste and reply  it very easily, at my own CONVENIENCE. I can think well before answering and my  answer will not be based on intimidation, pressure, emotion or boredom. Well,  mostly! I can back up my claims with URLs. I may also ask for proof / stats and  research on them easily.     IBOs are fed with so much tape talk. They use it day in day out  while a normal person need some time to prepare his / her response. Which is not  so easy in 1-1 conversation.     Another thing is friendship. Human beings, at least me has a  weakness to avoid direct confrontation to an apparently friendly person. I seek  out to find a mutual ground where we both can agree so I can get the hell out :)  In writing I find myself brutally honest and questioning every thing, including  myself.     I am becoming quite a fan of open discussion forums. I dare ya  all IBOs!! COREs, Eagles, Platinums, Diamonds and CAMs.  Start an open  discussion forum . Invite EVERY ONE there. Moderate profane language only but  that's it. On second though, no. Don't even moderate that. Some one using  profane language just make himself look bad. Let every one know about that  forum, and then prove them wrong. Can you? Can you hold yourself their? Are you  a winner big enough? Are you secure enough? I am challenging ya!    
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
                 A kiss is a lovely trick designed by nature to stop speech when words  become superfluous.   Ingrid Bergman     I don't know why I quoted this stupid quote :) Not all quotes  make sense.     For a while, I was thinking about my involvement with Quixtar, and I was wondering "Who I have a problem with?" Quixtar? Or BWW? My upline or my sponsor? I would be objective here:     Quixtar     They are basically a portal on which people build their businesses. I actually don't have any beef with them. I'd try to be even more objective, so here it goes:     Pros         Excellent products: They are 20-50% more expensive but it was upline + BWW push to do 300PV, not them. They even have average IBO income stated and have 50 PV retail rule. Good old Shoppers Drug Mart is also quite expensive, so I don't have a problem here.         Customer Service: I have not received better customer service anywhere else! Their buy back guarantee is awesome, I’ve returned a lot of items :)           Cons     They turn a blind eye to all the abuses done by BWW and other Motivational organizations. In their response to the NBC Dateline segment, they defended themselves, not BWW or other QMOs (Quixtar motivational organizations) while no one actually attacked them! They refused to appear on Dateline show, while they were given a chance, and put a recorded response way before the dateline show was even aired. I don't know why they are hiding? They should enforce mlm rules more strictly. But as Ken McDonald said to Bo Short, "What would happen to the business"     BWW  urlLink  (Britt World wide )     Pros           Learned public speaking, people skills          Learned very good teachings from books         Cons           An QMO, responsible for doing some not-so-legal stuff i.e. moving a product that has no end customer, like tapes / books / seminars. Their representatives sucked me in, and 'motivated' me to waste money in expensive products. I have a pile of tapes sitting on my home, full with hype and bashing everything other than the "system". Average cost to be a core:        $60 STO + $24 opens + $100 / month (6 trips to US, one trip cost AT LEAST $200) + 300 PV => $650 extra (300 PV is actually $750 but I subtracted $100 I saved by avoiding Wal-Mart) + $50 extra fuel + $21 Kate + $10 website = $915 / month        And my upline said how one could loose money in this business!  Priceless! ($915 x 9 months!)     Upline     Well, I won't talk about my personal experiences with them. If some of my relatives read it, it would be hard for me to refrain them from getting physical against that dude. I'll picture a general, business view of them.      Pros           Drove several time from US to Canada for me          Worked on my prospects          Spent time talking / yelling at me         Cons           Make me spent $900 ish a month, including push for seminars, tapes, leadership tapes and put order on 30th, which is still stocked. I’ve left more than a year now!        I was not told the number and cost of conferences, STO, traveling involved. I should've known so I could make an informed decision.        Brainwashed, or try to brainwash me that system is only thing    good in the world, rest is pure evil.           Put religion second, business first attitude.           When I told I quit, kept talking to me on phone for 1.5 hours    while I was at the office and he was at home          Called me several time on my cell, resulting huge bill,    despite my request not to          Told me FTC approved this business. FTC never stamp on any    business, it just has some guidelines. BWW violates some of them!         Sponsor      Pros       Never pushed me to sign me in, never begged me not to quit  Always calm, cool and nice  Helped me on daily basis  Lend me lit packs, books and tapes       Cons           Lied to me, by giving impression that they are making profit. I really doubt they are making any profit to date, which at least covers their expense. There were $5K worth of tapes in their guest room last time I saw!        I was not told the number and cost of conferences, STO, traveling involved. I should've known so I could make an informed decision.        When I quit, they told me after a month that I was not doing business properly. Dude! I was with you at least one hour daily for a year, why didn't you tell me then? I did whatever you told me!           I have asked about the tools, I don’t know if I could return them. That will be the real test of character. I've yet to see!     So it turns out, I've a beef with QMO, i.e. BWW, not exactly with Quixtar. Well a little with Quixtar. BWW need to make training free and easy. People shouldn't have to spend so much time and money on 'training'. Free Mp3s on net, no seminars will make it much feasible. My system expenses should not be more than $30 a month. Also retail should be taught to IBOs and should be necessary. Self consumption should be discouraged. In fact, 70% of the products should be retailed, as FTC said! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is the name of a BWW tape, not  negative ol me bashing all free enterprise :)    This tape says how ppl doing a JOB are pigs, and they don't know that how stinky job is, as every one around them has a job. So,   Pigs don't know pigs stink .  Let me carry this statement a little further. I won't call who is a pig and who is not, but I'll very humbly try to let the 'pigs' know they stink. Hey you started it! I am using your tape title. After all, you know so many nuggets of wisdom that rhymes and poetic brainy quotes.       So here it goes, p*** don't know that:     	Bill Britt didn't retire, he was asked    to    urlLink    resign .      urlLink    He and Peggy were separated on November 21, 2003 .       urlLink    Why they were separated .       Peggy claims him to have lost over $20    million in fraudulent investment schemes.           urlLink    IBO Hall of Shame , who stinks now eh?    	A Diamond walked away form diamond    ship!  urlLink    http://formerdiamond.com/        urlLink    NBC story about Quixtar  (in the front page of above site)       urlLink    rebuttal Quixtar's response to the show.       urlLink    Quixtar business analysis page       And some data from that page:                           amquix.info quote:                        67.7% of IBOs who registered in 2001, did not renew in 2002.   The average IBO had just 0.23 members and clients registered   Only 18.4% of IBOs registered even one person.   The average IBO had 38.5 PV/month. (100PV is shown in the plan)   65.6% of IBOs never once attained 100 personal PV in the previous 11          months.   21.5% of IBOs had a ditto delivery profile   Only 1.9% of Members and Clients had ditto delivery profiles.   The average PV point cost $2.70.                            And on the same site:    urlLink  http://amquix.info/amway_directly_speaking.html                            Rich DeVos said:                       Now, the tape business, if it is not used as a support for the Amway business, will oftentimes be an illegal business -- in fact, it could be called a pyramid -- because, d -- does not get sold to the consumer. Which means that all the tape business does is take money out of the organization, and because the final person can't retail it, it never brings money into the organization. Now, I'm not arguing about the value of it -- we accept the fact that motivation is vital to this business. Good, honest motivation is important to the business. But, it must be motivation that builds the business -- not become a business in itself.                  
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes, what exactly is wrong with the System (of Quixtar    TM  , e.g. BWW   TM  )?  It gives people opportunity to make money. If some one hasn’t been successful,  s/he should change some thing. After all:    Businesses work, people don't   Ok here is what’s wrong. Quixtar System, in my opinion, is not completely in accordance with FTC rules. "System" teaches it that way. Please read FTC site.   urlLink  http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/alerts/pyrdalrt.htm   And more:  urlLink  http://www.amquix.info/TOD_FAQ.html   In a nutshell, here are my concerns:   Not so legal activity 1:  Does every IBO meet the 50 PV retail rule? My upline told me to report 50 PV as retail. Did I "retail" 50 PV, NO! I was told to lie.   Not so legal activity 2:  In pyramids, a product, which has no value outside the pyramid, should not be sold to participants. What about the "system"? How many retail customers will buy tapes? Quixtar saves its ass by saying it is optional, but "system" tells so is success, and one must be on standing order to show their seriousness. And seminars, oh man! Try to be in good books of your upline while not attending them.   Not so legal activity 3:  If I am behind my quota, I should not be receiving call from some upline to complete my order. I can't retail in last hour! I'll end up stocking. Stocking => Illegal!! I've received such calls. And after a year of quitting, I still have those stocked products, along with the pile of tapes.  I lost time and money in BWW   TM   / Quixtar   TM  . Am I alone? Nope! There are 40  million ppl who have joined and left Quixtar   TM    / Amway   TM   in last 40 years.  There are 400,000 active IBOs in North America. How many of them are making money? I am talking about the profit section of their Income Tax return, not the net income box.  And here is the best: It is a  urlLink negative  some game . At any given time, This Quixtar / BWW pyramid as a whole is losing money. How the top dudes make money? By product movement and system push to their downline. What is the average income of an active IBO? According to Quixtar, $115. And it is a net profit, including bonus coming from one’s own shopping. What is the average expense of the system? STO + expensive self consumed products + Seminars + gas + baby sitting etc. Lets say $300, a very conservative figure. How these guys pay for it? Ironically, Jay Oh Bee. So what is “System” doing? Sucking money into it. As a whole, at any give time, whole organization is losing money. As there are some expenses going outside the system, e.g. travel etc.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today, I contacted an IBO. I asked him a question: "Hey buddy, do you know Quixtar was on TV". He said yeah I watched it. Then he asked me "Are you in Quixtar"? I said no, I quit. He asked "Because of this TV segment?" And he said he is sorry that my life is controlled by TV etc. And I should see Quixtar Facts blah blah and listen to all the responses. One thing really pissed me off when he said there is a lot of negative converge about Islam as well on TV. Will you quit Islam as well?  I had no intention of getting into a debate when I asked him. I just found that segment hilarious. But this ridicules comparison of Islam made me say that please don't compare apples with...blue sky. There is no comparison.  To the all positive people out there, who want to argue with me about TV  credibility, please:   1) Refrain yourself from giving this ridiculous example of religion vs.  Quixtar when we talk about media coverage.   My upline have told me that exact line, it’s a typical Quixtar programmed talk. I could answer it very well. I’ve seen negative sites about religion. They did not shatter my beliefs a single bit. I saw negative sites about Quixtar, and more I read, more I’m convinced that it’s an illegal scam. So what it is? Some sites working some not working? Actually it’s not the sites or TV but it’s the GOD DAMN content there that matters!!  But his example is so absurd that I may give you a psychiatrist’s card you if you say it one more time! It’s like comparing Moon light with bud light or apple with Mount Everest.  Let me give you a better example. Compare business with business. Ask me there is a lot of crap about Microsoft, why I am still using Microsoft products? Answer being: Microsoft products, as evil as they are, are still MORE feasible to me than other software out there. They do, well almost do what they are suppose to do, i.e. deliver the promise. I may not be the happy customer but I am their customer, and I’ll continue to learning Microsoft technologies as long as they help me do my work. As simple as that.  Here is a lesson for you in the above example, quixbots: There is nothing in the world that is perfect, even near to perfection. There are flaws in every invention, limitations in every creation. It is a principle. Fight with me, don’t fight with a principle. How can you be sure that Quixtar is perfect? Your upline is always right? It doesn’t make any sense.   2) Don’t assume I am fighting with you   Dude, I just asked you have you seen this video or not, and you challenged my religious beliefs by your ridiculous example! Its shows some un-security on your side, doesn’t it? Ask me some question about my company, i.e. how stupid our site is. I’d laugh with you! Even I’ve made that site!   3) Don’t defend yourself by attacking credibility of media.   When did I say TV or Internet is all true? It never was and probably never will be. Almost all news are biased, every body gives them a spin. Does it mean every thing they say is false? Nope. Does it mean I am saying that media is always right? Not really! All I’m saying is be objective about the facts in front of you and use your brain! For the record, I quit without reading any negative site and dateline story was aired a year after I quit. I just saw my gains and losses and where was I after a year.   4) I know many lines of Quixtar:   I’ve used them and I’ve been in the q-business. I may not have getting new  teachings but are there really new teachings?   5) Please understand, I don’t get any PV for spreading negative.   I don’t get any pat on the back from any upline by pulling you out. Go ahead and spend all you’ve got. You know your odds? Oh you don’t? 99% chances are you’ll be out in 2-5 years. Wanna bet ;)   6) Please don’t tell me to never complain as I was given an opportunity blah  blah.   There are 400, 000 active IBOs in North America and I bet you every body will be happy to sign me up! Your tone will change the moment I say ok sign me up. Won’t it?  Now let me tell you some facts about dateline story, Quixtar response and  Quixtar facts.   urlLink  Response to Quixtar's Response to the Dateline Exposé of May 7, 2004 by Lindy  and Vicki Mack   Btw I know this guy Lindy, via internet. I discuss with him on almost daily  basis in  Neutral  Discussion about Quixtar   Please read it first then talk to me. I’ve listened to every video you asked in  urlLink http://www.quixtarfacts.com  and I’m impressed with their ability to dodge the complaints. Btw they were given an opportunity to participate in dateline. Why didn’t they do it? Why they video tape them and put it online, like cowards. They were hiding the questions, weren’t they?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         There are two types of people, people who have money and people who have excuses.   Quixtar / BWW tape talk      When I was in the BWW   TM    / Quixtar    TM   business, Diamond lifestyle was my only goal. The only people who appeared successful to me were diamonds, and every body else was a broke looser. I encountered a lot of 'negative' prospects, yet no one was able to give me a logical reason what's wrong with BWW / Quixtar. Reason being they have not done any formal research on it. Even if they did make some point which I couldn't answer, I always said, "How much money do you make, smarty pants! Your lifestyle sucks as compared to the diamonds. If you are so smart, why you are not so rich". Well, i didn't exactly say it but you get the idea. For me they were making excuses and avoiding work. They didn't have enough money to impress me, yet they had a lot of excuses.      To all other people who are in Quixtar    TM   and think like I did, let me tell you a story about a person who did not make any excuses. He was no lazy nose-picker. He was a diamond, and he was rich. He became a diamond in 5 years. Not many people are able to do that.      But then he discovered something. He found that a legal and ethical product business done by a somewhat restrictive MLM model can only generate upto a certain amount of money. Money enough to replace job but certainly not enough to own jets, yachts and palaces etc. Then he found out something else was going on. There are a lot of tools pushed to other people involved in Quixtar   TM  . In fact, one won't be called "serious in the business" if s/he is not on monthly tape and book program, which costs $60 - $80 a month. In fact there are more tapes recommended than that, leadership tapes or fast track tapes. There are seminars almost every month all over US and they are pushed very seriously. These seminars costs at least $80 USD. And cost of hotel &amp; traveling makes them even more. And even paying all those expenses didn't deliver the promise of "success" to a very overwhelming majority. He saw that most people end up loosing some serious money on these "tools". Wait, It gets better! What is in these tapes? What is "taught" in seminars? Almost ALL hype and promoting the "system".      So what he did? He  RESIGNED  from the Diamond ship.  Something a person with integrity and morals should do.     So what am I doing, Am I making up lies? Isn't it what internet  does? spread lies about good organization?      Well, his name was Robert 'Bo' Short. He was on Dateline NBC.  Read it here:   http://msnbc.msn.com/id/4375477/      Also, you may visit his website,  http://www.formerdiamond.com .  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>