<Blog>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, today was get ready for camping day, which means that I won't be blogging for a week. I will keep a journal and enter them when I get home, however. Today I woke up and put on my work cloths (including the pick nick shirt which always gets questions when I wear it for load in or n e thing) Then Rachel came and I went to the library for books for the trip. I got Oliver Twist and Fehrenhieght 451 for summer reading. I also have Ethan Frome kicking around. I am not sure what I will read. I also got the 2nd newest xanth book, which I have not read yet and an older one which I really want to read and a few other things. We are probably going to listen to books on CD on the way up though. Then I worked on packing up kitchen things. This whole time, of course, we were watching the Olympics. I don't like summer Olympics as much as winter Olympics but you gotta watch! Then after becoming VERY TIRED we ate dinner and watched some of Reign of Fire. (an excellent movie in witch Matthew McConaughey plays someone butch for a change) Now I have come online to blog. I am so annoyed that I still haven't got to talk to Ben! Now I may never know what I wanted to tell him! I also need to call Andrew while I am away. He's been really busy and I've been really sad! Well love to Ben and Andrew! I will talk to you guys soon. So I cannot believe that i forgot to tell you the most important news of like my entire life. Yesterday my father told his boss that he was leaving. This makes it real! He cannot chicken out! I love Rachel and Christian but the fact that dad lives out here kind of makes my life miserable except for the fact that I get to see them. Rachel is coming camping with me so that is really awesome. It won't be so boring. But anyways the first time my father told me he was leaving MI I actually cried tears of joy. I have never cried tears of joy before! I will miss Rachel and Christian so much but God! I am so happy. But It's also weird to look around at all of these places that I have seen my whole life and realize that I may never see them again. April may have been the last time I will ever see the butterflies at Frederick Meijer Garden. Next week may be the last time I will ever go to the Kava house. A week from Friday will be the last time I ever see Dad's apartment. After all these years (15 years 7 months and 24 days) it seems like I could never leave. I love you especially to Christian and Rachel and to my HCT friends and Marissa and everyone else who reads this blog and all my other friends!. Have wonderful weeks and I will see you on Monday. (for my last Monday in MI) 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't have time to blog yesterday because I went to bed really early. Yesterday I went to the Kava house with Christian, Rachel, and Jeremiah. I had a diet coke and the 4 of us split a cookie. (it was a big cookie) Then we walked to Rachel's house. We started watching Kill Bill Volume 2. I hated it a lot. It was so boring. Then Joe came over and he and Rachel got into a long discussion in the back room and Christian and I psycho analyzed Rachel for a while. Christian got really mad. Then Jeremiah left and Christian and I ended up sitting outside. Then Christian got mad and left. He was mad at me because I wouldn't leave with him. I mean Rachel was clearly having a problem with her boyfriend and I think that if we had anything to say to her, it needed to wait until she wasn't fighting with Joe. Then Joe and Rachel resolved what they needed to resolve and we hung out. It was a lot of fun. I have never had a problem with Joe, I think Christian wants me to hate him, because Christian hates him. Then Joe went home and Rachel went to band practice and I went home. Then dad and I had pizza and watched some of Addams family values. That movie is so funny. Christiana Ricci has all the best lines in that movie. ( Amanda Buckman : Why are you dressed like somebody died?  Wednesday : Wait. ) Then I went to bed at about 10:45. This morning I woke up at 10:30. I watched some ER (the one where Abby deals with her mothers Manic depressive disorder) It was disturbing for me. Then i did some packing and some laundry (oooh fun) and watched some Lord of the Rings extras and I watched emperors club and now I am watching the commentary. And I still haven't had a chance to talk to Ben! I did talk to Kimmy on the phone and yea... He's odd. I miss HCT a lot. It's so sad. You spend you're whole year waiting for these five weeks and then before you can even blink it's over. I hate that. And who knows when I will have another chance to see all these people. And the really scary thing? I almost always know what my next show is and this time I really don't. I was going to SM for The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe. Heather had asked me to earlier in the year but now she is not directing it. I have emailed Rick about it but they don't have a director yet. I am really hoping to get to work on it and I hope a lot of the kids will too. Especially the kids who have graduated from Discovery Company. They are really great kids and I hope they don't leave. I"m really afraid of us all growing up and leaving. I suppose the most important thing is how much fun I've had and how much I love HCT. It's sad though, how everyone's leaving. So many people have left this year, graduated, moved, or just left. I miss them. Earlier this year something made me think about all these people who are gone from HCT. It was frightening to think that all of these people who, like, are HCT for me, are people who have been gone for years. Sometimes it's odd how it seems that all these things that happened 5 or 6 years ago (god it's been a long time) seem like they happened just yesterday. Well I think that this has actually been a rather short post! I will end this with listen to Wicked it's amazing! I really love that musical. Andrew asked me last night what the most beautiful song I had ever heard was. I really don't know. It puzzled me. Leave a comment if you have any thoughts.  I've heard it said 
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, today I finally got to hang out with Rachel and Christian. First Rachel came here to pick me up and we waited around for Christian. He was supposed to meet us at my house (apartment... thing...) so after waiting for like 20 minutes, Rachel and I decided to go without him. Luckily for him, just as we were about to walk out the door, he showed up. Then we went to the Kava House (or local coffee shop) we hung out and talked for a while and harassed each other. Then Rachel's friend Jeremiah showed up. I had never met him before so that was cool. He and Rachel flirted, then me and Christian bitched and then we walked home. Then Joe (Rachel's BF) was supposed to meet us at Rachel's but he didn't come and she got pissed because we girls (oops, sorry Christian!) had to put up the bunk beds on our own. So then we dragged Rachel's regular bed downstairs and brought the bunk bed up stairs. We also managed to put it together successfully and Rachel probably won't break the bed and die tonight. Then Christian had to leave and me and Rachel watched some bad TV. Then she went online and talked and I called Andrew with my phone card (well at least it's not one sided codependance! He calls me too!) and we talked. I felt bad because he is really tired. So Andrew, if you are reading this, I don't care what time it is, even if it is 2 pm, GO TO BED, get some rest. Then I was online IMing for a while and just as Ben came on (because, as we all know, I have been trying to remember what I wanted to talk to him about) I had to leave and barely got to say two words to him! I did find out that he can't do Wizard of Oz. This is very sad. Stupid religion, what does he need to be confirmed for anyways! And confirm what? (can you tell I've never been catholic) Then Rachel and I went with her dad and his family to a fish place. I don't eat fish but, as usual at fish places, I had fries and chicken tenders. The fries were really good. I like her family, they are really amusing. They are also nicer than my family (my mom's side at least, my dad's side is lovely). Then we went and got ice cream. I had raspberry frozen yogurt twisted with vanilla frozen yogurt. It was sooooo good. I love frozen yogurt. It is way better than soft serve. Then I came home and dad and I watched Photographing Fairies. Despite it's happy name, this movie is no laughing matter. In fact it is quite bizarre. I do not recommend it and nearly everyone dies. It's like a Shakespearian tragedy . In fact it is probably more tragic that the Scottish Play (which I recently saw) because no one you like very much dies except Banquo, MacDuff's family, and Duncan. Also, in the end the good guys get to be king. At some point I should blog about Stratford. Also, the Scottish king is not a tragic hero because, unlike Hamlet, he is not a hero! (he's not even a nice guy) Now enough about that. Then I took a shower! YAAAAYYYY SHOWER. I like to be clean because when you are not clean... You're dirty. I would like to end with that little gem of wisdom and say good night and I love you! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So... I forgot to do this yesterday. Isn't that sad? One day and already I am a failure. Oh well. Alright... Yesterday... What happened yesterday. Well after the high speed chase and the resulting hang over... Alright so I woke up late, I watched bad TV, I went on the internet, then my dad came home and that was the end of it. Also I tried to find Jacki's phone number which I don't have. This is depressing. She is going to my school this year and I have never had an HCT person at my school so I am, excited about it. All you HCT people out there, if you have Jacki's phone number, let me know. Now today I woke up late, but not as late as yesterday, and I went online. Then I showered and got dressed and watched more TV. Then I had to go to Tai Chi with my father. Last time I went I sat on the side and read a book. This time, however, Dad's young (22), hott, male, instructor decided that I wanted to join in. So I did. After a whole bunch of exercises that were basically stretching and meditating at the same time, we played with the energy ball. Unfortunately this is not energy volleyball or energy basketball that Andrea and I play while we are supposed to be paying attention to acting instructors. This was individual energy ball and I don't think you were supposed to bounce it. Then we learned some the beginning of a tai chi form. (series of martial arts movements done slowly) This is rather like dancing with sticks. I think it offended my father's manliness when I referred to the opening foot position as ballet first. (which it was) Since I have no kinetic memory, this took a while for me to get. I hate to admit this, but it was actually very fun. Now dad wants to do it on the beach in petoski when we go camping. (So watch out, Rachel) but it really is fun. Then we came home and watcher this old movie called bladerunner. It is from back when Harrison Ford was still attractive. I have to say he aged well. Yesterday I distinctly recall wanting to talk to Ben Tomaiuolo. I don't remember why but if anyone talks to him tell him I wanted to talk to him. I probably had something important to say but I don't remember what it was. Maybe if I talk to him I will. I haven't talked to Andrew in way too long. He keeps having stuff to do. But he and Mel both got good grades so congratulations guys. I have talked to Kimmy (James) lately and I don't recommend it. He kept talking in code and he thinks there are hackers and he really might be losing it... or he lost it a long time ago. I read some of his Lobster Comics yesterday. He has some online and they are funny. Not as funny as when I get to read them because I have stolen his sketch book and hit him with it however. I was supposed to tell him that he can still use my scanner but I forgot. I talked to Japneet today. This was very surprising since I haven't talked to her since 8th grade. It was nice to talk to someone from back then. I always wonder what would have happened if I had stayed there. I really want to see everyone from my year. Just to see them, to see how they turned out. So apparently Japneet has moved to Toronto! That really seems like it would really stink! Well this has just gone on too long about nothing at all so I think I'll end it here. Right after the biggest news of all. BREE IS DEAD. This sounds cruel, I know, but it is so amazing. My house will finally smell like a house not like something died in it. Apparently she died of heart failure. I think that it had been so long since she had a bath, that she got wet and melted. So good night, but with a quick shout out to Marissa-I'm sorry it took so long for me to return you calls Andrew- Thanks for getting me through this summer Chasya and Christina-I am going to miss you guys so much this year! I can't believe you re off to college already Chana- Don't be silly. You rock, I wouldn't have spent my summer with someone who didn't. (the Rob thing not withstanding, that was a different situation) Don't get yourself down. Alright! I love everyone especially all HCT people, my Enfield people, my NJ people (lol, just garrison), and my Michigan people (Rachel and Christian)! Good Night. Oh and if you made it all the way through this post a comment so I can give you an imaginary cookie. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                So all my friends have blogs now and don't want to talk to me, so I just jumped on the bandwagon.           Now this whole post is just going to seem really self centered but it is my blog so I think I am ok with that. Also, did you klnow that anything you post on the internet can be read? Somepeople who like to hide things from me and only me should remember that.           It makes me so angry when people assume that they know how I will react! Like whenever I ask someone to come to a show and they don't come I get these phone messages saying "look if I can't come please don't be angry" (Love you anyways, Andrew) Like aren't I allowed to grow up? And then there is when people refuse to tell me things because they think they know how I will react. Well, people who claim to be angry with me because I haven't talked to them in three years (not true by the way) really have no basis for the assumption that they know me at all.           And it annoys me that he wouldn't tell me. Like aren't I his friend? and then you get the inevitable "well I guess maybe not." And it's just crazy that he would give people the specific instruction not to tell me! like do my friends here hate me that much? And why bother with all of that when everyone and the kitchen sink can know but me! What exactly did they think my reaction would be? And you know the really shitty part? If he had just told me I would have been happy for him. but after "well she's not ready" now I am just annoyed. Like you think you know me so well that you know how I would react, and after "3 years" why does she even care what I think. And I could totally put this down to him being stupid and exactly like him if it weren't for the fact that... well he seems to have a reason for not telling me.             And with all the time I spend at HCT I guess I kindof feel like I'm not a part of life at home. And I come to Michigan and Rachel and Christian are so happy to have me here and it's crazy because I feel at home here. I feel like they actually know me instead of just this person I used to be. I don't know how to explain this feeling but I somehow feel that people don't want to believe that anything bad has happened to me. They don't what to deal with the fact that I have a pretty scary past if you look below the surface. And maybe thats my fault for not telling them. If you just look at me you probably see barely anything bad at all. But it's not true and I'm not the same little kid anymore. and maybe they don't really know me either. Probably Andrew knows me best of anyone because I tell him most of the truth. And Marissa, because she knows the other side of me. Probably if you put the two of them together you might get a clear picture. But here I feel like if I had something I needed to tell my MI friends, they wouldn't judge me for it. and I guess some people who have known me a really long time might have a good reason to not realize that I am growing up but, god, Rachel has known me since I was two! she has known me longer than any other non-family member and I don't feel like she's trying to stop me from being me. I wish people could just do that. Know my past and understand why I am what I am. And there are just some scars that won't heal, even when the marks disapear.         So I guess this blog ended somewhere it didn't start! Thats what happens when you type with your train of thought! But anyways, yea I am pissed at people who just don't tell me things. I mean I guess I don't really have a right to know but it is really shitty to go "I have a girlfriend but I won't tell you who she is because she isn't ready for you to know." Hey, princess, if she's ready for the whole world to know just but reading your blog I don't know why you can't tell someone why actually knows you. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>