<Blog>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        The car left the road so suddenly I didn’t have time to react. You think that you will be able to do something in that instant. I’ve done enough motorway driving to have considered the options as triplex shatters all around, your glasses fly off, you tuck your feet under you, you step from the vehicle, Chuck Jones like at the moment of impact, unscathed to view the un-toyota shaped corrola. “bloody hell that was close” you say to your fellow accidentees, who similarly have all escaped. As I say, lots of mileage. Back-ache, boredom, and shattered ankles. You may detect in me a tendency towards the morbid. I don’t apologise for this it’s not my fault. Every peer group has its rites of passage. Hypnogogically speaking horror features strongly. Influenced at an early age by the luridity of The Encyclopedia of Horror films, a much loved and thumbed volume in the school library. And what was that series on ITV on Saturday nights. Not Tales of the Unexpected. Wasn’t it just called “Thriller”.  Now my darkest fears approach. Diana Dors as a witch, postcard picturesque Sussex Villages with their hedgerows concealing untold menace and people bricked up in chimneys ‘cos they knew too much or not enough. It was a feature of those longed for weekends. An escape from the horrors of school to the horrors of the imagination. A man haunted by the number of the beast, reoccurring everywhere he looked. Phone numbers, car registrations, house numbers. A woman tormented by visitations, mysterious phone calls, threatening noises in the seeming banality of her sunny flat. Late night lonely paranoia brought out into the daylight which would normally banish the irrational. These images feed my fears, the laws of physics suddenly ruptured as a screaming dervish, all rotting flesh and fingernails rends apart the fabric of space time to rip me to shreds, suck out my soul as it screams an eternity of agony and blood. Even now as a so called adult, late night lonliness instils these sensations. Every creak of this Victorian terraced house a message from the underworld. We’re coming to get you, to strap you down on our obscene torture table and commit unspeakable acts of vivisection as you observe the details of our acts in extreme close-up longing for death but unable to make that transition. 
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sUm buocks wot aye 'ave reDd resuntlee  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       1o things that prove life is good:      1. Malcolm in the Middle.   2. Line 6 Pod.   3. Adobe Photoshop.   4. Central heating.   5. Jazz Record Requests. (BBC R4)   6. Le Mans 24 Hours.   7. Frijj choc' milkshake.   8. Nikon D70.   9. Will Alsop.   10. Waterstones.  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  www.wiganworld.co.uk/fred   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        That’s really when the panic attacks started in earnest. Not immediately after the old mans G3 but close enough for me to feel his fear irradiating me. After they moved to B******. After the bypass operation and his fear sharpend. Doubtless distressing. But traumatic also for those around him. Not stressfull in a Normandy landing Houston we have a problem kind of way. You and I aren’t trained to kill or build an oxygen release valve out of available components. The only available components we have are our emotions. And , if you don’t know how or when to express those intense feelings of guilt, fear, anger… well, you're fucked. We’re all fucked. Same old story, ce la vie, que sera sera, plus ca change… nothing new under the sun.  If it is cancer wouldn’t there be other symptoms? Loss of appetite, nausea, bleeding, contutions. Is my tongue feeling funny ‘cos that microwaved chicken chow main… Always trying to read the signs. For best results cook from frozen. Well I’m not very warm so I’ll just get on with it. 850 watts for six minutes. Is this what mobile phones are doing to our heads forming a crust on the grey matter. But nothing ever gets crisp in a microwave except boild rice. Is that a golden crumb coating you wanted on your left temporal lobe? Ahh, lovely fags! 
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      composition#7  urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My knee hurts. 
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       10 things that prove life is rubbish:      1. Call centres.   2. Big Brother.   3. Harry  bloody Potter.   4. Nicotine addiction.   5. Middle age.   6. Andy McDowell.   7.  Humidity.      8.  Football.    9. Panic Attacks.   10. Chris Moyles.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  www.rhubarb-rhubarb.net   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I can do cuddly too.    urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        What would the son do without the brother? There’s a tingling numbness down the right side of my throat. Starting just below the ear and extending to my adams apple. Some times my tongue and lips tingle again with the buzzing. It gets worse when I smoke. But now I realise its not so much a buzzing as a hiss, or has it just changed as my mind wandered off. Now the light is closer, in fact here it is, lamplight through a window.  
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         got those selfridges charge card blues.     urlLink      
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ...and  anything  could happen.  
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Dearly beloved, bretheren, sisteren, momer’n, dadr’n. Praise be! Hallellujah! Mercy!  I come amongst you with a message. a few  well chosen words in plain language. Hear me people. What I say people. With your God given ears people. Taste the words in the air with your tongue. Thtath ith,  juthst therwe, th’  vewwy tip.  We shall not be blinded, or the truth hidden from us by his shiny baubles and gew-gaws. His gimcrack devices of this so called digital information super highway traffic jam, gridlock buzzword quotin’ media savvy, creative type high falutin sumbitchin gosh darn melon farmin, shitkickin hootenany wishy-washy PC liberal, fudamentalist, commie pinko fag hog lovin Nimby naysayers comin’ into our livin’ rooms and tellin’ us what we can or cannot do!!!!!! I think you know of whom I speak. Lemmee hear you say hallellujah!  I come amongst you on this joyus day for a very special purpose. I come amongst you this day to bring glory. Mmhmm I come amongst you this beautiful day to speak the truth and speak with truth ooooh yah! Yay my cause is just and my cause is righteous. MERCY!  You are all here for one thing, and one thing only. Do u want to know what that one thing is? Do you want me to tell you? You know you do You know what you want You want to hear the word DO YOU WANT TO HEAR THE WORD? Well listen up people and hear the word. Whats the word? I’ll tell u the word. I, the very reverend Nathaniel Q Kellog III, pastor of the 1st Erdington Church of the All day breakfast say unto you… The word is…   The word is…  SALVATION! Lemme hear u say yeah!  And you will come to salvation in only one way and in one way only . When one comes among you bearing the truth and filled with the light. For I have seen the light. And I come amongst you bretheren, sisteren, momma n’ daderr’n to introduce you to a friend of mine.  Yes, a very special  friend. Some of you are familiar with this friend already, some of you have yet to be allowed into the prescence wherin those henceforth agreeing to this aknowledgement of eachothers hithertofore un–beknownst to the party of the third part shall therefore and hitherto thence knownst apart from of with too and as in yet for  if  I could read your mind love, what a tale my thoughts could tell just like an old time movie ‘bout a ghost from a wishing well.  For he walks amongst us , this friend of mine. Yay though I walk  through the valley  of cash and or credit I will fear no shopping mall. I shall turn neither left nor right nor up nor down round or through in my quest for  the style, size, color, fit, price/practicability APR 15 ½ % discount designer label consumer tested demographically researched product of my choice. My purchases shall not be in vain nor not never shall they hang in the darkest recesses of the closet in perpetuity. Not whilst I’m draw ddddrawin’ bbbbreath  Mmmmnike, mmadadadadadidas kokokokokokakolapep c prada isssssssissssey mmmmmiyake Nikeaddidictaspumawackk wackk ooomya ya ya gullellifuffesesesimarashtikastanastasasasttttttan mmmffffhhh  mmmffffhhhh  pppppppp praise the lord! pppppass my tambourine and bring on the snakes. Hallellujah.  
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        and we're talking about the bloody weather!!!   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       you don't say.   urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        caution, bad karma ahead.     urlLink   
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ...needs to sort out some coding somewhere 'cos i'm a  LEO  and i was born in the year of the  TIGER . 
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Into the treeline now and “crack” that is the noise my forehead makes when I hit it against an overhanging branch. CRACK. I clutch the damage and it’s warm and wet. Great now I’m bleeding, just what I need what with the car going off the road like that the front wheels just seeming to slide out from under me the buzzing getting louder and closer.  I think I’ve got cancer. I’ll roll a cigarette. The big Casino. The oncological nightmare. Hushed voices and magnetic resonance. Flowers and needles. Deeply inhaling Duma halftsware shag he continues. ***s mom died of it, of the throat. Silk Cut I believe. She was a lovely woman. Sausage and mash cartwheels and grated apple sandwiches. ***s sister S** was dads nurse when he was in hospital. Grade three myocardial infarction. The doctor insisted that it was indigestion so he went back to bed and it just got worse. So my brother called the doctor back and insisted that the old man be carted off to hospital. Pronto. What would the father have done without the son? What would the son be without the father?  
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         just been up the high st to do some shopping and indulge in a little pavement rage, muttering crude comments as i get stuck behind another mothers meeting outside bloody dorothy perkins, school holidays adding to the crush and high humidity making me slough off brain cells though my lug 'oles. one queue after another adding precious seconds to the time i'm out of the house, sucking the very lifeblood out of me as particles of my essence pop in and out of existence appearing and disappearing in various parts of the multiverse. still eh, you've gotta laugh.   
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink       a randomly selected abstract colourfield  
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     wood & rope.   urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     raspberryripple 01.  
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So here we all are, trying to find some justification in our lives. Through material possesions, with sex and pretend sex and swatting flies and art. We look harder and harder on an ever diminishing/expanding scale in and out to the infinitely small and the infinitely humungus. Brobdignagian and Lilliputian. Balance is all. A means to prove to the world and to the self that one exsists. Touch me feel me kiss me kill me suck me fuck me. Where do I start, where do I begin. You know what they always say…  I’m lost on a heath, well I assume it’s a heath. The clumpy grass suggests as much. And, I assume that I’m lost. Because there’s something I can’t quite figure out. I know who I am, I know what year it is, and the name of our current Prime Minister. All that doctor patient kind of stuff. So it’s not amnesia. But I can’t quite grasp how I came to be in this place as oppose to where I was. What! Hey! Duh! It’s getting dark and it’s starting to rain. And now, having said what I just said I seem to have been stumbling around in this twilight for some time. Or, no time at all. Quite some time. Quite. And there’s a light. Just up ahead. I’ve just noticed it. It’s flickering so it must be behind or in amongst some trees. It’s difficult to tell now it’s getting darker and the rain as it spatters my specs is multiplying the growing point of light into firework starbursts. The ground is uneven making me miss my footing and occassionally splodging into a boggy bit. And I forgot to mention the smell. Faint but distinct. And the noise, just beyond the sighing of the wind. Once again barely pereceptable but unmistakably…there. 
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        well, it took a lot of mental energy but i managed to suss out sending pics. if i can remember what i did i might send another sometime. but what's with the clock thing? strewth.    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     wood.   urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Here we bloody go. Nothings ever easy is it. I really wanted to stick some pics into my blog, but now I find that in order to do so I've got to download some extraneous bit of software. It took me long enough to learn soddin' fotoshoppe so I don't want go thru all that palaver. Seems like it's just going to be text then. As I have already mentioned, jargon (and particularly computer jargon) really rubs my rhubarb. I don't have a "URL" to download my pictures from and I'm not about to start now. So unless someone can tell me how to insert a picture that I have already spent hours editing, cropping and composing to my complete satisfaction you're all going to miss out on the greater part of my loveblend and soulwallop. (&amp;, i forgot to change the time on my last entry so i'm a time traveller now for crying out loud) 
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Welcome, wilkomen & bienvenue.  
</post>


</Blog>