<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      on a sidenote... how the hell did wirth find out im dropping chem.. who told him?!?! O.o... sigh... was hoping he'd find out *after* the speech so he dun kill my marks... >. oh well.. i guess all u chem ppl must be happy im leaving.. get to move up a place.. :P   random quote (paraphrased): ~shen~: im doing 14 units, 4 subjects wirth: 4 units each subject?  go figure.   also.. wtf is up with this time thingy.. keeps setting it to like 4am.. >.<
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was good.. ^^  double cello concerto in the morning... the soloists have no idea wat theyre doing... but hopefully it will get better... love the music anyway ^^  maths.. got to play with dominos! lol! thx for bringing them joey ^^ then.. maths results... so scary at first... and the result is... 111/120! yay! lol.. not too bad for 3 hours of study --> 3rd in year.. dunno how the yr12s went tho.. ^^ then.. software... another scary moment... 49/50!! yay!! lolz.. i bet kermode enjoys robbing me of half-marks just to piss me off... oh wellz... coming first now!! w00t...  music class... got to piss off prero yet again... lol... one day he'll kick me out of class... i can tell... :P listening to 'the rites of spring' by stravinsky... wat can i say... its a retarded piece.. >.<>.<>   had to write a sonnet for english... sigh... oh well.. heres my attempt... complete with 14 lines, iambic tetrameter and 'abab' rhyming scheme and stuff... >.    a sonnet for friendship   a friend is someone you can trust, no matter what you're going through. though time and trials may bring up rust, there's nothing your true friends won't do! i know, my friends, you'll make mistakes, i humbly admit i will too; and even if my weak heart breaks, i'll always put my trust in you!  for these mistakes are what will show the love you truly feel for me. without mistakes we'll never know the things we seldom say or see. though time may make us drift apart, i'll always keep you in my heart.  lolz.. and there we have it... my dodgy attempt at a sonnet >.  random quote time!! lolz.. too lazy to find anythings.. heres some.. random song lyrics! my fav song for the time being ^^ half the stuff dun make sense cause they dun usually sing english and its made to fit the song... :  deep forest by do as infinity:  There must still be the soul that you have left behind, hidden somewhere In the deep deep of the forest lying among the trees People who are too tired they just don't look around, any farther They disappear into the eternal darkness of a foreign place  Could we still have seen it if we were there? Could we have seen it if we were little.  Go on wait our live and lose those things behind  Wrapped around our lies, we stand there voiceless Wonder leave our lives until we find the way Searching for the light For eternity  Things are passing and changing and moving around  But the colors of the sky Still remain the same as we used to know Every single day  We are running so free now ignoring the risk  The limits that we had We leave our fears behind take another chance  Our souls will live again  If we catch the rhythm of time We could probably fly so high  Go on wait our live and lose those things behind  Wrapped around our lies, we stand there voiceless Wonder leave our lives until we find the way Searching for the light For eternity   lolz.. oh well... kinda loses its effect if its not sung... nice song when listened to tho ^^  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       this post will consist of random quotes, as they arrive, to show the world the brilliance that is known as jason hu... only you who have met jason can truly understand... :   Jason: do u know who sherab is? ~shen~: nope Jason: ok, don't worry then Jason: its like sleeping with max ~shen~: uve slept with max??! Jason has left the conversation. * Jason is now Offline   Jason: By the way, Raymond is so happy when he heard that you will be travelling with us! ~shen~: so u can rape him? Jason: i doubt it Jason: what am i saying Jason: NO ~shen~: lol Jason: of course not Jason: :P ~shen~: jason wants to rape raymond.. this is soooo wrong Jason: lol, female are much better :P Jason: and NO, i don't want to rape angela  ~shen~: ur gonna bomb the ski place?? Jason: with what? ~shen~: er..a bomb? ~shen~: thats what u usually bomb stuff with Jason says: where do i get a bomb Jason says: no serious, where do i get a bomb? 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       haha.. where to start... joey's new favourite word is 'wrong' ^^ wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong   lalala ^^   friday... joey brought this dragonfly thingy to school! and its magnetic and cool and stuff! ^^ then we reading some story thingy... and i kept cracking up for no reason... >.<>.  today... music practice in the morning... sigh... u'd think a *percussion* ensemble could play in time... i soooo wanna quit... oh well.. double cello concerto tomorrow! yay!! :D   then.. english essay!!! aaargh!!! lolz... panic panic panic... 5.5 pages in an hour seems alright.. til it gets compared to 10 pages o.O finally... bus trip home.. when u'd think its all calm and quiet and i get to relax and not do anything for once... then theres a food fight.. sigh.. and they expect me to go and *do* something about it... blah... evil kids >.   random quote time! yay! :   ~shen~: i get a badge soon! thats gotta count for something!   I'm God's little baby and Daddy's little girl, but I'm far from perfect : ^^   I'm God's little baby and Daddy's little girl, but I'm far from perfect : haha.... well.... was thinking i might steal ur badge     *hugs badge when he gets it* ^^  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today.. got back half of the 2u trial results... 53/60... sigh... thats what happens when shen only gets 3 hours study.. >.  saw king arthur today... yay... MINDLESS FUN ! YAY! lolz...  random quote: I'm God's little baby and Daddy's little girl, but I'm far from perfect: yes........ I'm icecream.... eat me.......  O.o... interesting...  *edit: 5 × 12 does not equal 48.. sigh... 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mark has pink bedsheets! lolz... just had to say that.. ^^ i mean... not that theres anything wrong with pink or anything like that... ^_^''  today... joseph met alysha... sorta... interesting quotes include:  Djü'zæf ²ºº¾: its scary Djü'zæf ²ºº¾: she wont tell me her name Djü'zæf ²ºº¾: i sed hoo r u Djü'zæf ²ºº¾: and she says " i dun kno" Djü'zæf ²ºº¾: wtf?!!! Djü'zæf ²ºº¾: she says shes been stalkin me and my dog bel  soooo random... :P  figured out wat to get for ming's birthday! yay! then five minutes after ordering.. i found another site which was cheaper... evil websites...  -_-  random quote of the day!:  [JSo] parano: you look like some sort of secret agent [JSo] parano: you have something shifty and secretive aura about you... [JSo] parano: or is it sleepiness?  *WHAT* is going on there?! lolz... i agree with teh last bit completely tho... ^^ 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lol... this post started off well.. couldnt figure out how to login to blogger... had to ask ming for help >.  bah.. appears half the post got deleted... >.  long day today... music... and no-one else can play the piece! great stuff.. ^_^'' vivaldi double cello concerto tomorrow tho! yay! :D fell in love with it after playing it at con access... ^^  got back prac exam results... found out that they didnt care about the results... gave me full marks for my fudged results, and screwed me up cause i couldnt draw a table.. >. king arthur excursion on thursday... yay..  random quote from mings blog: -What do I get to do? "The Atom Probe is EMU’s latest acquisition and one of only 4 of itskind in the world.  summary: we're screwed.   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      blah... this is.. my first time using a blog! mwah! mi sooo lost... wat am i supposed to do... >.<>.  hmmm... mings bday in 3 weeks... so far.. his suggestions have been : mp3 player, hackysack, disney songbook, lockpicking kit, utada hikaru/deb fung cd, and something else he cant think of...  random quote : y would he want a haystack???  lol.. the joy of learning to read... ^^ 
    
</post>


</Blog>