<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         What is this you ask? It's a redneck pet carrier.   Thanks to the guys at   urlLink  boners.com    (over 18 content - BEWARE)  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a long time since I watched the Olympics.  The fact that I don't have cable and thus no channels on my TV to choose from not withstanding, I just haven't been interested in it for years.   It seems to me that the Olympics is no longer about being higher, faster or stronger, it's all about money.  It's no longer about coming together to compete in a spirit of brotherhood, it's about gathering as many sponsorships as possible.  Doping scandals, judging scandals, bombings, etc.. has only deepened my cynicism all the more. Never mind that every country that donated funds to help build the new IOC complex in Switzerland have all received the Games, or that judges have received huge bribes, er, I mean gifts from committee's trying to bring the games to their city.  So much for the purity of sport.  Now here's the latest.  The Iranian Judo champion rigged his weigh-in to be found overweight so that he wouldn't have to fight an Isreali competitor.  He was disqualified from the meet.  According to Abdollah Ramanzanzadeh, a spokesperson for the Iranian government, it would be against: "[O]ur policy to recognize the Zionist regime in any international event.  We cannot accept the presence of anyone in international events under the flag of that regime."  Heaven forbid that Muslims and Jews actually  meet on a field of battle where they can't actually kill each other.  Admittedly, Isreal is not a shining example of religious tolerance, but Iran is hardly one to throw stones either.   At best, the Olympics are supposed to be about putting aside political differences and competing together as athletes first.  At worst, it's about settling international differences using sport as the proving ground instead of the battlefield.  What Iran has done flies in the face of those ideals.  What has the IOC to say about this?  Nothing, not a peep.  According to IOC representative Giselle Davies:  "The issue has not actually come on the agenda of the IOC," she said at today's press conference.  I guess it would be too much to expect the IOC to take a moral stand on this issue.  Haven's know that they've never done it before. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have discovered what really killed Tolkien. It wasn't pneumonia, he was murdered.  And I know the identity of the murderer!  You can find the murder weapon at  urlLink ttp://homepage.mac.com/evanbaumgardner/iMovieTheater6.html   I hope you have a strong stomach.  Whoever knew Mr. Spock had a sadistic streak.   Thanks to Illiad over at   urlLink  User Friendly    for the link. PS. You need  urlLink Quicktime  to view this, just follow the link.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Anyone seen the trailer for Resident Evil : Apocalypse? (see it  urlLink here )  I'm not a big horror or zombie fan. As a matter of fact, I have yet to make all the way through M. Knight Shyamalan's  urlLink Signs  (I think I'm about 1/3 of the way through) because I can't stand the tension. And Signs can hardly be described as a horror flick. I won't tell you what I did to my friend's couch when I tried to watch The Amityville Horror.  I am a wimp, I admit it.  That being said, I think I might go see this film or at least rent it. Why? Well, as much as I love  urlLink Oded Fehr  (Ardeth Bey from The Mummy movies), that isn't the reason.  I want to see Toronto's City Hall get blown to bits. This is almost as big a thrill as seeing The White House get immolated in Independance Day (people in the theater cheered). I just wish former Mayor Mel was inside The Big White Urinal when it exploded. Show him there's more to worry about in the world than Kenyan cannibals and their big stew pot.  Gods, I hope I don't have to watch the first one.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      According to MSNBC, a woman and her cat have been re-united after 18 years. Seems that Leslie Dumas lost her pet Seagull after a fire destroyed her home and she moved into her boyfriend's mother's house.  Now Seagull's back where he belongs, albeit fairly long in the tooth and blind from cataracts. But he's home where he'll be loved and cared for, for however long he has left.  Interesting how life works sometimes. We often circle around trying to figure out where we belong in the world, then when we least expect it, we come back to where it all began because that's where we most need to be.  Welcome Home Seagull.  Cam  Read the full story  urlLink here  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello!  Welcome to my blog.  Well, this isn't so much of a blog as a meandering through whatever happens to be working it's way through my consciousness at any given moment.  So sit back and enjoy a guided tour through my id, ego and superego.  Cam 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>