<Blog>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So my friend Mario visited this weekend, and surprisingly, everyone had a good time.  Now, if you know Mario (and I apologize Mario if you're reading this), then you know how rare an occurrence this is.  We didn't really do much, just hung out like we did back in the day.  It's nice when you have friends that you can do absolutely nothing with and say it was fun.  Mario left early, early this morning and I assume he made it back in one piece since I saw that he was just recently logged on AIM.  I cooked this afternoon like a maniac, preparing all sorts of food for Yoshimi.  I made batches of steamed plucots, peaches, pears, Japanese sweet potatoes, and golden beets.  She already taste-tested the pears.   I'm relieved that she's finally enthusiastic about solid food; I was beginning to worry that I'd be breastfeeding her until she left for college.    For dinner Tom made hamburgers out of real ground beef, not ground turkey like we usually eat.  I figure that a good way to gain more weight is to increase my protein and fat intake, so that means I'll be buying red meat when I grocery shop.  We topped the burgers with brie as an added fat bonus.  YUM!!!  For dessert I'll be eating cookies and ice cream and drinking some brandy.  Double yum! 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is it sad that Tom, Mario and I are spending this lovely Saturday night looking at those high school reunion websites for old classmates that we either would like to see again at the talked-about-but-not-planned reunion and those we would like to forget?  Oh yeah, remember her?  Yeah, she hung out with that other chick?  What was her name?  Eh, who cares.    I'm looking forward to my reunion if only to show off that I'm successful in life.  See, I never felt like I was the popular one in high school.  Now I know that a lot of the popular kids in high school end up not doing much afterwards.  I'm happy that the prime of my life was not during my adolescent years.  And the whole purpose of reunions is to see what others are doing and if you are better than them.  And if you are, then you have won.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yoshimi has been more upset lately.  Last night she cried and cried.  I couldn't figure out what was wrong.  Finally, I realized she had pooed a while before and had been wearing a dirty diaper for a few hours.  The poor kid.  See, up until recently you would know when she went number 2 because you would hear it--juicy, farty, diarrhea-like sound.  Now, she poos in silence.  Since she has been eating her solid foods, her poops have become less runny; now it's the consistency of thick, creamy peanut butter rather than watery mustard.  I apologzie for the gross imagery.  Anyway, I'm going to have to check for dirty diapers for more often.  Oh and another thing, she now hates dealing with diaper changes so it's a constant battle every time.  She's unhappy with a dirty diaper and she's unhappy getting a clean one on.    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was on my daily perusing of the  urlLink Glitter  boards, and came across a thread on these awesome John Kerry tees and where to get them.  So I follow the link to  urlLink politipunk , and order myself the blue KerryBears shirt.  It was a toss-up between that one and the yellow heart one.  I actually think I like the yellow one a little more, but I'm cheap and went for the less expensive shirt.  I'm so stoked about my purchase!  I can't wait to get it in the mail and proudly sport my new tee.  Now, I'm not typically the kind of person who displays their political views--I don't have any bumper stickers on my car, I don't have any other political clothing or buttons or things like that--but I couldn't resist these tees.  Plus I really don't want Bush to win.  If he does, I may have to move up a little more north to Vancouver, B.C.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hope that something of interest will spring to mind while I write. I don't have anything in particular to say, but I feel like typing. Now, I would normally start up an IM with my brother with the possibility that he'll have something good to say because I sure as hell don't, but I already chatted with him earlier this morning and I doubt much has changed within a couple hours.  Yoshimi cracks me up. She's trying to sit in a spot where there is something in her way, but she refuses to move. Instead she keeps clunking her head against this file portfolio thing. She looks at it, but doesn't move. Wait, now she moves. She's trying to climb up my chair. Oh, she's hungry.  My baby is 9 months old and only within the last couple of months have I started to enjoy breastfeeding her. You know how you hear that breastfeeding is such a wonderful bonding time, blah blah blah. To be honest, I never really liked it. I have a big milk supply and I know I should consider myself lucky because there are women who do not, but it has made life really uncomfortable for me. I would leak every single time I'd feed Yoshimi, causing me to wear these stupid breastpads for over half a year. My boobs would easily get engorged, causing more leakage and more pain. Letdown, which is the action where the milk ducts release the milk, hurt. Oh, and when we travel--ugh! Yoshimi's schedule gets all whacked out and she doesn't want to eat, causing me more pain and misery. On top of that, every article of clothing I owned smelled like spoiled milk. Nursing frustrated me. Only recently have things begun to lessen. Letdown isn't as painful, my supply isn't as big (perhaps because of my light weight), and Yoshimi nurses better. I finally have that bonding feeling that I've heard about from outside sources.  Sometimes she looks up at me while she's nursing and smiles and giggles.  Other times she just wants to be close and cuddle.  You know, I might actually  miss  breastfeeding her when it's over. But I won't hold my breath.    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My baby has her own  urlLink blog .  She tells me she is very excited about this.   urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...but it's not what you might think.  It's not that I weigh too much, it's that I can't keep the weight on.  With running around after Yoshimi and breastfeeding her, I can't consume enough calories to maintain my weight.  I'm 15 pounds lighter than before I got pregnant.  I've already had two doctors tell me to eat anything and everything in sight.  So that's what I do; I eat a couple ice cream bars a day, Totino's pizza for lunch, some sodium laden frozen prepared dinner, chocolate for snacks, and alcohol (in moderation, don't want to affect Yoshimi's milk too much!).  Maybe I need to switch to whole milk for my cereal.  Or heavy cream!  Or melted butter! I don't want to clog my arteries, and I feel like crap since I eat crap, but I'm not sure how else to get the extra calories.  I just hope that Yoshimi gets more into her solid foods and gradually starts to wean herself off the boobie milk.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      According to weather.com, the high here in Portland was 101 degrees.  Now, when you think of Portland weather, images of rain, rain, and more rain should flood your mind, not 100 degree heat.  It's a good thing that there aren't too many days like this during the year.  I look forward to those first brisk days of autumn where the air is crisp and clear and you can smell the seasons change.    Trying to sleep when it's too hot in the house sucks.  Sticky, sweaty, uncomfortable.  I took a cold shower earlier tonight and that was nice for about, oh, 5 minutes afterwards, but then I started sweating again.  Ever since my pregnancy last year, the heat is more unbearable for me.  Maybe it has something to do with my hyperthyroid condition.  Maybe it's hormones. Maybe I'm allergic to the sun.  Who knows.  Whatever the reason, I wish I had a cure for it.    So... Mom IMs me today and says, "Don't freak out, but I'm getting a hysterectomy."  Uhh, how am I not to freak out?  And why does she tell me this over the internet?  Pick up the phone!  She says it's cancer, but "the good kind," meaning that it's uterine cancer, which is very treatable, compared to ovarian cancer, which is not (or so I'm told).  I guess all the reproductive goods get taken out and the cancer along with them.  She also informs me that after the operation she won't be able to get pregnant.  Damn, and I was just wishing she and Dad would give me a younger sibling that would be younger than my daughter.  There goes that dream down the drain.  I plan on flying down to the bay area when she goes under the knife.  I wish that Mom wasn't so nonchalant with things like this.  It's frustrating that she never likes to discuss matters of importance and avoids it at all costs.  She reassures me that everything will be fine, but I'm a worrier and I'm worried.  Oh, she also was recently diagnosed with diabetes.  As if one disease isn't enough.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have now joined the blog bandwagon.  i will write about things of which no one will read.  blogs are vain.  it's a journal for public viewing.  and of course, in the hopes that someone will read this, i have more incentive to write.  on that same token, however, am i free to write whatever i choose?  what if i say X about Y, and Y happens to read it?  what are the chances of that happening?  do i risk the chance of my real world colliding with my internet world?  would that be so bad?  will my comments of smack come back later to bite me in the ass?    my reasons for blogging are obviously selfish.  it's for me to vent, gush, blab.  in other words, communicate, but without having to actually talk to anyone, because, god forbid, i would have to pick up the phone and dial a number.  plus, the phone works both ways and i'm not getting any calls on my end.  this makes me think that people either don't want to talk to me or are too busy.  i think it's a little of both.  sigh.  my first few posts will probably be the most lengthy, and then slowly dwindle down in size as time goes on and my caring for blogs lessens.  i hope this is not the case, but let's be honest, how much enthusiasm and energy do i have these days?  most of it is spent on yoshimi and the rest is spent on sleep.  yes, i'm enthusiastic about sleep and i love to spend my free time napping.  it's been a year and a half since i've slept for more than 4 hours straight.  naps are what i do best.  wow.  i suck at writing.  all my paragraphs are the same length.  i follow some kind of pattern that has been engrained in me since high school english class.  it's not very exciting.  and i don't seem to have a point.  i could never take my writing to the next level.  i should work at this.  i should also work at using caps.  Okay, here we go.  See, with word processor programs like Microsoft Word, they automatically capitalize things for you, so over the years I have gotten lazy with hitting that Shift key.  This is something I need to get back in the habit of doing.  Let's talk about something fun.    Yoshimi!  She's saying "mam mama mam ma" right now.  So cute.  She's pointing to my nose.  This is one of the cutest things she does.  She points with a slightly bent index finger.  I know it doesn't sound cute, but believe me, if you saw her do it, you'd agree.  It's as if she's saying, "Hello? What's this?" with her finger.  Yoshimi, like her mommy, is vain.  Yoshimi loves her reflection.  She must know she's a good looking baby.  I know that all parents say this about their children, but in my case it really is true.  Yoshimi is the cutest baby.  Ever.  I see other parents with their babies and I think various comments: -Nope, not nearly as cute as Yoshimi. -Ugly -Yikes! -Kinda cute -Maybe the kid will be better looking when s/he gets older  Of course, I could never say these things to the poor parents of not attractive kids, so I end up saying something vague like: -Oh, what a tiny baby!   -Babies are precious, aren't they? -What a cute outfit she has on -Isn't it nice when the baby is sleeping?  Seeing other babies makes me realize that Tom and I are very lucky to have the world's cutest baby.  I know people must envy us.  I play this game with Yoshimi where I stack some blocks up and she crawls across the room and knocks them over.  She then claps at her accomplishment.  While she's knocking them over, I move to the other side of the room and pile some more blocks up.  After she knocks one stack over she crawls across the room to the other stack and proceeds to do the same thing as the first pile.  This game can go on forever.  Unless she sees something on the floor during her crawl over, like a plastic Easter egg, and in that case she forgets what she was previously doing and starts gnawing on her newly rediscovered toy.  Whew!  I just put Yoshimi down for her nap, which is no easy feat.  It's not that it's really difficult so much as it just takes time.  She has this routine where she has to crawl up and down our bed and play all around before she can settle.  This can take up to an hour and a half.  I have no idea why she does this, but every single time before she goes to sleep this must be done.  This past weekend I took down the crib from her nursery upstairs and moved it into our bedroom.  I took the sliding rail off and put the crib adjacent to our bed.  Now Yoshimi can get used to sleeping in her crib because up until this point she had taken over our bed.  It's nice to have our bed back.  The downside is that Yoshimi has this new territory that she must include in her crawling-on-the-bed/crib-before-going-to-sleep routine.  This adds a half an hour to her crazy routine.  this is getting long.  time to post.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>