<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I don't want to be Going through the motions   Once again, Monday seems to have clubbed precious Sunday over the back of the head and dragged its body and stowed it in a cupboard just before we could really see how good it could be.  The lovely Lisa and I managed to get a soft-shoe in on Friday night and came third in the foxtrot match competition...which is always a little exciting. After growing up in a school that believed that the reward is in the task, and that ribbons are instruments of Satan...Its nice to finally be able to stick something on the fridge, albeit 13 years to late.  But anyhow.   Not much happened this weekend, although I think some highlights included purchasing 300 big ones worth of beer and wine at  urlLink Dan Murphy's , and Lisa managing to beat me into submission over the purchase of an outrageously priced pair of  urlLink tweezers .  millennium is coming!   Practicing a part Nothing seems to penetrate my heart.   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       from the creators of  urlLink Thy Dungeonman  comes....  da na na na!   urlLink Peasant's Quest   a spectacle of graphics and sound.     
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been told that one of the benefits of adsl and a tonne of bandwidth is that you can focus your cosmic powers, like some kind of death star, and get your hands on your wildest dreams.  Which in my case, includes 80s cartoons.  So I have joined the search for the Auracite...as I attempt to lay my hands on eps  of ' urlLink Spartakus and the Sun Beneath the Sea '… which I am getting a little bit excited about. If it's anything like my previous experiences with cartoons like  urlLink Ulysses 31 , then I'll probably be disappointed - but I wouldn't be human unless I had these cathartic experiences from time to time.  in other news, sources tell me that the Thai place down the road has decided to change hands, and their 'pad thai' receives the thumbs down. Maybe you guys could consider using some kind of 'pad thai paste'? Or something...you know, for flavour. Maybe some non-spoilt tofu would pep it up a bit as well?  Just a thought.  Not much else is happening, the lovely Lisa and I plan to head out and about to buy some new  urlLink magic shoes . After that I think we might do a  urlLink senior walk or two , and relax in front of some  urlLink Buff . 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So after managing to not burn a church down on Sunday, I come at last to glorious Tuesday.  Give me your worst.  What happened to Monday you ask? Who can say, except that I suspect it may have something to do with the captains at the good ship  urlLink IBM  being outrageously excited over the impending release of  urlLink Workplace 2.0.   well, it means something to me, anyway. Specifically, a long weekend.  Back to Tuesday. I finally managed to get my  urlLink link light  to stop flashing, and the friendly IT guys presented me with a shiny new keyboard, for use with my faithful lappy. It has exciting features such as:      'Print Screen'     'Num Lock'  Run 'calc.exe'         and the always popular 'Esc'.    Until next time,    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>