<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, 1 day left... Less than 36 hours and I will be in the presence of my favorite band in the world. For those of you who don't know who that is. It is the DAVE MATTHEWS BAND... man I even love the name...j/k....or am I?? Anyway, I am a little tired last night I got home about 3ish and was still wound in my head so I was up until about 4am. I had some stuff on my mind, so a friend of mine went out to eat with me. She is so beautiful! Personality, Physically, Kind, Caring....I could go on but I dont need to. She has helped me a lot lately, more than she knows. Anyway after we ate and talked, I still was WIRED when I got home, so I played some online poker; DAD had been hooked on watching it, so I play online just to have a little fun with it. I listened to Dave, becasue when we were talking last night, we got onto that subject. I told her about one of the songs that had reminded me of something that came up in conversation. Some of you may know it.... Say Goodbye. One of my all time fav's. Anyway....once we got done eating, she wanted to hear it, so the Dave cd I made her had it. We got in her car and listened to a couple songs, and then got to that one.. IT IS HARD FOR ME TO SKIP DAVE SONGS TO GET TO JUST ONE!!!! OK?!?!? So I made her listen to a couple others first.... but anyway, the point of the story. I got in a Dave mood, I hadn't been earlier. I was still in the Christian mood from the concerts the past weekend. BTW... it doesn't take very much to get me in a "Dave Mood". Still, I wasn't really craving, until then. As I am writing this post, I am listening to the Central Park CD. Great CD. Best Live show I have heard them release yet. 100,000 Fans...loud enough you can hear them on the cd singing with Dave and the Boys. Moral of the story... I ramble... and jump back an forth between ideas. Anyway, that is all I have to say about that.... More When I return from my trip this weekend. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Congrats to my boy Nick McPherson for making the  urlLink OU Drumline . Nick was one of my seniors from Noble High. He tried out at OU for the line and made snare. See Great Teachers....great students...LOL. Well I can't take all the credit... he has talent, just needed exposure to some real drumming. Real stuff that real lines play... so, Alan and I helped as much as we could... Still he learned alot, and is learning even more. I just wish all the kids down there had that potential. SOME could if they wanted to put their heart into it.  Anyway... I miss drumming so bad.. I went to Regal Cinemas and watched the DCI Championship Quaterfinals, LIVE from Denver. Makes me wish I was still involved as much as I wanted to be. Bills, and life get in the way though. Sucks...something you work so hard at... Bleed, Sweat, Cry, Give 110%, all to just basically do nothing with after it is all over. Take with you the fun, great, good times; and life lessons learned, and move on with your life. Try to make the next project you start at, the next thing you perfect. I am not saying that I perfected drumming.... no one will ever... but I put alot into it, and I think I am pretty good for my level of learning. I wish I would have had the oppertunity to take it to the next level. Funds was a major part. I did try out for the Blue Knights, and was told that if I had made the camp the month before, I would have probably been offered a spot. That was a great, and horrible feeling at the same time. Great in reguards that I knew I was good enough to make it, but horrible in the fact that I didn't. Much like many things in life.... another thing that passes you by....... 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well.. not doing anything. I am really bored... I guess I could start writing some stuff again. I really need to read some stuff before I do though. Anyway 3 days left... 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Not much to say today...except.. 6 more days to Dave... 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, let see.. Saturday was awesome... woke up about...7am... went and ate breakfast with the gang. At noon went iceskating until two... I could stay on the ice forever though...came home for a bit.. Met back in Moore at 5 at Taco Bueno, ate again and chatted until 6ish, then left and went to the Revival for Christ Church for the Jonah33 concert. Get there and it is three acts... The Preachaholics, Paul Wright, and Jonah33. All were great... I especially liked Paul Wright, and Jonah33. The Preachaholics were Gospel rap, and it was ok...not really into it, but I enjoyed it, when I could understand what they were saying... Sound system wasn't the greatest, and there were five of them all sing at the same time.... you know.. you have seen rap shows. Paul Wright... amazing... this "White Kid" basically (couldn't have been older than 23) is just his acoustic guitar, and a turntable DJ. It was awesome... he sings freestyle hip-hop/rap to acoustic and a turntable.. The DJ was awesome though, he played bongos....well I might add....while still doing the turtable. He also played Djembe really freaking good too. he was awesome... but the way Paul Wright could sing freestyle was just amazing.. VERY TALENTED KID. Jonah33 was really awesome too.. Great Rock group, that isn't all about LOUD AND HEAVY, no one can hears what we say or are doing... but still heavy enough to make you bang your head...LOL. All in all was an amazing time..... NEXT WEEKEND DAVE 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Man...is there anything better feeling that getting a good haircut.... I know there is, but still, if feel pretty dang good. Well... not a lot going on today... filled my car with gas, when to Wal-Mart, got my haircut, went and ate Mid Del Taco (I love that place) stopped by a pawnshop....just to see if there was something I couldn't live without, and there wasn't. Other than that... nothing going on... gotta work tonight, but hopefully it will be a quick day. Tomorrow, is going to be busy, so I guess I better rest up... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well it is only Thursday, and I am wishing it was Friday. That means that tomorrow would be Saturday, and we get to have our Saturday breakfast... Oh man it is so good to get all of us together, and cook, the food is absolutely wonderful.. Biscuits &amp; Gravy, Sausage, Pancakes, French Toast, Hasbrowns, Sweet Bread....just to list a few. (BTW sweet bread is some kinda of pecan pie type thing with biscuits rolled in cinnamon and sugar on top, then baked... it is SOOO good...oh yeah... it isn't really a pie, just reminds me of pecan pie) Anyway, I guess I have to wait another day. :-( 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Well I am not doing anything today, and it feels kinda nice.. Normally I am out running around doing things, or having to go to work and cover a double shift. Doesn't bother when I get the paycheck, but I hate going in to do it. But I guess that is pretty much life huh? Anyway a good friend of mine and I were talking about needing to write a song together... I mean... I am a musician, and she write some of the most beautiful poetry. HELLO.... Songs are poems to music...Well basically. Anyway she sent me a couple she wrote... I mean to tell you... I love them.. deep, dark, very personal....but at the same time very surface level.... if you know what I mean. You probably don't but oh well. Anyway I started into them... I had a little thing I had written that I thought that could just put words to it, or around the melody... NOPE... God stepped in and gave me something totally new. New melody and chord progression... the words seem to fit in perfectly with it... huh I wonder why (said sarcastically). NEway I guess I can post the lyrics to the chorus for now.. I haven't really put a lot into the verses yet. So here I guess. OH yeah, I have titled it LEAD ME  CHORUS  Take my hand  Show me your will I am lost Show me home Take my hand Show me your way Gently lead I will go.  With the music, I wrote with it, has a sound almost like ballad/celtic/folk to it... kind all those combined... I have never written anything like it before... but than again, I haven't really written much.  
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright, here we go... A little about me..  My name, Dilon Buser... I live in Del City, OK. I grew up mostly on the outskirts of Norman, out by Lake Thunderbird. I went to school in Moore, where I was in both the Jr High, and High School Band. I was on the drumline thru both, and absolutely love marching percussion. I taught Noble High's Drumline last summer, and hope to be involved again this year. I absolutely love the Dave Matthews Band... have been a fan since '97, and have been, I guess what you could call obsessed since about 3 years ago. Right about the time I started learning to play guitar. Yes, I play guitar, taught by myself, with a little help from some friends. For the most part though, all by myself.... I wanted to be able to play music, and being a percussionist, well, let's just say that I was limited by what I could play. Anyway, I have taught myself, and have been able to develop it further by playing with my Church Band. I started attending the Crown Center in Moore about a little over a year again... I was going thru some hard times, and some real depression, and needed a way out...I found God. Well enough that I wanted more, and stuck around. I think that playing with the band has helped me stay around longer than I thought I would have, but whatever the reason, I am still there....well kinda. WE moved into a new building so I guess it isn't in Moore anymore. BUT YOU GET THE IDEA. Other that all of this, not much to know about me.... oh I can't believe I almost forgot. I LOVE HOCKEY. About, wow...five years ago, a close friend of mine got me into it. I couldn't even stand on skates.... Barely the quads, muchless the inline skates... Quite funny I am sure it was... I didn't think so, but everyone that laughed must have. Anyway, I got good enough to join and team and started playing Inline Hockey in norman. I played there for about 2 years I think... Then I found the mother load of hockey, well atleast around here, ICE. I am so much a better ice skater that I was at inline. It took a while to adjust to the different environment, but I love it. I played all the time up until about a year ago, when work took most of my time. I still want to get out an play occasionally. Anyway, that is all I can think of for now... 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well this is the first time I have ever even thought about a blog. I have gotten from a few friends, that it is good for getting some things out. I don't know who will read this, or if anyone will....but we'll see if helps or not. SO.... anyway... that is it for now... gotta jet and meet Jeff for lunch.  Dilon 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>