<Blog>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        why the hell does everyone want to know what type of guys I like? why does it matter?! but anyway, Im listening to Slayer right now, Seasons in the Abyss to be exact.....I had a dream about it last night so its only suiting that I listen to it right now....its awsome, Im trying to play it on the drums....fuck! some creep just walked by.  I hear hes a drunk and hes really rude....oh well, Ill send my Minions after him soon enough....I watched a documentary on JFK Junior this morning, and it was pretty sad.  But I had t leave before it was over so I missed the conclusion, but I wonder....did someone sabotage the plane or was he really doing drugs or did he just crash?  Im not to well versed in the subject matter though, so Im not one to say....Im the only one of my age that I know of that actually watches documentaries anyway.....haha.  Everyone else is just stuck on fucking MTV, god I hate it, but I could type 50000 pages about why I hate it and why it sucks, but I just dont have that sort of time right now, but I will kill it someday....somehow......oh hell yeah, evanescence (I cant even spell it!) is real hardcore....why does everyone think amy lee is hot? shes not, Im a chic and Im not into that shit  but still, shes not hot! and no, I am not jealous!  but anyway, lets all get together and kill MTV, it poisons the mind that.....so hows it goin today? Megadeth told me to have a great day last  night  and it was awsome, Megadeth is awsome, I even blessed upon them a capital letter! Wahoo! so yeah, did you know that Im related to Chris Poland in some weird way? thats awsome, now I actually have something of interest to tell my friend/s but they dont know who he is....oh well! peace sells.......but whos buying?   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        If anyone is around the ottawa area and wants to go to a Metallica show (floor tickets) with a weird metalhead female you should respond to this post because nobody wants to come with me....just as long as you arent younger than 14 Im happy.....really dont want togo alone but youll have to pay about $100 but its worth it man. so reply and well talk , just as long as you arent younger than 15 Im happy.......   
    
</post>


<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        wahI woke up this morning and I couldnt for the life of me figure out why people would want to put hydrogen peroxide in their hair......but I had a brain cramp......whilst I was applying it to my ears I almost had a heart attack when I realized it was to bleach hair....doh!  ears are in close proximity to hair and I almost got some on my hair not that it would do much if I rinsed it off quickly but still.....I have blue black natural hair which I am very proud oh! *ahem* all the crazy people have to dye it! haha, yes my hair.....it changes colours.....My Hair: when I was little it was black, then it was dark brown, and now its black! [dont count all the times I've dyed it though, Im talkin natural colours here] just like my eyes, they were blue then they were dark brown, then they were this weird hazel colour and now theyre turnin green!  and I dont dye my eyes, trust me.....what a load of crap, havent I got anything better to do then to sit on my ass and type shit about my hair? uh, I started reading a new book today, Stephen King of course, who else.....Dreamcather this one, but Im only on page 15 but so far it seems good....I was also sad this morning because I couldnt take the dog for a stroll since I slept in and he seemed sad by that since he doesnt get much walks I dont think when Im not there.....I think he gets bad treatment, think of all the other abused animals! I really love animals, I get along with them better than people, so I guess I should just treat all the ones I meet the best I can and donate to animal charities and shit....listen to me! Im bullshittin again so I should go.....   
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hmmm.....Kerry King......hey, he got capital letters too right? so that must mean I like him right? well no I dont really like him exactly, but he is a kick ass guitarist, I was just listening to some of his solos....I just respect him, theres a better word.....haha, great....on the topic of solos, why the fuck isnt there more drum solos?! or bass even, bass solos sound good at least to my ears.....I almost never hear bass solos except when I went to that MetallicA show in may, when Sully (Godsmack) and the drummer (cant remember his name dammit) did like a 10 minute drum solo with like, tom toms and bongos and everything, now that was awsome, or at least I thought....Im not a high class top champion 1st place Neal Peart drummer person though but it sounded great, yes it did....they should  put that on their records....maybe they do......gah, we need more drum solos! FUCK GUITAR!!!!!! and singing too for that matter , unless you got a good growl like David Vincent or James Hetfield or Tom Araya [bet youd never heard those names all in the same sentence eh? I just love'' James, hes my hero....] then you should shut up! and none of these fake vocals like Angel Gossow did in some arch Enemy shows.....I dont care what the excuse is you pussy! anyway, hows buisness, fellows?  oh, have to go boost somebodys car......   
    
</post>


</Blog>