<Blog>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Its Tuesday and I am absolutely miserable, no, I'm annihilated.  Just last weekend, I was on top of the moon.  Now I feel like I'm on top of the city dump!  My mother brought up the wedding invitations and whether or not I'd sent them out and I snapped at her and made her cry!  Oh God, it was the worst!  Ari and I haven't spoken since we started seeing other people, and Peter hasn't responded to my emails OR my phone calls.  What's that all about?  Have I officially lost my mind?  Is there any chance of getting it back?  I emailed Ari earlier this morning (couldn't deal with actually calling him) "inviting" him to meet up with me for coffee.  Boy, do we have to talk!  Deep down, I have no doubts about marrying him, but something happened to me while I was fooling around with Peter.  I realized I needed more, and it has nothing to do with Peter or Ari, but with me.  I can't pretend to be content anymore.  I need to be assertive in getting what I want, and I need to learn to do that with Ari in my life.  My friend Jocelyn, who's been in the loop on my recent "experiment," emailed me about a new movie about a couple that decides to mess around before their wedding day.  It's aptly titled  urlLink SEEING OTHER PEOPLE , and stars Jay Mohr and hottie Josh Charles (I loved him in THREESOME!).  It comes out on video today so I plan on checking it out.  Could it be too close to the truth?  I do hope Ari and I can get it back together.  I miss him!--AG
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Had no time to write Saturday!  I was abducted, and not against my will!  Peter picked me up at the promised time on Saturday, but towards the end of the evening, told me I wasn't going anywhere!  At first, I thought he was teasing, but it didn't take long for me to realize he was not playing.  Was I scared?  At first, yes.  He pulled out these sheer stockings from his coat pocket, says, "I've been waiting fro this all night!" and while flashbacks of Tony Curtis as the Boston Strangler came to mind, he starts laughing hysterically.  Seeing the look on my face, which must have been funny to ANYONE else but me, he realized I was thinking the worst.  So when he reassured me that his intentionals were strictly sensual, I calmed down and listened to his request: that I tie HIM to the bedpost and have my way with him!  OMG squared!  I have never, NEVER, in my life dreamed of being a dominatrix nor did I ever imagine I'd have it in me.  I'm a nice Jewish girl from a nice Jewish family!  Do nice Jewish girls do this sort of thing?  Perhaps Betty Page was really Jewish because I discovered the beast within on August 14, 2004, and now there is no turning back!  The sex I had with Peter was amazing, no MORE than amazing!  I have never felt so pushed beyond myself, as if every curiosity I didn't even know I had was only partially quenched, and now I want more!  With my wedding day fast approaching, things are going to have to change between me and Ari, who God only knows how things are going with him!  I haven't talked to him in ages, and its LATE and I have an early morning tomorrow.  But I'm still singing like a magpie!  More later...AG
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OMG!  I met my "mystery" man Friday night and the experience, which was only meant for one evening, is becoming a weekend love affair!  His name is Peter, and he's an investment banker for one of the larger investment firms here in San Francisco.  He's tall, with remnants of what was once a lanky frame in his youth.  That's not to say he's overweight or out of shape.  On the contrary, his tall, lean frame has filled out nicely from working out regularly in the gym.  He has salt and pepper black hair and jubillant, encouraging green eyes.  He has big hands and a deep, masculine voice.  Friday night, he made me feel like I've never felt before: coddled, pampered, and very sexy.  We made love last night!  I've never slept with anyone on the first night!!! So anyway, he's picking me up at noon today to continue our rendevous!  Its all top secret!  I have no idea where we're going, what we're doing, or what I should wear!  I'm acting like a giddy little girl!  It's great to be alive! Later!---AG
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This was not an easy arrangement to come to.  Both my fiance and I did some major soul-searching, asking tough questions of ourselves and of each other.  Would seeing other people weaken the foundation of our relationship?  Would our love for each other somehow weaken and fade away?  Our future plans for marriage were at stake! In the end, we believed in ourselves and each other, and felt that pre-marital exploration would, if anything, lead to a more broadened perspective on our own relationship and of ourselves as individuals. Over the next couple of weeks, I will begin my own exploration, and seek experiences with other people that I have yet to know.  In fact, my first encounter will take place this evening. More to come...
      
</post>


</Blog>