<Blog>


<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Beautiful mural on one of the buildings in Crawford.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Alison hanging out in Dubya's ZIP code...&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Because my parents are extremely cool and I enjoy traveling on gasoline purchased by other people, I have embarked on a weekend trip to Granbury, TX to spend time with my family. We have fun in store for us because any section of Texas is just bursting with interesting sights and tempting shopping, but the best part of my journey took place today on the way up to Granbury. This trip will include a trip to see the dinosaur prints in Glen Rose, shopping on the town square in Granbury and seeing the sights in Cowtown; as enjoyable as all of this may be, none of it could compare with the 8 mile detour from our route on Highway 6 into Crawford today. Crawford seems simple enough with its population of 705 and its identity as a farming community, but there is something very special about this little town. In 1999, George and Laura Bush purchased a ranch just outside the sleepy little town and Crawford went from a place people accidentally detoured to a place people centered vacations around.       Being in Crawford today was a joy for this Babe for Bush! There are several shops featuring Texana and country chic decor while others feature jewelry and clothing. Each of these little shops also carries a wide array of Bush 2004 and "Crawford, Home of President and Mrs Bush" merchandise. They are all so pround that the President and First Lady chose to call their charming little town home. The locals treat guests with utmost courtesy and their adoration for our President and First Lady is evident after seconds of conversation. Every storefront had a Bush banners and most yards had Bush signs up, so I was feeling very much at home.       During our two hours in Crawford, we managed to make a haul while shopping on Main Street. I am now the proud owner of Bush buttons, a Bush Cheney 2004 t-shirt, a Crawford magnet and some booty to bring home to my Bush loving grandparents. We also ate lunch at the little restaurant that has been featured numerous times on the news as George and Laura seem to have an affinity for the cheeseburgers served there. I had the cheeseburger as well and opted for the onion rings favored by the President rather than the friend jalapenos favored by our first lady; I'll have to give those a shot next time. After eating lunch, we drove out toward the President's residence, Prairie Chapel Ranch. We knew, of course, that we would not be able to actually drive by the ranch. Generally, anyone can drive by the ranch so long as the stay on the main road, but we knew the President was actually occupying The Western White House today and such a trip would not be allowed. We drove out as far as we could, wanting to get a feeling for the land our President calls home, before being turned away by a local deputy and a secret service agent.       If you are ever out around Waco and are thinking about detouring, definitely do it. Crawford is a charming town with great people, nice gift shops and delicious onion rings.  I believe I'll visit again, perhaps during our 43rd President's second term. :-)  
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A liberal pundit attempted to politicize this picture from a Yale yearbook by saying Bush was unsportsmanlike and not fit for office. I look at it and say he's got hustle. Who better to lead our nation in a time of tribulation?&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        OK, so John Kerry is not the most ridiculous politico in the United States. I think we'd all agree that he is no competition for New Jersey's Governor "I am a gay American" McGreevy. However, when Democrats finally realize that this New Jersey situation could hurt them and force McGreevy to resign, Kerry will, in fact, be on the top of that list (since Barney Frank has been quiet lately.)  President Bush announced on Monday that 100,000 troops will be reassigned from their positions in South Korea and Europe. This makes a lot of since, especially considering the purpose of having troops in such places to begin with. We needed troops in Europe during the Cold War because the United States realizes that strength and power brings added responsibility. The Cold War has ended and having troops in Europe is no longer the necessity it once was.  John Kerry, in typical election year criticism, says,     "Nobody wants to bring troops home more than those of us who have fought in foreign wars, but it needs to be done at the right time and in a sensible way. This is not that time or that way."  That's interesting, because two weeks ago Kerry was on the record saying,  "If the diplomacy that I believe can be put in place can work, I think we can significantly change the deployment of troops not just there but elsewhere in the world, in the Korean peninsula, perhaps, in Europe, perhaps."  They don't call him flipper for nothin'.  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Alison at Six Flags with a really cool caricature of one of her favorite Texans and the fellow she is voting for in November. :-D  urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Alison and Erin living it up at Six Flags...or at least having their heads pasted on someone else's body because they wouldn't put up the 13 bucks for the real picture. &nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       OK, so this is a first. I have not been able to sleep. I've never been ashamed of the fact that I, Alison, am a night owl. Everyone knows I am a night owl. This is news to no one. The eerie part is that I have had my first completely sleepless night. Sure, I've pulled all-nighters, but none of those all nighters occurred while I lay in my bed attempting to sleep. See, my all-nighters were either typical church lock-in or college fare. This is some weird adulthood sleepless night and quite frankly, it's freaking me out.       The lock-in/slumber party all-nighters were never a problem for me. I was always the girl that could really pull off that whole not sleeping thing. I was also the girl who dug in the luggage of the sleeper, pulled out a bra and panties, soaked them down in water, stuck in 'em in a plastic bag and then opened the freezer. I was the girl who made enemies at slumber parties and felt absolutely no shame. Lock-ins were never big sleeping events for me, either. I think it had to do with two fundamental problems: social butterfly syndrome and idonotsleeponfloorsitis.  It's pretty simple, really. When I have friends around, I won't sleep. I'll just stay up and giggle, flirt, tell wild stories and never miss the sleep. Also, I don't sleep on floors. I mean, sure, I'm sure I could, but I always believed it was useless to put my body through such torture when I could fall into my own bed, exhausted, at 9 AM. After all, anyone who has ever pulled an all-nighter would agree that the best sleep comes with pure exhaustion.       College all-nighters were not so different, only cooler. I loved and mastered the art of not sleeping in college. My freshman year was filled with all-nighters; my mother worried, but she was sure I'd outgrow my passion for all-nighters by the middle of the first semester. That didn't really happen. I did eventually start sleeping, but the majority of that sleep occurred during the daytime hours between my last class of the day and supper. Then, after supper we would begin our "day." It was awesome. My sophomore year was quite similar, as my roommate was a night owl and we would have a blast sitting up drinking Tallsups (that's coke, people) and singing never ended renditions of "Sing and Be Happy." We were both altos, so we'd take turns on the parts. There were also more memorable specific all-nighters.  One great example is election night 2000. I had an incredible election party with a ton of friends and even a professor. I figured they'd all be out by 1, and the ones that lingered until that time would be the talkers. However, my first guests began leaving at 2 and the last guest left at 6. See, we had no idea what was in store for the American people and we had this pipe dream that Florida would somehow have their butterfly ballots and general incompetencies sorted out by 6 AM. We were wrong. Clean-up in the kitchen lasted until around 7:15 and the snow had begun falling at 7. I don't drive in snow, so I skipped class and caught up on my sleep that morning.       Tonight's all-nighter is not even comparable to the all-nighters of my youth. Those were intentional. This one is completely accidental and totally frustrating. Because I am leaving for Six Flags at 6:30, I rolled my sleepless, energy charged body out of my bed at 5:30, deciding that minutes of sleep would only make me tired. Now I can keep myself awake by worrying that falling asleep on the Titan will cause my neck to snap in two. This could be the beginning (or middle?) of a very interesting day.  
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Football Debate....&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Looking back to the 2000 Election cycle, I actually thought the Democrats would learn a thing or two about making up incredibly stupid stuff; after all, Al Gore didn't fool anybody with his "I invented the internet!" load of bull. Apparently, John Kerry and his psychotic sidekicks are seeking to prove they can get away with lies more effectively than the last Democratic presidential candidate. It seems Kerry would have shied away from the lies after his "Christmas in Cambodia" experience, a story he has told 50 times and an experience that was "seared" into his memory, was proven to be untrue this past week. That was a big one. Anyway, today in response to the Bush campaign's criticism of Kerry's absence during important votes concerning intelligence, the Kerry campaign replied saying Kerry had once served as Vice-Chairman of the Intelligence committee. It seems that Kerry's folks need to check their facts. Kerry did at one time serve in that capacity, but it wasn't John Kerry; Bob Kerry did, however, do a splendid job as Vice-Chairman of the Intelligence committee. I certainly don't expect to see this anywhere but Fox.   Oh, and this just in from abcnews.com:       As his plane was flying from Oregon to Idaho on Saturday, Kerry defended his taste in sports, saying, "The guys who do it are all local guys -- plumbers, construction workers." Asked if these regular folks fly from one state to another, the husband of the condiment heiress downplayed the cost, saying, "What? 250 bucks for a ticket?" Luckily for Kerry, the moment was not on camera. But it was the kind of moment -- if captured on camera -- that could undo months of work.       This guy is trying waaaaay too hard.  Not much else going on in Alisonville, just the obsessing over politics. After all, I think I was the only kid in the 4th grade who not only watched every moment of both conventions on TV during the election of 1988, but also kept a scrapbook of political cartoons and political ads from the election. of course, I was also the kid who chose to buy a set of old campaign buttons at the LBJ library in Austin instead of going for some other fun souvenir. I really love election years. My blood pressure goes up and down and I feel like I'm getting a workout without ever setting foot in a gym. Must remind myself that sitting on the couch watching election coverage will not improve physical fitness. I think this will be a fun campaign for a lot of reasons. First of all, it's pretty tight right now. It's a heated race and those are the most fun. Also, we have the down-to-earth Texan on the Republican ticket and uptight and overpolished Mr. Heinz Kerry on the Democratic ticket. We're just warming up and I can't wait. :-)   
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Alison holding the Bible she won for saying her 66 books of the Bible and hoping to never be a distraction again...  urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yesterday I was sitting in morning worship services, singing some of the greatest hymns ever and attempting to suppress the HUGE smile on my face that kept creeping up as the child behind me amused me with his enthusiastic singing. It's not that I have a problem with smiling while I praise God. It's just that this was the song used to prepare our minds for communion, I was about to turn to Isaiah 53 to meditate during the Lord's Supper and I was on the verge of giggling. I admit, I was a little distracted, but children are such wonderful distractions. After all, the congregation that worships quietly without the sounds of children occasionally interrupting is likely a congregation without children present, and that's just sad. Also, I remember the numerous times I was slapped around for being a distraction and I realize that I  deserve  to be tested by distraction in church. There were the times I made faces at various people in the building (at least until my parents or my Mi-mommy caught me) and my brother and I did once fumble the communion tray (the juice, no less) in a way that was not only distracting, it almost made us run short of juice. I started thinking about my most distracting (not to mention embarrassing) moments during worship services and to be honest, they aren't memories from my early childhood, when it is natural to do embarrassing things. One occurred when I was in junior high, while the other two occurred in college. Yikes!     When I was growing up, I would sit next to my great-grandmother on the second row on Sunday mornings. She needed to sit there as they had hearing aids that were wired into the sound system available on the second row. I would find the song numbers for she and one of her friends, as they had trouble hearing them clearly (the hearing aid thingies were way overrated) and I would also grab their hands occasionally to let them know the song a song was over and they could quit holding the note. ;-) This just happened to be right in front of the preacher and his family. I had really long hair and loved to play with it. I was flipping it back and swinging it, just like any prissy preteen. When the preacher stood up to do his sermon, he started walking and I felt tremendous pain! I yelped out loudly. He couldn’t walk any further because something was holding him back. That something would have been my hair. It was all tangled and entwined in his clip-on microphone. I managed to get it tangled in there pretty good. He started working it out, and when he realized it would be a while, the song leader got up and led a few songs. I think there was more laughing going on than singing, though.  My junior year at Abilene Christian, I was walking in late for chapel. If you’ve ever been to Moody Coliseum you know that it is circular and you can pretty much see anyone in any section. There were probably about 3,000 people in the coliseum that day. They had already started singing and everyone was already seated. I saw my friends up in section F on about the 12th row and headed up that way. . Once I saw my friends, they started laughing because I was late and people were staring. I sort of laughed a bit too, then I started running up the steps. I was really going quick and high kneeing it up the steps. I guess my knee didn’t come up high enough because I sure enough tripped and fell facedown, fully sprawled, spread eagle on the steps. All of section F started laughing and there were chuckles coming from other areas, as well. For the rest of the day, people from sections C, J, K, L, you name it, were coming up to me and telling me they saw it.  Another chapel story... My last spring semester at ACU, I walked into chapel and I was, once again, late. I was wearing a really cute sun dress that came just to the knee. It was floral and I had bought it at the Gap the day before. I really thought I looked good! I was also wearing a new pair of flip flops that matched it. Anyway, off of the fashion trip. My friends had saved me a seat in the middle of the row and there were strangers on both ends. I didn’t want to crawl over a bunch of people, so I did a pretty common thing and just stepped on the seat below and was going to step up to the row where they were sitting. Well, the seats are staduim/theatre seats that flip up and when I stepped up the seat, my right flip flop fell off and slipped down into the fold of the seat. I shifted my weight and the seat folded up. My foot fell down in it and my dress flipped up, which exposed a good bitt of flesh. It was extremely embarrassing. My friends were laughing, I was laughing and my flip flop was missing. It is also really hard to get your foot unstuck from a fold up seat, but even harder when you can’t stop laughing. I finally got up and found my flip flop after chapel.    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    President Bush Visits with victims of a Missouri tornado&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Although I love keeping up with news and current events and rather enjoy being able to turn on my television and see news at any given time, I cannot help but hate the pioneer of the 24 hour news cycle. I despise CNN and almost every time I flip over to CNN I despise the channel more. I don't hate the newscasters, because they are people and that's just wrong; I simply hate what they do. I hate the way their liberal slant makes my lunch linger in my throat. I hate the way their anti-Bush sentiment makes my blood pressure rise. I hate the way their snide, underhanded leftist remarks motivate me to waste moments of my life writing about them. Nonetheless, I feel the need to vent. That's why I have this blog thing anyway, right?  As anyone who has glanced at the front page of a newspaper today knows, Florida was hit by a devastating hurricane that goes by the name of Charley. Charley was destructive and vicious, leaving a trail of material ruin and sadly, families grieving for their loved ones. Today, the day after the storm, President Bush announced that he would be visiting Florida to survey the destruction and make sure relief workers had all they needed. That's what Presidents do, right?  Then we have CNN's take on the situation. Moments ago, a CNN newscaster made this statement:     "This President usually doesn't go to disaster areas. With an election only 79 days away, one must wonder if politics are involved."     CNN followed up this gem by showing John Kerry throwing a football (and looking a bit on the queer side) with an aide and noting his willingness to be supportive of the people of Florida during this time. You know, John Kerry didn't make a statement about natural disasters a year ago. Of course this time, CNN didn't say, "With an election only 79 days away, one must wonder if politics are involved."  The President usually doesn't go to disaster areas? WHAT? This is a president who has been defined by his comfort to people in a time of disaster. This is the man who visited Ground Zero days after the September 11 attacks, stood on a pile of rubble, grabbed a bullhorn and made a promise to the people of New York and the people of America. The archives on CNN's website contains an article stating that President Bush visited the victims of tornadoes in Missouri. Less than a year ago, Bush went to Virginia to inspect hurricane damage and basically do exactly what he is planning to do tomorrow morning. Hmmm...with just over 400 days left before the November 2004 election, one must wonder if politics are involved. Stupidity.  I have sneaking suspicion that CNN would pound the president for any decisions at this point in time. Had Bush decided NOT to go to Florida, what would CNN say? Would they call him cold and uncaring? Out of touch? I suppose we will never know, because as president, George W. Bush is doing his job. Deciding not to visit Florida for fear of having his actions work against him in the election would be like a senator (not that I have anyone in particular in mind) skipping important votes in order to campaign.     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Yay, it's Friday the 13th and I   took my last Summer final today! It was pretty quick and painless, which is right up my alley. Anyway, just thought I'd post my favorite college final joke because my brain is much too tired for blogging today.       Joey was taking Calculus at UCLA. He struggled with it, and worried about failing. Final exam time came, and he studied and studied, but, still he was not ready. The Professor passed out the exams and told the class that they had only 30 minutes. Every five minutes, he reminded the class how much time was left. This only made Joey more and more nervous. Finally, after 30 minutes, the Professor said, "Stop! The exam is over. Turn them in!" One by one, the papers were handed in. But, Joey just kept working on that exam. The Professor decided to wait it out and see how long it would take him. After another 20 minutes, Joey turned in his exam. The Professor asked him, "What are you doing?" Joey answered, "Turning in my exam." The professor then told Joey, "The exam was over 20 minutes ago. You have failed!" Joey then looked the Professor in the eye, and asked, "Do you know who I am?" The professor answered, "No." Then Joey asked, "You really don't know who I am, do you?" as if he were a very important person. The Professor again, said, "No, I don't know who you are and I don't care!" Then Joey shoved his exam right in the middle of the other exams, that were on the Professor's desk, and said, "Good!"      Genius, pure genius! I wish I could pull that off, but, unfortunately, all my professors know (and fear) me.  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The kid behind the crazy wolf story...  urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Here is a little story my cousin Cole dictated to me when he was 7 years old. I came across it today and I kinda like it. Enjoy!      Once upon a time, there was a three headed old man in his cabin. He had three dogs, one for each head. They were called Uno and Mino and Calico. He had a crack through his cabin. Late one night, the old man heard a strange sound. Just as the old man started to run, he reached for a taily-po. A mad wolf came through the door and chased the ma, but the old man lost him. The old man cooked it and ate it and he went to sleep. But he wasn’t asleep very long. He could hear a “Scratch” and the old man said, “What’s that?” Those dogs ran and tore the fence down. That splooter had left those dogs way in the swamp. The old man was by himself and went out and called his dogs. He said, “Heeeah, Heeeah!” The dogs did not come, but the old man threw some snot over at the wolf. So the old man went back to sleep. When he went to his bed, a furry wolf was laying under the covers and he said, “You know, and I know, and I want my taily-po.” The wolf could see him and he got clearer and clearer. The wolf reached out to scratch him in the face, but he old man was too fast. He jumped out of the way. And the old man said, “Hang on a second. I have to use the bathroom. Hang on wolf.” And he jumped in the toilet and flushed himself into the swamp. And he was stuck in the toilet and the wolf could see him and he got closer and closer. And he said, “goodnight” and that thing scratched everything up and the old man went back to sleep. The next morning he chopped the wolf’s head off and made some wolf’s head cheese. Then he said, “I’ll have another wolf come to my house tomorrow. It will be real comfy.”  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My brother and I with our great grandparents.  urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I spent the past weekend at my parents' house in Buna and, because I am quite a night owl, found myself awake and looking at family pictures long after the rest of my family had gone to sleep for the night. Seeing pictures of myself at all ages and with family and friends who impacted my life led me to reflect on my life and the blessings in it.     One could say that I led a charmed life as a child; my childhood was carefree--idyllic, even-- and I was never burdened with the worries of so many children in the world. The pictures showed me the ways in which my family, my church family and my community impacted me and shaped the person I am today.     The first set of pictures I came across were of my family and I. There were baby pictures of me being held by my parents, grandparents, great-grandparents, aunts, uncles and others who nurtured me and loved me. I was actually  always  being held, which  might  explain why I talked at 6 months but didn't take my first step until I was about a year old. ;-) There were pictures of me as a child playing with family members, learning how to interact with people and feeling completely confident and a stranger to vulnerability. There were pictures of family holidays, pictures showing a family that was thrilled to be together and thankful for every day of life we'd been blessed with.       On my second box of pictures, I came across pictures of the people I'd been surrounded by as a child in church. I saw photos of my friends and I at church activities and photos of the adults in the congregation that made all of that possible. I saw pictures of myself being encouraged, edified and treated like a person with a purpose, even when I did not seem capable of doing much more than running around sweating or coming up with new ways to be a smarty pants. These were the people who taught me the value of service to others and showed me Christ's love through their own love.    The third set of photos were taken at the Buna Redbud Festival, South Jasper County Little League Opening Ceremonies, at school and at other important places and events in the sleepy little town of Buna, TX. Growing up in a small town gave me a unique perspective on life. I am of the opinion that a small town is a wonderful microcosm where the residents learn about loving picture and have a special understanding of human nature and the types of people who make up the world. In my small town, I saw compassion for the helpless, colorful personalities, and the value of community.   These photos reminded me of all the things that made me who I am and have shaped the way I view the world. I am thankful for Kodak, that I can go back and see these memories in living color, and I am thankful for the people who gave me these memories .                  
    
</post>


</Blog>