<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had to write this 3 times cause I HATE COMPUTERS  Congrats to Phelps for winning his 2nd gold, but you need to stop listening to Eminem.  Meryl, encourage people not to date this year, you have a lot of authority in school this year.  Pray for Bigham, and me, we both are looking for guys to hold us up in our faith.  I am getting people to swim left and right, lets just see if there word holds up.  Im getting to know all my teachers and slowly gaining some leverage.  Today was chapel and it was weird, maybe I’m not used to having Evander Holyfeild sit in my chapels. I actually said hello. Maybe I’ll burn him a CD or something.  Jamie, I got some good pictures today. It’s been a while sense I’ve hit anyone so I hit my brother, I got in trouble. Good luck with the nerds.  I get to see Jason Upton this weekend….I hope you all get to see him before Jesus come back.  urlLink www.jasonupton.com  What’s your view on not kissing after getting engaged…should you try and make it to the wedding day without kissing…...? 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      holy crap, im so pissed off, I just wrote my best blog ever and just finished and it kicked me off. AHHHHHHHHHH! heres the short version, Spilt nesquick powder on floor, Put it back in container along with cat and dog hair, I still drank it all, Got in trouble.  Congrats to Phelps, first gold medal for the USA. Would you rather stare at the sun until you go blind or have 5 finger nails pulled from your body? ouch and animal hair tastes weird..... 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The clock watches you to see if your watching it, don't stare, its rude, a glance every once in a while, and your ok, but if you stare oh how the clock will treat you badly.  I glanced up at my clock in that study hall, we have study hall on a block schedule and that means its an hour and a half of working on work no teacher has given yet. Very slow class. Well I got out my bible, and began to read. I really am starting to get curious over the way Matthew, Mark, and Luke write down what Jesus has to say. Luke, being the doctor, is very careful to throw in the details, which means there's not a lot of laziness. Mark writes the more miracles than either but out of the ones everyone has his are always the shortest, (or close to it) This shows that he wants to put everything he can into his work and save space or is he being lazy. Matthew is a little harder to figure out, he has a different heart when it comes to his writings, but I need your help. I recommend that whenever you read a verse in Matthew, Mark, or Luke, look up the verse done by the other two. Underline if a sentence was said in all three, this normal means it has significance, for example, In the parable of the mustard seed, all three talk about the birds landing in the tree.....must be important. And circle the things that only one of them say, It's a really fun thing to do. back to study hall, I got hunger pains at 11:20, kept reading bible and found a verse that spoke to me, Phill. 2: 3-11, and after feeding myself spiritually my physical hunger went away. I tried to think about food and to see if I could bring it back but it was gone. I still had an apatite but the pain was gone. Amazing, nah, I just look at it like God just making a hard school day a whole lot better.  Here's my question, In the Passion, the movie shows Satan screaming in fury and rage when Jesus dies on the cross, But I thought Satan wanted Jesus to die on the cross, and Satan wasn't beaten until the resurrection......? 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To see where the night might leave, ok, I got this of a real life TV show, but It could be showing up real shortly in the lives of the American people. It's about  Suicide.  I think we all have they same view, never the less, I will try to mix things up here. The police had arrested a woman because she was the last one at the scene, a suspect, it was latter proved a suicide, which is true, here's where it gets weird. This lady arrested has a fatal and painful disease and has thought about killing herself. She started a blog and thought it would cure some depression. It did at first. Then when she thought nothing else could help, she started getting emails from people who were also thinking of killing themselves, to make a long story short, she ended up helping and encouraging, from teenagers to old people, to give up and stop living in pain and to kill themselves. She had been doing it for years, through the internet. Well the reason they found her at the scene of a crime was because one of her "patients" tried a suicide and it failed, the patient called her and asked if she would bring over some insulin (she had a small doctors license) so she could overdose, she brought it the drug over and handed it to her patient and said good luck, and left before the act was committed, as the doctor left the building a camera got her leaving so that's how the cops tied her to it. The patient did kill herself. She never once 'touched' a "patient". Well it went to court and the two side came up like this... We should be able to choose what we want with our bodies.... or Even failed suicide attempt patients are happy they made it through the tough times...  Overall I want to ask you, the judge ruled mis-trial and the doctor got off because the jury was at a dead lock for like 14 hours or something. If you had complete power as a judge what would you charge her with. If the doctor encouraged my daughter to kill herself I would want her dead for murder....but is it murder. But what if someone had a painful, fatal disease, is it right to encourage someone to give up.  I want to encourage you to uplift people and to not try to drag people down, from your enemies to your brothers and sisters, for me, I'm at a dead lock on this conversation, hope I got you thinking....... 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok I want to start with something tricky, "My Mom said that what my Dad said was true, But my Dad said that what my Mom said was false, Then my Mom saying Dad was true is really false, Then if what my Dad said was false then my Mom was true, And if my Mom was true.................ouch that hurt to write.....  Ok well hello everyone. I really want to challenge you guys on a spiritual level. Stay around. In Bible today my Bible teacher made us right out our mission statement.......A mission statement is a statement that sums up what you want your life to represent and what you want to do in your life for God. Here's mine.  " My overall mission statement is to worship the Father in everything I do, and everywhere I go. And to be a constant working instrument in my father will."  The reason I used the word instrument was because a tool, or instrument, is used to accomplish or help get to a main over all objective. It may be a small part of getting it accomplished but at least I relies that I want to have a part in it. one more question.....  We know Jesus had to die for our sins.....But did he have to die on a CROSS? Be careful.  Heres a verse that will also make you think about something else. Isaiah 53:2-3 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If school today could be described as a jellybean, it would be cocoanut flavored, my reasons being that every so rare ocation it tastes really good. But after a while it will make you very sick. The girls at landmark are quite friendly, probably because I'm the new kid. It happens. The guys on the other hand aren't very nice, I have like 70 friends female and 2 friends male. Its not my fault. I am afraid however to talk with certain girls for longer than 5 min. Because the same guy or guys show up right as I start talking to her. It seems no one really dates publicly a lot, maybe a few groups. But I don't want to get killed for talking with some one else's hubby. Over all its a school with the strictest rules and regulations. I swear that if they go to walking in a line to and fro, that I will be returing to NC. You cant were a shirt with a logo on it. Instead of searching for drugs there like,  "Hey Jimmy, this kid has a shirt with a logo in his locker, the usual punishment? OK! "  I haven't found where the sceams are coming from but I sure am sick of seeing the light flicker. Oh well, On a good note, my art teacher has some photography in her college background and will be teaching a course on it for the last end of the year and she is letting me sort of be a leader in that department. Fun Fun, she is even going to put up some of my work. I also got to show my Bible teacher something new he had never understood in the Bible, Matthew 8, jesus and the centurion, try to find out why Jesus was  Astonished , no one in the history of the Bible has  Astonished  Jesus except this guy......Call me after 9 at 678-787-6858 and I will tell you, It gets deep and you might not figure it out....  that's my challenge, I enjoy school for now, ask me some tough questions, If I don't know I'll make something up and you'll probly believe it. But I leave you with a tough question..... If you only had one animal species under you control and power what species would it be? 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I completely forgot to say goodbye to sweet summer and to say that "that jerkhead fall can bring his pretty leaves cause I have school tomorrow", the good thing the pool opens for swimming in 2 months! go swim team. If summer's a cliff then I'm jumping tonight. Hang on NC, I'll be back for homecoming! Oct. 1st. Just count away sweet Oct. (thats a band). Woe is me. Oh she doth teach the tourches to burn brightly. The weird-bobble head kid is bringing himself to a small town in GA, Oh how change is around the corner. smiles. I am so dead. Everyone ask David B. why I would die if I went to jail. He's right. Enjoy Jesus. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello, This is a place I have longed to enter. Somewhere that will let my fingers talk for themselves and the relief can be an upmost revival. Tomorrow I reunite with 7 wonderful kids that I went to school with in third grade. The things we remember are scarce but refreshingly surprising. For example I kissed a girls hand and she told on me, which by the way happened in my Gold Aerostar Mini Van, well, I got in trouble and the other day she actually apologized, It was weird. I hate using periods at the end of my sentence so you will see a lot of comma's. 6 girls and 1 guy, excluding me, will start to hang out and see how much of the 3rd grade we can act out through out this hectic 11th year of high school. I had crushes on 3 of these girls and I am testing to see if crushes then mean anything now. So far nothing but the longing to hang out with cool people, School should be fun, Its sorta the feeling of coming home from a night of tricker-treating and realizing that you have more candy then anyone in your family.......It actually happened once, I think. For those smart enough to find this site already I congratulate you with this, rootbeer jellybeans are quite good even if they look like the shampoo jellybean. Ok as you read this I'm already working on other post's so Enjoy and follow along to see if my default personality can survive art class with about 20 sophomore girls (really), I kinda scared...... I miss NC, you'll understand on my next post. I leave you with a question. Would you rather live with a 100 old people (80-90's) or a 100 crying babies? very scary. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>