<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WEll I am not relaly sure when my last update was, but i have been really busy wit ths and stuff. I started to play Doom 3 and wow... all i have to say is that you will need adult diapers if you play that.School sux but it is 1/36 over. If that is not close enoguth then there is no hope for us all. I am going to frys today at noon. if you wanna come let me know... If i like you i will take you...fi not sorry... SUX FOR YOU Anyway... Continue with you lives, Mega Man is back on... and I CANT MISS IT!
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I finished my reading last night, and didnt go to bed till like 12 - 1...but that is not the point, I got up this moring and was at school at 6:30, and that is also not the point...THe point is that today was freshem orientation thing... it was "fun. and by "fun" I mean "more fun than a sledge hammer to the nuts.""(Thank y9ou Mr. ALlison for putting that so wonderfully.) I realized now why nobdoy likes freshmen, because I bet we were the same way a few years ago. Any way After that was all over with, I went and saw all of the teachers in which homework was a possibility.... and found out hat my only homework is to shop, which is no problem. My teachers seem nice, but I have learned to never judge a book by its cover. speaking of books.... the reading that I had been freaking out about doing last weekend... YEA... IT IS OPTIONAL, THAT IS LAMEEEEEE!!!!! I DO NOT DO OPTIONAL ASSIGNMENTS, unless i turn in an ond project again. So anyway I HATE SCHOOL, and school hates me! That is all, Dont forget that you can get 10 bucks for doing nothing by going to  urlLink http://www.freeiPods.com/default.aspx?referer=7875766  (sign up with a free email account), then once you ahve done that sign up for a 14 day free trial of ancestory.com  Use it for like 2 or 3 days, cancel it.... and when it registers on me... I will give you 10 bucks... and all you have lost is that you will get some spam... so make a bogus email account?!?! 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WEll, it appears that thanks so some of my awsome and wonderful friends, I am almost 1/2 way done... w00t! (I DIDNT cheat or get all the answers, I foudn out I only had to 2 sections instead of three) anyway... THat is all, carry on with your lives, nothing important!
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well.. yesterday was yesterday... Got up late... Took sister to school.... ate lunch with Jon H. and then went to School for THS... O Yea, by the way if you are in THS, especially if you are on the leadership team, I am pissed off at you. We made teacher webpages yesterday, and by we I mean Sam, Jon H (NOT EVEN A TURNER STUDENT!!!!) and I, there were insufficient people and so nobody could keep teachers comming.... SO THANK YOU YOU UNGLY RETARD!  Anyway after that I came home and did some reading... I am now on philospher 5 of 19... and I am officially screwzored! Anyway... Adios 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, well, look what we have here.... Come here little children I promise that all is well! Ok anyway today was a very unique day...I watched tv till like noon....went to school (BAH school starts in 4 days which is the !cool) then once we got done at school we went to CiCi's for some hella good pizza o btw if you have not been to the CiCi's at Beltline and Josey... go NOW, well after you finish reading my blog... it is proally the best cici's... anyway by the time that i was done with that and got home it was like 4:30 and I basically went and falled asleep. O well se la vi. I just woke up about 10-15 minutes ago and now am writing in my blog...  The problem is... I was supposed to do about 5 of dem dere philosophers for IDeas that shape a nation.... Have not done it yet... and i reallly got to do it cus i am on philospoher 2 of 19 and all 19 and Huck Fin shate gots to be done by Monday...so pray for me... Or give me a free IPOD... dont pretend like u dont know how either.... Read my last post...    DEEEP THOUGHTS:   Do fish get thirsty? Why do teachers assign all this crazy work over the summer that nobody does till the last minute anyway? 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok today was really uneventful...took a nap....went to frys.... worked on summer reading, that reminds me... recenty a website has come to my attention in which you get a moth of unlimited   LEGAL    music downloading.... and I get an ipod if i can get 5 of you to do this...so it is reallly a win win for everyone... SO GO HERE  urlLink http://www.freeiPods.com/default.aspx?referer=7875766  Did i mention that the first 5 people who do this and sign up for an offer will recieve 10 dollars CASH.... and if that dont make u wanna do it... YOU ARE A LOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO  OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOSER Ok, and now for a new section that will hopefuly be included in each post...    DEEP THOUGHTS:     (I am to tired to think of anythign deep right nwo... but i promise there will be two tomorrow)  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, well.... here we go basically I have decided to begin a blog so now you guys gots to suffers through my Awsome gramma and poor spelling abilitys as well as my PIMPTASTIC capitalization, I really wanna see if I Can make an entire post with no puncuation, for no other reason other than I think it will look cool,  So here we go today was a day, it started hella early and got over late, it is kinda like a day that you have where you go and do stuff, but dont really get anything done! DOH!!!! i just realized that commas and the like are puncation. THAT SUX! o well back to the story... wait...there really aint much more to this story, o well DEAL WITH IT! I was teching all day is what i think i was getting at, but now i no longer rember because i just drank like a ton of dr pepper wich is i think the reason i decided to collect gmail accounts... O well school starts in less than a week and i still gots both books to read and do assignments on... now my vision is starting to go blurry and i thinking that blinking is a good idea fo realz.... BLA COMMENT OR SUFFEEER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! _PS incase  u didnt understand I WANT FEEEDBACK BIZZLES 
    
</post>


</Blog>