<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think the reason I hate physics is the teacher, Ms. Miller(the skinnier of the two). I think she thinks that we are all stupid. So, she decides to teach us like that. I just feel like yelling at her, "Do we look fucking stupid?". Other than that class and everything else is going pretty well. Jen and I are doing well, which is always good. Graduation is May 19, I'm counting down the days. Only...oh screw it there's still a lot of days left. If you want to know exactly get a calendar and do the counting yourself. Sorry if it seems I have an attitude, I really don't. Control the pet population and have your pets spayed or neutered. Till next time everyone.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So nothing exciting has happened lately. However, I did go to LSU for fan day and saw Coach Saban as well as many great Tiger players. I also saw some of my friends from last year who graduated, I'm gonna miss those guys. Well, I must say that short day is the best thing to ever happen to high school. It feels great getting out of school two hours earlier than everyone else. That's about it for this one. Oh yeah, I love you Jen. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you couldn't tell I was being sarcastic. My night was, well, pretty boring. A whole lot of doing nothing mixed with more nothing. I actually could have avoided the boring night but that would have meant drinking until I was drunk. I have no problem with that but sometimes it just gets old. Besides I need to rest up my liver for the future. I mean in three weeks I'll be in Baton Rouge getting drunk as well as every following Saturday until the end of football season. If only there was something to do tonight besides drinking. I was really in the mood for poker but the usual guys I play with weren't in town. Everytime I read over what I just wrote, the words translate in my brain to blah, blah, blah. I think this was my worst post over. Sorry for letting you guys, and girls, down. Hopefully, my next entry won't suck as much. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For many of us, who live in Louisiana, tomorrow is the first day of school. The first day of a fresh start to prove to everyone, our teachers, parents, and fellow friends, how intelligent we are. Many people look forward to this day, to see friends again or to show off their new clothes, shoes, etc. I, however, view it as just another day at school. There's nothing really special about it. What does this day have over any other day of the school year? I say there are only three instances where the day is different: 1. any day before a holiday 2. the last day of school 3. the day of an exam or report card. Why would anyone think the first day of school as an exciting day. It signals the start of going back to school for 180, or less, days. To me the first day of school is just like a Monday. Luckily, this is my last year. Hope all of you have a great year in high school or college. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a bad day. Why do bad things happen to good people? Well, I consider myself a good person. Some stuff happened between my girlfriend and I, I won't elaborate because it's our fucking business. Let's just say I was the one who unded up being upset. On to other things. I will never play no chip value poker. I don't see what's the point of not making the chips worth something. If you can't tell my by now, I lost. I guess it's the fact that I, at first, have the better hand then everyone else gets lucky and ends up beating me. To cap off the night it's raining. What a great fucking day. Sorry for the explicit language but it hasn't been a real good day. Stay classy San Diego. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know what you're thinking, "why is your weblog pink?" . Well I decided since my blog is called "writing in my diary pt.II"(thanks Petey Pablo), I would make my blog as gay as possible. Hopefully, I am succeeding in this. Like most blogs I guess I might as well discuss what I did today. I'll try and make this as short as possible. Woke up, shower, post office, Best Buy, home, Subway, home, tennis, Justin's house, home, girlfriend, shower, girlfriend, back to Justin's house, Cane's, home, girlfriend, and finally movie. You can fill in the rest of the details yourself, just don't think anything perverted happened, cause it didn't or else I would mention something. By now, you're probably wondering what happened to me. Truth is absolutely nothing. I figured you needed something to attract the reader, i.e. a catchy title. Sorry for leading you on, but you'll get over it.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>