<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       first day of school...today sucked....school sucks...you suck....suckity suck suck suck...die  
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       godddd...last night was fun and stuff but god damn was it a late one. after kliens party, me, andy, and emma got burgerking and we skateboarding in the parking lot after that me and andy went skateboarding in my driveway for bout 2 and a half hrs, then we watched the shining until fuckin 6 in the morning...i just woke up bout 30 mins ago too  
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       k...im sposed to be reading a book for school...its gotta be done by monday and im only on pg. 38...fuck that shit id much rather fuck around with my blog obsessivly like a little faggot than read that god damnd book...at least here i get to listen to that kick ass MIDI vrsn of Silver and Cold...if u wanna get midi for ur blog or w/e u can click on the HTML help in my links post, and heres a link to a really good   urlLink midi site  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ...   urlLink guy with a mohawk  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       adrews party tmrw 6:30-11...dunno where...prolly his house, but go it might be cool...actualy i have no clue i no nothing bout it, oh well at 6:30 be somewhere in bellevue and dont leave till 11...that would make me happy  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       today was one of those days where you work like 90% of the day but do fun stuff for that last 10%...i did almost ALL of my summer q's today and i just need to finish #4 with andy tmrw...and read an entire book by monday...well that  does  blow but the good side of today was that me and my old man recorded a song that i wrote today, it sucks cause i played both guitar parts, he did the base, and we used a machine for the drums, but maybe ill redo it with real drums and some horns...it REALLY needs horns, any ways, now im done my work and bout to talk to shelby, good times...peace  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i've had this blog for less than 24hrs and think ive already run out of worthwhile things to say, so i have put together some links to a couple websites that i enjoy going to...have fun    1. urlLink newgrounds.com    2.   urlLink ccs.com   3.   urlLink singingfish.com   4.   urlLink bored.com   5.   urlLink gamespy.com   6.   urlLink funnyjunk.com   7.   urlLink urbandictionary.com   8.   urlLink shelby's blog   9.  urlLink andys blog    10.   urlLink HTML help if ur into this sorta shit   11.  urlLink  proof that bush is the dumbest man alive   12.   urlLink omfg!   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ok...so i went to the doctors to get my shots...that sucks right?...guess what...i got to have a physical...no offence to anyone, but having my balls rubed by a 45yr old man isnt exactly my idea of a great time. anyways, so after my mom left the room he goes "ira...have you or any of your friends been smoking marijuana? or drinking?"   now of course i wanted to slap him in the face and call him a fuck head for even asking, but instead i said i didnt know. long story short...doctors can tell if you smoke weed by rubbing ur balls...at least he looked impressed  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       some badass pics of my favorite bands:          
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ok...today has been WONDERFUL...i woke up at 11 something, because emma got her new skate board, it was great i got dressed and we skated around and it was fun...now im pissed cause emma kicked me twice...once in the leg, and once out of the computer room...good times...lol i think i just got her in trouble!!!!THANK U DADDY  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  magegimp@hotmail.com    its not so much that i think u might wanna know it, so much as i wanted to see if could make the link...  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ok...its 2:02 am and i think my OCD's are kicking in...i cant stop fucking with this...its so damn addicting...fuck...i need to stop  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       this, strangly enough is NOT my first blog...its just the first to actualy have anything in it...  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       this is gay...this is gay...this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay...this is gay... this is gay...this is gay...this is gay...this is gay...   
    
</post>


</Blog>