<Blog>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How do I plan to lose 50 lbs, you ask?  By jumping on the low-carb bandwagon. NO, I'm not doing Atkins--there's no way I could ever stick to that for life. But, I am attempting to keep the carbs below 80g net per day. I am also counting calories, too, because I know from experience that calories DO count. So what have I eaten today so far?  Breakfast: 3/4 cup cereal, 1/2 cup skim milk  Lunch: 2 Sausage Patties, 2 slices reduced-calorie whole wheat bread  Snacks: 1 orange, 1 oz. of dry-roasted peanuts, 1 container of fat-free yogurt.  Dinner: 4 oz. turkey breast, 1/2 cup of mashed potatoes, green beans and 1/2 cup turkey gravy.  Total Calories: 1140(Yikes!) Total Net Carbs: 78g  I need to get off my lazy ass and exercise. But this blogging is oddly addictive.  On a personal note, my husband Gary runs a small golf course in our town. He leases the land from one of the local business owners, who informed him today that he was putting the land up for sale in a couple of weeks. He is asking $500,000 for it and wondered if we'd be interested in buying it. Oh, yeah, we've got that money in our back pocket, mother fucker! So it looks as though Gary will be on the job hunt in the near future. In a way, I'm glad--he spent entirely too much time there and now he can be home with me more, but, he really loves what he does and I hate to see that taken from him. More to come in the future....... 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I began what I hope to be my final attempt at losing this excess weight.  I weighed in this morning at 175 lbs. EEEK! At 5'3, that is just plain FAT.  How did I get this way?  Looking back, I have always had some difficulty maintaining a good weight.  As a child, I was not fat at all, but "stocky", "sturdy" and all the other adjectives used to describe a non-skinny child.  My real weight issues began at about age 11, when I hit puberty with a vengeance.  I suddenly had these enormous tits and began gaining weight in earnest.  By age 13, I weighed 140 lbs at 5'1.  It hit me that I needed to do something about it when my normally very gentle mother told me that "I didn't need to gain any more weight".   She understood better than anyone the journey that I was about to embark on; she, too, has struggled all her life with her weight.  So I began watching what I ate.  I don't think I really had a goal in mind, I just wanted to be smaller.  By the time I started eighth grade, I had lost 7 lbs.  No one really noticed my weight loss, I was still the same old fat & ugly April.  So that October, I decided to buckle down and lose the weight for good.  By Thanksgiving I had lost an additional 9 lbs, bringing my total weight loss to 16 lbs.  We went home to Kentucky for Thanksgiving and all my relatives gushed over my weight loss! It was the best feeling in the world, and I think it was the catalyst that allowed me to continue to eat well and exercise.  By the summer before my freshman year, I weighed 110 lbs. and looked HOT. I was getting a lot more attention from the male sector of our society and was enjoying attention from a number of suitors.  I gained a little of this back, but maintained a weight of 120-125 throughout high school.  Shortly after finishing high school and starting college, I began dating Chris, my first love and the man I lost my virginity to.  Happiness and comfort set in and the weight began creeping back.  Throughout our stormy relationship I managed to put on 30 lbs.  Chris didn't care, but deep down I hated myself for allowing my weight to creep back up like that.  We dated for nearly 3 years, and finally broke up in April of 1999.  At this point I realized that I was back in the dating arena and had to make myself presentable again. I embarked on a crash diet, sometimes eating nothing more than a beefy mac frozen dinner and a hamburger ALL day.  I also walked 2 miles a day, 5 days a week. In a little more than a month I was back down to 125 lbs.  I had a few flings, slutted around a bit and then, on July 17, 1999, I met the man I would later marry, Gary.   God, when I look back on the early days of our relationship, he and I were SO HOT.  Isn't that the way it is with everyone?  Well, in no time flat, my old friends Happiness and Comfort showed up at my door again, and I proceeded to gain back all the weight I'd lost post-Chris.  Gary, unlike Chris, was concerned about my weight gain, though he never came right out and said anything, I could tell.  At any rate, we got engaged in February of 2001 and I began planning a wedding!  I began WW in April 2001, lost 8 lbs, then maintained throughout the summer.  I joined back up in August and lost an additional 12 lbs. I never made it below 130, but I thought I looked pretty damn good.  Gary and I ended up getting married in Vegas in January 2002, and shortly after that, the weight creeped back on.  I stopped using birth control pills in May of 2002, weighing 147 lbs. at the time.  By November of 2002, I had reached my all-time high of 175 lbs.  By this time I realized that I had a condition known as  urlLink PCOS , and that that was contributing to my weight gain more than anything.  I put up with it for about 2 years and in March 2004, I went to my OB/GYN to get help for it. He put me on Metformin, which is a diabetic drug known to help PCOS'ers with their symptoms. I stopped gaining weight at that point.  I ate just about what I wanted and maintained my weight of 175 lbs. However, that wasn't a weight I wanted to be for the rest of my life!  For one thing, Gary and I are trying to have a child without any success(PCOS is a common cause of infertility for women) and I know that losing weight will make the journey easier.  So, here I am today, at 175 lbs., vowing to take the weight off FOR GOOD this time.  Maybe seeing it in writing will make it more real to me.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>