<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got home after a 2-hour session involving grad pics. I actually went all out on this one, justification being that I have been in school 6 years and counting. Might as well get the nice package so I can finally prove to one and all that I am a bonafide graduate. :) I did the whole shebang, formal shot, toga shot, sablay shot and one creative.... creative being capoeira, no surprise there, though I did wear a pair of angel wings... kunwari anghel ako. hehehehe  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Only my love for the internet and all things cyber has kept me going on, logging on faithfully every midnight to check e-mails, chat with overseas friends and of course, update blogs....I really should get to bed though... tomorrow are my graduation pictures pictorials. :) At friggin' 8:30 in the AM!!! oh well... i still dont know where it is though... hhmm....  wednesday  - since I decided not to go baguio anymore, I decided to rest my tired, aching body (which is is STILL tired and aching) all day aka bumming around the house...bumming can be pretty hard though. Witness the following heroic attempts at becoming true-blue bummers:  a.) texted peeps about possible movie rendevous "The Village". No takers, except for Honeylette ( my housemate who I have been planning to watch this movie for the longest possible time, but our schedules clash).   b.) checked DVD collection. Seen almost everything, and not really relishing the fact that most of them are shitty recopies.  d.) decided to retouch my roots. Now usually, I usually get them bleached the natural way aka sea, sun and sand. Yuma did such a splendid job  I almost feel sorry that she did it for me. :) thanks to Yuma!  e.) still had at least two hours to go before football, why not go to capoeira?   so to capoeira I went....and from there, to football.....    * my lip is still swollen from the hit that Michelle gave me when she rushed me.... I look like someone beat me *   thursday dawn - 1am to be exact  - the mark of a true party person is to keep the party on! and so, even if my legs were supperwobbly and aching and just plain tired from capoeira and football; a really cold shower, some gay friends and awesome reggae music, revived me like a  plant on water. Reggae Mistress was in TOP form as usual, with my crush. hehehehe....  * he held my hand and smiled at me *  thursday -  OUCH! training today was either off or lack of people?!?.... yes, we trained again today,  I redefined the term "muddy", and sure yeah, MUD everywhere! Then I got home ( I have no idea why, as I took several hits).   "your breath fills my veins with life and purity"   Lucy 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah yeah, so I am writing at twelve midnight on a tuesday, which gives me like an hour before wednesday,,,, to write about my monday... but do I really want to write about it?!!?   Monday was an altogether shitty and happy day... shitty because I didnt get any sleep due to the E (makes you REALLY hyper), and happy because everything around me was SO beautifully sharp and clear and awesome.... shitty because I had a short but concise conference with my poetry professor on my poetry portfolio (which got a frigging B by the way.. sob!) she said that I was stuck in the 18th century language mindset, and I should write using more contemporary language.... happy because she said that I had keep and acute observations on life and I should write about that more....shitty because I had to go to Math (ugh! and double ugh!).... happy because Math didnt turn out so bad, we did geometry today.....  One final cool thing to happen this Monday was my meeting up and joining in the Ragnarok Rogues. They are a flag football team and are all cute chicas. :) The tourney opens this sat, which gives me like three days (starting today), to catch up, learn my positions and integrate into football....this kinda put a a damper on my plans to go to baguio, as we have training everyday....  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, justin, maggie and I planned on going up to baguio tuesday, staying there till thursday, then coming back thursday evening in time for friday classes. No classes on thursday because it is quezon city day... anyhoo, we invited jason along, and he willingly agreed to come....    Sunday came with me chilling at my friends pad (to read more about that, check out Sunday). I gets a text from a cool chica friend of mine. She was looking for potential flag football players, and decided to text me. ( wow! athletic pala ako!) She told me to go their meeting this monday at chili's tomas morato..... it was cool. I got to meet the entire team, (well the first string anyways) and they all seemed to like me. :) Only problem was that our first tourney is this sat, which means that I will have to go to training starting today till thursday to catch up, adjust and be a competent football player.   I was torn between Baguio and football. If I go to baguio, I fulfill my once-a-month trip out of Manila, I would be able to chill with Jason, Justin and Maggie, and I would be able to relax. Downside is, I will end up spending 1000, which I could dearly use for thesis research fees, xeroxing, etc. If I stay, I will be able to do more research on Public Spaces of Manila i.e. thesis, plus save 1000, plus attend a capoeira class, then flag football session.... decisions, decisions?!?  I chose to flake out. I made up a stupid excuse (I had to fill in for a PA who quit one of our productions... for the record, that PA hated the director and had wanted to get replaced) and told my peeps I wouldnt be able to come... Had lunch with maggie though, and she convinced me to go....  Now, you are wondering, where is the loneliness??? well, they are my friends.... and I really want to see him and his horses though..... but some chicks were commenting on the lateness of the hour, the wierd artist dude who is really spaced out.... and he texted me saying that he and our other friends are leaving tomorrow, but that they wanted to go home... cant say I blame them, I mean, this is Manila. So now, he thinks its better and more fresh original......  I am SUCH a flake. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whoa! I cant believe I completely forgot what it feels like to take e. I took just half a pill because I hadnt popped in a long time.... jeezz luizeee, i am still feeling it!!!  saturday night turned out to be more of a bummer than a blockbuster.... Mark is hella hella cute!!! slightly balding but beautiful smile and eyes... he had to turn in early (?) because he hadnt had sleep in like 50 hours or something... ended up hanging out at yet another bar that succumbed to the musical bandwagon that is poppified hip-hop.  sunday was awesome! was chilling around the house, didnt want to text the IC crew, didnt feel like working on any school stuff. I gets a call from Astrid, who invited me to chill at Brandon and Shannen's pad. It was chill! Red (astrid's bf) and Brandon took turns spinning funky grooves and lounge ear candy, whilst people were "passing it to the left hand side". Much, much later, as more peeps showed up, somebody brought the "Energizer Mouse". We all took halves of each and MAN OH MAN! :))  i can feel every wisp of hair brushing against my skin I can feel the wind sliding over my body i can see the minuscule brushstrokes on erin's painting I can taste the coffee's bitterness oh too pungently   my whole body is on fire, its hundred million senses hypertuned. I wish someone was here so I could make mad sex. :)  Trippy BABY!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up to the sound of my cellphone ringing, and it was mark. Mark Higginbottom to be more specific. Apparently, he is mark's (my mark) sister's boyfriend's friend who is from TO, and who is in Manila for one night for work. Mark gave him my number because I am apparently the Asian connection now. He sounded pretty 'canadian' on the phone.... I just hope that he wont turn out to be a total dork...  hang-overs, ugh!  In other news, went out with justin and the others last night, in the belief that we were going to this bar called Bed in the gay area of Malate. We ended up going to Absinthe because, 1.) everybody else (lily, jason,christine, wayan) thought they were going to makati and 2.) wayan is indonesian and the indonesian group at IC is extremely homophobic..... I was kinda pissed because I had texted my gay posse and they were there....and also because I wore my usually slutty-but-not outfit because I knew that noone would hit on me at Bed.  never hooked up with my gay posse.....have to make it up to them....  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      .... and my brand new Adidas sneaks, which I thought was totally cool until I found out (the hard way no less), that they were absolutely not waterproof. Hence, I had slushily trudge my way to my last class, my feet soggily reminding me that flippies are preferable to walking around in wet socks and equally sodden shoes. Gave me a nice reason to leave my last class (STS or Science, Technology and Society) early, so I could trike my way home and change into nice, comfy flippies. Now, if only I can get past cross the mini-Red Sea that separates me and the road from my flat's gateway..... 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so here I am, checking my email and making plans with friends from out-of-country. Watched "Faust" at SM Megamall earlier. REally awesome music! Silent films played to jazz?? how conceptually practical and creative is that??? I have always been interested in the creating, the connection of hundreds of thousands of elements to produce something so beautiful that it touches one and everyone... a connection is made and for 3 seconds, everyone feels exactly the same way.....  speaking of creative process, my flatmate Erin, who is an artist, is creating a painting for an upcoming exhibit of hers.... its just so visceral to see her poised before her (in this case) flat surface, sketching and fleshing out her thoughts and herself through the means of color and light and photographs and paper.... otherwise known as mixed media...  and since it is now 2:43 am , Philippine time, I can officially declare it Friday the 13th. Bad luck! :)
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       .flickr-photo {	border: solid 1px #000000;}.flickr-frame {	float: right;	text-align: center;	margin-left: 15px;	margin-bottom: 15px;}.flickr-caption {	font-size: 0.8em;/*	color: #666666; */	margin-top: 0px;}  	 urlLink    	 		 urlLink Puerto Galera July 04 055 ,  originally uploaded by  urlLink moondrag .	 
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, my first ever blog and i fall into the trap of ranting about ex's. Typical. But as this is my personal (take note!) PERSONAL blogspot, I can say whatever I want. :)  So, back to the subject of ex's. Had a wierd and nasty break-up with this guy about four months ago. But arent all break-ups like that anyways?? I keep forgetting to delete his email address from my mailing list, so as a result, I get emails from him ever so often. So far, they (the emails) have been safe, friendly updates on his life, until the latest one.... the first few paragraphs were the typical "my-life" stuff.., when all of a sudden, out of the blue, kersmacK! he talks about how he is on a dry spell and how was my lovelife, do I have any prospects?!?!?   Come on now. We can be friends, but take it slow right??? actually, I dont even KNOW how to take it. Common sense says that he is interested in my life as a friend, but I am tempted to read more into it, like maybe he is asking in a roundabout way if I have finally gotten over him..... sheesh.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>