<Blog>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I remember for the 1988 Olympics held in Seoul (pronnounce, soul) Korea, I was completely awestruck to see so many Taek Won Do artists on the field doing their presentation. All choreographed very well. Today I read that the dood responsible for putting that sport into the Olympics and further onto world recognition, was jailed for corruption and bribery charges. Of course many of you readers would be like, yeah is the nature of politics, but in Korea, it's almost near permanent custom (example: it's customary to tip the nurses and doctors for better treatment, old school, but still happens. example: girls/wives being sold to strange people at the cost of their own debt from bribery). Everyone there IS corrupt because once you're in the cycle, you have to play along. Otherwise, you'll loose everytime. In the US, it's more subdued because the population is soo much larger.  Linking to the movie - Last Samurai (tom cruise and all),  I deeply feel that South Korea has lost their identify and are not acting like teenagers ("who am I?"). North Korea being like the bastard son is say "I'll kill everyone and commit suicide if I have to get noticed!". All cultural aspects (movies, music, news, business practice, TV dramas) are all westernized, having a super-sentimental love scene, and hearing Little Kim in the background. Current pop music is also tainted because all the guys have no balls. It's like listening to Michael Jackson doing a Dr Dre number.  In the broad picture, I believe that South Korea is trying to do the right thing. I still have hope, but I get dissappointed by the country almost every week. An example is New Song-do City. I was thinking about going there to help build this city and to live there. The Inchon Airport is expected to traffic 50% of all flights when this city is complete. But as with business practices in that country, it's likely that a few people will goto jail for bribery.  Projecting backwards, my dad at my age graduated with an architecture degree and had a very respectable job. His designs were incorporated into many new villages and cities of the time. But he dropped everything, packed a single suitcase, gathered all his cash, and came here to start completely over. For me, it's almost impossible for me to do that sicne I've already started my career track. To drop this and goto a different country (without knowing the language) takes some balls to do. My mom did the same thing as with many other koreans of the time. Doing some analysis, I'm glad that I'm here instead of Korea. although part of me will regret the awesome developments happening over there, I'll be miles away from the corruption that breeds there. The fresh immigrants today or FOBs (fresh off the boat) all have that corruption and it divides the korean amerian societies here.  Another disappointment is the Korean army. A recent Korean law states that any male between 18-35  who are of Korean decent must report to the Korean Army regardless of citizenship. As the story goes, a Korean male (US born) in the US army was pulled from his company to go serve in the Korean army. Absoluetly insane.  Ok, I'll stop there. I hope the US and S. Korean teams kick ass. Don't ask me to pick between the two. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm been working with the imagecreatefromjpeg function and a weird thing happens. There are some jpg images that view fine in the browser but does not when using a simple imagecreatefromjpeg script.   // jpegtest.php // use as jpegtest.php?imagename=[filename]  header("Content-type: image/jpeg"); $im = imagecreatefromjpeg($_GET['imagename']); imagejpeg($im); imagedestroy($im); ?>  The binary representation of the jpg file can be found here -  urlLink http://www.geocities.com/tapsemi/datastruct.html   I found that all of the well behaved images follow this order, however, the troublesome images switch the DCT and Hoffman sections. Obviously, my first hypothesis is to switch the order of the sections and write out the jpg file. I wrote the whole analysis thing in a php class and seems to work. just need to verfy things here and there. My class is also buggy and doesn't output the complete binary data stream. After I fixed my own bugs, then I can conclusively say if my method fixed the problem or not and possibly send the suggestion to PHP or GD, when I figure out where the problem lies (more about this below).  There have been suggestions that the problem might be stemming from the GD library itself, but I'm not sure about that. To make this assumption conclusive, I'm going to need to know how mozilla handles jpg images or if just hands it off to the gd library too. If mozilla uses the GD library, then the problem is in PHP. If not, then it's probably a Gd library problem and I need ask someone there. I'll probably do this in my next stage of testing. I've looked through the PHP source code and my head starts to spin. Currently learning the ZEND developer docs at php.net.  One thing that amazed me is that it's possible to make an online hex editor. If this is so, then it might be possible to make a php based assemmbly simulator. If this is possible, the other applications can be made with just php and it's possible to start my Global Terminal computing idea to reality (Linux user space and other techs). Sure, sure Java can be used, but php had more potential to grow (unless java become open source). Also, I haven't been able to find a limitation of PHP. Maybe my projects aren't ambitious enough. It's also my hopes that during my inquires to aid me in my quest, people will start to realize PHP can be used for things not previously thought of.  I've also did a google news posting. Hopefully I'll get an answer. ----------------------------------------- Hello, I'm doing a number of personal experiments with jpg images and I havea few questions. Most of the question comes from the binaryrepresentation of the jpg file.  1. JPG File structure order preservationWith reference to this link http://www.geocities.com/tapsemi/datastruct.html Does the order of the different sections need to be preserved? If not,how much section swapping can one do without loosing the file identityof a jpg file? (In another words: What are the terms of sectionswapping)  2. Duplicate image detectionI'm curious as to which of the sections in the jpg file can be used touniquely identify the image regardless of the image size. I'm playingwith the idea of using the DCT or Hoffman encoding section as meansfor identification. I currently have an algorithm that takes pixelinformation every 10 pixels on a diagonal line on the image. Theemphasis is on rapid identification/dulicate detection. My goal is toidenfity 1,000,000+ images per second with a 7200rpm ATA HDD on asingle processor ~2Ghz computer and scalable within a HPC environment(cluster actually)  3. JPG File structure referencesWhere can I find more information about the JPG file structure fromthe binary point of view? I'm looking into the possibility of usingjpgs as 'DNA' maps/masks for signal processing of high speed digitalcommunications. If work in this area has already been established,please send me some references.  4. Legalities of Reverse EngineeringI'm wondering if it's legal to do these types of reverse engineeringwithout having a copy of the JPG standard (I know it helps to have it,but more content rich and fun doing it in reverse)  Thanks in advaced. It's my hope to to develope something useful forthe community.  James  -----------------------------------------   Sometimes I wonder if I've gone mad. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First blog entry. I guess it's nice to have it. I've tried other places, but I guess if I get Googled (search engine, email, orkut), it can be thought of as an investement. Google is looking for people with PhDs so, I guess I could be right about this 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>