<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't know how they do it.  Writers are notorious for being drinkers.  To me, there's nothing more difficult than writing while drunk or hungover.  I'm experiencing the latter right about now.  I'm feeling like a machine that's out of order, and I'll be writing about the latest dysfunction in my life.  Weird.  My friends have had to endure listening to my endless bitching about how hard it's been for me to meet guys for the past eight months.  Yesterday I met up with a guy, and it was a disaster, much like every experience with guys this year.  He was sweet, very cute, and I enjoyed listening to him talk.  The problem was that I couldn't be fully engaged in the conversation.  I just didn't know what to say.  I was totally zoning out, and my mind drifted to random crap that had nothing to do with our conversation.  All I wanted to do was lay down and rest.  I wish it were perfectly normal to just say to someone, "Hey, I know we just met, and I know I'm the one who suggested hanging out, but is there anyway we could save conversation for later and just lay down and stare at the clouds?"   Therein lies the problem I guess.  I'm too stressed out and focused right now to be dating.  Plus I'm continuously working through issues I've had with my ex-boyfriend.  But the process of working on my goals and working through past-relationship shit has never felt lonelier nor more difficult.  I suppose once I get through it  all I'll be a stronger person, but when you're thick in the middle of the process, the end seems nowhere in sight.    When I'm having a hard time practicing for the LSAT, I wonder, Gee, if I had someone to care about and vice versa, maybe I'd be having an easier time focusing instead of feeling like this ghost of a person.  It bothers me that I've assigned the most meaning to my life in terms of how well I do on a stupid fucking test .  I have a lot around people around me that I'm grateful for, and little by little I'm recognizing things about myself that make me appreciate life and give me meaning, but for some reason, I feel it necesssary to share it all with someone.  Sometimes I think what I have is too much for me to handle alone.  I've been stuck on thinking what the next sentence should be for quite some time and tie things together because right now, everything is rather disjointed.  The only thought that occurred to me to let words keep flowing is that maybe, just maybe, I'm so worried about the possibility of failing that if it does occur, I'll feel so broken and low that I won't be able to depend on myself to cope with it.  I'd have my friends, but it's not the same as having someone you love there by your side.  God, I wonder if people who grew up in healthy families exeperience this kind of bullshiit.  All of this sounds like trite, cliched crap.  But you know, it's the kind of stuff that helps uncrowd my mind.    I think I can study now...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      When I was in the Creative Writing program at SFSU, I had to do a ton of writing exercises each week.  It got the point where I felt like I was out of ideas completely.  Or in other instances, I'd stare at my computer screen, and whatever ideas I'd have in my head earlier in the day no longer seemed fresh and interesting when I tried to flesh them out.    That's how I feel now.  I've been trying to think of something good to say in my next post, but feared it would only come off as, "whoa is me, my life is a bitch."  I'd have damn good reason to think that though.  I might explain that in a bit.    But this thought was particularly striking to me today.  I was pretty desperate to clasp on to a dramatic idea/fantasy in my head to literally force upon myself a fresh perspective of life.  It sort of worked.  While fighting off a very strong wave of post-lunch food coma at work, I got it in my head to finally call my doctor about my x-ray results.  Earlier in the week I went to the doctor because I've been getting short of breath and have been having trouble breathing in general.  For someone at 26 years-old, that's pretty unusual.  So I got it checked out.    The receptionist who answered my call kind of weirded me out.  After she looked up my information, her warm disposition shifted to clinical efficiency when she asked,  "what number do you prefer to be reached at for a private message?"  I held my already shallow breath out of surprise.  What was this about, I thought.  I gave her my number slowly, hoping she'd detect the concern she raised in me, and then she abruptly told me the doctor will get back to me and hung up.   When I put the phone down, I thought, God, what if this is something serious?  I wasn't prepared for this.  And then a sick idea popped in my head: So what?  So what if it serious?  I got to thinking that if my days were numbered, maybe I'd start appreciating life a bit more.  And I was!  I was sitting in my cubicle thinking about how short life is, and in my case, how it may be even shorter.  The papers around me, the keyboard I was touching, the office walls and other cubicles all looked beautiful to me.  Every thing I felt bad about in my life seemed so trivial.    I don't know how the suddenly appreciative perspective wore off, but it did, and it disappeared rather instantly.  It was like I walked through a fog and into light, and when I turned back to look at the fog, it wasn't there anymore.  I could see everything as being just as shitty as I remembered it being always.  The doctor never called me back.  I still have no idea what answer to expect about my x-ray results.  But I'll tell ya- I'm not too worried about it.  Even if I get bad news, I know that things might not change about how I see life.  Why should it have to?    It's a sad thing to cling on to ideas of hope over and over again just to let it bring you down.  I realize that the stuff I'm saying is all a reflection of stuff going on in my life.  If things were going better, I'd have a better attitude.  All the time, there will be people who say having a better attitude makes thing go better in life.  Those people are either heavily medicated, criminally stupid, or have so much sex that they have no time to actually engage and be part of the workings of society.    Yeah, rather than chronicle the mundane details of all that ails me, I enjoyed bitching about the larger picture.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I called my oldest sister to wish her a happy birthday.  This was a big deal.  I don't keep in touch with my family that much.  I'm not mad at them.  We're on speaking terms.  It's just that they're all far older than me, so they all feel like cousins than actual siblings.  But I suppose from their perspective, I'll always be their little brother.  For me, I'm just not big into family, and I keep my distance.  Why bother getting closer now?  Plus the family just keeps getting bigger every year.  There's just no way I can keep up with everyone.    Well, I sort of did some catching up with sis and with her husband.  I didn't quite tell them, "Oh, by the way, I'm a big homo."  It's not like they don't already know.  What's my personal life got to do with them?    A lot, apparently.    My brother-in-law told me about how my sister keeps telling everybody how much of a striking similarity there is between her oldest son and me.  She's definitely qualified to make an accurate assesment because in a way, she's the one who went to my parent-teacher conferences, informational meetings, and other chaperoned events since my mom didn't (and still doesn't) speak English and my dad was (and is still) always working.  She spent a lot of time with me in a parental kind of way.  But just the basics of course.  She had her own life to live too while leaving more motherly duties for my actual mom to take of.    Despite all she's done, I've always sort of been jealous of my sister.  She's smart, pretty, and married well.  She's got a good life, and now so do her three kids.  Although, her oldest son, who I think is about 12 years old (see how much I keep up with my family!), I'm not sure will have it so easy.  While I was still in NY, I sort of got to watch him grow up.  He was a little brat, and he was difficult to deal with because he's also very bright.  Smart kids are the worst to be around.  He didn't endear himself to me.  As he got older, I became aware that I didn't really like my nephew because I noticed the many similarities we shared.  He was a bit of a sissy.  He liked pink, didn't like playing sports, was overly emotional, always wanted to be around Mom and always had to be the center of attention.  When I visited home recently after not seeing him for over a year, the only thing that changed about him was his height.    The kid has a bright future.  He's got parents who can be more involved in his life than mine ever were.  His family is more well-off, and I hate to say it, but the little brat may end up being smarter and better-looking than me.  But he's going to have endure so much torture in school for being who he is, and he may lose so much of what makes him stand out as an exceptional person.  Sure, people of all walks of life had to endure junior high and high school trauma.  But there's something absolutely brutal about growing up in a Republican environment right outside of NYC, like Long Island, where he is.  The bullies have something more tangible to compare you with.  They see first-hand all the "freaks" their parents keep them sheltered from whenever they make a trip into the city.  Worse yet, they've got the smarts, braun, and money to try to make your life a living hell if you're not like them.  My nephew is in for a horrible, depressing journey to adulthood.  I think about the distance I keep from my family, and how I don't share my personal life with them.  Sometimes I think that if I can help spare my nephew  just one ounce of grief that I had to endure while growing up, maybe he'll have less pain than what I've had to live with.  Maybe he'll never have to feel washed-up at a young age.  No matter what I do, it won't be easy for him.    One way I want to help him out is to follow my dream.  I always wanted to be successful when I grew up: be a famous actor, have a few books published, or just be rich and happy.  Silly measures of success to some people, I know, but that's what I wanted.  Each time I think about how much shit I had to put up with just to be happy with my life, I realize how much I survived and how strong I have been.  And now I deal with the arduous task of trying to get into a top law school and becoming a successful lawyer who will also one day write fiction books too, and it can all be too overwhelming for me to handle- almost to the point where I want to quit.  I guess I should keep working towards my goal so that my nephew has someone to look up to.  Maybe my success will get him through the days of his self-discovery and give him hope that one day, everything will be all right.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today I saw a lesbian couple get off the bus.  The one with the shaved head walked beside her lover with her head in the air like she was entranced by angels singing to them about their love.  She smiled.  Her face was peaceful.  If someone took a snapshot of her, cropped out everything and everyone around her and just presented her image out of context, they'd think she took a shot of morphine.  She looked like an idiot.  It made me think, "Good fucking, god.  Did I ever look that stupid when I had a boyfriend?"  And instantly I remembered, Yes.  I have seen pictures in which I have a ridiculous ear-to-ear grin on my face while standing next to my special someone.  That smiling, happy creature seems like a stranger to me now.  I've officially been single for too long (or maybe finally, long enough to have clarity) because I've come to the conclusion that couples are truly, deeply odd.  I've forgotten how people become couples, why they become couples, what makes them stay couples- it's a foreign country to me again.  This one-time serial monogamist is now completely baffled by the concept of relationships.  Brings me to my next point: Logic.  For anyone who has taken or will take the LSAT, they will discover it is a very difficult test with no prior education in formal logic.  It is especially difficult if you have lived your life by your own  means of logic, and not the standardized methods used by others use to rationalize opinions, beliefs and arguments.  I came to the conclusion that for the 26 years of my life, I've been living as an insane person, simply going around saying (in paraphrase), "This is so, because I've decreed it so."  I always humored myself with that line of thinking, but it's not so funny when you're trying to do well on a test that measures how well you apply logic principles.    Where exactly is this going?  My decision to become a lawyer is either sucking the creative life-blood out of me that I regretfully neglected, or it's helping me to become a well-adjusted adult that sets goals and actually takes steps to accomplish them.  I'm starting to think being creative and being well-adjusted are mutually exclusive.  Before this idea of becoming lawyer-John, I had love, I read tons of books, I wrote, and I had fun even with having to endure extreme poverty.  Logical thinking is not part of who I am.  It is eating my soul alive and turning me into someone I don't know anymore.  I have a different way of thinking that sometimes makes me feel like someone else's brain has been transplanted into my skull.  And the strangest thing of all- despite this drastic transformation I'm undergoing, I can almost say that I'm happy to be going through it.  I just don't know how the journey will end.  What if I don't become a writer nor a laywer?  What if keep going through life just being a peon?    There's no hidden message here of save yourself, follow your dream and all that bullshit.  Sometimes things "are "just because that's the way they "are".  It's not inherently good, or bad.  It's what you make of it.  Right now, life for me now is like a giant pile of manuer.  Someone recently told me that in some regions all over the world, manuer is mixed with dirt and clay to build beautiful feats of architecture.    Reminds me of the wisest thing I've read in my life.  I went to the bathroom at this Indian resturant.  Right above the toilet paper roll, someone scribbled: "Nothing is True Everything is Permissible."  Just like that.  No punctuation.  I tried to make sense of it all in my head, and then I was like, "Holy Shit!  That's just like on the LSAT."  Assume whatever you want to be true.  Knock yourself out.  It doesn't really matter unless you want it to.  Relationships, LSAT questions, writing- these things are all fighting for title of what matters most.  In my convoluted way, I laid out some stuff I think about.  I bet it was a real bitch to make sense of all that l said.  Now you know how I feel. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So I put the hummus away, stopped surfing online, and am trying to quiet the thoughts of how beautiful people make me sick. It's not that I'm bitter or jealous of the exceptionally genetically gifted. I just don't like them- sort of how I don't like pate. It's just gross to me, and I start to gag.  They look so happy. When I see happy, perky people in general, I want to put a pin to their head and let the air out. People probably say the same thing about me when I'm out and having a really good time with my friends, but I don't care really. To exercise my right to judge, I must be prepared for judgments upon me as well. (Though if I hear what someone says and it doesn't please me, a serious ass-whooping would be involved.)  I'm imagining there's a lot of happy people today. The California Supreme Court nullified all 4,000+ same sex marriages that took place this year in my fair city. That really bothers me. Gay marriage made so many people in this country unhappy. And now its remnants are being dismantled. All we'll have is a memory that gay people once had their love legally recognized by the city of San Fancisco, but no formal, substantitive documentation to prove it.  It just looks bad. A huge civil rights movement was just a flash in the pan. And now what? I'll have to endure ignorant assholes on the radio, in the news or in the elevator talking about how a wrong has been made right. I swear, for the next few days, when I hear people discuss gay marriage, I'll feel like I'm eating nothing but pate for breakfast, lunch and dinner.  And then the govenor of New Jersey resigned today because he had an extramarital affair with a man. I wonder if it occurred to the majority of people that maybe he wouldn't have been married to a woman in the first place if people were more accepting of homosexuality. What a mess bigotry creates.  Anyway, I'm done with my ranting for the day. Time for a nap before the tranny rock show tonight. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I should be getting to bed, but each time I stare back at my big empty thing, I keep thinking that there is so much I haven't done in the day, and that there is so much yet to do. And so if I were limited to one metaphor for my life, it would be an empty bed at night- a bed that should have my body's indentations, but doesn't. It doesn't even call for me. It sits there, like me- flat and demanding, but without specifically asking for attention, almost denying that it's asking for attention when it's really begging for it.  It sounds so dreary, the way I put things, but that's just how I am. I figure that if I live my pain loudly enough, one day it will do something. Maybe I'll reach someone who can make it stop. Maybe prettier words will come together and become something useful, like a story or book. To some extent I've put those thoughts behind me. But as I get older, and as I make decisions that lead me further away from my creative ambitions, I feel some need to reconnect with language and put these words online. It's like there's the spirit of a writer inside me who's slowly dying, and these are his last words- sort of like Ted Hughes' ode to Sylvia Plath. Hence the blog.  As I write, I feel disappointed with what's coming out. I wanted something cooler, more moving, more beautifully said, like what comes out during the rare moments I sit down at my computer or at a notepad and try to tell a story. The shocking thing about getting older for me is how useless the struggle for perfection really is. It's a losing battle I wish I never took up in the first place. But then I find myself joining in the fight at the most inopportune times no matter how much I try to let go of attaining perfection. Point is: I'll say lots of things on this here thingy. They can't all be epiphanies, tragedies, comedies, enlightening political insights, etc. It'll just be my life- my highly imperfect, flawed life that I don't enjoy as often as I should.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>