<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Texas/Oklahoma Wildflower seed Mix Item 3341   We visited Wildflowerseed Farms near Fredericksburg, TX a few weeks ago and I bought a quarter pound of this seed mix. I plan to seed the area up near the beginning of my long driveway, it alread has a good mix of wildflowers on it. This morning I went out and pulled up a good deal of Johnson Grass, in a week or two we'll get out and mow down all the foliage that is there now and scatter the seed. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      checked the rain gauge this morning, we got another two and a half inches... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      in the gauge this morning. Everything is very soggy, and it is too wet to do some of the things I planned to do today. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     It's a good thing I got a photo the other day of this marigold my daughter picked out and planted, this morning I went out and all the yellow flowers have been neatly pruned. It is totally de-bloomed! The bright orange ones were untouched, only the yellow ones were eaten. I suspect deer...and now that I think of it, earlier this summer the deer ate the yellow portulaca moss roses down to the ground.  Is there a pattern here? Do deer prefer to eat yellow flowers? I hope not, yellow is one of my favorite colors... 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Checked the rain gauge this morning, there were just over 3 inches of rain from yesterday/last night. It's about time, we haven't had any measurable precipitation since June. There is a chance for more rain today and tomorrow, we'll take it! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The fall 2004 catalog arrived today, and I am lusting after the  urlLink Jumbo Waterwise Garden Collection ... I just adore those bright, vibrant colors, pastels don't do much for me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Good article on  urlLink solitary bees , and another article on how to construct a  urlLink bee house . 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Cape Plumbago - (Plumbago auriculata)  I'm pretty sure that's what this plant is. The girl at the nursery told me it was Chinese Plumbago, but it doesn't look anything like the pictures I've seen. It is tender to zone 8, which means I very well may lose it this winter. Purchased June 2004.  It is supposed to prefer full sun, but I've got mine in part sun. It is very fresh looking, and has been in bloom nonstop since planting.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Purchased three in spring 2004; two are doing well, one is just barely hanging on. Most references say to plant in full sun, but I understand they prefer part sun in Texas. Mine may have just a little too much shade, the two are doing well but they are leaning out toward the sun. I plan to move them in a few weeks when it cools down a little.  The foliage is a nice bluish-gray, and the fat flower spikes are very dark purple! 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am learning a lot from Texan garden blogs, here are a few of my favorites:    urlLink Soul of the Garden  (Austin)   urlLink Zanthan Gardens  (Austin)   urlLink prairie point  (Dallas)   urlLink Wuv'n Acres Gourden  (My good friend Karen Marie in Oklahoma)   I'm sure I will find more, and add them here. I can't seem to find a way to add lists or links with this template and I am far too chicken to go messing about with the template as it is...  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Spent most of the afternoon moving the Mondo grass to shadier spots. I will probably regret placing some over in the Kitty garden, another armadillo has moved in and tears it up every night...
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Sheet Mulching for the Home Garden   Very interesting. I think I will try this over in the corner where I want to plant a pecan tree.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Boy I have  lots  of these. Ranchers hate them, many keep goats because goats will browse and prune them up as high as they can reach.  Malcom Beck has several articles on cedars:     urlLink Cedar Flakes For Mulching & Growing     urlLink Cedar and other brush thickets used to an advantage    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I found a cheap copy of Scott Ogden's  urlLink Gardening Success with Difficult Soils: Limestone, Alkaline Clay and Caliche , at amazon.com and ordered it last week, it arrived today!  This is an excellent book, it helped me to understand what I was dealing with here. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     Tiny watergarden I want, displayed at the  urlLink Hill Country Water Gardens  and Nursery in Cedar Park, just north of Austin.   Darling J. prefers the huge overflowing jug. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    another jug fountain... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Overflowing jug
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I read a couple of interesting articles on gardening in hay bales and I thought I'd give it a try.  Here is the article from  urlLink Nichols Garden Nursery , and here is a  urlLink newspaper article .  I couldn't find wheat straw bales, but I have access to various types of hay bales. I'll just have to deal with sprouting weed seeds. I set three bales up behind the vegetable garden Monday evening (August9, 2004) and wet them thoroughly. Yesterday I wet them and then poured Fish Solution over them, I am supposed to wet them every day for 10 days before planting. I ordered  urlLink Nasturtium - Glorious Gleam Mix  (Tropaeolum majus) from Nichols, and I haven't decided what else to plant. Maybe pickling cucumbers?  The good thing about these hay bales is, after they have rotted down I'll have a new bed! I want a place to put perennials like herbs or asparagus, this will allow me to work over the main beds without disturbing them. :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This spring I bought a flat of mondo grass (40 I think) and I think their situation was too sunny. Yesterday I moved some of it to the small tree circle, an even shadier spot. Hopefully they will hang on until the fall season.  I still have about 20 more to move...   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We moved to Central Texas a little over a year ago and bought a home on 1.49 acres, just east of the little city of  urlLink Lampasas .  The locals *snort* and say "hahaha, you have  Sugar Loaf  "  when I say I live and garden east of town, (this must be what  caliche  is called.) I must say it is  very  different from the clay I gardened on in Maryland and Virginia, and the sand in Georgia. And the rocks! We have picked limestone pebbles, rocks and boulders out of the soil and used them for tree rings. We have also scavenged limestone blocks from building sites for use in the garden. I'll have to post pictures, I am really enjoying working with limestone...  The average rainfall for this area is said to be only 19 inches a year. The problem is that when it finally  does  rain, it comes down two or three inches at a time and tries to rush to Pecan Creek instead of soaking in.  So after reading every gardening book I could get my hands on at the little county library, I decided to build raised beds and begin with a small vegetable garden. So this winter, I drew out a 21-foot diameter circle with intersecting paths, and with the help of Dear J., edged the whole thing with blocks. Here is a picture of the site, this was Valentines Day 2004, and the only snow we've had in over a year!     Then Darling J. brought me bunches and bunches of burlap sandbags, which we used as weedblock, and filled the sections with a truckload of lovelylovely organic garden soil from Nolan Creek Nursery, Nolanville, TX.  Here's a picture early in the summer, this is my tomato section.     I planted one each determinate, indeterminate and grape cluster tomato, two basil and one marigold in this quadrant. And yes, I know the tomato cages are upside-down, I couldn't get them through the burlap! They worked just fine with a boulder or two weighing them down...I am still getting tomatoes, even through the heat of the summer! J. has been taking sacksful in to work and racking up brownie points. This section has grown a lot since that picture was taken, I promise to take new pictures, maybe tomorrow... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Zone Map for Texas from the  urlLink National Aboretum .  See that salmon-colored kidneybean shape right in the middle, which is zone 7b? I garden right on the line between 7b and 8a...  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just testing you know... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>