<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Insects:   The average hive/colony insect is, in itself, nothing too spectacular. A simple organism at best, sometimes with a defence mechanism which is nothing too stellar, just creating  a moment of pain and an hour or so of rage. All one has to do to prey on said insect is be fast enough to catch it. Ants and bumble bees aren't very fast. So, how do these insects survive on their own? Simple. They don't.  They live in hives. Huge, multi-tiered colonies where each insect is but a part of a giant über-organism capable of everything that a complex being can do, and more.    Humans:   The average social human is, in itself, nothing too spectacular. At best,  it is a simple organism with close to no defence mechanism at all. All that a predator has to do to prey on said human is to be fast enough to catch it. Humans aren't very fast. So, how do these thin-skinned, clawless beings survive on their own? Simple.  We  don't.   We  live in cities, towns, hamlets, villages, societies, whatever. Huge, multi-tiered colonies where each of  us  is but a part of a giant über-organism capable of incredible feats.    A Comparison of Counterparts:    Insect equivalent  – Human organ counterpart –  Human being counterpart.    Queen  - The brain. The queen's word is Law. With a capital. -  Political leader. (President, prime minister, monarch, etcetera.)    Worker  - The hands. They get everything done. Housing, decorating, you name it. -  Almost everyone. (Everyone with a non-military occupation.)    Warrior  - The fists, feet, whatever you use to put the hurt on people. -  The military.     A Conclusion of Sorts:   You may have noticed the emphasis on  we ,  us  and the like. Know why? Because that's the Hive Mentality. Every time  we  cheer on  our  favourite sports team, or vote, or watch television, or obey a law, or do what  we're  told,  we're  acting as part of the Hive Mentality. Disagree? Just try to walk down a crowded corridor without moving out of anyone's way. Can you do that? How about walking down a crowded corridor without getting out of anyone's way, or without anyone getting out of anyone else's way, or out of  your  way? Can you manage that? Didn't think so.    Solutions?   What can  we  do to help ourselves out of an intellectual pit? To stop  ourselves  becoming mindless drones? Well,  you  could become a deviant from society, a hermit, a castaway. Or  you  could simply cogitate. That's right, by actually thinking,  you  too can become an intelligent  INDIVIDUAL ! There's really nothing to it. The next time a law is put in place, or you have to vote, just think " why? " Disagree with the law/custom/whatever?  Do something about it . Don’t just exist,  be .  ~Duncan 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A rather large amount of athenians moved out of athens before the Olympic games. Almost all of the events sold only half of the available tickets. The dressage sold 142 of said tickets. The stadiums were barely completed in time. There were two drug scandals before the games had even begun. The coverage is, at best, sketchy.  The honorable Mr. Juan Antonio Samaranch jr. will  still  say that it was the "best Olympic games ever."  Goes to show you, eh? 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Think about the age-old question of "If there were a thousand monkeys at a thousand typewriters, how long would it take for one to write a novel?"  This is assuming that each of the monkeys had been trained to push random buttons on the typewriters and so on and so forth.  Truth is, there's a fantastic chance that the monkeys would never, ever ever write a novel. You see, the monkeys would probably fall into a pattern of pressing the same keys over and over. Even if it were random, the monkeys would have no memory of what they had pressed. Even if there were  infinite  monkeys, there is still a good chance that they would never write anything more coherent than "I'm a sixties rock song." The monkeys, you see, have a strong chance of pressing the same keys as their monkey brethren.  What you need, see, is a kind of past/present memory. None of the infinate monkeys may write the same thing as another monkey, nor may they write what they have already written.  Follow that method and BAM! one in every six-billion monkeys has a classic tale of good versus evil, or a recipe for clam chowder, or an essay on "Rock Music and the Print Media."  I want infinite monkeys.  ~Duncan 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello there, my humanlings! Welcome to my hallowed halls of learning and Pretty Things(tm).  Just a quiche of a post before bed, to make sure that all is in order.  Testing, one  two   three  .   Good.  G'night!  (Why on Earth not?) 
    
</post>


</Blog>