<Blog>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a weekend!  If any of you have never been to Manitoulin Island, the long weekend in August every year is a great time to visit!  This year, we decided to be a part of the festivities and become vendors.  What an adventure it was! This is an outdoor event by the way.  The first day we set up outside of the Rec Centre in Little Current on a small grass walkway between the drive and the parking lot.  (it was about 9am for me)It turned out to be a great location becuase we REALLY needed the tree that we set up under.  The day was overcast, threatening to break out in a heck of a storm.  Across from us was a clothing vendor and his family who were a great help when my tent refused to go up on its own.  (Its really wonderful to meet such great folks!)  I had a great lady set up beside me (Rayvin from Eclectic Enchantments here in Sudbury) and the two of us rode the bad weather together.  Luckily she brought tarps which were much needed when the storm finally broke through the gray sky and we got dumped on.  But it was a blast! I was selling while holding onto the frame of the tent while the wind DROVE through everything, pieces flying across the grass... some quite far! All you could do was laugh and enjoy the great company of the people who came to our tents supporting our business.  (Thanks!)  The weather finally drove us to close up shop as it was tearing down larger tents beside us and causing a heck of a mess.  But it was a great day!  The next morning I set up quite early on the main street downtown in Little Current.  I had a fabulous view right onto the walkway of the docks looking at the North Channel.  At 8am the temperature had already hit 28 degrees C.  HOT! And no wind!  I brought extra stones with me for the base of my tent just in case!  The main street was blocked off, so we had to unpack our vehicles and move them.  The heat continued to build and so did the energy of the day!  Right on the street, we had the perfect view of the parade going by and later in the evening the fireworks that went off on the shore across from the walkway.  I'd like to thank EVERYONE who attended the festival and came to my booth for making this show a fabulous success for us!   The streets were jammed with people and I was lucky to be beside a great food vendor that made the most fabulous home made breads and fried bologne! YUM!   By 7pm I was feeling pretty tired.... my family was meeting in Little Current for a dinner and they were sweet to bring me a plate to munch on - Thanks!! A big thankyou to my cousin Peggy, who hosted the dinner (I did not get to thank her properly as I was extremly busy when she showed up)  The night continued on and finally around 11pm we had to close up shop as the fireworks were about to start.    My mom and daughter helped me to unfold our travelling show quickly so that we could get our cars over the swing bridge before the crowds started to head out.  For anyone who has not been to Manitoulin Island - it IS an island and the only way on is via a one lane swing bridge OR the ferry on the south side.   We folded up the shop and headed out over the bridge and STILL had a lot of time to sit on the back of the truck watching the beautiful lights in the sky.  I'll be there again next year!! Raven 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hi!  You know, sometimes being a vendor in Canada is not easy. I've been looking for a good e-commerce solution so that I can sell in both currencies (US and CA)... Right now I am using a really great service provider that I'm really satisfied but I can only sell in US dollars..  If you find something you really like on our site and you are from Canada, for now you can give me a call (or email) and we'll work out the price and I can ship your item to you. (All the contact info is on our webpage)  I'm hoping that by mid September this year I'll be able to offer Canadian prices but I wont make any promices until I work all the bugs out.  Anyways, I'm off to make some more creations.. right now the stock is low on the site since we had a fabulous time at Haweater weekend. Maybe I'll post about that later on.  Raven    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Greetings and welcome to our Blog      What's a Blog? I know I thought that the first time I saw one of these things... its a place where you can come and visit and read all about Renaissance Market and things that go on here.      It's a personal inside look into our business and maybe some of the "little" things that go on in our lives from day to day.  Call it a peek inside of the shell you see here on the internet, a place where you can become a part of our day.      Well I hope you enjoy our view behind the magic curtain.      Be well! Raven  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>