<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I jammed with Brian and Randy.  (This is Jeff's band, minus Jeff, who got married Saturday and is busy.)  Brian invited a singer/songwriter he'd never heard to come jam with us.  JD, though a very sweet young woman, is a novice musician.  She didn't get her guitar in tune.  I suffer when I must endure an out-of-tune guitar.  Afterward, I learned that Randy felt the same. Brian couldn't really hear her. She is an OK songwriter, though the intonation problems made that difficult to ascertain for certain.  She finally left at 10:00 PM and we had one jam...what a waste of an evening.    Was I too polite?  I don't want to go through that again...I get so little time to jam.  She drove over an hour from Priest River...it would be so uncool to be rude.  That's not the kind of person I am.  I guess this is just turning into a diary...that's not my intent.  Oh, hell, why not?  So, I have nothing profound to say. That shouldn't surprise anyone.  Randy, Brian, and I discussed the issue of what and why we are being a band.  What do we want to do?  None of us are songwriters.  (Is Jeff?)  Do we want a singer?  Do we want to perform?  How will we structure what we are doing?
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dana "quit" Joe's band yesterday.  I guess we'll lumber along for awhile to see if things change for him.  If they don't, then we'll need to look into getting a new bassist.  BACKGROUND: I play in two bands...one is Joe's band.  It is a good band and Joe is a great song writer.  The other is Jeff's band.  It is a jam band working to find an identity.  I have only jammed with them once before tonight, my second jam.  Jeff won't be there.
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The experience for me is one of meditation while playing my instrument.  It first happened spontaneously when I was 17 years old.  I was performing with my band and suddenly my hands were playing guitar without me!  My thoughts stopped and I just watched as my hands played the best performance of my life. Perhaps this is what athlete's call being "in the zone."    I have since become obsessed with recreating that type of experience.  My focus over the years has been primarily on improvisation, though I think now that I was mistaken about the importance of its role.  I think now that the pratice of mindfulness is the key...that experience was one of mindfulness, and mindfulness can be cultivated in every moment of daily life.
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm trying to make an artistic expression, through music, in a capitalist culture and, obviously, they are not a good fit.  I've been playing electric guitar for thirty years now but haven't communicated successfully as an artist.  There are probably a lot of reasons for that, and maybe this blog will aid in my progress.  Music is as much about growth as a person as about making a sound.  I have no choice...I must make a sound.
      
</post>


</Blog>