<Blog>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Currently I am researching several properties in Forest Grove, completing ownership histories and developing Chains of Title.   Sometimes this sort of work can be time consuming and slow going.  However, when I find what I've been looking for its like finding buried treasure!  What a great feeling.  I've let out several "whoops" of joy sitting at the microfiche machine in the somber County Assessor's office, and people wonder what the heck I have to be excited about. :)  I'm working on a house history for a property in Portland.  Researching house histories in Portland is a bit easier, since the city has kept pretty thorough records since the early 1900's.  I recently completed a house history for a property in The Dalles, and that was a bit tougher, since the records going back into the early 1900's were not very complete.  I did find a really nice gentleman though, who was doing some work for the local geneological society, who helped me out.  I'm discovering that many people in this field are so generous with their time, and will go out of their way to help you out when you're stuck!  I'm working on research for a cemetery drama which will be performed in Hillsboro in September.  I have names of quite a few individuals who are buried in the cemetery, and I need to find out enough about their lives, so that actors can portray them for the drama.  This is a really fun project!  For example, we have a gentleman who's parents are buried in the cemetery.  He married a European heiress, stole her jewelery and made off for Brazil.  Quite a shady character!  We're trying to get one of our local city planners to play him in the drama...  The third major project I'm working on is an historic calendar for the Hillsboro Historical Society.  We're not quite following in the footsteps of the famous Forest Grove folks, who took off their clothes for their cause.  We are simply using historical photos of Hillsboro.  We've got the photos picked out, a graphic designer has agreed to donate her time, and we now are in the process of raising money to offset the printing costs.  Our goal is to have the calendars printed by November, in time for Christmas.  So many people are excited about this project!  I presented the numbers for printing 250 or 500 calendars, and they were so enthusiastic they wanted the numbers for printing 1000! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Please contact me if you are interested in historic research or any of the other services I can provide, such as: House History Research, National Register Nominations, Special Assessments or Tax Act Projects  You can email me at  urlLink kim_fitzgerald@yahoo.com  and I will be happy to talk with you. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
          What are the benefits of having a property listed on the National Register?                 Local communities, states and the nation benefit from having tangible links to the past, including events, people, and artistic expressions that have molded the character of our nation.           Listing is recognition of a property's importance in local, regional, or national history.           Property owners are eligible for a number of grant and tax incentives as well as technical assistance in rehabilitation and maintenance of their historic property.           Listing properties has financial benefits for communities by contributing to the revitalization of neighborhoods and business districts and by promoting tourism.                     If my home is listed on the National Register of Historic Places, will I be prohibited from making changes to my property?                      No, you are not prohibited from making changes to your home. In order to insure that the changes you make do not negatively effect the historic integrity of your property and cause your property to lose its eligibility for the Register, the National Park Service and the State Historic Preservation Office recommend that you follow the Secretary of Interior's Standards. Contact the State Historic Preservation Office for a copy of the Standards and technical assistance.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The Federal Investment Tax Credit Program authorizes a twenty percent investment tax credit for substantial rehabilitation of commercial historic properties listed on the National Register of Historic Places.  The rehabilitation plans and specifications are reviewed and approved by the State Historic Preservation Office and then are forwarded to the National Park Service for final certification. The rehabilitation work must be done according to the Secretary of the Interior's Standards for Rehabilitation.  In return for the credit, the historic building must be used for an income-producing purpose for at least five years. Owner-occupied residential properties do not qualify for the federal rehabilitation tax credit.  The typical savings for a property owner depends upon the amount of money invested in the rehabilitation of the building. It also makes a difference when the money is invested into the home or historic building. The earlier the investment is made, the more money is saved.   An Example   If an investor purchases an historic commercial property for $100,000, and invests $150,000 to rehabilitate it, through this program he would be able to claim $30,000 (20%) credit for this project which would be subtracted from the amount of individual Federal income tax he would have to pay.  If this commercial historic property owner has an income of less than $200,000, he may use the tax credit to offset the tax owed on up to $25,000 of his income. So, for this taxpayer in the 36% tax bracket, he could use $9,000 of tax credits per year (36% x $25,000 = $9,000). Any unused credits are carried forward to the next year. *     *Ms. Fitzgerald is not a professional tax advisor. Please consult your CPA for expert advice on property tax information and property investments.   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oregon has a unique program available to National Register property owners, and contributing historic property owners within National Register Historic Districts.  If you are planning to renovate or restore your home and are planning to invest money into it, this program will freeze your property taxes at their current rate for 15 years.  In return for this benefit, owners agree to maintain the property in good condition, carry out an agreed upon program of rehabilitation, seek SHPO design review and approval prior to making changes to the property.  The typical savings for a property owner depends upon the amount of money invested in the rehabilitation of the building. It also makes a difference when the money is invested into the home or historic building. The earlier the investment is made, the more money is saved.   An Example   For example, a homeowner purchases an historic home which has an assessed value of $100,000 with annual taxes on the property of $1,600 a year.  If this homeowner plans on making $50,000 in improvements on the property, it will increase his property assessment to $150,000 and if his tax rate remains at 1.6%, his taxes will increase to $2,400 a year.  If the property is placed on the Special Assessment program, the taxes will be frozen at the original rate for 15 years. Therefore, the property owner can expect to save approximately $12,000 in taxes over this fifteen year period.  If this owner plans on making $100,000 in improvements to this property, bringing the assessed value from $100,000 to $200,000, the owner will save $24,000 in taxes over this fifteen year period.  Keep in mind that this example does not take into account other market factors including the potential annual 3% increase in RMV of property which can occur without any significant improvements to the property. Therefore the tax savings to the property owner could potentially be greater. *    *Ms. Fitzgerald is not a professional tax advisor. Please consult your CPA for expert advice on property tax information and property investments.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If you are a historic homeowner you may be interested in adding your home to the local cultural resource inventory in your community.  Some communities offer local grant programs for historic homeowners who are on the local resource list.  These grants can help pay for basic repairs and maintenance of your historic home.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Do you believe your home is significant in its architectural style or workmanship? Is your house associated with a historically significant person or event?   If so, it could be eligible for the National Register of Historic Places. Listing in the National Register of Historic Places honors the property and recognizes its importance to the community, the state or the nation. Owners of listed properties may apply for Federal and State historic preservation grant funding when it is available.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       “If these walls could talk”  Have you ever wondered about the history of your historic house? Who lived there before you? Why was your home built the way it was?  Through deed research, assessment records, building permits and other historic documentation, a detailed house genealogy can be put together to answer all of your questions. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>