<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Yesterday Sandra drove us to Stuttgart, Germany to do a little sightseeing and what not. You know do the castle and museums which was pretty sweet and it was raining so we wanted to be inside anyways. A couple near accidents (jk) sandra just got her liscence. Im going to Swiss tommorrow so wish me luck! Check out this webpage to see the castle i went to yesterday its pretty cool and it reminded me of a miniture Versille (the palace in Paris i went to last year) love all  urlLink http://www.schloesser-magazin.de/de/objekte/lb/lbth.php        Love Emily     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Some Sizzling Poetry For The Soul     The Chimney Sweeper   A little black thing among the snow,Crying "'weep! 'weep!" in notes of woe!"Where are thy father and mother, say?""They are both gone up to the church to pray."Because I was happy upon the heath,And smiled among the winter's snow,They clothed me in the clothes of death,And taught me to sing the notes of woe."And because I am happy and dance and sing,They think they have done me no injury,And are gone to praise God and his Priest and King,Who make up a heaven of our misery."    William Blake    How do I love Thee?   How do I love thee? Let me count the ways. I love thee to the depth and breadth and height My soul can reach, when feeling out of sight For the ends of Being and ideal Grace. I love thee to the level of every day's Most quiet need, by sun and candlelight. I love thee freely, as men strive for Right; I love thee purely, as they turn from Praise. I love with a passion put to use In my old griefs, and with my childhood's faith. I love thee with a love I seemed to lose With my lost saints, I love thee with the breath, Smiles, tears, of all my life! and, if God choose, I shall but love thee better after death. Elizabeth Browning    Because I Could Not Stop For Death   Because I could not stop for Death— He kindly stopped for me— The Carriage held but just Ourselves— And Immortality. We slowly drove—He knew no haste And I had put away My labor and my leisure too, For His Civility— We passed the School, where Children strove At Recess—in the Ring— We passed the fields of Gazing Grain— We passed the Setting Sun— Or rather—He passed Us— The Dews drew quivering and chill— For only Gossamer, my Gown— My Tippet—only Tulle— We paused before a House that seemed A Swelling of the Ground— The Roof was scarcely visible— The Cornice—in the Ground— Since then—'tis Centuries—and yet Feels shorter than the Day I first surmised the Horses' Heads Were toward Eternity—    Emily Dickinson      Post your fav. poems in my comments section!       PS: 6 more days until my journey, kind of got bored of thinking last night. Just had a mind overload lately i guess cause i was like bored of thinking and was like lets just talk about mindless things instead of going indepth into death, life, and much more. For some reason the talks with my best bud in Germany (Sandra) have been about death, but just because i've been thinking a lot about life and with that obviously comes the topic of death. We wouldn't care so much about living if we didn't know that it wasn't for eternity. I wrote my uncle a letter but i have not sent it to him yet, what if it doesn't get there on time? Well im gonna head off the internet and doing somethign even less productive lol, i have 8 hours to go before we go to the english movie at the theater. lol. Its like i live to watch movies this week cause i have nothign better to do which is kinda sad. Oh well i will have plenty to do next month, which is kinda scarey cause i have no idea what those things will be...but exciting! Thanks for the comment Sammy you chicken fucker.     Love Emily  
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Song Of The Day: "When your feeling sad and low, heres a number you can count on...Call me"(or email Emily at e_elmo20@hotmail.yom) "don't be afraid to just call me, call me and ill be around"    That was the song of the day and I hope you all enjoyed it immensely. Well Emily's day was very productive although I think I spent like 200 euro on clothes and shit. Ah. That is not good considering my budget but I had to make myself feel good didn't I? LOL. So that's what I did today and tomorrow is the party night which I will up date you on right away!  Your job is to answer the question of the day!!!!!!!!!!! What is the one thing in the world that makes you feel happy whenever your having the shittiest day?    Get back to me on that one, just go down to the bottom of the page and add your comment. Love to hear! Emily   
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Welcome    : ( Emily, thats me, has a blog for you! Come one and all and experience reality, truth, ok some bullshit, and a good sence of humor. Now thats one way to sell myself...the other i cant do online)                               to the blog of a   brilliant brunette   (how you like that sammy) Im sitting in  Germany  right now relaxing and about to go shopping and get my hair done, how fucking typical of a girl is that? HAHAH Anyways im on the search for an  epiphany  right now, way across the world and im realizes tons of things. And the funniest one is that you dont have to go away from home to find anything out usually unless i mean the people in your world are holding you back. One thing i ahve realised is that men in Africa are creepy and you should run away...run for your life. lol. I went to  North Africa  for 2 weeks with two good firends from Germany and we met some hotties and what not, you know the good old days on a vacation. Im leaving in 8 days to go travell around europe alone and find myself. This whole trip i have been thinking and feeling way to much and i think its time for me to just let it all go and let it happen for itself. I know im going to have tons of experience scarey and great on this trip but i dont need to force them to happen. I guess this blog is just going to be about my trip and finding myself. Maybe you can get good tips on what TO DO and what NOT TO DO.    PS : SAMMY I MISS YOU AND I HOPE YOU LIKE THE BLOG ACTION THAT I GOT GOING ON HERE: LOL: NOTHING LIKE A GOOD BLOG TO START YOUR DAY FUCKER!!!!!!!   love emily  
    
</post>


</Blog>