<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      READ ALONE..... ESPECIALLY THE POEM   CASE 1: Kelly Sedey had one wish, for her boyfriend of three  years,   David Marsden, to propose to her. Then one day when she was out to  lunch  David proposed! She accepted, but then had to leave because she had  a meeting in 20 min. When she got to her office,she noticed on her  computer  she had some e-mail's. She checked it, the usual stuff from her  friends,  but then she saw one that she had never gotten before. It was  this poem.  She simply deleted it without even reading all of it. BIG MISTAKE!  Later  that evening, she received a phone call from the police. It was  about DAVID! He had been in an accident with an 18 wheeler. He didn't  survive .  CASE 2: Take Katie Robinson She received this poem and being the  believer that she was, she sent it to a few of her friends but  didn't  have enough e-mail addresses to send out the full 10 that you must. Three  days   later, Katie went to a masquerade ball. Later that night when she  left to get to her car to go home, she was killed on the spot by a  hit-and-run   drunk driver.  CASE 3: Richard S. Willis sent this poem out within 45 minutes of  reading it. Not even 4 hours later walking along the street to his  new   job   interview with a really big company, when he ran into Cynthia Bell,  hissecret love for 5 years. Cynthia came up to him and told him of her  passionate crush on him that she had had on him for 2 years.  Three days later, he proposed to her and they got married. Cynthia  and  Richard are still married with three children, happy as ever!  This is the poem:    Around the corner I have a friend,  In this great city that has no end,  Yet the days go by and weeks rush on,  And before I know it, a year is gone.  And I never see my old friends face,  For life is a swift and terrible race,  He knows I like him just as well,  As in the days when I rang his bell.  And he rang mine but we were younger then,  And now we are busy, tired men.  Tired of playing a foolish game,  Tired of trying to make a name.  "Tomorrow" I say! "I will call on Jim  Just to show that I'm thinking of him."  But tomorrow comes and tomorrow goes,  And distance between us grows and grows.  Around the corner, yet miles away,  "Here's a telegram sir," "Jim died today."  And that's what we get and deserve in the end.  Around the corner, a vanished friend.  Remember to always say what you mean. If you love someone, tell  them.  Don't be afraid to express yourself. Reach out and tell someone what they  mean to you. Because when you decide that it is the right time it  might be  too late.  Seize the day. Never have regrets. And most importantly, stay close  to  your friends and family, for they helped you make a better person  that   you   are today.        Regards,  The Simply Me  "give smile to everyone but give your heart to only one"  urlLink  
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       well.... i don't know what should i feel this past few days....      you know, prelims and everything... then samahan pa ng probs sa   love life, family and school hehehe...  grabeh...       Prelims???   GRRrrRRRrrrr.....   i just hope pumasa ako...   you know i'm not expecting anymore to get a high grades.. i know   my standing and everytime i think of it i really feel bad..   i hate myself. i feel like i'm the weakest. i'm the least among   them... i can't accept the fact that i cannot bring back my   achievements (not only academically but also in other ways)   when i'am still in my elementary days.. or even in  my 1st year   or 2nd year high school days....   going back on my prelim grades... most of them... haaaay... as if   i didn't study... grabeh... pero, ok lang naman yung iba.. so far...   and eto pa, you know what???!! my prof. in english and i had   a misunderstanding... until now, hindi pa kami nag-uusap...   i just hope it wont affect my grades that much..   kasi pag nangyari yun, ewan ko nalang...         love life???   hehehe... eto, full of love... ok naman kami ng   cutie ko... at least he's starting to understand my situation..   and he can also accept the fact that i'm already in college...   harhar... may story kasi yan eh... anyway, i'm not gonna tell   it for now... siguro, secret na muna... hehehe... joke... i just need   a lot of  time for that.....         family????   i don't what to do with them, they can't understand my situation..   i also don't know how will i tell them that my grades   aren't pretty much ok like what they were expecting... it's hard   to live with those stupid expectations!!! grabeh... i'm fed up   with my family probs.. if you only know it....         shool????   here.. we're busy because of our upcoming activities.   mr. and ms. precom, epoch, reporting, and a lot more...   so far, im enjoying it... and i should enjoy it cause i chose   to be with them... and love being with them...   i miss my friends...      hi cutie!!!! thanks!!!!! sige!!!!    guyz... help me... what do you think i  should do to hadle those things???      i have to go!!!! see you!!! i still have a lot of things to accomplish!!   bye and have a nice day!!! *mwaaaahhh*  
      
</post>


</Blog>