<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Excerpts from: Journal of O/our Journey Day & Date:  08/20/04 Friday  ...Last night was very good and very needed and very good... i never in a million years thought ANYTHING could feel as good as orgasms and all that surrounds them.... But honestly i think sub space may be a tie... no kidding. And when they both intermingle OMG OMG OMG...  
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Excerpts from: Journal of O/our Journey Day & Date:  08/20/04 Friday  ...Last night was very good and very needed and very good... i never in a million years thought ANYTHING could feel as good as orgasms and all that surrounds them.... But honestly i think sub space may be a tie... no kidding. And when they both intermingle OMG OMG OMG...  
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Journal of O/our Journey Written by Master Charles slave: diamond  Day & Date: 08/18/04 Wednesday  Very busy day today. Master has meetings this morning and at 5pm also so i will be at the shop till close and i have an AVON meeting at 6pm. Master said He would call from the meeting this afternoon and let me know if they have food there or if W/we will meet somewhere for a bite after the meetings. This morning and i guess last night i dreamed several times. Not about sexual things, all about being Master's slave and what it meant and personality etc etc....  The interesting thing in the dream is i was either talking to Master about the things i am going to say here now, or He was reminding me of much He has told me... refresher training me i guess. Funny how my internal thinking quiets and speaks to me at night sometimes like that. Anyway, i didn't have time to write my journal this morning before breakfast so i am sending it to the shop as Master said He would check His email just before He left for the meeting. And, i want to get this to Master before He leaves so i need to be quick. If He would just reply to my email and say He got it or something i would really appreciate it. :)  Bottom line: Last night when Master and i were joking about my talking or not talking etc... and i said: "Don't You like my personality," to Master, Even though W/we were kidding around to a degree, i also knew that i haven't been practicing my speaking and not speaking in the ways Master desires me to. Last night i struggled with thinking that "Master was not wanting to hear what i had to say &amp; doesn't He want me to have my personality" aspect of it. But in my sleep these are the things that were said: i know that Master and i get along well. i know that W/we fit well T/together. i know that the only real thing W/we both dislike and need to come to a much better place soon so W/we can move into a fullness with less limitations in that area, is my fat and that is something that although is taking so much work and too long is still indeed temporary. By the way i am determined to find a good and workable plastic/reconstructive surgeon. And after Master gets me the three month member ship at the gym i was thinking about stepping my three days up to about every day except Saturday. (At least 5 days out of 7...) Anyway i will talk to Master about that later. Back to the dreams last night....  In the dreams i spoke to Master about things that concerned me... "Don't You like my personality Master, Don't You care what i have to say?" Etc. etc.... It all came down to this: Yes Master likes my personality, He likes and loves me. However, even my personality... or i should say any aspect of my personality He doesn't like or would prefer to be different is His decision and not mine. And, as His slave that is something i should accept, not question, and endeavor to change to His liking... period. i know that i, without Master's training and lining up with what He desires of my speaking and demeanor, speak too much, too loudly and draw too much attention to myself. i don't do it to draw attention to myself, but nevertheless i do. i know that i am to speak only when spoken to outside of a business situation. i am never to interrupt anyone especially Master. i am not supposed to speak until a commercial comes on if Master is watching TV. i am not suppose to speak until i make eye contact with Him or ask to actually. i have gotten far from that somehow and i am sorry Master and i will be very aware of my speech and demeanor as it is far more important to me that i please You, than to speak whenever and however "i choose". 
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a nightmare of a morning! First it all started out with a nightmare. i dreamed that Master was in possible danger from a crazy man (i think He was a deputy or detective lol...) who had just killed His partner who was having an affair with His wife. And here was one of the very disturbing parts: He cut Him up and deposited the pieces at the sheriff's Dept and the hand on the severed arm (on top of the pile... OMG it was an awful dream...) was still moving & twitching. In the dream i was with a friend and we knew the man who got chopped up. We both were freaking. Then somehow my son (22 yrs old) came into the dream. (In real life He is across the country in the southeast). But He came to visit and was helping me get to Master in the next town to get to Him before the crazy man did. In the dream the man was after anyone who cheated on their wife/husband/gf/etc... And He was convinced Master was cheating on me with an ex gf in a neighboring town. It was all really weird. Master was laughing at my dream as i told Him about it this morning. A few things made sense but most of it was just chaotic and nonsensical. But it was so real & upsetting it was hard to shake it even after i woke up.  Then as i was fixing Master breakfast the top of the egg carton came open and 5 raw eggs splatted onto the freshly mopped floor... Took a while to clean up that mess... i still got Master's breakfast done before He came downstairs though.:)  Then after Master left for work (laughing as W/we talked a bit about my nightmare), i scrambled around to get an AVON order together that had to be delivered about 5 minutes away before 7:20 A.M. and i couldn't find the clock that went with the order. i knew i had had it right there in the office it was weird. Finally i ran down to Master's Drycleaners thinking maybe i had left it there but it wasn't there so ran back home to find it right there under a box flap... geeez... i got it together and ran it to her and had it in her hands by about 7:17... Whew....  i went back home and cleaned the house a bit and got my hair fixed etc. And then started loading the car with my AVON stuff. It was about 8:20 and i was on the way to drop off the paperwork for Master's Courier Service phonebook ad &amp; then go & open the shop. i had everything loaded and the car key in my hand and went to put it in the ignition and it few out of my hand and sounded like it landed in between (the bucket seats). i thought "figures'... what a morning! 35 minutes later i am in tears as i couldn't find the key!!! i tore the car apart moved the seats back and forth went through everything including my open purse and a bag i had on the seat... to no avail... NO KEY... AHHHHH!!!!! i went to a neighbor and she got a flash light &amp; we very quickly looked again but still couldn't find it and i had to get to the drycleaner as it was 9 a.m. and time to open it, so she took me to the shop. A very sweet older man was waiting for me to open but was very nice about it and was concerned about me because He knew i usually get here early to open. If anything He reminded me how much of a slave i really am as He touched my cheek sweetly in a grandfatherly sort of way and said there, there honey it will be a better day now and smiled. And apart of me relaxed at that moment lol... i thought geeez i really do respond automatically as a slave....  i dreaded calling Master as although i have never lost a key in my life before i came here... in the last few months i have lost them several times (only once actually losing them never to be found again). But the key to the car is a computerized key and costs about $100 to replace it.  Anyway i called Him and He started laughing and said i was a disaster area... i figured at least that was better than Him being upset... i will be so glad when W/we find that stupid key, it is driving me crazy!!! Well i am at the shop now and customers have been calling and in & out and spoken to Master re; business things a couple times and He is being great. Although i sure hope we find that key easily tonight so He doesn't get too frustrated with me over it... sheesh.... what a day so far....And that dream as that was really bazaar... What s going on that moon retrograde thing or what? Well better get back to work... Hope your day started out better than mine lol. slave or not... This girl has had one heck of a day so far... Blessings, diamond  p.s.- It is now 5:20 and i popped on here for 5 minutes to say Master ran by the house when He got back into town and found the key between the seats. He said it took Him about a minute... geeeez i am really happy and really perplexed at the same time.... But mostly just REALLY HAPPY He found the key.... whew... So glad this day is winding down. Well i have a few errands to do before Master gets home so i am outa here... :) Think i will just work on staying out of trouble for the rest of the day... And then slide into a hopefully much easier tomorrow.... :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Since last week when Master has started moving things up a notch and i guess testing me to find out just how deep in Him i am or willing to be in reality not just desire... i began to realize how far i really am from what most importantly Master desires/expects & wants of me and what Master and i B/both need/want &amp; desire of me as well. i wanted to know exactly what Master wanted/expected of me and i pushed Him to write it out for me. Something tangible i could take on and understand and grasp. And He did last night. It startled me as i knew i still had so very very far to go and that He is right that many times i do put far too much energy in things that i care about (internet especially) rather than making what i know is priority to Him be priority in me. He mentioned yesterday about the housework.... not being up to par (dust etc...) i surface clean... Master wants me to deep clean. i run through with the time i have and make everything look good and do what has to be done that say but don't near often enough just stop and scrub doors and baseboards and polish furniture instead of feather dust, etc. That needs to change now and i do understand that. Master knows i have a lot to accomplish with various things and He does make allowances for those things, it is the wasted time i spend on the internet when the house is not up to His standards that bothers Him. Plus i find a lot of time "finding myself" in my groups. There is nothing wrong with community... that is good. And O/others giving T/their insight & encouragement and experiences as well as my experiences touching O/others...that is all good and positive and i am sure Master would agree. But i have used the internet many times to seek validation that i should be receiving from Master alone. And also for comfort, direction, insight and encouragement that i should be seeking from Master not O/others. Others can interact and enhance but my purpose and validation and comfort, love, direction, encouragement, pats on the back should come from Master and anything else is just gravy... side dishes to enhance the main entree.... not the main entree. Master is to ALWAYS be the main entree. i do get that now. ~snip~ i am not saying it is not good to hear and react with O/others that are living an M/s life etc. But i see now that drawing from them instead of seeking out what Master needs of me and inwardly questioning Master and even myself instead of just focusing on Him... being His slave... doing His will, that which He desires of me and being at His feet and available for what ever purpose He chooses... Glad to get up and refill; His glass or throw something away instead of thinking "my body aches and i just sat down"... that is a wrong attitude & thought process for me as His slave. ~snip~ Following are excerpts of what my Master wrote to me (last night): What do I want of you?I want all of you without hesitation-forethought-holding back. I want total abandonment of yourself to Me. Nothing less. you will know when you have reached that plateau. you will feel it deep inside of you. ~snip~ you cannot feel these things until you reach the threshold of knowing you are where you need to be so that you will feel secure in O/our relationship. Blind obedience to My will and my desires. The word "no" will not exist in your vocabulary. you will feel and have nothing but positive thoughts and feelings about U/us and O/our relationship. And I don't believe you can reach these emotional and mental goal until you have reached your physical goal. When that happens all the things that you feel you need from Me you will receive. Until then you have support and love and understanding - although sometimes it may not feel like that to you. ~snip~ W/we will do things My way and that is the only way. In am the Master Owner Lord Lover Daddy and when you accept these precepts fully only then will you be the slave you were meant to be. you are striving to reach perfection - it is a never ending uphill battle but the rewards are great - emotionally physically and mentally. The only way you can reach these goals is to strip yourself of your old being and face the future in your nakedness, totally accepting to divest yourself of your will and put on your Masters will in ALL things. The only limits you should accept are the limits set by your Lord and Owner. It is the Master who sets the limits because it is He that pushes the slave towards them -never exceeding them or causing emotional or physical damage. Distress yes - damage no. Each limit pushed is pushed with distress and each limit overcome is overcome with joy and satisfaction in knowing that you have pleased your Master and that He will reward you for pleasing him, knowing that you have please Him for His physical pleasure and your emotional pleasure. ~snip~ That woke me up. i wanted to hear, i wanted and even needed to know... But the actual truth of it and knowing how far i am from what i should be hurt... deeply hurt.... ~snip~ It basically destroyed me... the me that was left, the me that i thought was much gone.... That Master sees as still mostly there... she must go and submit herself to Him now as she thought she had already, but understands now that she only has in part and that is what Master sees. Master did comfort me last night and remind me this is a journey and that He knows my intentions and i have progressed much and going in the right direction etc and that helped... Actually it made me understand that a few minutes of comfort, encouragement, acknowledgement, direction, love from Master far surpasses hours of it elsewhere from O/others... i will make Master my complete focus now. i will listen to His tapes, read the above He wrote to me and focus on Master; put my attention and focus on doing the things i need to, to please Him and to keep myself where He knows i need to be mentally and emotionally in order to be fulfilled also... i need to go get Master breakfast now so i close saying the words i have said often that are so strong right now that they are like a knife penetrating me.... reminding me of Who Master is really is and who i am as His.... As You will and mold me i will submit all to You Master. i love You very much, diamond  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Originally written on April 8, 2004.     Master's slave diamond and her Master switched "roles" for the day on Sunday... Yep, you heard Master's slave correctly... she and her Masterswitched roles all day yesterday (Sunday...) Whew did T/they learn alot... When Master and His slave were long distance T/they used to kid around about "switching roles for one day" and T/they have mentioned it several times but never actually did it until yesterday.First diamond really has to say she respects her Master so much for even doing it. she knows it was hard for Him to do right from the very start of the day. It was pretty fun to her for a little while until the novelty of it wore off...diamond woke very early trying to think about what she should do and how she should act as "Mistress". she decided she needed to get her Master's attention so she made Him a very interesting black elastic collar... only not for His neck (lol). Tight enough to feel but not enough to be too uncomfortable to remind Master that He was to roleplay as her slave that day. she knew if she didn't do something like that (the "collar" and name changes :) to remind T/them B/both of T/their roleplaying T/they would never pull it off.she pretty much shocked her Master because she had Him sit on the floor in front of her as she told Him the "rules" (which included no farting or belching except in the bathroom lol). she told Him she would call Him "slave" in private (she always calls Him Master in private and a couple times she accidentally slipped and did call Him Master & said yes Sir etc lol, as it was hard not too) and "Charlie" in public (she usually calls Him Charles in public). They went to breakfast to a cool little place in a neighboring western restaurant/saloon, it was really neat and enjoyable.she surprised Master several times throughout the day by takingstrong control of His habits like answering her with "non-wordsetc.). (lol &amp; yikes...) Master kept very craftily topping from the bottom especially in a number of sneaky little ways thatsaid "today" she was "Mistress" (so funny to even say...)but "tomorrow" was on the horizon... A few times she was kind of scared to keep on going and doing what she thought she should as Mistress & the stressing over it was exhausting to her. The morning with the drive &amp; breakfast with Master was really nice. And she admits that at first "being in control" felt good and it was even fun. she wanted her Master to know how it felt to not have choices, to be a slave even in very basic things. Well He got it all right... although she soon found out (about midday) that Master had a bit of an awakening of His own. And not what she thought, the opposite actually. (yikes...)Believe me, it is exhausting to try and be Mistress when first of all you aren't one and it becomes really stressful after a short while. Secondly, you miss your Master's control/dominance & even worse i was still affected by things Master said even though He was roleplaying the slave, which by the way it is very hard to try and be Mistress to a total and complete nonslave to begin with. Especially when you are not attracted to submissive "boyish" men so you have no desire to really experience the submissiveness from Him accept to turn the tables. i am strongly attracted and moved by control and dominance so after the novelty wore off it became far more stressful than fun. And i still had hours to go. Maybe i triedtoo hard i don't know. But i did what i thought i was supposed to. About midday i asked Master to rate Himself and then me as slaves. He rated Himself at a "0" (but i would give Him a "1' just because He did it for the day... gotta respect that... lol...) He was never really out of control and He knew it but He did try to give it what He could. i was actually very impressed He had the guts &amp; wisdom to do it as much as W/we did. Even though at the times i didn't realize He was storing everything He was learning for changes He would initialize immediately. Geeez.... (Kind of backfired on me there...) But when He rated me out of 1 to 10 as a 5 i got so affected by it (upset) & kept asking/pushing for details when He said He was changing things etc until He told me specifically what He was changing &amp; i immediately "went back to my slavespace" internally even when He said it. There were things i didn't want Him to do and i questioned Master as to if He felt sorry for me etc... He said no because it was my choice etc... that i WAS a slave, His slave and these things would be for my ultimate good as they would help keep me in my slavespace and make a me a much better slave. And then used one of His favorite sayings that i don't particularly love tohear: "Often the ends do justify the means...") Even when He was relaying the info i pushed for... Internally i felt everything immediately tighten and began to feel myself going into my slavespace just with Him telling me what He was going to do... One thing was keeping a "timeline" when He is not around saying specifically what i am doing... (when working the site, when exercising, when cleaning the house/doing chores and specifically what was done etc... egaads... i guess gone are the days i wait until the last minute and not get all the chores done etc... Then there will be immediate punishments (switched once with a cane for each infraction (the cane was recently given to Master by the local BDSM group. Master didn't think i could handle getting too many at one time as i am kind of a wimp...) i have kind of felt it needed but now that it is happening i am kind of freaking inside... i will just try not to mess up too much because it hurts and it is humiliating... Master is pretty particular about the house being as spotless as possible etc...Yesterday Master kept racking up so many infractions... all from attitude and topping from the bottom lol. i was stressing like crazy over knowing i should "punish Master". Actually, i didn't think i could do it until He said something about a couple very sexy girls on TV then i got aggravated and got my "self" back enough to. i caned Him... i really did it...OMG!!!! Then i was freaking inside again.... What a weird day. By the end of the night i was just drinking wine for courage. By then i was just tired of it all... i needed desperately to feel Master's control and i knew i still needed to follow through. Plus i desperately needed to make love with Master and i guess i felt it was my chance to do so at night (Master is a "morning person" *wink*) with candles and music etc. i had planned to give Him a massage etc and end the night sweetly but then right before W/we were to go upstairs i asked Master about the day how i did and how He felt He did etc. He said i was a bitch as a Mistress &amp; that upset me so badly it did me in. i just couldn't take it anymore. i tried to hold it together but ended up sending Him upstairs and then i just started crying... Finally i went upstairs and i laid down up in Master's arms (crying and mumbling about not wanting to be "Mistress" anymore) It was a bit after 10:00. i don't really know what i said... i just knew i needed to feel Him again as Master and i just didn't have it in me to go with the Mistress thing anymore. Master was really great about it... He did laugh at me some but more in a "poor baby" mode than making fun of me... He flung the "collar" off (lol) and took control of His very badly in need of Him, slave. He made love to her and sent her immediately into a totally different "headspace" *very big happy mmmmm smiles*. And, she fell asleep in His arms... later in the night she felt Him kiss her on the top of her head and everything inside of her was (and is) just so very thankful to be His...     she learned so much yesterday... she knows that she will indeed be a better slave and Master has said He knows He will be a better Master as a result. so it turned out to be a good experience for B/both of them although T/they neither ever desire to repeat it... :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Please Note: This essay/post was written on 5/19/2004.  i have been fascinated & very drawn to  mind control and hypnotism in my journey with Master.  i also am very hypnotizable.  Master has spent weeks (actually months now) learning to use this tool with me and it has been & continues to be a wonderful and very freeing experiece. May i ask what Y/your thoughts and comments regarding this subject.  i know to some giving of my mind blindly for Master to mold sounds extreme but i am His slave & property and belong completly to Him and also very much desire to do so.  i look forward to Y/your comments. Blessings to A/all.      Hypnotism & the Molding of Master's slave    Master spent weeks (months) learning about hypnotism with much direction and assistance from a Psychologist/Hypnotherapist/Master Friend. i have to say i don't know how much He has continued to learn about it. But i doknow He has done 4 taped "messages for me now and i don't know what is said on any of them except for a few words in the initial greeting and the very end saying to wake and feel good etc. (This note inserted on 8/16 Master has now done a total of 8 tapes for me and i love to listen to them. i have a new one from Saturday that i will belistening to every day this week. :) Master has chosen not to tell His slave what is on the tapes. At first she was so curious it drove her crazy not to know was on the tapes. But now although she is still curious she finds the whole mind exchange deliciously thrilling. she feels it is an amazing gift her Master is giving her to speak directly into her mind as He wills. she wanted/needed/desperately sought not to struggle... she needed to feel secure in Him and let go of any fears that would keep her from completely releasing all to Him. And she truly feels that has or at least in most part is taking place inside of her. she is thankful..she knows she has far to go to be as He wills... not even just to "do" as He wills but also "be" as He wills... That is truly her greatest desire. To be completely His as He wills. That His will is her will... no separation in the two, therefore no struggle, no fear, no hesitancy.Is she totally there yet? No... she still has far to go. Has she comefar... she really does think she has come a ways yes. But that isnot for her to say... You would need to ask her Master that.she knows she has far far to go in Him and she is but a lump of clayin His hands that He may mold as He wills. her Lord/Master/Owneris also the clayMaster that will mold her into all she is to be inHim.she is happier inside than she ever has been. Yet there is a part ofher that grieves that she is not yet all He needs and desires her tobe. she knows she must continue to strive for excellence. It is acliche' yes... to be His perfect slave... but she must strive toattain it... because as she has said before, He is worth it, He isworth her excellence, He is worth her all. she understands now thatshe not only loves Him with her entire being mind, body & soul...but she is honor bound to Him. He has truly become her Owner and sheis His property now... living breathingproperty that is dependent on Him to enjoy &amp; experience true life,experience joy, even function well... He has literally become herlife source now. The amazing thing is she no longer fears how deepHe is inside of her now... instead she revels in it... revels inHim. It is good... it is very good... she knows being one whoconstantly analyzed and questioned everything, there is no way shecould have come as far as she has or be as free as she feels in Himthus far if He had not taken the time to speak to her mind as Hedoes. He also speaks to her consciously of course among other things. Butthis use of hypnotism is very good for Master's slave diamond andshe is thankful & grateful to her Master for taking the time to moldher in this way. she is a very thankful and blessed slave indeed.she has so far to go and she will ever strive to be all herLord/Master/Owner requires and desires of her... she must... it isall that is truly important to her... it is her call in this life tobe as perfect as His slave as is possible to be and she willcontinue to give all of herself to become all that He needs, wants &amp;desires. His needs and His will have become and continue to more &more become hers as well... Dear Master, Your slave loves &amp; needs You so much and she is so blessed to be Yours. Thank You Master, thank You for making me Yoursand believing in me... i will not fail You Master... i love You withall that is within me and desire to be all i possibly can be according to Your will Master.Yours as You will, diamondThank You A/all for letting me share these thoughts from within withY/you. i look forward to Y/your comments (positive and/or negative). Blessings, Mastersdiamond_LMO
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    For Master's Use 1 yr&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Darkness Master's slave&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         What A slave Isn't & How that Relates to Mastersdiamond_LMO  written by: Master's slave diamond/brenda per her Master Afternoon of: 03/10/04  A slave isn't one who is independent. her dependence instead is in & on her Master, not herself. Master's slave has behaved many times as though she was still an independent woman/person but when all is said and done it is very obvious that she is not at all independent but extremely dependant on her Master from the inside out for even her well-being. Even being able to think and function well depends on His approval &  assurance of love and value in her. she knows she has no right to and it is not wise to behave as if she is still independent and will  remember at all times & in all circumstances “the truth of the matter” and behave as such.   A slave isn't one who has the right to do, say &/or react as she chooses. Instead her rights, speech and reactions should all be tempered by &amp; subject to her Master's will, desires & wants of her. Not based on her own will, desires &amp; wishes but His. Master's slave has many times reacted & spoken wrongly and she now understands this is no longer permissible or acceptable to do under any circumstances.  A slave isn't one who can react to her emotions, hurts or confusion at her will & in any way she chooses. Instead she is one who must learn to die to "self" and make her Master's will come before everything within her even her hurts and confusions. she is to voice her concerns, confusions and/or hurts when &amp; in the manner Master says it is OK to do so or in her journal only. Not at any time or in any way as she chooses. Master's slave has done horribly with this. her emotions have gone crazy many times and she has become hurt and sometimes angry or confused and then reacted very poorly as a result. Again she understands that regardless of the issues and/or circumstances that may arise, she must continue to put her Master first in her mind, reactions and demeanor and question only when appropriate to do so, with respect and in the manner Master chooses.  A slave isn’t one who can keep her thoughts to herself. She is to have complete transparency with her Master. Be completely truthful and tell Him anything that she thinks or feels that may be of help to Him or be a tool in determining what is best Himself and her as she is His property and He owns her thoughts and feelings as well as all she is and will be. Even her emotions are subject to Master.  Master’s slave knows there have been times she has not told Master things she should have or chosen what portion of something to tell Him in wanting to make it easier on herself. And she realizes now that in withholding anything she is basically topping from the bottom. She apologizes for withholding information or portions of information that Master may have found helpful because she feared what He may do with that information. She knows that is not her decision to make. He is to choose what He does or doesn’t do with any information. But all is subject and due to Him.   A slave isn't one who makes accusations toward or believes the negative of, or questions her Master even if the circumstances appear that He has mot been truthful or said something she does not understand. It is a slave's place to believe in her Master in all things and not accuse and choose to trust and believe in Him no matter what circumstances appear to be. If Master says red is black and black is red she is to accept it as such and react accordingly. she had one time to choose to trust and believe in Him and she has done so. Master's slave knows even in her heart today she questioned her Master's truth and integrity and it is not her place to even think as such, much less accuse Him in her heart or to Him. she understands now that is not acceptable or permissible and she is very sorry.  A slave isn't one who has rights as she determines. When Master's slave gave up her rights  to her Master she & He determined a few key things that were agreed upon by B/both of them. Other than those agreed upon needs that Master has recognized and has chosen to give to her as crucial to T/their relationship, she has no rights other than what her Master determines her to have. she realizes that is down to very basic things even speaking, how she thinks... dresses, makeup, how she wears her hair and jewelry... really everything... she gave all to her Master and has no rights other than what He grants her. It is not within her right therefore to do, say or think anything outside of what He indicates to her as His will. This one is really hitting her as she realizes suddenly that everything He has allowed her: The ability and right to make decisions as she sees best when He is not available for her to ask and the rights granted to her by her Master to work the site and business as well as what she wears, who she speaks to, and many other things. her Master is very good to her and does allow her much freedom. she knows she hasn't always been aware of that or been appreciative of that either and she is now aware, appreciative...  and humbled... as well as thankful for His confidence in her. she is so sorry Master that she has not thanked You, praised You, been grateful for the freedoms and rights You have given her.  A slave isn't one who owns herself. A slave feels a strong need for her Master to own her in a very real sense and all that entails. Master's slave has not always behaved as one who is owned property or possession but has many times behaved as if she is equal to Him. she remembers He is Master/Owner & she is His slave/property and she is sorry she hasn't behaved as such many times. she can barely breath for some reason this realization is hitting her hard also...  Master's slave is very sorry for her failure to show the proper respect and place to Master in all those areas.... she thought she had and was for the most part. And though now she knows she has surrendered and is no longer struggling or battling her Master, this essay has brought much clarity as to who she is to be, Who Master is and how poorly she has behaved & reacted regarding many of these areas. she is very very sorry Master... she again see You high and lifter far above her. she sees and feels and remembers the "power exchange" and remembers very suddenly and so strongly that her head and neck are hurting at the impact of it. she is humbled, she is so very sorry... she is Your slave and will behave as such. she is privileged to belong to You Master. she loves, needs You  & understands more this moment than she ever has what it means that You are her Lord/Master/Owner and she is Your slave/property.... she is so humbled... she is so sorry... she is Yours As You will, brenda/diamond/baby   
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         The Magic of Enslavement  Written by Mastersdiamond_LMO on Feb 5, 2004  The strongest thing that motivates me is to "keep my focus on serving my Master well" and what i call keeping my mind in a "slavespace".  It is that when i do so, Master assumes His role more strongly and, at the same time, rewards me much more with His love and tenderness (cuddling and holding me, as well as in other ways *wink*) and is generally much more fulfilled and happy Himself as a result of my demeanor and submission to Him.  i need all of Master.  i need His strong and consistent control and ownership of me as my Lord/Master/Owner as well as needing His tenderness in the Daddy/Protector/Love side of Him.  And when He is pleased, He has a tendency to reward me with all of Who He is and i adore all of Who He is   And i am sure that any slave knows exactly what i mean when i say that the rewards of a happy, pleased, powerfully content Master/Owner is the most amazing motivation a slave could ever have.i know that just feeling my Master's pleasure with or in me can literally put me in a subspace like place.  The more i release to Master and show Him by my thoughts and resulting actions that HE is my priority and HE is first above all else, including myself, that HIS Will is my will, the happier and more fulfilled He is and that truly thrills me.  At those times, i feel I am making a difference in His life and being by loving and serving Him well and that fuels the deep slave love i have for Him and strongly continues to  further propel me into all i can be for Master.   One thing I know: Nothing can substitute  for a heart that sincerely loves and adores her Master so much that she wants to serve and love so well and His knowing that His happiness in her "rocks her world" far more than anyone or anything else on the face of this earth could come close to even touching her. i Love and adore my Master with all i am and all i will be... All is His and He will be my only Master always, forever,  i could never have another Master and He knows it.  He knows the level of love and commitment i have for Him and in Him.  He knows i love and need Him more than life itself and it is true, i do exist for my Master.  i have learned (and continue in that learning) what love, life, vulnerability, joy, sadness, worship and adoration, deep need and fulfillment really are in belonging to my Master/Owner and that, as i see it, THAT is the magic. 
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ~her Master’s slave~ 
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          In early 2003 i discovered D/s (Dominants/submissives). In May of 2003 i met my Master. Along the journey i began to know that i was created to become His slave. This page is a peak into O/our 24/7 TPE Lifetime Committed Relationship. When i first met Master my online name was sweetbabyb. i had been exploring the online world of D/s having stumbled acrossed it one day. i saw the words Dominants & submissives for a chat room. It struck me for some reason...it made sense to me although i knew nothing about it other than the words i read. i was afraid to enter the room (that makes me chuckle now...) And i went in saying "i know nothing, i am curious about what all this means". Two Doms/Masters took hours to explain things to me. They spoke a lot about positions and form but the psychological aspect is what intrigued me and drew me. i was hooked to how it made me feel when some of these "Doms" spoke with me. They said "wow you are a natural it is so in you..." And i thought, "this is crazy stuff, i need to get out of here and quit this..." But i couldn't... i kept going back again &amp; again learning more and more and searching out and reading much on the internet. (See links below for definitions & further information.)  The second night i had gone to the chat room i met a "Master" Who asked me questions for hours and then "collared" me online immediately. Everyone told me that was way too fast but the way this Man made me feel was incredible. Unfortunately most of O/our interaction was sexually driven. i am a very sexually wired person so although i knew it was not quite right i rode the wave. He would call throughout the day and bring me to glorious orgasms over the phone and message me at night and tell me i was meant for Him and He for me etc, although i never felt that within me. i liked Him &amp; i was becoming addicted to what He could do to me... But i knew He wasn't a lifetime commitment to be sure. That wave rode for 2 months before i said good bye. i thought this is crazy these subs/slaves & Doms/Dommes giving so much of T/themselves then going from person to person... Insane... No thank you!!! And i posted in the community i was a strong part of and said goodbye to all my friends there. That i must go as i couldn't handle the lifestyle with all of it's emotional ups &amp; downs etc.... i knew SO VERY LITTLE about the lifestyle then.  i received several emails about my post. One of them from this Man/Master that i had read some posts about and looked for His picture out of curiosity but never found. Something about Him intrigued me and pulled at me even though i didn't know Him or anything about Him other than a couple brief general intro posts. His email was very nice... but there was a wisdom in His words... i was immediately drawn to Him in a way i have never been drawn to anyone. i answered the email and He happened to be online and answered back. W/we sent a few emails, then began to message and later that night He phoned. From the very beginning with Him it was different for me, very very different... i knew there was something about this Man that everything inside of me was drawn to... But i didn't understand it at all. That was Memorial Day Weekend on Saturday. We messaged and spoke on the phone for many many hours that weekend, breaking only to grab a bite to eat and clean up and sleep a few hours and then would be back at it... Talking, asking questions, exploring... He immediately became my Master, not just in word but deep inside of me. Master changed my name to first sweetbabydoll_SC (Sir Charles) and later to swtbabydoll_MC (Master Charles). He was new in the lifestyle also and W/we explored and grew T/together. W/we were B/both naturals it turned out. Master was so full of wisdom and insight that it just flowed from Him, often He wasn't aware of it really... it just flowed as a part of Who He was (and is). Through much growth Master trained, learned with, molded and spent hours getting to know the past, present and creating/enhancing the future of His submissive. In a natural outcome of T/their growing and developing she became His slave giving all of herself to Him to have and use as He chose to do. T/they signed a Master/slave contract that He had her write and He wrote one as well. The written words were powerful to her. her whole life, her thinking, everything about her began to drastically change as He unearthed her authentic self: her Master's slave & property: His to be whatever He chose her to be. He changed her name soon thereafter to "Mastersdiamond_LMO (Lord/Master/Owner).  It was/is important to her that He not leave her one day sad and vulnerable and so completely enslaved to Him. It was/is important to her that He genuinely loved her and valued her. It was/is important to B/both of them that T/they love and enjoy E/each O/other as well as live T/their life T/together as Master/slave. T/they B/both has a knowing that this was all meant to be. she came to know this was her destiny and purpose... to be all her Lord/Master/Owner chose her to be, to improve her mind body and demeanor for His use and pleasure. she received much fulfillment from His pleasure and when it was compounded with His dominance/ownership it was &amp; is powerful beyond her imaginations. When the additional sexual component was involved it sent her soaring far out of herself and it amazed her, He amazed her. she began to love Him and crave His ownership and love to such a degree that it encompasses her.  Master came and collected His slave/property from South Carolina at Christmas/2003 and moved her to His home in Nevada. T/they have grown much T/together... two steps forward, one step back, three steps forward... she has been real time as long as she was long distance with Him now and T/they continue to move forward. Master's friends, who have also become her friends don't know the lifestyle T/they lead. Most of them think they are a bit kinky lol, but nothing more than that. In reality, Master is indeed her Lord/Master/Owner and that is truly a powerful combination.  she has been fascinated through this whole ongoing journey with how the mind works and can change so completely in a relatively short time as her's has with her Master's training and guidance as He has unearthed her, then molded her as He wills. she responds so well to hypnotism that her Master spent hours with a Hypnotherapist's (A friend Who is also a Psychologist and Master) help in learning to use it in His training of her. she loves it so much and listens to His tapes often as they make her feel so very wonderful & owned and free to be all she should in Him. she is working hard on improving her mind, body and demeanor that she may be His perfect slave and please Him well. her focus, her fulfillment, her life is all intertwined in Him... her Lord/Master/Owner: Master Charles. she is grateful, thankful and honored to be His.  Thanks for listening to a bit of her journey so far... If interested in more details: Please look for her essays, writings and sample journal pages (all soon coming). Please find some links below to definitions and sites that give more info about D/s and M/s. Look forward to hearing Y/your comments. ~diamond   
</post>


</Blog>