<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Because all the trees are blocking the view. I don't think it can be said any simpler.  I am sure I am not the first to note this major flaw in the spirititual practices of all of the organized religions ... Buhdism included. The prophets who have been touched by the light of God must have been be overwhelmed? We are tiny brained, frail organisms with a short lifespan and an inability to get beyond the concept of self. The rules are the trees and the forest is our salvation. Mankind must see the forest before we can see the trees. Isn't that simple?  If God is present in each of us, then being kind, merciful & compassionate to our fellow man must follow God's plan. I have been reading Jewish, Islam, Christian &amp; Budhist ( the Buddha was a prophet) writings and this theme appears blatently obvious in all of them.  Even the most obtuse human being can comprehend the GOLDEN RULE. The long journey begins with taking this first step. Every day, treating others as you would have them treat you, keeps you on the Golden Path.  As being less obtuse than most, our task is to open the eyes of those who would follow the OTHER ONE. Anger makes the obtuse squeeze their eyes shut & their journey will be a small never ending circle. We must temper our words as directed by the Golden Rule. We can stray as easily as they. Pride commeth before the fall &amp; the leaves of the trees of the forest disappear in the fall. May you all see forests of evergreens!  

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am trying to get closer to God thru my thoughts and eventualy my actions. One book I am reading "WORDS that hurt, WORDS that heal" by Rabbi Joseph Telushkin, mentions the story of Oliver Sipple. At the time it occurred, 1975, I was extremely closeted and would not have read about or discussed it for fear of exposure myself. My sexuality caused great fear & anger in my youth &amp; I wasn't even having sex. Oliver Sipple saved the life of Gerald Ford in 1975 when he prevented a shooter from killing the president. All eyes in the nation focused on the ex-marine & closeted (to his family) homosexual. Oliver Sipple was outed by the press &amp; consequently ostracized by his mother and father. For him his life was over and he died as a lonely drunk in his appartment 6 years later. Heroic action aside, But for the Grace of God, that could have been me. Coming out was the first step in my long journey. My small steps are quickening since, but I still have a long way to go.  In the name of God, the Merciful and Compassionate. May all Muslims, Jews & Christians look into their hearts with open eyes so that they may see the true joy of embracing the gifts of mercy & compassion.  These gifts from God can never be taken away; but once discarded, they are gone for an eternity. Thank you God for opening my eyes to your presence within and let my actions help bring Your Merciful & Compassionate Light to those who do not know their eyes are closed to the gifts You have given. Amen.    

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It is such a joy to see my father be kind to Lucy (my dog). I have dealt with anger all my life ... "The sins of the father ..."  OK, "MONK" is on & I work this weekend, GOTTA go.    

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Over the years I have spent much time thinking about God, Jesus, Spirituality & how to make sense of it all. When much younger, I enjoyed math & physics classes because if I worked on a problem long enough and understood the basics, I could eventually arrive at the answer. In fact, I thought the human experience was like this up to around the age of 25. There just had to be an answer.  I have finally come to the realization that,  No matter how long & hard I think about GJ&amp;S I will always end up at the same point: I will never KNOW the answer AND just thinking without acting is a waste of time. Since I will never KNOW the answer , I can at least begin recording my thoughts. This blog is an opportunity for me to see how I continue to evolve as I age.  My exciting thought for the last few days has been concerning the Gospels of Thomas.  I have considered myself to be a TRUE Christian most of my life ... my belief system being TRUE ... not always my words & thoughts. I have, and will again (unfortunately) say hurtful things to others in anger. I still am angered when I see and hear "Christians" quoting from the bible to condemn or judge others. Being Gay , I find it angering to hear about our "Christian" legislators making laws to drive same sex couples apart. I actually have homocidal thoughts every time I hear about the ongoing death and suffering we are causing in Afganastan, Iraq & around the world for the interests of a minority of people. I am not the person I want to be yet but I have hope.  The Gospels of Thomas have an appeal. I understand little of this philosophy now but am researching it and hope to meet some others who have similar thoughts.  Gotta cut this short. Mom & Dad are coming down for dinner and the house is a mess.  Jack  

						
</post>


</Blog>