<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man I love Allie so freakin much.  She is soooooooooooo awesome.  YAY!!!!  man holmes, my sister rocks!  just been listenin to some tunes with her on the computer.  she is my world 
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what the hell is wrong with me???!!?? i am such an idiot i can't do anything right 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Get busy livin, or get busy dieing.    That's damn right"             -Shawshank Redemption 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here are some things going on in my life:     Sent off my Naval Academy application today.  Really really nervous about that, hopefully if they think i am a strong enough candidate i will hear something from them the beginning of September.  I have got my fingers crossed!!     Girls have gotten me drinking again,  damn it.     Polo practice is going great.  We are really getting the hang of it, we all know our goal and are set on the right track to do that.  Wish us luck!!             (for those of you who do not know, that is winning state)    Already bogged down with work.  Not really, i am just a retard.  But i do have a project due Friday, in Tech Theatre of all places.  What is this lady thinking, it is supposed to be easy. 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will give her a ya and a yah! and a highhhhhYA!!  and then i'll kick her sir    let me tell you whata wow!  
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      but i am still the asian sex bomb!      -steph 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Danny Devito:  Hey hun, what kind of pants should i wear to go huntin?  Marissa Tomei:  Picture this: Your walkin along, see you a deer next to a pond. It puts its cute deer lips on the cool clear water and takes a drink.   THEN BAM, HALF ITS BRAINS ARE BLOWN OUT!!!!  Now let me ask ya, do you think it would give a fuck on what kind of pants the mother fucker who shot you was wearin??!!!!! 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Prom is so far away but it seems to be the topic of the days.  If none of yall know it will be in the Sky Room of Incarnate Word.  It is pretty nice but really cheap.  I have an idea of who i want to take, and none of yall know her which is one reason.  But things may change. so that ends that topic. no mas. 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, i am hopefully getting my classes changed finally tomorrow and this will be final.  Brit was upset because i was getting out of 2 of the only classes we had together, but it turns out she might do the same thing i am doing.  I am dropping humanities unfortuantely, that would have been a really cool class.  Sorry!!!  well, it is good to finally get back in the groove of polo.  I really missed it, but today it was so awesome.  Coach Plummer is a good coach, he is a cool guy.  Anyways, what teacher gives homework on the first day AND second day of school.  i am actually studying.  OMG!!! AAAHHHHHHHHHHHH 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate the school and the people that it teaches. Except for a select few and i think yall know who you are.  I find it funny how people who need 8th period swimming ALWAYS get 1st period, and people who want 1st period ALWAYS get 8th period.  Why are they so stupid.  You would think they would get it after 4 times of doing this.  But no.  School is school. Coach Plummer is a cool guy.  I am looking forward to what he has planned for us tomorrow at our first polo practice.  I really hope that Orb pisses him off and fires him.  That would be awesome. 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blah Blah Blah Blah that is how i feel Blah Blah Blah Blah B'mo got hit in the balls with a basketbeel. 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to the pool today for emily's and stephs going away party.  Even though steph wasn't even there.  Got in the pool, played keep away, and by the way, girls really suck at that.  2 guys can beat about 10 girls in a not even 25 yard pool.  Pathetic. Allie was there.  (there you go allie, you are in it). Then i went to julio's house for his party thing too.  IT was a lot mellower because everyone was tired out from jumpin on the moon bounce.  That was awesome.  Saw a lot of peeps that I haven't seen in a while.  And it made me not want school to come around even more.   
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i kinda forgot the username and password for my other blog, so I made a new one.  Some people say i won't write in it.  I will show them, maybe. 
    
</post>


</Blog>