<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry for the delay.  If you are just joining us, please read the other posts before you read this one. it will make a lot more since.  In March of 2003 I sort of ran away for awhile. I spent a lot of time out in Denver with my best friend Jerry.  Jerry and I am been buddies for years now. If it was not for my Mom and Jerry I would have killed myself years ago.  Jerry use to be 550lbs but, a few years back he had weight lose surgery. he is about 275lbs now. I am so very proud of him, what he did took a lot of guts (pun attended)  Jerry is more family to me than a buddy, he was one of my friends that was with me when Mom died. He took off time from work to come out to Des moines. just becuase my Mom asked for him. Mom cared a great deal for him.  I also spent a lot of time in Provo, Utah during 2003 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, so you will know where I am today, I need to go back a few years.  2001 I started a very very very small leather shop, which i ran out of my basement. I made a lot of things from very mild to more adult items. I went out to a lot of events and a few renaissances fairs as a vendor and loved it. It was a ton of work, making all of the items, loading, unloading, setting up and so on. Bit, i did really enjoy it. The money was ok, and was getting better with every event. It was starting to pay for its self and a little extra money left over to grow.  In the fall of 2002, i went to two very well known Renaissance Fairs. one in MN and one in KC. I was working on getting into a big Renaissance fair as a vendor. In late Sept of 2002, I got a call from my sister that my Mom was ill, I was needed back in Iowa. (that is where I am from)  In less than a week, I had moved a few things back to Moms house, the house I grew up in. I wanted to be there, I wanted to help Mom, and the family, and Moms little dog Ethen.  I had to put all of my plans on hold to help Mom and the family. Mom was 78 and in failing health. Before you jump all over me for putting my life on hold for helping to take care of my Mom, for me it was an honor. If you do not have a Mom or a family that you are not willing to do what it takes to help, maybe you are the ones that need help. (sorry, to be blunt)  The next few months was hard for my family, My sister, my Brother and myself helped to take care of Mom. It was a bad time, but something good came out of it, my Sister, Brother and I got veryu close to each other. I really got to know them better then i ever had before. I should tell ya that My Sister is 60?. my brother is 55 and i am 41 as of last saturday. So, there is a little age gap.  During that time. I felt like we was a family. We always got a long, my brother and sister and I but was never really close, until this time. I tryed to put that feeling into words, and i would try to say cute little things to my brother and sister to let them know how i was feeling but, it never came out right. I sounded more stupid then i did greatful.  In Jan of 2003 Mom passed away at the age of 79. I was at her side, and two fo my friends. My brother and sister could not make it to her bedside in time, but was there shortly after. The next week was rough, as you might think. But, My sister and brother was there helping with the plans for the funneral. It was a nice service, and a nice graveisde service.  A week after Moms funneral I was back here in Aurora, IL. My sister and her family had moved into Moms House.  Hate to sound like a whimp, but I need to close here for now. Talk at ya soon 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi All,  I am new here and wanted to say hello.  The reason I am here is, the last few weeks I have been told by more than one person that I am becoming a hermit, and I do not let people to get close, blah, blah, blah. A buddy said, I should do a online Journal so, Here I is.  Just so you know, I do not spell very well, my wording may get very odd at times, but I will try to make things as clear as I can. Also, I may get very very personal. I mean, thats the point right?   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>