<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have finally decided to put something worth reading on my website.  This is going to be a compilation of techniques which work well together on Soul Calibur II.  Feel free to post if you feel I've left anything out, especially those of you with the XBox or GameCube version, since I have the PlayStation2 version.  Anyway, the first person I'm going to do is Ivy.  Here goes.  1=down away    2=down    3=down toward    4=away    6=toward    7=up away    8=up    9=up toward    +=hit these two buttons at the same time    A=horizontal attack    B=vertical attack    K=kick    G=guard    : =ends in following stance    no space=enter commands right after one another    lower case then uppercase=slide first button to second button    H=recommended for versus humans only    x=hold last command          Horizontal Advance - A+B (Spiral Serenade), A (Serpent Slash: Spiral Tribute), A (Raging Flames: Serpent's Embrace), AA (Violent Spirits)         Quick Chaos - 214 or B+K (Pleasure Change: Whip State), A+B (Venom Strike: Serpent's Embrace), 6B+K (Stinging Souls, Long Range, if closest to enemy.  Otherwise, use 4B+K for Close Range)         Farce (H) - 1 or 2 or 3+B+KGB+K (Fear's Void, Any Range (Cancel): Crouch to Asylum)         Aerial Entrapment - 8A+BA (God Whisper: Enemy in air), B6B (Squire's Cage)         Aerial Punishment - 8A+BA (God Whisper: Enemy in air), 214Bx (Venom Lash: Serpent's Embrace), A+B (Released Souls)         Total Entrapment - 6B+Kx (Embrace of Lust), G+B (Dominion Throw, Heartless Guide, Sunset Cradle, or Sweet Dominance), 3B+Kx (Gnome Huntress)  This is a personal favorite.  The only thing I have left is a tip for fighting Ivy.  Beware her dirty tricks: she is one of the few characters who can keep you on the ground almost as long as she wants.  At every chance, get within her sword's range and roll sideways along the ground.  Raphael is a personal favorite for fighting her, because of his dodges.  Yoshimitsu is your worst choice, as he does not move sideways well except at a cost to his health.  Necrid, Nightmare, Astaroth, and Kilik are probably the actual best for fighting her, since they come the closest to matching her long range.  Okay, that's all I have for now.  Stay tuned as I master other characters for more tips!
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, anyone who reads this!  I was just wandering around Blogspot and found out something very cool - Blogspot is not exclusively English.  I saw Blog with some Arabic dialect, one with Chinese symbols, and one with Japanese symbols.  Just think of the possibilities this opens up!  We could make a UN blog!  We could solve world relations with the click of a mouse and the push of a button!  All we need is some high-quality translation HTML, about forty expert linguists for moderators, and knowledge of several different languages for e-mail contacts, and we'd be set.  How's THAT for a vision?
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a post regarding the chance, although very small of Sony buying out Nintendo instead of Microsoft.  This stuff could probably work either way, but I own a PlayStation, and can therefore make more points about it than I can about XBox.  The point of this post is to try to give Nintendo characters a new chance at life.  I'm sure that the only reason they all seem gay and immature in the Nintendo games is that they are in, well, gay, immature Nintendo games.  The characters themselves are worthy of reconciliation, though.  If put in an XBox of PS2 game, they COULD be pretty cool.  So, here is my analysis of every important Nintendo character I can think of.  Mario-Occupation: Plumber           Ethinicity: Italian           Video Games: Too many to count.  The only ones that matter are Super Mario World and the original Mario Kart Racing.           Appearance: Short, slightly fat guy wearing a red hat and suspender overalls.           Pros: Can shoot fire balls, ride a dinosaur, become invincible, and jump many times his height.           Cons: His own company went too far, much like with Pokémon, effectively drowning him.           Chances of Reconciliation:  Actually, I don't think there's much hope for this guy.  The only thing i can think of would be to completely re-do his entire image.  Yoshi, who is also worthy of note, would have to be entirely refurbished to give him more of a standing among the veterans, such as the dragons in Drakengard and Reign of Fire.  The fire balls would have to be turned into some sort of FLAMING INFERNO (sorry, got a little carried away) and the invincibility would have to do something neat, for instance, disintegrating enemies on the spot.  If none of this works, he could make guest appearances as a flunky in some other game.  Maybe.  Wario-Wario is hopeless.  He is a copy of Mario, and should die.  Samus-Occupation: Bounty hunter/police force or something like that.            Ethnicity: Probably Japanese at first.            Video Games: Once again, too many.  I think there were four, not counting the GameBoy versions.            Appearance: Woman dressed in only a bikini, protected by a huge metal suit of electronic armor.            Pros: Can create bombs at will (at least on Super Smash Brothers), fire a giant laser beam, and jump fairly high.            Cons: I think the only con was that her first appearance was on a Nintendo platform.            Chances of Reconciliation:  I think all Samus needs is a good, well-planned PS2, but preferably XBox FPS.  Or, she could make some sort of guest appearance as an optional character on someone else's game.  Link-Occupation: Rescuer of Zelda.         Ethnicity: Human or maybe elven.  I'm not sure.         Video Games: Occarina of Time, Link's Awakening, Four Swords, and some other one.         Appearance: Elven, short, and dressed like Robin Hood.         Pros: Can carry something like twelve weapons at the same time, is skilled with all of them, and, with the ring of power, can pick up and throw boulders.  In some games he can throw some sort of fire powder, too.         Cons: Can't seem to see when it's over with the princess.  I mean, come on, she keeps getting herself trapped in closed rooms by other people, and all he does is just go save her again and again.  Get a clue, Link.         Chances of Reconciliation:  Very few, if any.  I think Sony would have to make this game - Microsoft does better with shooters and action RPGs.  It would have to be some game where he turns dark and goes and kills the Princess, then does something along the lines of God of War.  Yep, that's right - I am become Link, destroyer of worlds.  Okay, that's all I have for right now.  If you have any other ideas, feel free to post them.
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, I was in the car on the way to church this morning when I realized that the grammar on several other websites is absolutely horrendous.  Therefore, I have compiled a list of grammar rules that should be used, even when posting on a site like this one.  1.  Corekt spelling is esinchal. 2.  capItolS shouLd alWaYs bE used WISELY. 3.  There are no sentences that you should drop the preposition of. 4.  Keep entirely unnecessary words off of my site! 5.  People should always use the correct words in they're posts. 6.  Remember to use apostraphe's correctly.  Its good practice! 7.  Conjuctions should always be used correctly but properly. 8.  Never use no double-negatives. 9.  While subordinate clauses should not be used as sentences. 10.  Commas, are not always, necessary.
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, everybody who has enough free time to look at this.  This is my first post.  I hope it does not show up anywhere other than the posting spot.  That would be bad.  Anyway, this is my Blog, and I am SiberDrac.  That is, the electronic impersonation of me.  The reason I have not posted my name is that if I did, you might find me, which would lead to… bad happenings.  So there.  I'm just as paranoid as the people hunting me behind my back…  Fell free to post on my Blog.  Because it's mine.  Have fun.
    
</post>


</Blog>