<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      About a week ago, we experienced a wonderful cold front that suddenly turned shitfest, texas into November... and it was great. Everything was affected. Immediately, I had come to terms with a "falling out" (that was really much more like an explosion really) that happened between my best friend and I almost two years ago.  Explaining it in detail would be a really pussy thing to do... come on, I'm not that bad. (I am soooo gonna complain on my blog about this! OMG!!!!11111nociurjhei) But basically, we were inseparable for four years, and then one night she stayed at my then-boyfriend's house (yeah, don't even ask about that.) and went into great detail about all the things she hates about me. This came as a great shock, and I stopped calling her. It just hurt too much. I figured I was somehow making her happy by leaving her life entirely. I know, that wasn't like me, but I didn't know what else to do... it was like the entire foundation of my personality or identity or whatever was ripped out from under me. So I retreated into myself and concentrated on things that have no room to reflect on anything. Now, it did have a few advantages; I'm sure that I'm a much stronger person for surviving it... and I'm now (laughably) a member of National Honor Society, Spanish National Honor Society... shit, what else... Anyway, I didn't have to worry too much last year when I didn't do a fucking thing in school.  And more importantly, this whole "fiasco" allowed me to become good friends with Diller, and I don't know what I would've done if he hadn't let me unburden all my troubles on him.  Aww, teary now.  But to the point: as the air chilled and my attitude lifted, I began to look on things in a different light. Maybe my then-boyfriend was trying to take advantage of me, maybe there was some misunderstanding, maybe I simply didn't care anymore, and maybe I subconsciously missed all the fun times with her.  To make matters even more pressing, she's graduating this semester, which doesn't leave much time for me to sit and debate.  Hold on.  Jesus.  I'm too pissed off for this right now.  I'll explain later.  Jesus. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      School's here. Waaah.  Currently working on government and economics like the busy little bee that I am (so what if I'm half-heartedly watching VH1 and listening to Weezer and eating pot roast and playing with my new Tamagotchi and so on.) that's right. Busy little goddam bee.  Speaking of Tamagotchi's, I just got the new generation of "Tamagotchi Connection" toys... I know what you're thinking- what a nerd, why would anyone want such a faggoty little responsibility? To which I reply... meh. I don't care. I am a nerd. And they're fun. So there.  In addition to a bigger screen and a price of only $14, they now come with the ability to make friends and even mate (finally a love child with Dylan!) to create new generations of your pet. You can have up to 50 friends, so I'm hoping everyone will get one, and we can get the lovin' on... 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I realize that last post sounded kinda depressing, but fear not, one thing keeps me reeling from pissed to elated. And that thing is Yash.  That's right, that boy that somehow has managed to make me crap my pants time and again for about two or three years. That boy that I never had the courage to talk to. That boy that now wants to get to know me. That boy that is "interested" in me.  Jesus.  I guess I'll give a little background to this Yash character, and perhaps show some insight into why exactly I find him so goddamn intriguing (lest I sound like a shallow teenage girl). You see, along with looking like a Jewish Benjamin Mackenzie (from The O.C. for all you intellectual types that are too good to waste your time with T.V., let alone some teeny-bopper drama), this boy is also a native Spaniard- fluent in Spanish, of course- a scholar, a comedian, and a romantic. This may seem like a lot to know about a person without actually talking to them, but I'm a pretty perceptive person... believe me, one of the reasons why I become attracted to someone is because they have such personality, it just shows I think.  Anyway, a friend of mine works at Chili's, and what do you know, Yash just got the job. So after a lot of embarrassment and flushed cheeks, we're waited on by him. Ah, him. Things go pretty well and we make several jokes about the crazy "Foxy Lady Society"- don't ask. Unbeknownst to me, that friend of mine gets his opinion of the experience, and more importantly, me. Thanks, Diller. Anyway, turns out he's actually interested and would like to get to know me better. As I said before, Jesus. I still can't believe it. Maybe it sounds like I'm being overdramatic, cheesy, a little too enthused... well fuck you. I kid I kid. It just amounts to the same issue I've been having with myself lately... accepting that I don't need to think of myself as ugly just to be modest. I swear to god, my worst fear is that I'll believe I have worth. Maybe I've read too much Salinger and fear the unthinkable "phony" status; or worse yet, becoming a Big Haze (for you Nabokov fans out there) and being an translucent prick. I mean, it seems so easy to tell when someone believes they're hot stuff. But that's what this blog is for: learning to accept that I'm not the same loud Italian girl with curly eyebrows that I was a few years ago. Yash is interested in me.         
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    That's my dad twenty years ago drunkenly signing off the coast of Japan.  In a submarine.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's see...  Just recently, I had a "thing" with a friend I've had nearly all my life which actually turned out to be quite unexpected, nice, scandalous (say what you will, I'm comfortable with myself.)  and also very dumb.  But as we said then, "Because we're dumb!".  Anyway, after an ordeal with past boyfriends/ girlfriends, we finally made it possible to actually pursue a relationship.  Now, I'm not saying that I was entirely ready for this, so I know I'm partly to blame for what ensued; after being in a relationship for over two years, I was hesitant to return to the whole responsibility of having a "boyfriend".  Maybe I just didn't like him as much as I thought I did.   By the way, I'm trying to be as nonspecific as possible- I hate the type of people that bitch and name names on something as cowardly as a blog, you know what I mean- but I hope it's not impossible to understand... oh well, I guess my friends will understand, and that's all that really matters.  But returning to the aforementioned issue, the friend now has a girlfriend.   After a few days after a date-type thing.  What the hell.  I guess what gets me is that he never told me, and he really led me to believe that "we" could work out, and the "Oh, I like you sooo much" crap.   Maybe I'm being too cynical; I should be glad, right?  I mean, I wasn't ready for a boyfriend, and now I don't have to worry about it.  Great, eh?  ...nope.  I just feel dumb, but I suppose it's a fitting ending for something that began with the words "Because we're dumb!". 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey there, it's  regis .   So here's the deal:  there's a lot of caca in the whole "life" thing right now, and i figure i might as well get it off my chest; sorry i had to subject you to it.       geez... where to begin...   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>