<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This whole "fallen from grace" scenario has been bothering me lately. I can't help it. I've been thinking about it all this weekend and it just pisses me off. The fact that I worked so hard to get to where I was and just like that, it's all over, isn't fair. I know life isn't fair in general but this is absolute horseshit. That's the power of somebody's mouth and a bunch of mindless idiots that follow what they're hearing. Alex and Rich both brought up the same point that these people are all a bunch of assholes who equally all have a low brain capacity and I know that what they're saying is true. It doesn't make it any easier to deal with the fact that I got fucked in the end though. That's my problem that's been tough to get over. They'd probably claim that I'm all mad and throwing a little hissy fit since "people don't worship me anymore" or something along those lines but that's not it. I'm mainly mad over the fact that our high school group of friends was broken up and ruined for selfish reasons. It might not seem like a big deal now but down the road, it will. We're getting too old now to fix fucked up friendships and the more time that passes, there's less of a chance that anything will ever be fixed. Maybe that's the way they want it. I guess we'll see how it plays it. I'm focusing on moving on but when I have some down time, that's when I start to think about it. I shouldn't think about it at all but I do.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was totally exhausted last night after I got home from work. I took 2 showers just to make sure all of the dirt and grit was off of me. I was working in one of the rooms where the wood was charred black from the fire so I had that shit to contend with along with all of the other usual mess. I got paid though which was nice. I got more than I was supposed to get so that felt really good. I couldn't even make it past 10:00 last night. I was way too tired and sore from this past week. I probably could have made it if I tried and drank some more beers for motivation but I knew it'd be best just to hit the sack. My social activities/outings have virtually became non-existent. It's hard to believe that for a year and a half to almost 2 years, I was never home, always out, always meeting new people etc. and now I don't really leave the house unless I absolutely have to. Things have just went in this direction so that's that. Some of it is my own doing too because I try to avoid spending money these days since my income is sporadic. There aren't many jobs left that are "secure" but when you work construction that's one of the least secure jobs there is. I'm actually off next week since a few of the main bosses will be on vacation. I might get a call some time during the week to come in for a day or 2 and I might not. I can use the week off to rest and get some things done but that money would have been nice. My birthday is Tuesday but we'll try to forget about that for now. I was thinking about going out tonight down in Jersey but my brother is working today and tomorrow. He was the one who was supposed to ride with me and navigate. I guess I'm not going out now. It'd be nice to meet some women since that hasn't happened in months. Maybe I'll meet someone when I start classes again in early September. I hope so at least. Either that or I need to make that trip down to the mall to see this chick. I was going to do that on Thursday but I was too dead from working all day. I should do it this week and bring Alex with me. Hahaha, I'm figuring his stupid shit might actually help my cause. I'm not exactly sure why I think that but maybe I'll try it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This construction shit tires me out so much but I can see a noticeable difference in the size of my arms so there you go. Same thing happened when I worked at bear mountain back in 1998 and 1999. They're not huge or anything but you can see a nice tight form with the veins popping out on the inside elbow/forearm area. Tomorrow is friday which is nice. Me and Kevin were supposed to hit a Yankees game and buy tickets off the street but with all of this overtime he's been working it's probably not gonna happen. This nigga is gonna be getting paid which is good for him. It's kind of funny because the whole thing about "a nigga getting paid" came up at my last job and now at my new job. It's just a funny phrase in general. How can you not laugh at that shit? Hahaha. Not much else going on. Just basically working, busting my ass everyday, coming home, tallking on the internet to mostly Tara, Heather, and Rich and then hitting the sheets. There ain't shit else to do anyway. I renewed my driver's license yesterday since I last did it before turning 21 and I'll soon be 26. I used to freak out about getting older but these days I don't give a fuck. Whatever. Looking in the mirror 17 times a day hoping not to see any wrinkles, making sure I've got no zits, fixing my hair just right etc. I usually would pass for 21 or 22 when random people would guess my age and that would seem like some kind of accomplishment but I think I'm finally over that shit. Fuck it, I'm 26 and that's that. Well I'm 25 for another 4.5 days but will be 26 soon. Who gives a fuck, I've got a bunch of other shit to worry about. The last thing I need is to dwell on something I can't do anything about.   LOL, wow! The Twins just got ahead of the Yankees 10-9 since I last checked and when I looked up, Sheffield hit a solo HR to tie it 10-10. ARod just got a single. I'm IMing Rich and he's bitching about it. I'm gonna end this now. Hopefully I'll post again tomorrow. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It must be tough to have an oversized ego and virtually nothing to back any of it up. It's as if half of the country was holding a wad of $100 bills in their hands yet the Federal Reserve Bank had $10 worth of gold in the vault. I think that's why I get so aggravated when he's busy indirectly insulting us and taking potshots at me. I can't stand someone whose all hype. Worse than that, I can't stand someone is all of THEIR OWN hype. It's bad enough if other people are putting  a useless sack of shit on a pedestal but when it's they themselves doing it that's when I get pissed off. Nobody else really has any respect towards him so they're like "fuck him, whatever he says means nothing since he's nothing." For some reason I still get mad just like he wants me to do. It's because I know that's a terrible performer, a mediocre guitar player, a lack luster songwriter, bad producer and deplorable singer. He shouldn't even have slashes in his title. It's like pick one since you're not very good at any of these things. He'll never get anything of his own off the ground but even if he does, it's going to be fun to laugh at that shit. I might even have to waste $5 at the door to see it. Hahahahaha
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today is my grandfather's 85th birthday. That's pretty wild when you think about it. This is my father's father. My mother's father was 88 when he died so these guys both hit some pretty high numbers. It's amazing too since they're both from the hardworking manual labor era of the 20th century. Asbestos, sawdust, plaster smoke etc., drinking Hamm's and Schmidt's as soon as they got home. It's odd that I've reverted back to that. The main idea of me going to college, or anybody going to college for that matter, was to AVOID that type of work. It's kind of like when I was growing up and every single day I'd hear "get good grades in school so you don't have to end up like me fixing shit for a living and getting dirty everyday." So I'm working construction now. I get dirty as hell, lift heavy shit, do dangerous things like climbing on 2-story roofs etc. but the money is right. I've applied for a lot of jobs in the past 6 weeks that involve me using my degree and skills but have gotten nothing but rejection notices. I got one yesterday which was kind of disappointing and then got another today. I'm not broken up and devastated over it but at the same time, it gets to the point to where it seems impossible to get anywhere. Don't get me wrong, this construction shit is paying me more money than any bullshit office job that people "THINK" is prestigious and important but you always think of the long run. When this construction shit ends then where am I? But then again, when my old job ended where was I then? That was supposed to be a "real" job that was secure. LOL, that's pretty funny. My sole intention after getting the pinkslip was to "one-up" them. I think I've done that. I'm bringing home a lot more money than I was, have a 5 minute commute as opposed to a 45 minute one and get out early everyday. I'm just trying to seize the opportunity for some quick cash. I try to keep my mouth shut, do the work, secretly look for as much sitting around time as possible and then leave. That's it, plain and simple. My mission these days is money... bottom line. It's one of the main things on my mind and rightfully so. If I play my cards right I can really build up the bank account and have some leverage. If I didn't have my Jeep I'd have even more money than I do now but I'm not going to harp on that since I like driving a nice vehicle. My shit is a V6, arctic blue, and rides nice as hell so I'm not gonna think of the lost funds. Anyway, I've already spoken too much about jobs and money and that stuff. As far as the personal life goes, it's been fairly quiet over the past 3 months. The band no longer exists and most of the people I've seen, talked to, and hung out with are from my past. I talk to my friend Tara from college in NYC almost every night, I've seen Alex Blanc several times and am going hiking with him (rain or not) tomorrow, and was supposed to hang with my boy Dan from USC tonight in Jersey but we called it off due to the rain and thunderstorms from the hurricane. We figured driving home fucked up at 2AM during a torrential downpour wouldn't be a good idea. It'll have to wait til next week. Also, I've been hanging with my brother a lot lately since he's actually been home. It's a cool thing when you think these people were once in your life in 1999 and 2000 but are gone forever and then all of a sudden, something happens and you're good friends again. It's cool and I'm definitely happy with it. Some of the other USC heads who now live in NYC are going to meet up with Dan and I some time over the fall to hang. I haven't seen most of these guys since 2000 when I left so I'm looking forward to it. I think my life definitely hit the skids in more ways than 1 this summer but I was able to take the lemons and turn them into lemonade. I lost most of what I had and I'm sure there was a handful of people who were sitting around laughing about it but fuck 'em, I'm back and that's that. I got some other things working too. I'm proud of myself for getting back out there and trying to make things happen. I just need to think positive and look ahead. That last sentence is easier said than done but it's the key to being successful. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>