<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so frustrated! I agreed to go out with a guy I sort of liked... now he is possessive and stuff. ugg... I don't know why I did it I knew his sweetheart 24/7 thing was a lie. So why the hell did I do it????  grrr. He is fighting for my honner and stuff like that... I don't want him to! Half the fights he gets in the middle are little ones like -whats up with your name- kind of fights. That I probably started! belive it or not, I like to fight little fun fights. But I wish he'd just leave it alone! :*-(  cry 
      
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today is good I get over crushes fast. I haven't had a lot (only ones in the last month, I'm on my 3rd) but they only last like a week. hmmm. all great guys though that I still like (just not crush) Ok so now I'm on this guy, who is a complete sweetheart. and umm, really likes me back like alot. I think, unless he is a good lyer, which he very well maybe. but who cares 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Did you know I was bored??? I want someone to be online... I am so very very very bored... ARE YOU??? ok thats all for now bye 
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I feel like adding alot today... hmm... I'll just keep this open and keep writting to you throughout my surfing time. Yes you are in for trouble! hmm... I'm looking at my messages I wrote earlier today... I have no life  you know what I should do... I'm reading the comics for 9thElsewhere... and I should put up my graphics here... NAW they suck...maybe I should put my stories up here though.  although if I did that I might as well create a whole separate blog for them.   urlLink blackfire2468@hotmail.com    I am reading alot of anime... I don't know why??? can you explain me to me... pLEASE!  I keep exiting out of my window... why am I so silly???? hmm... I am confusing... Maybe not... but you know how TV shows allways have guys complaining about how confusing girls are... Well they're right WE are confusing... 
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        aha... The life of me... Living in a soap opera.  I have problems sleeping (like non of you have problems) and with school starting (even though I've been an insomniac since before I was born) My mom decided I needed help. So anyways, it started with no sleeping in the day. No problem, I only sleep in the day cuz I'm bored. But it didn't work (DU) so she got me pills. They work beautifully. Unfortunately, I now have no caffeine, no sitting on bed during the day, exercise tons, no, No no, No, no. I'm kind of tired of No. Anyway, today is actually kind of good. My parents have ignored me (so like I used to, I can do what I want), I got caffeine (no non-caffeinated soda at subway), and overall a very good day. HE HA.  Now I have a problem, that I know how to fix, but don't want to. Ok there is this guy that I have liked on and off since 5th grade. He is really a nice guy. Unfortunately, in 6th grade (I liked him at this time) he asked me if I liked him. I freaked out and said no. Now I am completely 100% crushing on him (I haven't even had crushes until recently, its always been that I like the guy a lot a lot). Anyways, I think he likes me back. Actually the only doubt of that is he has always been very friend and nice, but it seems different now. So I am almost positive he won't say anything (even if I hadn't screwed up I don't know if he would). So that's my problem, considering we're pretty good friends, I can have 3 choices. 1-Flirt more, and see if he is um.... Courageous enough. 2-Tell him... Scary. Or 3- be friends and leave it at that. HMMMMMMM  So far today has been old history nothing new, but great fun anyways.  
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Welcome to my site... I really haven't had anything put here yet... ok great fun... bye
</post>


</Blog>