<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I've decided to start an online journal for myself. I've tried to do this in the past and failed, but I'm going to give it another shot this time. I'm at a confusing point, not sure who I want to be, where I want to go, what I want to do. Maybe this will help me to get my thoughts out and straightened.       Right now I'm feeling very lost and unsure of myself.       I'm nearly twenty-five years old, and sometimes I feel like I have no idea who I am. I feel like I push to be someone who I imagine other people want me to be. I have a hard time separating who I want to be, and who I think others want me to be.       I made a few changes this year. I've started wearing makeup on a more regular basis, and I've been wanting to dress more feminine than I ever have before. Part of me thinks I'm doing this because I feel better about myself and I'm no longer afraid to embrace my femininity. But then another part of me thinks that I'm just doing it to get other people to respond to me more, and to like me. After all, what do people like better? A tom-boy in jeans with a pale complexion who doesn't stand out in a crowd? Or a nicely made-up girl in a skirt who looks like she takes care of herself?      I think for the first time I'm really feeling myself growing up and it's frightening in a way. So much of myself and what I identify myself as, is based in my childhood, and now that my childhood is years away, I'm not sure what I am anymore. Am I still a tomboy in jeans? I feel like that on the inside, but then I look in the mirror at myself, and I see a growing woman. I honestly feel like I don't know who I am anymore and I need to try and find myself.       When I was a kid, my identify, was based on what I cared about. I related to characters in my favorite books, to the music I listened to, I internalized everything and made it a part of me. But now that I'm older, I feel like I need to identify myself in different ways, and it's hard.       I hate my job. I hate my profession. I do graphic design, and it achieves nothing in the world. I feel like what I do has no positive effect, and more than anything, I think I want to be the type of person, who uses their life to have a positive effect on other people's lives. But then I'm afraid and unsure. I don't know what I can do to give my life this feeling of achievement. I don't know what I can do, and I'm afraid to open myself up to trying knew things because I'm afraid of failing or making a fool of myself. I've just got so many thoughts mixing around in my head like a whirlwind and I can't make any sense out of them, or out of myself.      Who the hell am I?  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>