<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I was at Starbucks with my friend tonight having some coffee, relaxing just bull sh*ting. We got on the topic of dating guys. It is no secret that dating is hard and kinda sucks. I mean I have met some real winners let me tell ya. My question is, are there any good, stable minded guys out there that aren't just looking for some good squirrel?
My friend has this theory....For example there is a guy (we'll call him Ted), somewhere down the line Ted was involved with someone and he got really hurt by her. Now she is happy with someone else, and Ted now is afraid of commitment. Now all of us single ladies out there are stuck with all these Ted's.....These Teds are not wanting anything serious cause they are afraid to put themselves out there, so we get their emotion whiplash. What do you think about that theory?
It is true though so many guys don't want anything serious these days...Not saying I want to run out and get married tomorrow....I don't need a ring for a while. All I am saying is that I don't wanna be a booty call, or a one night stand. I want a friend, someone to hangout with, talk to, go see a movie with and etc...etc. Why does that seem like it is so hard to ask for or to find for that matter? Must I spread my legs just to have a guy around?   Why is there no stability anymore....or am I just in La La Land and need to get with the program?  

     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        We all try and move on after being hurt, right? It is easier for some more than others. Is there any easy way to get over a heart break?? 
  
 -There is " The Rebound ", when one tries to get over a guy or girl by getting under a new one. I feel that is only a temporary fix. I mean come on, I know our ex's broke our hearts but do we really need to become a one night stand junkie to make ourselves feel better? Been there done that, let me tell ya I only felt worse afterwards. 
  
 -There is the " Overly Picky ", when you meet a guy or girl and if they have any traits of your ex you find yourself running in the opposite direction. What's that about? Not every guy or girl are heartless jerks. You have to give them some sort of chance. Just because they may dress, talk, or like the same things as your ex doesn't mean they are your ex. 
  
 -There is the " Pity Party ", when you find yourself looking for those depressing love songs that remind you of your ex. You break out the box where you threw all the pictures, cards, and the little keepsakes that he or she gave you. I have found myself to do that from time to time, but then I think why am I punishing myself over someone who obviously didn't care much about me.  
  
 -There is the " Alone-Phobia ", when you tend to find yourself looking for anyone to fill that empty void. All because your not used to or your afraid to be alone. COME ON ALL YOU LADIES!!!! We don't need a man to survive. For all you heart broken men the same goes for you. We were all breathing and doing fine before these ex's and we will still be breathing after them.  
  
 I could go on and on....Basically I feel that the best way to get over a heart break is to take some time to be alone. That's right, time ALONE. To find yourself, and figure out what you want for YOU. It gives your heart some time to heal, and lets you get your head together. Rushing into any new relationships could only make it worse, and might even lead to more heart break.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         They say that time heals all wounds....If that's the case why do I still feel like I can't breath, like I can't move on? It has been seven months since I had my heart broken, and yet it feels like just yesterday. I can still remember every detail of that day, from what he was wearing to what cologne he had on.
  
  Is there a reason why the people who get hurt like to torture themselves by reliving every moment? I ask myself "Why can't I just forget about him? Why can't I just pretend like it never happened?". One day I am fine and then next thing I know I am listening to sad, depressing songs and wishing I was with him, the man who broke my heart.
  
  Just recently my ex and I have been in contact. I thought that maybe if he and I remained friends it would help me get over him, that it would give me closier. Why do we do such stupid things to ourselves? I can't help but ask myself "What was I to him??? Just some piece???" Anyway, my reasoning behind my site is to let all the heart broken people know they are not alone. To give them a place to express their feelings, to vent without having someone tell them "I TOLD YOU SO!!" So please feel free to express and share your experiences.    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>