<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was a good day...i went to church, learned some good stuff...and i saw you there.  You were setting there, as beautiful as ever, and i was happy.  Later everyone went to the lake, i enjoyed that, espacially the service, were i sat in your shadow.  If you only cared for me the way i do for you...ohh, what a love that would be.  I've been waiting for a while, but that doesn't matter, my feelings for you haven't dissapated, i doubt they will.  Your the first person i think of when i wake up, and the first person i pray for, before i sleep....what a love this could be.  countless hours spent dreaming of you, but whats sad, is that your in love with another, and there is nothing i can do to stop it.  But all in all, today was a good day. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I saw her again to day, but nothing more than a passing glance.  What i wouldn't give, to hold that girl...i've written her several songs, she knows how i feel about her.  But sadly, for me, she is already in a relationship.  So i find myself once again lost in this dark spiralling chasm, gasping for breath, hoping yet again to catch a fading glimpse of her beauty.....she's so beautiful.  My story is nothing but a speck in all of history, but it is still my story, and i won't let it end unhappily, i won't stop loving her, if indeed i do love her....there are many definitions of love, mine is wanting to just be near her, nothing more than to see her, but ohh this lonelyness is dark, so very dark...hopefully she will find her way to me, maybe, if i'm lucky...she's so beautiful. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hi there, my name as you can see, is Brock.  I've been looking everywhere for a place for me to express myself, Thank you blogger.com.  I'm starting this school year as a junior, just turned sixteen, not looking for a girlfriend, because i've found one...she doesn't know it yet though...well, i guess i'll create a profile now...if you want to know more about me, head there.  ps, this is what part of the alphabet would look like if q and r were eliminated. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>