<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will probably not be the only time I rant about the food in Japan (hence the Vol. 1 of the title), but you'd understand if you were over here. If you like fish, and are willing to either prepare it on your own or accept it in whatever form it appears in a restaurant then you would probably be okay. However, I'm sure even the biggest culinary of underwater life would soon grow tired of it.  Quite honestly the best meals I have had in this country - with only an exception or two - have been prepared at home by Ashley; though she does set a high standard. It's not that the food here is horrible, but even the most mediocre of edible genres requires variety. You can have Ramen noodles, curry'd whatever ya please over rice, meat on rice, these funky looking omelot/pancake with fishy teriyaki sauce on them served by vendors absolutely everywhere for 100 yen, or there is sushi. Oh, and I'm sure there are a lot of sushi enthusiasts out there that think, "But I love sushi." You are forgetting one harsh reality about sushi: even though it is reasonably cheap over here I'd have to spend an assload on sushi to ever be full.  Which brings me to the next contrast of eating Canadian cuisine versus Japanese (yes I realize it's hard to specify anything as Canadian cuisine, and that I might as well call it American, but at home I eat my meals in Canada, prepared by Canadians from Canadian ingredients) . You know how when you eat a meal in North America, you sit back and unbuckle your belt, and maybe the button of your pants if it was like a big turkey dinner or something, and you have to sigh and don't want to get up, because you just ate so much you can hear the hungry Ethopian children crying? Well, that feeling seems about as far away as Canada itself right now. (Does that count as irony? maybe I should call Alanis and ask her?) Now, I feel like a fat, overfed balloon of a McKid sayin this, but I really miss that feeling. Sure I've probably lost five pounds already, but everytime Ash and I go somewhere enough money must be brought so that if we are out of the house for any multiple of two hours we have enough for that many meals. It gets rather tiresome planning trips out around your stomach. In fact as I sit here at the internet cafe, which I left for only an hour and a half ago, I am begininning to notice I am famished though I ate three hours ago!!!! Please stop the madness!!  I've already had McDicks more times in the last month (4) out of sheer desperation, than I have in the last year. It's gross in so many corporate American ways I was trying to escape by coming here, that I can't even count them. But . . . c'est la vie!  Oh yea, and ya know what they call a quarter pounder with cheese in Japan? A McGrand. You know why?  Because of the metric system.   Alright, before this descends into a forum about Japanese McDicks. . .   
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well . . . let's see.      I've been here with Ash for about a month now and we're having a pretty good time. Ash and I went to an 'onsen' the other day. That's Japanese for hot spring. It was up in the mountains north of Kobe, took us about an hour and a half to get to, but man . . . the most relaxing time of your life. Finally got to see some greenery as we were in a little town called Arima that is literally in the side of a mountain. The spas were really cool. The hottest water I've ever dipped my tow in, and very very soothing once you're in. I'd show you some pictures of the actual spa, but apart from not being able to take in a camera, I don't think you want a picture of a bunch of old, naked Japanese men. I'd say it was a very humbling experience, but I'm a white guy, they're all Japanese . . . well you know how myths are . . . they're generally just myths, but I can always pretend that's why they were staring at me and not just because I was the only naked white guy they'd ever seen.      Still working on how to add pictures to this frickin thing, apparently they already have to have been web-posted or some garbage. I dunno, well until next time . . .      (insert appropriate japanese phrase here)            
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone,      Alright, forgive me if this first message is brief, but I already tried this once and accidentally deleted the whole frickin' thing. (Thank god university taught me how to type.) Well after seeing various blogs posted by friends of mine on their long journeys, I thought this might be a fun alternative to e-mails, and might even give me a little extra freedom in the way I do things. And besides I always wanted a web-page owned, operated and about me (ok it's also about Ash and japan and the two of us in Japan, but you get the idea).  
</post>


</Blog>