<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Through the smoked glass of the front door I saw a man fall. I heard the muffled thumps as he fell to the ground. My old man and I rushed to the back gate and barged it open. When had I put down the gardening tools we had brought with us I went in to see my old man helping ‘J’ up and getting him to a chair.  I first met J about a year ago. He, being the father of my old man’s partner, is the equivalent of a grandfather in my interesting family. Since I first met him I have probably seen him a dozen or so times. We’ve had family meals together, he’s more than once been round to fix the family car (which he helped buy), and, on occasion, we’ve been round his to lend a hand. I believe he was with the RAF in WWII, and/or shortly after, until he became a mechanic. He’s old school and he looks after his family. Based on my limited experiences of him I judge him to be a decent man.  J has cancer. I don’t believe it to be terminal but the medication he is on is strength sapping. It induces drowsiness and a lack of hunger, which makes it difficult for him to move around and consequently his muscles weaken through inactivity.  I never really planned on living beyond my mid-forties. A biological grandfather died of a cardiac episode at that age and I, even in my junior years, have had the occasional spate of chest pains. The way I saw it I might not live too much longer then 45 based on my genetic inheritance. Fair enough: we’re all born to die at the end of the day and I figured all I would have to look forward to at that age would be my prime behind me and a pension funded descent in front of me.  I mentioned this in conversation to my old man in the garden the other day. He stopped, looked at the blue sky, and told me that people on their deathbeds would fight to just get outside and look at the sun on such a day. Fight just to enjoy the pleasantly warm air.  Today I saw a man struggle to answer his own door and to get up and down his own stairs. Struggle to do what little he could. I got put of bed after either sleeping or dosing for 11 hours. I have lazed about for pretty much all of the holidays, not spending any effort to do hardly anything. A man struggled to do little more than open his own door.  I reckon there’s an awful lot of nobility in that man’s struggle, no matter how minor an event it may have been for. It shamefully reminds me I am but a child and that no matter how old or weak someone can become, if they struggle to do whatever they can then they are still a man. I hope to be able to struggle for so little if I ever am in that position as opposed to allowing lascitude to overcome me.  Excuse the gender discrimination.   
    
</post>


</Blog>