<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The human being - Homo Sapiens. That is our species. We are all part of it, and we all share similar attributes. Yet every human being is unique, every single one is hugely different from the next. I'm not just talking about out phenotypes(what we can see, our physical attributes), or our genotypes(what's in our genetic code ie XY or XX for male or female). I mean that no matter how much we all think the same, wear the same clothes, eat the same food or breathe the same air, we can never be exactly like another human being. Twins may look the same, but usually have quite contrasting personalities (Anyone ever read any Sweet Valley Twins books? Or am I the only loser in the world...guess so...) Human beings are special, even the simplest of thought processes involves complex reactions in our brain that can produce all sorts of effects. And we do it so easily, without even thinking, we think! And try thinking about not thinking, its impossible! No matter how much you tell yourself to clear your mind, you end up thinking about not thinking, it's a scary thing... Humans have an incredible capacity to think, to invent, to create, to speculate, and its all there at our disposal. The World really is our oyster. Ever looked inside a computer? We created that, a human being worked such complexity out, its genius, its amazing, and it makes me feel proud to be alive. Sometimes I feel like I should be doing more with this immense capacity to learn. Studying does tend to be tedious, but its something that enhances our capacity to use our mind, and it's been essential to all the inventions we have now. Imagine if the inventor of the Toilet, Thomas Crapper (that's where the word crap comes from, I promise!), had decided he just couldn't be bothered to study (what he studied, I don't know, but I doubt it was called making toilets for dummies), and then didn't invent the toilet, the world wouldn't be what it is today! Sure, someone else might have invented it, but you never know. It feels like such a waste, that humans only use a third of their brains capacity, and even then we don't use that space much at all. Think of things we could do if we used our whole brain. Who knows, even telepathy might be possible. Think about how complex the gene code is, and how hard it was to decode, it is absurd to think that the human mind is capable of understanding something we cannot even see with the naked eye. We still don't understand so much, and there are so many discoveries still to be made. Yet it all hangs in the balance. So many things could happen that could lead to the end of the human race, that it is frightening to even think about. Ever taken the tube in London, and thought that at any time terrorists could attempt a bomb attack? It's scary, and sad, because for innocent people, who have nothing to do with angering these terrorists, death is unfair. What about a possible nuclear war? There are world leaders out there who with a simple command could initiate the launch of a nuclear missile, causing a war that would end up destroying the world. And those are just the human possibilities. Think about all the things that could happen in space that might unbalance the earth's orbit, and send it spinning to an untimely end? That would be the end of us. And it is possible, because as you read this, out galaxy is spinning around in an unpredictable path around the universe. One day it may be sucked into a black hole, or crash into another galaxy, or get caught up in a supernova, and we will have no say in what happens! That's why, you've got to be amazed at how lucky we are to be alive, at what a gift it is, to think how complex the human body is, and how we might not even have evolved if that fishy thing that climbed out of the water billions of years ago had decided it liked the water and couldn't be bothered to venture on to land. Okay, Okay, so there so it's a big if, but that's the beauty of it, anything COULD have happened, and what happened? WE did! For me, life is a beautiful thing, and I'm going to cherish and nurture mine. As for the capacity to learn and enhance my mind, well, its great, but I'm on holiday at the moment, so studying can wait...  PS - To those who dont agree that human's are indeed special, i say that our innate ability to find ways to survive and further dominate all the other species on this earth muct clearly desmonstrate our superiority. Just by comparing our gene codes with those of other species it is evident that there is something about us that makes us superior. Humans manged to build vastly complicated societies before they could talk, think of neanderthals. They could communicate, but not exactly talk in the way we can, and who says bees cant communicate. I agree that all living speices are something amazing, but to be human is to be top of the chain. Simply being alive, with all the mechanisms we have working all the time is a magnificent feat. The examples of a rabbit digging a hole and bees creating a community are comparable, but once compared seem dull and simplistic in contrast. Think of what we have achieved in order to be superior to nimals. We envied birds power of flight, we invented the aeroplane, the parchute, the hanglider and even the space rocket! We envied how fish could swim deep underwater, so we built the sumbmarine and learnt to scuba dive. And we are still learning, tahts what makes us so amazing, humans can adapt quickly, and learn and improve themselves in a way that animals can only do with much difficulty and on a much smaller scale. Humans rule the world and being one makes me feel special. Be proud to be alive. Be proud to be human. 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Thats me, i hope the picture somehow links the reader to my mind in order to see things more clearly...&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>


</Blog>