<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Women can be so cruel.  She was already at the bar when Alain opened the heavy door to the dingy saloon that over the last few months had become his regular choice for post workday drinking and relaxation.  Alain never thought that he would ever be able to muster the self-esteem he thought was required to walk into a bar alone, order a drink and enjoy it quietly.  He had sworn to himself, since his University days, that drinking was a social event.  Therefore, a solo excursion to a bar would forever be helpless, lonely, and desperate.  But he had never been very good at holding a grudge against himself and immediately attempted to contrive a sort of academic experience out of his current situation.  This decision not to turn and flee lasted longer than he had expected.  So, standing awkwardly in the doorway but with new resolve, he searched for the appropriate place to sit.  Alain searched the few scattered faces around him.  They all seemed vaguely familiar like extras in the predictable bar scene of some marginally interesting movie.  For several years Alain had felt himself to be a marginally interesting character whose story, with an expert pitch, could find its way onto the big screen.  But it would only be great once some big time actor pulled out the performance of a career by really capturing the dreary, selfish and pathetic excuse for optimism that propelled Alain through each day.  After this realization, Alain had decided it would be best for the project if he never thought about it again but his current surroundings brought it back out of him.  

						
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The knight had been following me for several days.  He was adorned in full suit of silvery armor that remained untarnished through thick brush, beaches and swamps.  “What was his purpose?” I wondered to myself.  As I climbed atop every new hill, I could look back and see an unrelenting glimmer from the previous one.  He would always be there.  So I decided to rest a bit and wait for him.  The wind rustled through the long grass swaying around me.  It seemed to whisper words of caution as I gazed at my determined pursuer.  As the glimmer grew closer, I questioned whether this was in fact a wise decision.  He could be hostile.  If he were carrying news he would certainly not have made the journey in such attire.  I tried to take my mind off him.  This proved to be a much more difficult task than I had expected.  When I turned away I could feel hot breath exciting the hairs on my neck.  I could feel his cold blade turning my insides out as he took advantage of that one brief instant that I had let down my guard.  I saw myself stepping away from his second slash, this time to my throat.  But the damage had already been done.  I cradled my organs, steaming in the autumn air, as they crept from the gaping wound he had delivered me.  I fell to my knees.  Each dancing blade of grass lashed at me with cruel joy, scratching and scraping my blood-soaked arms.  My eyes filled with tears.  I lifted my head to glimpse the two blurred suns hovering in the sky before me.  I could feel the heat of both of them.  With great pain I removed my right arm from the nest it had created around my pulsing wound and reached for the hotter and brighter celestial body.  I wrapped my hand around the knight’s gauntlet, glowing white.  All feeling and pain was redirected as the hot metal burned into my fingers, soldering my quivering flesh to his hard, forged glove.  My palm gushed forth steam as it melted to the knight.  I tried to tear my arm away but the pain was even greater than submittal.  So I did my best to relax in this terrible state, for my end must certainly be drawing near.  I must have passed out for only a minute, but it could have been a day for that matter.  What must have awoken me was the intense heat building against my right cheek which was merely inches away from my attackers breastplate.  I attempted to wriggle my right arm but to my horror it had vanished into the fiend up to the elbow.  The knight was fusing me into his burning shell.  I pulled furiously to detach my forearm which was now most certainly his.  I cried out as my face pressed against his armor.  The burning reignited in my brain as it began to boil and my howling was muffled, as I no longer had my mouth.   

						
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This wedding was different than all the others.  It was different in the way that everyone who attended the festive event died.  Well, not everybody died.  Just everyone who ate or drank at the splendid event died but even that was a pretty large number.  The Bride’s family was dead and so was the Groom’s.  It would later come out that unanticipated levels of poison where incorporated into the food and drink prepared for the glorious occasion.  It would later be revealed that a wedding gift had been stolen from the Newlywed’s.  However the ownership of the gift was called into question due to the unavailability of any beneficiaries.  Therefore the gift had been stolen from the State.  Investigators assigned to the case were tripled now that it was a State affair.  It would later be discovered that no one had actually died at the once happy, once tragic ceremony.  The theft was reclassified as a merely a family concern but the wheels had been set in motion.  The transfer of ownership of the family property to the State, including stolen and non-stolen wedding gifts, had already been completed due to some excellent paper pushing by government officials.  A top official made a formal apology to all in attendance who, at this time, were no longer dead but still asleep.  What began as a simple misunderstanding between the State and two families would soon boil into a stew of bad feelings when the father of the bride appeared to refuse the offer of forgiveness by declining the government official’s handshake.  Only reports of the non-death aspect of the case had been analyzed before the ill-fated apology took place.  Immediately, the clerk responsible for handling the paperwork was promoted and shipped across the ocean.  The day was declared a State holiday and all government employees were sent home with the day off with the exception of investigators assigned to the stolen property case, who were immediately paid overtime.  This however did not help uncover any clues regarding the size, shape, weight, or whereabouts of the stolen gift.  The previous owner of the gift was questioned but could provide no real insight due to the fact that he was asleep.  He was later thrown in prison for not cooperating with the State authorities.  

						
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The Inevitable End is the name given to the series of events which will bring about the demise of Winky and Sam but the subsequent saving the World.  A note on the World:  It exists in all time so nothing is anachronistic.  The events, vaguely prophesized by the Magnificent Cube are as follows:  Winky will fall in battle and Sam will slay The Chosen One.  This foretelling is unknown to our protagonists at this point.  A note on the foretelling: This one point may seem to fly in the face of the earlier note stating that the World exists in all time.  It doesn’t.  Only events foretold by the Cube are unknown to the rest of the World until they eventually happen.  The magnitude of the Cube’s prophecies is such that each event marks a critical point in the history of the World.  The history of the World was known and catalogued at the beginning of the World by The Keeper of the Magnificent Cube.  Cube Events are so huge that all inhabitants are pretty much aware that a critical point in their history has been reached.  However, the Keeper would remark to the uninformed, “Yeah, that was a Cube Event.”  The Inevitable End, a mildly superfluous title after that explanation, is the final event foretold by the Cube.  The World, however, still goes on afterwards.  Sam, alone, walks the earth until his eventual unrecorded death and unattended funeral.  The Cube withers and dissolves.  The Keeper sends a copy of The History to each of the Twelve Libraries.  The World is well, good, and uneventful.  This is where we are going according to The Magnificent Cube.  A note on the Magnificent Cube: it is actually a sphere.  

						
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There are many characters that need to be explored.  It wouldn’t be much help to list them all at the onset.  Probably the best way to learn the histories and futures of the doomed cast is to appreciate them individually at glances over an extended period of time.  But a few introductions are necessary.  What should be said upfront is that our protagonists, Winky and Sam, are compatriots and friends.  They share a destination.  They tread separate paths.  They drink, never beyond the point of hopeless desperation but occasionally enough for them to feed the animals before sleep.  To Sam, any story worth telling is worth exaggerating.  Winky prefers stripping a tale down to its most basic elements.  Sam searches for reactions.  Winky searches for truth.  Sam is drawn to the earth while Winky looks up to the sky.  But high or low, dirty or clean, happy or sad, their journeys to the same inevitable end are long and hard.  

						
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The fearless two are back from slumber in the murky depths with revelations and insight.  As before, the goal is neither to inspire society nor provide answers to even the most irrelevant questions.  If anything, the two would appreciate puzzling enjoyment, cautious curiosity, and a brief but kind word for all their efforts.  The scope of material may seem vast and foreboding but there will be help along the way.  The insight will occasionally be harsh but always forgiving.  So just like biting into a piece of over ripened fruit or hearing very bad experimental jazz for the first time, you probably won’t realize what’s wrong until it’s too late.  

						
</post>


</Blog>