<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I get this question A LOT... so I wrote this to answer it:  In the spring of 1999, my cousin told he knew the International students Director from the University of the Ozarks in   Clarksville ,   Arkansas   and that he was in   El   Salvador   offering “scholarship helps” to international students. This wasn’t a full scholarship, just a pretty name for a discount of an already OVERPRICED private 4-Year University! So we talked to the guy (Dr. Rickey Casey) and my folks agreed to sponsor me to go up to   Clarksville  . Dr. Casey was very nice and facilitated my way up here. So I came up here for a semester and then realized that U of O didn’t have my major: Computer Science. So, after that semester I moved to a town 20 minutes East called Russellville to a public University called   Arkansas    Tech   University  . At U of O I had met this girl and we started dating. In my first semester, we had been going to her church in Russellville, called   Life    Center  . Since I was a “new” Christian and was looking for a new church to attend, it worked out great and I fit right in with the leadership! The next semester (Spring 2000), I moved to an apartment with my ex-girlfriend’s brother. Everything worked out great that semester until I found out my dad had to close down the factory and could NOT pay for any of my school anymore… so I finished up that semester and started looking for a place to stay since I was not going to be able to afford an apartment and much less tuition! That Spring I went to a Missions trip to   Mexico   and in it I met a guy from   Life   Center   who was a real successful business owner and he and his wife did a lot of marriage counseling. Well his son and daughter had moved out of their house and so they had a couple of empty rooms in their house. So I asked Andy and Sandy if I could rent a room from them. They came back with an answer and they said it would be great if I could move in with them and ALSO they would NOT charge me anything to stay there or even eating. So they brought me in as one of their own! What a blessing! Also, soon there after, that summer I found some people that paid for my tuition and fees! The story continues and I finished school, graduating with Cum Laude Honors in the spring of 2003 with a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science. And I give all the Honor and Glory to my Lord Jesus Christ for preparing the way for me and blessing me beyond recognition! After graduation, my friend Clint started a company in   Rogers ,   Arkansas   and hired me as the lead programmer. After a year of working with him, this other company approached me and wanted to hire me. They are based in   Fayetteville  , so I prayed about it and took the offer! And that is how come I’m here. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey, my name is Rogelio J. Samour... a.k.a.  Ro ... You have stumbled into my blog... in it you will find what I experience in life.... good times, bad times, and everything in between! Thanks for reading! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>