<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This morning just after I got up, Maya called and wanted to know if I wanted to go shopping.  I had 2 be at work at 2, and she at 3.  So we went shopping around the C-20 area.  After we shopped around, we went and ate lunch at IHOP, I don't think I had ever been there before, but it was really good!  I had frech toast, eggs, and bacon :-D mmm mmm soo yummy  After dat, it was almost 1, so I was driving her back 2 her house and she was like, so how long do u think u and AJ will  be together for?  I was like I dunno.  She was like u dunno?  And I was like well, I really like him a lot, but with school starting we won't be able to see eachother as much and im not sure whats going to happen..  She said she was really serious about Brandon and she hopes to be with him 4 awhile if not forever, awww :-) Then I was like, oh u should ask AJ how long, so she said she would at work.  It was like 8ish and I almost forgot to see if Maya had asked AJ, she hadn't cuz she forgot, so she said she would ask him..  Well she said she asked him and he said he was really serious about me, and she said she told him it might be kinda hard with school since we go 2 different schools, and she said dat it would almost be long distance, and she said dat she and brandon were going to make it work, but she mentioned that we were younger, and AJ said dat we may be younger and not as experienced but he want's to learn with me :-D  awwwwww.  She said dat he was really serious about making things work and said dat we should double date more too.  YAY!  I was soo happy, lol.  I was like yeah were definately going to make things work :-D awwwww. 
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday before work, I heard my friend Meghan talking about how she was swimming all these laps, trying to hold her breath for a long time.  It sounded like requirements for an sea world animal trainer, so I was like, what are you training for?  Sure enough she was training to be an animal trainer, at an aquarium in Miami, she would be doing seals, dolphins, and some other animals which I forgot..  I had so many questions because I too want to do something in that field.   I had wondered if she had a lot of previous experience with animals.  While she was in college she worked at Ripleys Aquarium in Myrtle Beach.   She went to Coastal Carollina College in Myrtle Beach, which is really cool, because thats one of the colleges on my list.  She said it was a great college, great party school, and she said there was ALWAYS tons to do, all night!  She said the shopping wasn'y great, but she said dat when she graduated two years ago, they were building the biggest mall in US!!!!  WOW, dats cool.  She said that u don't pay out of state tuition because Va doesn't have the major, Marine Biology.   She had a job for a year at an aquarium but her time ran out, so now she hopes to get a job in Miami.  They gave her the test requirements, which includes 50 push ups, and swimming 1 lap underwater and a bunch of other stuff.  After she trains enough she is going to go take the test!  I just thought it was soo cool!!! LOL 
      
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Today Maya, Brandon, AJ, and I planned a double date for today (we all work together), we had planned to invite a bunch of other peoples from work, but they were unable to come except for Alexis- 1 of Maya's good friends.. Well today I was like well if the date doesn't go really good today, im gonna have to question how good being in a relationship w/AJ is right now.  I picked AJ up at 1:00, we planned to see AVP at 2:00, so Maya, Brandon, and Alexis were going to meet us at the movies around 1:30. Well... They were a lil late so we got tickets to the 3:30 show and drove up to target to get some candy 2 sneak in2 the movies. I got skittles and a strawberry drink- wanted to get my breath fruity, lol.. Maya got a 2 liter of gingerale to bring to the movies! LOL it was so funny, and we were like if they tell us we can't bring it in we were just going 2 tell them we were taking it to the break room, lol right...  The movie was pretty good. AJ said it wasn't bloody enough, lol- Im glad it wasn't! AJ tried to do more than just cuddling and kissing,but I didn't let him, though Maya and Brandon were doing sumthin, lol, I think anything farther than kissing should definately be only when it's the two of us. AJ was doing some new things that were awesome that made me wonder, dang whos he been making out with, getting tips from? lol seriously.  After the movie, we all piled in2 my car and went to Rockwood Park where Maya though there was go karting- but turned out they didn't have any go carts. So we ended up going to this put put place in midlothian which had go karts.. They were so much fun! Brandon made AJ spin out, it was funny!  After go karting,we were hungry but we didn't want dinner, we wanted dessert. So we drove to fridays, but they had like a 20 minute wait and we didn't feel like waiting so we wen't to coldstone creamery instead, ohh I love dat place! I got birthday cake remix and it was really good. After we ate Brandon was like come here Maya I wanna talk 2 u, and they were walking really close to this big fountain that sprays from the ground and I was like ohhh hes so gonna throw her in, and he picked her up and she fell in!! I was like omg! And like half of her jeans were soaked! AJ was like I would throw u in but ur wearing white, I was like haha! After Brandon threw Maya in the fountain every1 was throwing water at eachother and we had a water fight, it was fun, lol.  After the water fight, Maya was like lets go play hide and go seek behind the movie theater. So we were walking back to the car and Brandon and AJ were goofing off taking there time so Maya was like lets go lock the guys outa the car, so we ran and got in the car and locked the doors, and pretended to start driving off, it was soo funny! AJ climbed on top of the car and it was hilarious, and Brandon was on the back of the car making the car go up and down. Finally we let them in, but only cuz we wanted to go play hide and seek.  So we got to the theater and played hide and seek. AJ had a "brilliant" idea to hide in these shrub bushes down this steep hill, I was like dats okay, haha he came out with thorn thingys all over him,aww, lol. We stayed til 9pm then we decided we should get home.  
      
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had to work night shift yesterday (5:30-close), and AJ had to work too except 3:30-8:30. Well I had to be in concession while he got to usher, lucky... Well, it didn't even seem like AJ was working yesterday, he was never around and he barely even said hi, well thats typical when were at work, cuz he doesn't want people talking, and I totally understand, but still its kinda frusterating, I mean hes sooo different when were at work, but people do tease us alot, so yeah. Well, Jessie the head guy in concession told me to go on break at 8:30, I was like cool I can say hi 2 AJ cuz he'll be getting off work, well he was kinda "busy" trying to find Tara (such a slut) to give back her pen. He said he would call me tomorrow (today) but he said he had band camp. Then Sam was going out the side doors and he ran to catch up w/her and he left and went out the door (nope, didn't say bye or anything), Heather was like, ohhh if dat was my boyfriend I would so break up w/him. she was like hes such an ass, and she was saying stuff like dat. I mean yeah he sometimes pisses me off at work n stuff, but dats at work, we can't do anything at work anyways. She was like u should really talk 2 him about it. well it was soon time to go back to concession and a few min later Heather came 2 say hi, I was like, so what should I say? and she was like call him up and be like "u didn't say bye to me bitch" and hang up, she said it would scare him. lol, I was like rite.. Then Jessie heard her say dat and was like, what? and I was like oh nothing, he was like no tell, me. I was like well AJs kinda been pissing me off, and he was like why, and stuff, and he said I should talk to him about it. I dunno tho, I don't think I'll worry about it too much, I think I'll just give him his space at work, and I have my own friends to chill w/at work, and yes they are guys, hahaha, lol. 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I don't want summer to end.  I have had such a great summer.  I went to Sea World camp in San Antonio Texas in june, which was a total blast!  I had so much fun, though I think back about how we had to get up at like 6am every morning, and I don't know how I did it, I still wanna go back next year though.  I met this really nice guy from work AJ, just a few days before leaving for violin camp which would last 2 weeks, I thought about him alot while I was at camp, and I couldn't wait to see him again when I got back, but violin camp was so much fun, and I met some really cool people, like Ally and Geni!!!     Well, I went back to work on saturday, and yay!  I got to see AJ (he was working saturday too).  We talked alot and he ended up asking me out on monday (July 12).- we have been going out since :-)   The last week of July I went to the beach for a week, I wished that AJ could have came- haha lol yeah right, like that would ever happen :-D, but I had still had a fun week, even though AJ wasn't there.  I bought a surf board the first day- I had checked about renting one, but it would cost 20 bucks a day and it was cheaper to buy one for 100 bucks.  I had went to a surf camp last year, so im not a complete beginner at surfing, lol.      So yeah, thats been my summer, going to sea world camp, violin camp, and the beach, and spending time with my friends and my boyfriend.- I don't want it to end!  Right now I get to see my bf several times a week, outside of work, we'll go to the movies, or I'll go to his house or he'll come to mine.  Im worried that when school starts we won't get to see eachother as much, but I hope we can make things work, and I know I wan't to, I just hope it all works out with us going to different schools and stuff :-/   
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      YAY!  I drove up to Virginia Beach w/dad to look at a 94 Toyota Paseo.  It was super cute, lol, and it was cool.  I got to take it for a test drive, and I loved the way it drove, it was easy to drive and easy to see out of.  It has a lot of things I like, like it's 2 door, and it has a sun roof and it has a CD player w/great sound system- it can go super loud :-D !! My dad had some complaints tho- like the windshield had a scratch from the windshield wipers and he said he would have to get it changed.  But finally he said I could get it!  YAY.  I got to drive it home, but it was kinda annoying cuz it was rainning really hard, and I couldn't go very fast- darn, lol, but I got to use the CD player and I listened to my Avril CD the whole way back, it got kinda annoying- the same thing 4 almost 3 hours, but it was the only CD I had in the car w/me- my other CDs were w/my dad in his car.   -I prob won't be able to drive itr anywhere til friday :-( cuz it has to get licensed first, and it stupidly is in my dads name so I can't get it licensed, only he can.  awww, I wanna drive AJ around in my car, lol. 
      
</post>


</Blog>