<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks for being a fucking prick Nic, yes, excuse the ryhme. What the fuck is up wiith you? Today, I lost most of the respect I once had for you.  I webcamed with him. He says:  "....ewwwwww. Much worse than I expected. People offline are a lot more mean then people online. I get called stuff all the time"  Well guess what? NO ONE FUCKING CARES. Those are the kinds of things you keep to yourself , retard. Dont even comment on this, you really hurt my feelings and I dont want to talk to you for a long time.  Way to be a great friend. 
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got school supplies. Its Juanitas 21 birthday. Thatsall I feel like typing...x_x   
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, I cant think of anything.....probably because Im so tired....Making some new sig stuff, so stay tuned later...Ill have them up...sometime. Anyway, Ill most likely be getting: Catapult Grip, White Grip with Black Rubber Grips, and Roller support and Blue plated Wide Deffense =3. I bet Nic is going to like this news. Sent some sounds clips of me to Rob. *am waiting for yours you cheap bastard* Thats all for me. Nite' 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, season one is over. Im sad because we wont see new episodes for awhile, but..now I can watch the whole series from the begining. So, yeah. Still trying to crack the code...but...I will break it, dont worry.Ankle still hurts. Visting the doctor tomorrow.Im making a photo for my profile, so expect one of those soon. Its only 11:30 AM here, so Ill post back tonight.   Currently listening to: Detective 1st opening song (English)  Current mood: bored. 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im tired. I am in a bitchy mood. Today sucked.I spent 12 fucking hours to try and get music on here. Im also going to try tomorrow. None the less, it shall be done. Even if I have to host it on something else, it shall be down. Kyle, if you are reading this, give me a picture ;_;. Ill be up for another 2+ hours and then wake up early and be so tired and bitchy. I pity my family.    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok, now Im getting pissed off >>;;;;      I have two weeks untl school starts and still no supplies. By the time I go, there will be nothing left >_         
    
</post>


</Blog>