<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Well it's me again....of course!! (Nee-cole)      Well Friday I had five friends come over and hang out for a while. Then we all went to John's for the night. My dad had given me 20$ since he sponsors our team. (it's called Shotgun Shellz) We used the money to get junk food. YUM!! We stayed up until around 11 playing Halo. Then the next morning we were up, dressed, and out of the house by 9. We had to be in Winter Park, at Thumb Fu by 11:30. (we watched SWAT on the way there) We were there by 10:30 and the place was packed!! But we didn't start until around one b/c a team was coming late. There were 17 teams, each with 4 players, we have 7 but were only allowed to bring 4. We didn't get out of there until around 7. When I got home there was no one home so I ended up going to a friends again for the night. Today we finished the movie b/c we didn't have time to watch it all on the way. It was a pretty cool movie, one of my favorite action movies. Well that's it, there you have it sounds fun, huh? O, by the way we didn't do so good because the team got to pick the level and of course they picked their best, and it was best two out of three. So we didn't make it past the first round. The first time we kicked butt though!!! We'll do better next time!!!      Well, thanks for being faithful to my site!!!! Well to Mikes site but I do all the work!!! But anywho gotta run!!      This was Nicole and Mike, Love Ya'll!!    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Hello to all and how are you? Well of course this is Nee-cole. And I am here to tell about Mike's day.   (Well yesterday and today)      Well, Mike and Baron had plan to come see me but things didn't work out. Instead they were going to go to Pinellas but that didn't work out either. See Carolyn and Travis told Baron they were going to get Suzie. So Baron decided he wanted to stay to see her I guess so anywho they ended up not going anywhere. Just stayed home and "hung out". Well, they showed up at church in these outfits that sound wierd Baron was sporting a Vintage suit that was pink and green plad and Mike was sporting a Vintage suit that was corduroy. (I think I spelled that right) Some ppl thought they looked good others thought not so good. (I would have been in the 2nd group) After church they went home (Jean's) and changed, then Carolyn, Suzie, Mike and Baron decided they were going to go see "The Little Black Book". Well Mike was paying for Baron so when they went up to the window and asked for the tickets and the chic laughed in their faces. (I would have too) After the movie walking out to the car, a bum got 50 cents off Baron. Mike stayed at Jean's for the night then went home the next morning at around 11 and was pretty tired b/c he didn't go to bed until about 3 so he took a little nap. And that's all folks.....Hope you enjoy knowing what he does everyday!! I bet it's really interesting to ya'll. LoL Well, Nicolina I am sorry that we couldn't come see you and I would have rather gone to see you, maybe sometime soon. I miss you.            Well, as interesting as his life is, my hands are tired from typing so I think I will end here... Did you like the part where they didn't want to come see me? I did, thought it was quite amusing. O yeah I forgot to metion that just know I got to talk to Mike's mom, she seems very nice. And I got to talk to my lil' sis Alyssa, she is so sweet I wish her and Lauren could change places for a while LOL!! But anywho Aloha!!        This is Nee-cole and Mike love ya'll!!        P.S. Aloha means hello and goodbye!!    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Well it's Nee-cole again it looks like I will be doing all the writing, but he will tell me happened in his day or week or whatever. So here I am being faithful to his site and he isn't on to tell me about his day!! But I do know this:  Today, I was suppose to go see Nee-cole but things didn't work out I am so upset. I was really looking forward to seeing her, maybe soon I can. I think I will go to my room and have a good cry, yeah that sounds good.  Mike is not going to allow me to do his posts much longer!! LOL But o well I guess he would have to do them then so haha!! But ya anywho....  This was Nee-cole posting for Mike!! Love ya'll!    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Hello to all,  Well this is acually Nee-cole writing, b/c Mike (Josephine) is too lazy to write,....so I am going to tell you about his day.  Well, the day started off great Baron woke me (Well him) up, We went to Bill's right after that, to cut up a tree. Fun Fun Fun. After that we went to Jonathan and Holly's to get rid of the deck that was moved by wonderful Charley. Baron threw me into the pool, later I tried to kick a piece of wood and I fell in again. So I got to go swimming twice today, fully clothed!! Speaking of this hurricane we are out of school for a week since, there is no electricity. Okay now back to my day....After that we came home (to Jean's) I took a shower and then Jean took me to my house and since then have been waiting on the computer hoping to get a chance to talk to Nicole. She is just a sweet person to talk to. O but i didn't get to tell you the best part Baron may allow me to ride with him, to Nicole's. I hope i get to go b/c i would love to get to see her.  Well, I hope everybody is doing okay, and Micheal is going to kick my butt!! LOL Bye, thanks for reading   Nicole, writing for Mike     
    
    
</post>


</Blog>