<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Now playing :   urlLink  Andy Griggs   , "This I Gotta See"  I just ate my last California Fruits Starburst. Life's not juicy anymore. It was "plum passion" flavor. I hardly ever buy candy for myself, but I was in Kroger a couple weeks ago and the big bag was on sale. Wowsers Inspector! Sometimes I can't even find the California Fruit kind when I  am  looking for them. So I had to take action and buy this ungodly sized bag of candy.  How many of you are asking yourself, "There's a California Fruit variety for Starburst?" Yes, my friend, there is. Or, if this were last Friday night -  YEAH there is!!!!    They are fantabulous... plum passion ,  red cherry ,  raspberry , and   strawberry  watermelon . The latter is my favorite. I'd eat cardboard if it came in  strawberry   watermelon .  Don't get me wrong, I have other favorite candies as well. Just one? Are you crazy??? I'm not a chocoholic though. I do like fruity/tart candies more than pure sugar candies. I'm a big fan of Butterfinger and Junior Mints. I love Almond Joys/Mounds. At Halloween I used to be scared of the flavored Tootsie Rolls - remember, they came in colored wrappers that were blue, yellow, red, orange. I'm sorry Mr. Owl, but Tootsie Rolls should strictly be chocolate. I only ate the red ones because, well, they taste like cherry Starbursts.  All of this aside, holiday candy is in a class all by itself. It's SO exciting! You get stuff you can't buy any other time of the year! And when else can you buy a Snickers in the shape of a bunny rabbit? Christmas candy is the most unique, and this super holiday is responsible for my favorite holiday candy.  Before the Christmas candy leaves store shelves, I buy 1 or 2 extra bags of this stuff and I make it last for 10 months.  What is it, you ask? Chewy peppermints of course!  I call them chewy peppermints, but techinically they are Brach's Christmas Peppermint Nougat.  Perhaps you've seen them....they are white with red around the edge and a Christmas tree in the middle, and they are individually wrapped, which I love.  If I were you, I would not want to eat something called nougat either - which surprises me that I ever tried the things.  But did you know the filling of 3 Muskateers is called nougat?  The peppermint nougat has a very different consistency though.  And that's it I'm not typing the word nougat anymore - I do not like it.  Who knew I could write so many words about candy?  It's a fabulous creation though.  I've always said my favorite food is sugar.        By the way, I googled everything I could and did not find a picture of chewy peppermints for your reference-  GRRRR.  By the way again, do not be fooled by imitators.  I hear a certain "old country store and home cookin' restaurant" has their own version now.  (I can't diss on those who ultimately pay my salary.)   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I really shouldn't be taking this time to write but I just have to get a break from work. However, today was payday (which doesn't get deposited until Monday, so today is a facade) and that was a super surprise. This week has flown by, and not only is it casual Friday, we had  urlLink Krispy Kreme  too. The past couple times we've had KK, I have resisted and ate my oatmeal instead. I was prepared today, brought my oatmeal, but the Krispy Kremes spoke to me. Did you know they whisper? It said "Rhonda...look how many varieties they bought of me today. I'm fresh. I'm warm. I'm glazed. I'm cake. I'm chocolate covered. I will melt in your mouth like a sweet concoction as smooth as molasses."  And they did, they did.  Tonirw45w46824 (sorry I got drool on the keyboard.) Ahem...Tonight I'm going to see  urlLink Pat Green  ya'll! I'm way excited! What's he going to be? Rockin'. What kind of time are we going to have? A rockin' one. And if it's really spectacular, it'll be smokin', blazin', and bitchin' too. No, I don't think it's particularly cool to end every "-ing" word with "-in'" but my favorite word of the moment seems to be "rockin'" so let's milk it for all it's worth. The milk's going to spoil soon though and isn't worthy of my milkshake. I will have heard more live music this week than I ever have since I moved to Nashville, and I love it. I saw  urlLink Jeffrey Steele  Friday night (he was rockin'), the Jenkins Tuesday night,  urlLink Andy Davis  Wednesday night, various songwriters last night at the  urlLink Bluebird Cafe , Pat Green tonight, and I'm going to see another songwriter  urlLink Sunday night . Isn't that great?! This is why I live here people - that and the unfortunate skydiving accident.  Alas, it is time to get back to work. But it's OK because I'm working on getting free kids meals to thousands of elementary students. We're developing life long customers here people! Welcome to the Peanut Gallery!  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       First of all, congrats to Paul Hamm - the all-time first ever American male to win an individual Olympic gold medal of all time in the history of the world ever! As Emily says, he's the "biggest gymnastics stud ever!" Really. Ever.  Last night  urlLink Amanda  and I went to see  urlLink Andy Davis  sing at The End. He's a fabulous local nobody, and we were starstruck. Just a little, but I was still laughing at myself. But alas! We are one degree closer to greatness - Amanda realizes she knows the bass player! Now we are 1 degrees to Andy Davis and 2 degrees to  urlLink Dave Barnes . However, if Bass Player knows Dave, we are just 1 degree separated! This could lead to many fun "How Many Degrees?" games....such as degrees to  urlLink John Mayer . Dave knows him so that means we are only like 3 degrees from him. Can we act on this please? In celcius preferrably. (I heart John Mayer.)  Hark!-I have gotten off track again. Andy only played 7 songs I believe. However, all my favorites were played so I am super happy. One of the new songs was unfortunate and contained the worst sound I've ever heard in my life - I did not know that a guitar could reproduce the sound of nails on a chalkboard, did you? Another new song was a fun little diddy about a girl with brown eyes. It was called "Brown Eyes." My assumption that it was, indeed, written for and about me was correct. Right? It's about me right? I'm in the mood to let my love for amazing lyrics show. I'd like to make a page for this exclusively and let it continually grow.  "We'll rent a comedy, rewind the best parts, and memorize the lines." (from "Laugh So You Don't Cry")  "When it gets down to it I hear background music when I see you." (from "Magic")  "You know when you steal away, thoughts in my head are nails in my bed, and keep me awake." (from "I Never See You")  "It's safe to say that you forgot you wanted me to tie that knot; This fella don't know what he's got...oh, oh how it hurts to watch, we could've had so much..." (from "Hurts To Watch")  "I still think I hear you pulling in but you wouldn't know why cause you're the one who's on the leaving end; if you waved goodbye and you saw me cry would you believe me then?" (from "Black Keys")  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        A fter the  urlLink Titans  game on Saturday night, the 3 Amigas went to  urlLink O'Charley's . Why? 1) We were hungry. 2) It's Amanda's favorite restaurant. 3) We had $2 off by presenting our ticket stubs! (aw yeah!) So in the midst of our random conversation, we get on the topic of Ace Ventura: Pet Detective. I can't remember how it happened.....perhaps  urlLink Amanda  quoted it. So we all begin reminiscing about the movie and  urlLink Emily  knows just about every line and Amanda can do the accent. ("Do you talk to the dolphin? Does he call you at home?")        So guess what! Today, on my way home from work, I saw one! It got on at 37th and off at 43rd where I assume it was going to Bloomingdale's to buy a hat, which will turn out to be a mistake. Sorry, wrong movie. So today, on my way home from work, I saw one! A pet detective that is. It was a funny looking Dodge Ram that caught my attention and when I drove past I saw that it said "pet detective" on the side! He had a very large cage in the back and was driving slowly. He had a single red "cop light" on the top of the truck, which scared my speeding self to death when I first saw it.         After I got home today, I threw away the petals from the first roses a guy ever sent me. Yes, it was just last year. However, I've moved on and now I'm moving (geographically) and the petals, unfortunately, are not worthy of gaining spot in the new apartment. I'm sorry Josh. They were fabulous.      
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Parade&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Alright, so I'm still playing around with the fabulous blog. I put the cowgirl picture in my profile. OK, yeah, I do like that picture. It was taken at Mule Day 04. Yes folks,  this  is why I moved to Tennessee. This was my first Mule Day experience but people apparantly come from all over the country. Mules are some funny looking creatures, and quite entertaining to those watching the "mule pull." The motto for this year's Mule Day was "Three Cheers for the Long Ears!" Yep, they got some long ears. There's also a parade, and crafts, and games, and bad bad bad food like funnel cakes and fried twinkies. Something tells me those weren't invented by Dr. Atkins.  I'm still gettin' the hang of this.  Trying to insert pictures of the mules confused my computer.  It did not confuse me; it confused my computer and blogger.com      
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    This is Amanda and I at WaterColor in Florida.  We called it "Spring Break 04" but let's not kid ourselves.  We are old now and it was just a 3-day weekend off work.  &nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well folks, this is my first post of my first blog. I am no longer a blog virgin.  Speaking of the V word, I saw Britney Spears wearing a t-shirt yesterday that said "I'M A VIRGIN" and then in smaller letters underneath that it said "But this is a really old shirt."  Pretty funny if you think about it.  I like a dry sense of humor.  I have wondered what, exactly, would constitute a wet sense of humor?  I think it is those people (ie: 60-year-old men) who think they are SO FUNNY that they have to make a stupid comment to you every time they see you, and then they laugh because they think they are hilarious.  Plus, they always have hearty laughs that sound as pleasant as nails on a chalkboard.  However, that was a tangent and I didn't mean to go past the "blog virgin" sentence.  Suffice this to say that although I hope Did I Shave My Legs For This is entertaining, I do not know how devoted I can be to it.  I really just made this so I can post comments on Amanda Jane's blog....but it's kinda neat :)    BTW, is anyone getting my Deana Carter allusion?  I shall explain in a future blog.  (Oh, did you hear that?  There WILL be more!!!)  Speaking of blog names, "Flying Wombat" IS TAKEN!  I have GOT to look up the joker who stole my thunder on that one.  If they only knew how they've desecrated something so sacred.  (More to come on this later as well.  Remind me.)   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>