<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah, I have started to try and skateboard...key word being "try". lmao. I can go straight alright but not far b/c my skateboard, which was not purchased by me, came from Wal-Mart of all places...so the bearings suck! And the wheels also suck! So, there ya go..lol. As far as tricks go,...nope, none, nada, don't think so..hehe. yeah! I'd even settle for learning an ollie. I need someone to teach me... 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I keep getting injured at dance practice...accidents? or am I on someone's hit list??? Before school let out I caught a staph infection on my chin. This was complete and total hell because I ended up having to go to the doctor, and have my large bump cut w/ a mini scalpel,...joy...During the summer @ UDA camp, which I guess can count as practice for this post..lol.., I was scratched by morgan which was ok, b/c of course she didn't mean it. Then Hey! I get another infection on my elbow, which is why I have been wearing a large band aid to school. Those infection thingys coming both from the practice area in the south mall at ellender being disgusting and dirty! Oh, then Katie accidently scratches me on my eyelid! I swear someone doesn't like me...   What have I ever done to deserve these things   ...lamo! hehe 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here comes the Spife courtesy of Josh..Go Josh...^_^;; I didn't know what a spife is supposed to look like so there..lmao..&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yes, the Spork is an awesome thing....^_^;;&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      OMG! Today was the first day of school...And this being my SENIOR year,...I get even more inpatient with Freshman stupidity than usual. Well woop-dee-doo, guess who has a Freshman class 1rst hour!!!!??? Me! Some freshmen know there place. These ppl walk into class like they own the friggin place! Yellin' and acting the fool! They are sooo unruly and rude.  It's sickening how they start talking about each other and making fun of ppl that are in class w/ them, and they are in the same grade. I mean, most of us upper classmen at least have some kind of respect for each other! If there are any freshmen reading this, Please try and act your age. And also remember that you annoy the Seniors, and...we will let u know about yourself whether you like it or not. oh, and we can Spork you to. So watch out.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hi.   I'm Ashley and this is my blog. Cool isn't it. haha. If you like my blog, please feel free to leave me some dang comments. ok...Oh, and the title of this post has absolutely  nothing  to do with this post...i love it.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>