<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       a   urlLink  This    blog is funny. I briefly thought that it might be written by my friend Dan, as it closely resembles a lot of our old Potboiler columns *written* by President Bush. But then I saw that the profile for Bush lists Usher and Lil Jon as favorite music. I don't think Dan knows who Usher and Lil Jon are...    a   Netflix sent out my replacement disc today. This is good. However, I think that Netflix might be cheating on me. With   urlLink  this    girl! I don't know for certain, but it seems a little suspicious to me.    a   urlLink  Last Comic Standing 3    starts one week from today. It's true I was pretty disappointed in the way NBC handled Last Comic Standing 2, but I can't wait to see Dave Mordahl again. I was at his show at Pantages theater earlier this summer, where he recorded his up-coming cd. He's got such great material, and such a huge following from the first season, I look for him to be a stand-out star this time around. Down-side, we have to deal with Sean, Dat Phan, Bonnie and Tammy again. I'm already proudly displaying the "I know I'm funnier than Dat Phan" magnet I got from Cory Kahaney at the first LSC tour.    a   A bunch of us at the   urlLink  Lost Soul Companion    website have organized a fun little land-mail project. We've each made 8 things for each other, so we'll all be getting a package with a bunch of different things sometime soon. I wanted to make sparkly playing card collages for everyone, but all my art supplies are burried in a box somewhere I can't get to now. So I made everybody a copy of the Definitive Flamingo cd. This is a cd whose tracks, I feel, provide a fairly accurate representation of my life and personality. I'm mailing mine out tomorrow, and I'm quite anxious to see what everyone else has been up to.    a   My friend Hannah called me late this evening. She was audibly excited and, in hushed tones, informed me that she was in a bar in West Bend, WI (where she's working on a campaign). The bar is called   Muggles,   and while it looks like a typical Wisconsin bar at first  ,  there is apparently Harry Potter stuff hidden everywhere!    I assume Hannah has been drinking a little  .   Good for her. She's working on a rough campaign. More about  that    later. Maybe tomorrow.  
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, I was home, here in Wisconsin, all summer. I went back to Louisiana at the end of July. I guess I got busy and caught up packing, messing around with my car, moving, interviewing for jobs, etc. But that's no excuse. That's no excuse for only finding out  TODAY  that Doug Mientkiewicz got traded to Boston  JULY 31ST .  I caught the tail end of the Twins game on TV this weekend and made note that Doug was once again missing at 1st base. The team HAS been very injury prone this season, so I hoped that perhaps he was just injured. But alas, it was not to be so. As I checked the internet for information today, I felt like I had been punched in the guts when I saw the picture of Doug in his new Red Sox cap. To make things worse, I read that many fans, unable to pronounce his name, are calling him "Mink." What the hell? That's not even close. Man-Kay-Vitch.  Man - KAY - vitch , people, please.  Embarrassing as this is to admit, the news of this trade brought me to the brink of tears, just as catcher A.J. Pierzynski's trade to San Fransisco did earlier this year. I have such an emotional connection to the Minnesota Twins, especially the entire 2002 line-up. It may not be healthy, but it's me.  I certainly don't consider myself an all-around sports enthusiast, but I like what I like. And what I like, I really like. I take things like this hard. I have not forgotten that fateful morning in 6th grade when I heard that the Minnesota NorthStars were being sold to Dallas. I cried so hard, and so long, that my mom had to let me stay home from school that day. And to this day, despite their success, I have trouble accepting that the Minnesota Wild is really a hockey team.  Anyhow, there's nothing I can do to about it. So, now I must focus my energy on mustering the will-power NOT to log onto ebay and type "Doug Mientkiewicz" into the search bar. I made that mistake with A.J. Pierzynski, resulting in a way-too-big-to-wear A.J. Jersey, an autographed picture, a bobble-head doll, and a Topps figurine. I bid on a ton of stuff, mistakenly thinking that other people out in ebay-land were just as frantic for  A.J. as a Twin  momentos. Oops. I won't be making that costly mistake again.    I love ya Doug.  
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, Chinese food was on my mind tonight (as it so often is on Sundays when no decent Chinese restaurants are open here), when one of those great "what if someone had a gun to your head and you had to choose..." questions popped in my head.   What if someone had a gun to your head and you  had  to choose to eat only mushrooms or only water-chestnuts for the rest of your life?   This is an especially troubling question for me, because I do not really like water-chestnuts. There is just something unnatural about them. It's as if their uber-crunchiness is from the devil or something. So, my initial gut-reaction would be to choose mushrooms.  However, with important decisions like this, one must not be too hasty. Let us not forget the " What if you could only choose ONE kind of mustard for the rest of your life? " incident. I was initially wooed by the sweet yumminess of honey mustard, until saner minds than mine convinced me that the tasty AND versatile yellow mustard was the way to go. Imagine what a disaster THAT could have been. My god.  So, I must examine this new conundrum very closely.  One must consider nutritional value. After much-less-than-exhaustive research on the subject (namely reading the back of a can of water-chestnuts and typing "mushroom nutritional value" into Google), I see that mushrooms can provide riboflavin and niacin, while water-chestnuts offer 5g of carbs, 1g of fiber and 1g of protein. Hmmm. I have no idea which is more important. It's at times like these that I wish I'd paid more attention in 10th grade Health class.  Texture could also play an important role in this decision-making process. This is one time when the melt-in-your-mouth goodness of mushrooms might actually work against them. The extra work your mouth has to do to chew through the water-chestnuts might trick your brain into thinking you're eating a much more substantial meal than you actually are.  I don't know.  I just don't know, dammit ! I guess I'm still leaning toward mushrooms, but if anyone with more nutritional know-how or any other strong convictions or arguments wants to weigh in on this, please feel free. 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, sad to say, there's trouble in paradise.  I was eagerly anticipating the arrival of the mail today, because I was scheduled to receive THREE discs. And sure enough, there were the three red envelopes just as promised. I giggled my way through  SNL: The Best of Will Ferrell,  secure in the continued strength of our relationship. Then I slipped  The Chappelle Show  in. And there it was. The first glitch in our almost-year-long relationship. "  DVD cannot be loaded.  " A cracked disc.   Naturally, I was devastated.  I had a brief discussion with Netflix about this issue via his "Report a Problem" webpage.  Netflix assures me that he's going to make this right.   I guess I'll give him the benefit of the doubt.  Because  that  is what love is all about, man.    
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            urlLink      Since the low-perfotrmance of charter schools has been brought into the lime-light, I've heard a lot of people whining about how unfair these numbers are. "They don't take  demographics  into consideration." "They don't show what sort of progress  has  been made..." blah blah blah blah blah. Guess what? Regular public schools don't get that luxury either. And these same folks are more than willing to point to  those  test-scores as indicators of a failing system. I say put up or shut up. And for god sakes,  stop whining  already.*    * disclaimer: the above was mostly prompted by a rather irritating email exchange between a bunch of Teach for America teachers I had the misfortune of being privy to earlier this week. It went a little something like this:      TFAer#1: Oh my god. Did you all read the NY Times today?  whine whine whine whine.  They must be wrong because I am always right.   TFAer#2: Yes I did read that. I thought it must be wrong as well, because   I'm always right too!     TFAer#3 :  I concur as well. I use fancy words like  concur  because I enjoy showing off. By the way TFAer#1, you are very very smart.   TFAer#1: Yes. Yes I am.    TFAer#4: Let us go discuss our vast intelligence and greatness over a game of ultimate frisbee!           
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Took this picture at a John Edwards rally in Baton Rouge a few weeks ago. Mr. White Collar wants us to support Bush's Tax Plan? No kiddin'.  urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Blossom the Puppy.  Who knew something this cute could also be sooo evil.  urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I'm not a mommy.  Really.  Thank God.  However, I did take Blossom the Puppy to Petco this evening.  It was not  unlike  taking a two-year-old shopping.   She needed a new harness, as she's grown out of her old one.  So we went there first.  But, like any self-respecting toddler, she was not at all interested in trying on clothes.  She peed on the floor in protest.  So, after clean-up in aisle 7, we headed on to the toy aisle.  Blossom quickly picked out the toy she wanted: a HUGE girraffe that was bigger than she is.  Then she wanted a stuffed trout.  And then a stuffed quail.  (seriously,  who  is designing dog toys nowadays?)  I ended up getting her a sensible toy to help with her teething.  Surprise, surprise, puppies don't really care about  sensible .   On the ride home she kept trying to jump from her shotgun seat into my lap.  Not a great idea when you're driving down the interstate at 70 mph.  At one point I actually had warn her  not to make me stop this car!!!     This is what I get for not having more pressing plans for Friday night.  Damn it. 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      with  urlLink Netflix .   Yup.  This is probably the healthiest relationship I've ever had.  Netflix understands that I change moods and priorities as often as I change underwear (and thanks to my strong committment to personal hygiene, this means quite, quite often).   If I feel the need to rearrange my rental queue 10 times in one day, Netflix never complains.  Netflix didn't mock me that time I kept   Say Anything   with John Cusack for several weeks just because.    Depending on how much time and energy I feel I can devote to our relationship, I can change my level of committment to Netflix whenever I need to.  I frequently go back and forth between 3 and 5 movies-at-a-time, and I never feel any pressure from Netflix at all.  And if I ever (god forbid) want to break it off entirely, Netflix will let me keep my rental queue online as long as I want to, because Netflix knows me well enough to realize that I will probably come running back to it eventually, expecting things to be just like they were.   I love you Netflix.  And I always will.  Speaking of me and my twisted ideas of love: I realize that I have often sworn off any notions of marriage.  However, if anyone (that is, anyone not entirely distasteful or conservative) were ever to propose to me  urlLink this  way, I'd probably have some second thoughts. 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My mom got a completely unsolicited  "W '04" bumper sticker in the mail today.  We all feel  dirty  just having it around.  We've been brainstorming dirty things to write on it that either start or end with "W".  It's a small bumper sticker, so it has to be short.  Pass along any ideas, please.   If we can't think of something, we may just put it on a vehicle as is, and then drive around like a jackass, cutting people off, not using turn-signals, etc.  Could be fun*.   Certainly the "Dear Mr. President, I've received my bumper sticker.  Please except my donation..." letter that accompanied the sticker will be sent back.  With the donation part whited out and naughty things written in to replace it.  Obviously.  *If our insurance company, or any impressionable 16-year-olds are reading this, please note that we are not  actually  going to do that. Because that would be  wrong.  
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I finally went to see  The Village  today. Even after I'd read the reviews.  And  listened to other people, who've already seen it, complain about it. I was still willing to shell out the $5 for a matinee, if for no other reason than to watch Joaquin Phoenix on the big screen for 2 hours. What can I say? I'm weak, and he's pretty.  Yes, I DID figure out the eventual big *twist* about 2 min into the movie. This was mostly because everyone has been saying "it's  so  obvious...." SO, I kept thinking "what's the most obvious thing that could possibly happen?" And, yup. That was it. Disappointing.  Still, I did like the movie. I dug the message that underscores the whole thing. If you've seen it, you know what I mean. If not, then, I guess none of this makes any sense at all. Sorry.  Bottom line: Joaquin: very pretty, very stoic, and totally worth the five bucks (this is the same reason I will probably see  Ladder 49 , despite the fact that it doesn't look like anything I'd normally want to see...but Joaquin sweaty  and  in peril? How can I resist?). 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Pretty, no?  urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink WELCOME TO WAX BUSH 2004   I don't think I'll ever tire of the creative use of "Bush" as a euphemism.  These T-shirts are awesome.  You should get one.  It will look great on you.  Really.  It will.
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Will Ferrell - A message from White House West   Anybody else miss Will Ferrell's Bush impression?  This was a welcome fix.
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      From the brilliant-beyond-words Kurt Vonnegut:  urlLink I Love You, Madame Librarian -- In These Times : "And on the subject of burning books: I want to congratulate librarians, not famous for their physical strength or their powerful political connections or their great wealth, who, all over this country, have staunchly resisted anti-democratic bullies who have tried to remove certain books from their shelves, and have refused to reveal to thought police the names of persons who have checked out those titles.  So the America I loved still exists, if not in the White House or the Supreme Court or the Senate or the House of Representatives or the media. The America I love still exists at the front desks of our public libraries. "
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I've basically abandoned my livejournal, and have become a livejournal ex-pat here in blogspotworld. It's nice here. Plenty of boat drinks and tiny umbrellas. Almost everyone speaks english. I'm happy enough.       I've recently made it home to Wisconsin after a grueling year *teaching* in rural Louisiana. A barrel of monkeys that was  not.  I won't go into it, because it's all just too depressing. That's part of why the livejournal no longer gets updated. I just don't want to re-hash the misery. But, the escape home wasn't exactly a piece of cake either. My car died in the process. Well, it didn't exactly die so much as it was really really ill (but not terminal) and all the car-doctors in the area decided to skip out on the  "Replacing a Brake-Line"  day at mechanic school. It didn't seem worth it to spend the $1200 + gas on a truck to tow it home, so I left it to a salvage yard for a complete loss. Damn. That hurt.   On a positive note, I had to make a brief detour to Chicago for a very short notice job interview on Saturday. The interview was right downtown in the Loop, and I got down there really early. So, I spent the afternoon hanging out in Grant park and walking around. Being in Downtown Chicago for a job interview with a non-profit made me feel positively  cosmopolitan  again. A little more  Sex and the City,  a little less  Green Acres,  if you will.  George W. Bush is coming up here to our little slice of heaven tomorrow. I've been nosing around to see if anyone is planning a protest, but haven't heard anything. My mom actually got a phone-call offering her tickets to the event. She was like "You've got to be kidding" and hung up on them. I told her she should have taken them and played the "Rah Rah GOP!" role. Then we could have gone and yelled nasty things until we got beat up by Secret Service dudes. Oh well. With Wisconsin's "major battle-ground state" status, I'm sure we'll have another chance.  Hmm. That's all for now. Must go watch some Olympics. 
      
</post>


</Blog>