<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I AM SOOOOOOOOOOOO BORED!      Little Seymore (aka daniel) is SOOOOOOO CUTE BLESS HIS LITTLE BI SEXUAL BEANIE lol!   I love him aaaaah cuteness!         PEACE OUT  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Another day of crappyneess not 2 mention the history test that I had nooooo rememberance was WOT so eva!   I LOVE MATTY lol mmk little outburst there mmk umm yeh!   WELL i'm bored once agen have nuthing 2 talk about as usual and i'm buggered OH and i'm goruchy coz there's no more white chocolate left and i'm TIRED N SOOKY:'(      Luv u all   PEACE  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      She won't get off the phone She won't leave me alone when I'm talking to that guy She can be a real nitemare Get's me 2 do her hair and says it neva turns out right But When I Put On a Face She can tell coz she knows me so wellllll  Closer Tha My closest friend someone who will be there till the end My sister sister Deeper than the deepest sea No-one loves you like your family My sister sister  (ok hand getting sore stop writing nnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnow!)  This Is 4 Sum1 by the name of strawberry shortcake and i've done a few bad things and i'd like 2 say sorry (even thought its from a few months back) i still don't believe that one is over it yet coz i've been told and i am honeslty sorry and you have 2 admit...I've been a good gil lately..and frankly I enjoy it! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        After a lovely morning of roll call i walk out into the corridor to find to my surprise a tic tac (the disturbing sence and trail of the one and only...DEMOND BOY AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH), yes the demond boy had struk the very spot i was about 2 walk on...anyway!     Recess (or waz it lunch I dno i can't remember) from being KNOCKED OUT BY A FREAKING BALL hit in the head(well not just a little hit in the head, it was THROWN AT MY HEAD by sum mysterious person i don't....know.....WHO but whoeva did they will b prosecuted...once i know wot i'l do i'll tell you) along with the after shock of the DEMOND BOY striking his prey (which was me) with his deadly supply of DA DA DAAAAAA tic tacs!     Well that was mainly my day OH and then there was this one time after school and this sweet little person came up to me and said goodbye and gave me a big hug and a kiss on da cheek and sed ENJOY YOU WEEKEND and 2 my surprise it was ANGEL WOMAN...DEMOND BOYS sidekick!          FIN   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well Hey Kidlets,      I thought I'd start off by welcoming myself and you to my thingo i dno wot they are but they seem koolness!   Well my experience 2day was exciting.....i saw a moonbeam of a life time and u could say it was a very shady experience!      well i'm boring so peace out rabbits!   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>