<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love going to concerts.  That has been my new hobby the last 4 years it seems.  I went to concerts sporatically for decade or so, my first being, Oingo Boingo.  I was 17 year old. From there, I enjoyed Rod Stewart on 4 different occassions... Saw Tina Turner twice, The Eagles on their Hell Freezes Over Tour.   There was a period of time in the Summer of 1994 that my parents bought a box at the then "NEW" Glen Helen Blockbuster Pavilion.  I saw a half dozen concerts that summer.  Don Henley,  Chicago, 1 of my Rod Stewart concerts, Lynard Skynard (yea...hi, only Asian in the audience!).  I've also seen I can remember the first time I ever thought I NEEDED to go to a concert.  I was watching Video Hits One, hosted by Richard Blade.  They showed Duran Duran's the Reflex.  I was a huge DD fan...HUGE!  I saw the kids in the audience, the gal crying, John Taylor!!!  I thought in my mind...I HAVE TO GO!  I'll DIE IF I DON'T!   I never went, didn't die either...  I did beg my Dad for the "Sing Blue Silver" Video.  He didn't have the money at the time and told me we could just rent it.  That wasn't good enough...I needed it, I wanted it, I had to have it!  My poor Dad...he bought it.  I realize now that I set him back a bit...$35 was a lot of money in 1984.  Thanks Dad...This video got me through the early 80's and being allowed to go to concerts.  In the last four years, I have seen numerous artists.  I'm very blessed to have an concert partner who has music in his soul.  He started his concert going at an early age, unlike myself, he was a 5 year old...first concert being, THE JACKSON 5!  I know...  So,  we really do it up big time.  I wish I can remember all of them but here is a start.  Janet Jackson, Tom Jones, Ed Harcourt(2), Beach Boys, The Stones (4), Sheryl Crow (2) , Justin Timberlake (2), Christina Aguilera (2) , Supergrass (4), INXS, Duran Duran (2 times, yes!), Chris Isaak, Al Green, The Who, The Strokes, The Vines, The Music, X-hibit, Ludicris, Outkast, Princ (2) , The Time, Pearl Jam, Black Eyed Peas (2) , Mooney Suzuki, Kings of Leon, Ozo Matli, Rick James, Teena-Marie,  Bruce Springsteen, Earth Wind & Fire, Chicago, Neil Young...that's all I can think of at the moment.   By myself...I've seen the Go-Go's from the front row, Cyndi Lauper, Linda Ronstadt, Hootie and the Blowfish, General Public, Mariah Carey, Blink 182, Rolling Stones (2), Wallflowers & Bryan Adams...that's all I can remember.  Looking at this, I'm pretty blown away!  I'm not even counting all of the local bands I'm gone to see, I'm a live music maniac! Yes!  So last night...at the Earth Wind & Fire/Chicago concert.  I talked to Michael Rosenbaum who plays Lex Luthor on my favorite TV show, Smallville.  He was very nice.  We were joking with each other about who passed gas.  I said, "It was you!!!"  He shouted, "NO, I swear to God it wasn't me...that's disgusting!"  Yea...maybe I could have picked a better topic of discussion.  Anyway...I'm done for now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I've decided to get into this blogging thing, why not? I've kept a journal in some fashion for decades, but now, I will do it for the cyber world to see! I'm thinking that this can be some kind of cathartic release for me so I am quite looking forward to it. I will write about last night's adventure in a bit...
     

    
</post>


</Blog>