<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mary, Aleshia, Allan and Nina trying to be "Thugs"...I think theres a reason why Im taking the picture not in the picture lol. Let me remind you that these people are the sweetest people ever lol&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why does everything have to be so complicated? I know life isnt easy but if your blessed enough to meet someone who is just amazing and so special to you- why do you have to be taken away from them? Like Im a real believer in fate and things happening for a reason-but we'll all find out in the future why everything cant be perfect. Sometimes it works out sometimes it doesnt. Everythings a test, and this is a real test of how strong I am! We're just gooing to have to wait and see 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         "The only thing scarier than seeing carnies at the fair....Is seeing Bob Maffeo at the fair"  I have to finish this later but lets just say me and aleshia had a good time!        
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha Sam the vegitarian! Were so mean for making her eat a bambi sandwich lol&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sorry Carl, I luv ya, dont get mad at me (maAAd or however you ppl say it in Michigan) but I just had to put this picture on!!!! Its very disturbing, I feel bad for the squirrel! Its just so awkward, but your still the man!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Zach and Tika in their Braveheart picture...wait I think thats my handprint LOL! You could tell I was all over him that week! Haha Jk Luv ya Zach   urlLink     urlLink     
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fair Parking  So after I left Aleshia, I went across the street to the muisc parking. We got those hot neon vests and bright colored flags! Ya I met this girl who played violin, shes a freshman, it was nice talking with her, and there was this other boy freshie, he didnt say much but he seemed alright. Then Nina and Mary got out and it was great seeing them, cuz I hadnt seen Mary in like 2 weeks maybe? idk and Nicole in like over a month! So we were so bored for a while that he went on the swings cuz there was nothing to do, and me and Mary talked about Colorguard and pretended to do our reutine on the little flags. Ok, All I have to say is there is a lot of really STUPID ppl in this world! So I was pointing my flag towards Mary, she was pointing the flag to Nic, but one guy thought that pointing at Mary meant to park on Mary lol and his wife was like shes poiting to her so she can point to the other girl!  Did I mention it was like 90  degrees and we had no shade!!!!!!!!! For 4 hours it was freaking humid and hot and we all got wicked bad sunburns, ya and thats after I put on sunblock-I pulled a Nina with my sunburness. Then people thought they could go out the second row which leads to the softball field but that was gated off. So one lady asked me how to get out and im like go to the end, but she thought I meant the end of the field so she drives over the basketball court, it was so funny. We ended up telling everyone to go over the basketball court lol.  Some guy asked Mary to sign for him lol!Me and Nicole started talking about Workcamp and her Monster camp, wow we had similar experiences, and met similar people. Granite State! Um so we had to lay on the grass for a bit, it was too damn hot! By 6, Pete was already there and I was talking to Adam and his friend about the fair cuz they just came from it, so they took over for us as me nicole and mary left to go swimming at nicoles.  We were playing with these noddles and they ended up breaking then me and mary were singing our workcamp songs lol, ya there still in our heads! Then we had supper and all that jazz and changed and Nic played piano for us. After that we were sitting having a drink, me and Nicole were on these stools so Nicole all of a sudden starts sliding off the chair!!!! And then I look and shes on the floor! Omg the stool was like bent on one side! Mrs. Anderson was so funny about it. Well it was a cheap stool so Ill give her that lol.  After breaking some stuff, we went watched the Prince and Me- Ive already seen it so i was like "Can i go online?" Im such an ahole but Im addictted to online stuff. So Carl was on and I havent talked to him all day, and then he said he had to get up at 7 to help out with the Red Cross- can you say perfect guy? lol. Then he left and Zach came on, I didnt even know he came on and i was happy cuz hes been busy doing bandcamp and having a good time lol, ive heard those bandcamp stories! Then I was talking to Zach and Dunnies friend Dan- he seems like a cool kid. Then Dunnie came on and i was like Ya chating it up with 3 guys from Penn! So then i went back to my house and Zach actually told Dan that I  said he would look good with this guy from my youth group! And hes like YOU THOUGHT I WAS GAY! It was pretty funny actually. And me and Dunnie ended up talking till midnight and later but he had to get to soccer in the morning so we both got off 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Workcamp Booth!  Well, If you in Marshfield right now, you know its fair time! How great, yep fair parking and helping the workcamp booth. Ok so 10 am, I went up to the fair grounds and helped Aleshia set up the poster and stuff at the Workcamp booth! Ya Mr.McCorry I heard messed up the passes? or was it Bob idk? So ya we dont have a pass for all week but its ok we got the one day ones. Me and Aleshia spent like 4 hrs just talking about workcamp! Workcamp memories will never leave us! We even talked about stuff we had forgotten about! So ya hours kept passing by and still no one donated! Me and Aleshia donated $1.50! Ya were cool! BUT that was the ONLY donation we got all day! LOL, me and Aleshia were being friendly tho! They would just smile say Hi and look at the pictures. We werent that pushy i guess, but we hate being pushy! You can come visit us if you want were inside the exibet building towards the back.Then we went over to Bob Maffeo's little hut! He got it all decked out with Hawiian stuff. Stop by and say Hi if you know Bob! So we were talking to Bob and we look at him and he soaked the whole font of his shirt with sweat! ew! He looked like he went swimming!!!! Nasty. He gave us free fries tho?lol. Did i mention to you it was like 90 degrees out??? I drank like 20 ounces of my drink in like a minute ! So we went back to the thing and still NO donations! Our posters kept blowing over it was the funniest thing! We were like AHHHHH GET IT!!! It was something to see! Then at 2 I had to leave Aleshia by herself- Im sry- but I had to go fair park   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WorkCamp Crew 2004- from left to right, first row to last  Carl, me, Rob/Julianne, Carol, Resident, Tika, Sam, Kristen/ Resident, Zach, George, Dunnie, Resident, and Jon&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys its me,  I got a message from the friends of music- I have to do fairparking from 2-6, and before that I signed up to help Aleshia with the booth for workcamp- but that was from 10:30 am or something like that, but I have so much time in between tho! I think the booth might for from 10:30-12:00 im not sure, but I have two hours in between that. We got Colorguard tonight at 6-8, hopefully I'll be able to move my arm-ouch I still hurt! Mary's coming too so It's all good! Last night I got Dunnie to get his own blog so his is coming along pretty well! Im still trying to get that picture up on my profile but it was so funny cuz me and Dunnier were like "This is so confusing!" Haha were so high tech  You know in that Garden State movie-how amazing would it be to meet someone in 4 days and have them completely change your life? I mean I met some ppl in 5 days that have brought out who I really am and showed me that its ok to be yourself, I know Zach keeps telling me that he doesnt usually act like the way he did at camp, and to be honest, neither was I- I always thought that I was shy around meeting new ppl- but Im just shy around ppl in school who already have friendships with other ppl and dont take the time to get to know me! SO thats ill I have say today- I write about my fair experience 2mrw  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Marshfield Youth Group  urlLink    Left to Right First Row-Nancy, Bud, Debby, Me, Dan, Nina, Amanda, Mary, Bob, Aleshia, Darren Left to Right Second Row- Matt, Pat, Mike, Melissa, Liam, Justin, Allan, Debby  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          What Ill miss about workcamp   Part I:      Our crazy crew- Crew #54 I'll never forget you guys! and dont forget the awesome crew#55-    Impromtu bleacher rehearles wiht Mike, that no one but us showed up to! Aleshia enjoyed them the most lol,     Jake's weird handshakes- I still didnt understand what he was doing,     Our fab 4 some in the showers - Im lonely now- "Im so glad your wearing clothes!",     Bob Maffeo Impressions- Liam with the napkin "ah my back!" "dYNAMITE" my voice isnt low enough tho,     Zach's shower stories- "God likes to show off in the shower" "Hey your fantasy came true"    YEAH WHAT OKAY- Dunnies is the man and anyone who doesnt tink so is a loser,     WHERES GEORGE? lol,     Making fun of each others accents- "ARNGE" "RAAAASPPPPburries" "It's pAAp not soda" "Whats a U-y?" "You's all" "Thats BAAAd" "Supa Kmaat" "Thats wicked cool" If your not from New England, dont try to use wicked cuz u dont kno how to correctly,     Sliding down the hallwayy- Nina breaks her camera, I bellyflop and look like an idiot, its so much easier with socks! Delaware flipping out on us lol     
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well Sam told me to get a livejournal, but I think that thing went too much over my head, It must be teh blonde hair seriuosly, um so I saw Shawna's profile and I clicked on this and well, this looks better so Im going to see how this works out for me  Yesterday I went for a run, then I threw the ball around with my Dad, I just realied Im not that bad of pitcher, I just need to work on some stuff. Then Ive been obsessed with twrilling the flag so I was out there for a couple hours even before Colorguard practice. Then I talked to Carl for like 2 minutes, and he had this band practice to go to and I had my colorguard stuff to go to. Mary and Nina werent there but I was ok with it because Katie's sister Keri and I get along well and Sarah Paret's sister is just as nice so I basically hung out with them for a bit. Melissa is sooo funny, she took the hoop and started pretending to hit Jason D. with it! I thought that was hilarious seriously. Um I realized Im really a slow learner through this cologrguard thing. Im getting better I promise!  Today, I cant even lift up my arm ouch, wow I think I overdid it lol  Hope you Guys enjoyed my first blog 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>