<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Due to the mind numbing character of my job, I have been doing a "low level" job search of sorts. I have basically been semi-randomly bombarding companies with my resume. What happens when you semi-randomly drop a resume on companies? You get call-backs by people about jobs you swear you never applied for in the first place. This happened to me last week. I get a call from a person wanting to schedule a phone interview for a position of assistant trader. I agreed, since I was vaguely looking for jobs in the financial field, but do not remember having applied for any sort of assistant trader position. In any case, the guy calls me back on Friday, at the agreed phone interview time, and says that he wants to ask me some basic math questions, like addition and subtraction. Fine. He also kindly asks if I could not use a calculator or pen and paper as he wants to test how well and quickly I can do calculations in my head. Fuck me. I answer his first 4 questions promptly and without error. Good, I'm a little more relaxed now. The fifth question is "what is 133 minus 261?". I err and answer "-118" (the correct answer is -128, in my mind not a terrible mistake). At that point, the guy makes a deep sigh and says: "I'm sorry. If we continue, this will be sheer torture for you. I'm sorry to have wasted your time." Click. Since when did being an ASSISTANT trader involve having ridiculous, infallible mental math skills? 
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the time has finally come for me to snap out of my perma-laziness and join the hordes of would be "bloggers". Not so long ago I ridiculed my friends that latched on to this, what I considered, fad. However, I have to say that I'm quite flexible when it comes to ideas (OK, OK, I'm a flake, I admit it) so here I am. Please note that since I'm still perma-lazy that my musings and speculations will probably be RARE by any real "blogger" standard. I will never be able to approach the prolific output of  urlLink Showalter's Politics  or the jibber-jabber of  urlLink Dockgoose  but might be more on par with the meditations of  urlLink Kriegsmarine , perhaps even surpassing the output of  urlLink Kriegsmarine . In fact I might be more active on other people's postings than my own. Also note that I will not limit my talk to any certain subject. Although I might opt to be more political here, I will also present you with irrelevant snippets of speculation on everything. OK, I'm already getting bored with writing this so I'm going to cut it short here. Not sure when I'll update again but it will definitely be sometime this week. Ciao, kids 
    
</post>


</Blog>