<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As senior year approaches, I've been thinking a lot about how I stack up against my peers in terms of maturity.  Its hard to say where I stand because in certain areas it seems like I'm ahead of the game but, as I'm my own worst critic, I know that deep down I'm a kid.  Not all that kid at heart kind of crap.  I'm a kid.  As you know from my profile and previous posts, I very much enjoy playground games like dodgeball and kickball.  That's okay. you may say, those are actually becoming hip again.  No, I think I like them at a different level than the twentysomethings who have founded those leagues.  To illustrate my point, I will tell you, the faceless and nameless, that I still am tempted to buy G.I. Joes.  Very tempted.  When I was at Target reserving my limited edition of Halo 2 as I said yesterday, I wandered done the toy aisle.  Not to reminisce.  To see what they had in the way of my favorite action figures.  I was pleasantly surprised.  Besides vehicles, they had figures in two packs for seven bucks and three packs for nine.  There was a Cobra three pack and I probably would have bought it if I didn't already have the Cobra Commander.  I pulled myself away with my last vestige of dignity (I was admiring them alongside a six-year-old) and left to find my mom and youngest brother.  But today, at Fred Meyer's it came at me again.  I even avoided the toy department in fear of another test of willpower, but Satan had other plans.  Browsing the school supplies, waiting for my the same brother, I spied a discount table.  Bored, I went over to it.  There was my second temptation.  A Cobra plane.  That converted to a hydrofoil.  On sale.  As I have neither a plane or boat for the bad guys, this almost proved to great for me to overcome.  But after almost three minutes of indecision, I somehow stopped myself and left.  But I fear the third temptation, my friends.  Even as I write this I am choking down regret that I did not purchase these infantile delights.  I am growing weak.  I fear I cannot leave the house lest I revert back to my seven year old self.  And the rationalizer in my wants to ask you, am I so wrong?  Is what I desire so bad? Tell me your opinion of my plight, dear reader.  I feel so alone.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I realized today that I am an addict to Minesweeper. How did I realize this, when it's so hard for addicts to admit their problems? Even addicts have to admit that one is addicted when one sees the little Minesweeper numbers even when one has his/her eyes closed and is not looking at a computer screen.  Yes, it is painful for me to say, especially here among such esteemed colleagues, but perhaps ridicule is the medicine I need to help me stay on the road to recovery.  And while I think about it, there are worse addictions...like to narcotics, opiates, hallucinogens, inhalents, Altoids, bad music, Fabio, toasters, etc.  That's my news for the moment. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and there was something strangely refreshing about it.  I think that just like the green leafy things that grow around my house, we all need a little water to fall on us and soak us sometimes.  Not that we'd die without it, but then, those plants won't die either.  But just that it helps us to reach a higher plane of health, some plateu from which we can stand and scream into the gray falling skys "I am alive!  I am alive!  I may be soaking wet, but I am alive!" before we realize the entire church is now staring at us. A weird thing about rain is how much it changes things.  I mean, its just a little bit of water, right?  We drink tons of water every day.  But once a tad bit of it starts falling on us, people totally freak out.  They drive really slowly, they run around screaming as they fail to locate their cars, they fight over strange little sticks with canvas, and some of them even curse loudly as their attached furry headcovering are drenched through.  (Something about messing up their style.  I fail to grasp it.)  People who would normally be quite glad to lay on a hillside with me and chat the day away are now flabbergasted at the suggestion.  What's their problem, anyways?  We're 80% water to begin with...how's a little more gonna hurt?  The most depressing thing about rain, though (well, the only depressing thing about rain) is that it covers up the stars.  My nightly glimpses into the black and starlit heavens has been a favorite time of mine to contemplate how truely insignificant that little peon is who decided to cut me off today and ended up almost causing a major accident.  After all, what does it really matter if i jumped out of my speeding hunk of metal, holding another peice of metal alloy, and began hitting both a large bit of metal and some carbon based object that was significantly softer than the large hunk of metal?  It really doesn't, does it?  Its times like these when I can convince myself that perhaps those other bits of carbon carrying much smaller peices of metal will agree with me and decided not to use their peices of metal to embed even smaller peices of metal into my carbon.  I find this view extremely relaxing.  But without the stars, its utterly impossible to obtain.  I did decide on the rules to my new sport, though.  Its called "Shirt Basketball".  Dunks (anything involving contact between either of your hands/digits and any part of the target) are worth one point.  This includes shots where you pull the shirt away from the target's body in order to make the shot possible.  Free Throws, shots where the target intentionally invites a shot after stopping and pulling their own shirt forward to enable the shot to be made, are also worth one point, unless they are made from four point distance, in which case it is worth three.  Here's where things get tricky.  Because of the wide variety of shirts worn by various targets, and differing amounts of room between said shirt and the target (caused by non-standard shirt types, larger-than-average amounts of cleavage, skintight verse baggy shirts, etc.) the points differ based on both difficulty and distance.  Standard scoring works as such: within five feet of the target is worth two points.  Outside of five feet is worth four.  Mulitpliers are added based on the difficulty of the shot.  Contestants determine the value of each target (and their attached shirt) before competition begins.  Both must agree on the value before taking a shot.  In the event a shot is made before a value is agreed upon, an arbitrary third party is asked to set a fair value.  When lacking a third party, the opponent is allowed to pick a fair value.  The maximum multiplier for normal circumstances is ten times the normal point value, with the rare exception of a shot being made on a target wearing only a bra (or appropriate equivelent) which garners a twentyfive times bonus, and a shot made on a completely bare target, which garners a hunderd times bonus along with a wack across the back of the head for being dumb enough to waste such a valuable opportunity.  Additional multipliers are added based on circumstances, such as backwards, no look (eyes shut), hook shots, off hand shots, using an unusual object (such as a computer monitor), using a difficult object (something that doesn't easily fit, also like a computer monitor or even something simpler like a basketball), using an awkward object (ice that the target cannot easily retreive), cauing the target to remove clothing to fetch the object, and evoking a positive reaction from the target (such as an invitation to retireve the object yourself).  Points are lost for injuring the object, evoking a negative reaction (such as a bitch slap or forced removal from a house or resteraunt), or shooting on a target in a dangerous situation (such as the driver of a vehicle).  It is also not reccomended to shoot on targets with which one is not familiar, or which one is not signifantly faster than.  I predict Shirt Basketball will make it to the Olympics by 2020.  Only you, my valiant readers can help make this dream a reality.  Go forth and throw things down shirts, men!  Do it for justice, for honor, and for the American Dream: to earn money without doing any real work!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm starting a weekly column here.  I'll call it Ben Questions the Billions. Question 1: Is the only difference between a cult and a religion numerical? 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just reserved Halo 2.  Supposed to be out November 9th.  Hopefully by then I'll be all done with college applications because I'm pretty sure I'm doing early action (or decision I don't know which is the non-binding one) at every place I apply.  Then I will have time to play the most anticipated game of alltime.  In other news, all the horsemen and assorted other cool kids from Jesuit went to Pioneer Courthouse Square to see The Goonies yesterday.  Turnout was great, the crowd ran the gamut from the hiphop crowd to goths.  All united by loving the phrase "hey you guys."  Proving The Goonies is one of the greatest movies of alltime.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            The four horsemen are assembled and the charge will begin.  The charge to retake the internet from the disgusting hands of the pornographers and return to where it rightfully belongs, the hands of teenage boys.  Beginning today, the horsemen will begin the most difficult, the most dangerous task ever placed upon any humans in history of mankind.  We will build up our readership, convincing people worldwide that our blog is more interesting than porn.  They will fight us, sending hitwomen with huge breasts after us (they will be easy to spot, beautiful women don't associate with the horsemen), but we will persevere.  One day, one glorious day, our site will have more visitors than all the porn in all the world.  Impossible, you say.  We don't listen to such words here.  We horsemen believe in the the green light, the orgastic future that year by year recedes before us.  It eluded us then, but that's no matter--  Tomorrow we will run faster, stretch out our arms farther....  And one fine morning---        So we beat on, boats against the current borne back ceaselessly into the past.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So this morning, I kinda forgot that I had no football today.  Which isn't very surpising, since I have it like every day except sunday for the next 80 months.  Or something.  But so I not only forgot that I had no football, but also forgot what time the football I didn't have was at.  This was an unbearable state of affairs, I assure you.  I attempted a mad dash up the stairs only to be brought startlingly short by the fact that my legs didn't want to listen to me.  They decided to listen to someone else, someone completely unrelated to me and also quite invisible, who told them their time would be much better spent by spasming out.  After all, what legs wouldn't want to just sorta quiver on the floor instead of actually sprinting?   This bodily mutany forced me to rely upon my trusty (and much more loyal) arms for my transportation out of my basement lair.  All went well until I came to the door.  Ever tried opening a door at the top of some stairs without being able to use your legs?  It was quite tricky...in the end, I propped myself against it, leaned hard, then managed to stroke the handle enough for it to somehow pop open.  Victory at last!   But with only one small problem...my football schedule is on the fridge.  High up on the fridge.  At what is normally eye level for my towering 6'2" frame.  Having your eyes reduced to midgethood (at only 6" off the ground, I was small even for one of the little people) makes it rather difficult to read things on the fridge 6 feet above your head.  Well, reading things 6 feet above your head on the fridge when they were made in point 12 font is always hard, its just most people don't have 12 foot fridges with football schedules on them, so I don't run into this problem every day.  Again, my brilliant mind came to the rescue.  STOOLS!  No, not the kind you leave in the toilette or some turncoat mafia member (both of which have about the same smell, slimy skin, and high value on the street) but the wooden kind you normally would perch upon to dine at my luxerious countertop in the kitchen.  With two of them placed the appropriate distance apart, I was easily able to lift myself up onto a sitting position upon a third.  It was kinda like doing a really monsterous dip, only with dogs staring in shock and my legs still doing their own little dance.  From this high and mighty vantage point I was shocked to assertain that practice had started a good hour ago.  But wait, my mind screamed, today could not be the 23rd!  It simply couldn't!  I hadn't watched Casablanca yet, and I absolutely knew it was due by the 23rd!  Faced with this cold, unforgiving logic, my brain was forced to admit, that no, today probably wasn't the 23rd.  Furthermore, the phoney thing clearly said it was the 20th.  But that couldn't be either, could it?  There was no football practice on the 20th...and if there was no practice, there was no reason for my legs to be so badly misbehaving, nor for me to have to crawl upstairs to check when practice started.     At this point, my legs decided the invisible stranger had led them astray from the True Path which is a body part's only real hope to enter the Divine Heaven that is Sitting On A Lazy Boy With A Giant Glass Of Iced Lemonade Watching Bond Movie And Eating Ribs.  Of course, my legs have never (and if I have any say in it, WILL never) eaten a rib, drunk lemonade, or even seen James Bond.  However, they understand that this is a blissful state, and they certainly enjoy sitting in a Lazy Boy more than running.  This leads them to beleive that this Divine Heaven must be a nice place to be, and hey, everyone else seems excited about it, so why shouldn't they? This allowed me to return my arms to their normal role of hanging at my sides and occasionally turning doornobs and reaching for remotes and lightswitches.  I decided the ordeal meant my entire body deserved a dip in the Semi-Divine Heaven that is a Warm Bath With Lots Of Bubbles And Soothing Music And Smelling Salts.  Though I was pretty sure I was out of smelling salts, I figured I could fake my nose out with with some fragrant bubble stuff.  Or maybe a nice candle.  I again had to face a flight of stairs to obtain my goal, but for this one I could asend as humans do, and not the humans who have paralyzing back injuries and no elevators or kind people to carry them.  However, as I walked past my front door, I looked out the window.  Through that window, I could see inside my car.  And through that window letting me see inside my car, I could see throught the window going out of my car.  And throught that window going out of my car I could see into my neighbor's window across the street.  And through THAT window across the street I beheld a strange sight indeed.   For my 19 year old blonde streetmate was dancing some sort of weird macarana-like dance.  And here I thought she'd already left for college, or at least moved in with some 24 year old hippie.  Wow.  People really should shut their blinds once in a while.  I'm not one to talk, though.  There are no blinds on the glass door in my basement.  And I love dancing around in my skivies down there.  But no one's dumb enough to risk peering through MY windows.  Are they?
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    But what *did* they want? 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Could my fellow horsemen copy some of my interests? I keep clicking them and realizing that I'm alone... so alone...  Don't tell me you don't like a good hunk of man-liver every once in a while. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      which took more guts than it really should've.  See, usually I think of myself as someone who's not afraid of anything--who'll try anything once as long as there's a reasonable chance of survival.  (It's not that I'm AFRAID of dying, it's more that I don't want to inconvenience God by making Him resurrect me so I can be Ultimate King of All That Surrounds Me.)  Anyway, I call, heart beating audibly.  Ring... ring... then, "...WHAT?"  In this age of caller ID, what can I conclude but that I really, really pissed her off, just by calling?  But I pretend that all is not lost.  "Uh, hey there!  How's it going?"  And it isn't!  "OH! Ken! Sorry, I thought you were my mom!"  Hmmmmm.  One more reason to earn that manly Eagle Scout award.  If this supernatural maternal reminder didn't happen so often, it wouldn't bother me that much, but...  I mean, I wasn't even planning on being a stay-at-home DAD, let alone Mom.  But it's okay.  Now I'm waiting for her to call back, thinking, "Hey, it could have gone worse," then asking myself, "Why do you even care?"  Honestly, I don't know.  Just don't know.  School hasn't started yet and I haven't seen her for over two months.  Shouldn't that have been cathartic?  So far it's been as cathartic as being anally probed by extraterrestrials that only measure the charge capacity of your nether regions--with a cattle prod.  BZZZZZZT!  Every day.  That prod doesn't even fit (please don't think about that).  And I'm left where I used to be--thinking, "boy, I wish I was over this," and then thinking, "wait, no, what I really want is for everything to work out," and then, "man, I could really use some kind of legal nerve stimulant so I can stop being tired all the time."  Hey, as long as it's not a cattle prod.  It might damage the cell phone--and then how would she call back? 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The anticipation for Ken's first post is killing me.  If you've read his "about me" you know its going to fucking rock.  I'm sure he's putting the finishing touches on it as I type.  Meanwhile, John participating in conditioning week for football, so we're going to give his absence the benefit of the doubt.  So it looks like Miguel is the only horseman who pulled through for me.  He did a great job; I can't wait for another post.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a shout out to our only reader, Shakeer.  Without him the blog would be 89% worse.  If you are offended because you also read this blog and you want a shout out, leave a damn comment once and a while.  I know its only been six days, but I was counting on the million monkeys on a million computers thing.  And its been a big disappointment.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the last two weeks I have really been looking forward to this weekend because there is a dodgeball tournament at a high school near my house.  Dodgeball is my favorite sport and I was brimming with anticipation over assembling and leading a team of friends into such a glorious competition.  As I was ironing out the details I clicked on the waiver because I had to read it.  No one over 18.  I am 18 in less than a month.  Their unequitable line in the sand crushed my soul, telling me I am not worthy to play in their league. I'll tell you what.  They will rue the day they excluded me.  I will train harder than anyone has ever trained for anything.  I will make Rocky's training in Siberia in Rocky IV seem like a walk in the park.  And next year, when they come back to Portland from their pansy headquarters in Los Angeles, I will tear the Beaver Ball trophy from their well moistuized hands and my triumph will be sung throughout the ages by all people of all walks of life who need the inspiration of heroes to continue their own heroic existence.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would normally put this in the comments section, but my esteemed colleague forgot to utilize that tool.  From my brief study of Sigmund Freud, I have formulated a belief that the real object of the punk anger is their small genitalia.  Besides the obvious implications that go with that territoty there is also a reduced testosterone level which prevents said punks from being successful at manly endeavors such as sports.  This coupled with their subpar intelligence leaves them little option but "reject" the society that in fact rejected them first.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me being me, take my posts with a grain of salt. I do not mean to offend. Most people.  It pisses me off how many people are posers and cannot accept it. I'm a poser. I live with this knowledge. I consider it one of the many marks that I, too, am human and possess original sin. But I suffer through the insufficiency. But man, some people...  For instance, it has come to my attention that to be a punk you must fulfill a minimum three requirements:  1) Be angry. It doesn't matter what you're angry at. But you must have a perpetual simmering rage in the bowels of your soul, stewing and propelling you to speak out. Express your anger with everyone, from the people who you deem responsible to the random passerby who will raise an eyebrow and probably regard you with disdain. Note that this in turn will make you angry at the random passerby as well, because they're only kindling the source of your anger. The source of your anger does not matter. It can change at any time for any reason if necessary to keep it going...or just because you feel like it.  2) Be ugly. It is vital to the punk mindset to go against everything that is natural to the human body. Dying one's hair many colors one cannot find in any of the nooks and crannies of nature is heartily recommended. Do this frequently. Also, dessacrate the human body as much as possible with tatooes spreading across from the tips of your fingers to the small of your back to the metatarsal area. Oh, not to mention body piercings. How better to express the anger you have against your father, your life, the Man, the cat next door, and your personal hygiene appliances than by showing that you don't care what they think? And body piercings are a great way to do that. Pierce several parts of your body, be creative, and remember: if you don't go through the metal detectors at least five times, you are not carrying enough representation of your flesh mutilation.  3) This one kind of leads into the other two. Be rebellious. As with anger, it does not matter. Do not accept anything except your own beliefs to be true. Your beliefs consist of everyone else being judgmental. And that life is unfair. You should never conform. Ever. In fact, if you are reading this now, you are submitting to corporate America by paying your electric bill or even just using a computer. Dell is laughing at you, and dead punk artists are rolling in their graves.  Very few self-proclaimed "punks" have ever really fulfilled these requirements. ...     The actual point of this post was that I hate Good Charlotte, who whines about everything in life even though they have millions of dollars, are now LIVING the lifestyles of the rich and the famous, whine about not wanting a 9-5 and how the lead singer's dad is an asshole in approximately 40 of their 41 songs....yeah.  Sorry to bash on Good Charlotte fans...but if that last paragraph offended you, bite me.  Actually, the only people I hold in any remote form of disdain are the actual hardcore punks. Granted I shouldn't judge folks before I know them...but always being wrong is kind of a deterrent from talking to people.  So in reality, I like posers more.  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As you can see, Ken has joined and Mike and John will soon follow.  And a golden age will begin.  We will turn a corner.  We will believe in science.  We'll work just as hard for your jobs as we work for our own.  Terrorism will lose and we will win because the future doesn't belong to fear, it belongs to hope.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This blog has had technical difficulties for the past few days, but they are now sorted out so we shall soon have two of the three new bloggers posting.  Which brings me to reveal something to you.  Why, you may ask, did this moron post by himself on this blog until he had it all figured out?  It seems like the gimmick is that there are four equally important bloggers and by doing this he just created an antipathy towards him by posting subpar material.  Well you would be correct.  I am a dumbass.  I wanted to have a few posts grounded in to assert my feeble personality before my friends amaze you with theirs.  I envisioned my posts as something endearing, like watching a newborn foal struggling to walk.  But it was probably just pathetic, like a foal born with three legs struggling to walk, while you know it never will.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A short public service announcent.  Coming back from a short campout and reviewing this blog and another that I frequent, I realized that the title of my last post is the same as the other blog's only I added an exclamation point.  I am certain that I subconsciously stole it.  I feel like scum.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently got a brand new kickball.  I bought one from Target about two weeks ago.  I really liked it.  My brother and I took it in the street in front of my house.  He pitched it to me.  I kicked it farther than I have ever kicked a kickball in my life.  Once we retrieved it I decided to be safe, take it inside, and wait until my next kickball game to experience the ecstasy of kicking this ball.  But wait.  My brother was inside our yard.  I decided to see how far it would drop kick.  Enormous mistake.  I am not a good drop kicker under the best of circumstances and here I was trying to kick super hard.  The kick sucked and it rolled right into my neighbor's only rose bush.  A terrible thing.  Now, I know there are a lot of awful things in our world, things a billion times worse than losing a stupid kickball.  But, since I do not possess an incredible emotional maturity, I mourned its passing.  This mopiness lasted a week.  The day we were set to go camping (which I did not want to do), I was surprised by a new ball.  A better ball.  One that came in a box like a basketball.  And cost twice as much.  It is a wonderful ball.  I love it.  Don't judge me.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
               Not about the music.  About the politics.  Shame on me but I have to write this while its still fresh in my mind.  I went to the Kerry rally at Waterfront Park.  I downloaded the tickets last night and went with my dad this morning.  The gates opened at 10:00 and he was supposed to arrive about 12:15 so I figured I would get there at about 10:30, wait at the gate, and do a crossword for two hours.  I knew a lot of people would be there, but I was not prepared for this.  We got there on schedule but there were lines everywhere.  We were at the back of a line the stretched for at least a quarter mile.  I thought it must be for people who didn't have real tickets.  (If you haven't figured out by now, I'm a dumbass.)  So we crossed the street and found a much shorter line but which turned out to be for vets.  When we got back to the original line, the end was on the opposite side of the builiding we were at originally.            While waiting there were dozens of solicitors for various causes.  And protesters.  But not very many.  A couple of guys had the usual Jesus Saves From Hell stuff and were telling us to repent from our wicked ways.  One was a real loudmouth and said some of the most stupid but funniest things I have ever heard.  One particularly trifecta of irony was the fact that his sign said Bush defends America and had pictures of various military icons, then he said Bush was intelligent enough to stay out of Vietnam, just like him (the speaker), and then he went on to talk about how they were both manly men and thats why liberal women didn't like them.  After this an astute citizen asked him if he knew Bush was a cheerleader in college.  Silence.  Then he said "Really?"  Everyone said yes and then the moron mumbled that he wasn't really into politics.  He was a goldmine.          It took about an hour and a half to go the quarter mile and by the time we were at the verge of the security checkpoint the police decided that the remaining thousands would be so far away they couldn't do anything even if they wanted to.  They didn't even check the tickets.  We ended up, after a fire marshal fence was torn down, about three football fields away from the stage and Jon Bon Jovi.  He was okay, had a lot of emotion and some intelligent things to say.  Then the usual lame people that nobody cares about started talking and it got really boring until six buses came off the bridge behind us and drove to the side of the rally.  Everyone got really excited but nothing happened.  More talking.  Then three (more?) buses drove by and the buzz was back.  Finally, squinting I could see him emerge on stage.  He shook hands, reminding the unlucky majority of the over 30,000 how far away we were.  Then his wife spoke.  For a long time.  She was nice but spoke slowly, almost casually and kind of repeat repeated herself.  Then Jim Rassman came on and was pretty good.  But the crowd was yearning for Kerry.  And he delivered.  And it wasn't just his acceptance speech from the convention.  He had particulars.  Plans that made a lot of sense.  It was great.  Unfortunately I had to leave early to get to work.  I only missed about 3 minutes.  I'm glad I went.  I'm sorry that was so long.  Believe it or not, but it was edited for length.  I left a lot of good stuff out. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The free iTunes song this week is good.  Good enough to make you download iTunes if you don't already have it.  An Irish guy under the pseudonym Simple Kid.  I heard him on some late night show a long time ago but I can't remember which.  Anyway, I like it.  He might be huge later and you will want to have said you heard him when he was a small fry.  His first CD is coming out soon.  So tell me either way.  If there's anybody out there.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Spock would be a Democrat.  I am not a Trekkie but I have seen a few episodes and movies and the phrase "The needs of the many outweigh the needs of the few." stuck out in my liberal mind.  Republicans believe in individual responsibility, and I am all for that, but a society like ours will always have people who for a myriad of reasons cannot support themselves without considerable help.  And if that requires taxing the billionaire citizens of our country (there are more than you think) a few percentage points more, than Spock and I would say it is the right thing for us and the exorbitantly wealthy to do.    No more political articles for a week.  I apologize.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just writing to explain the title. Once I figure out how to do it, three of my friend will join the blog.  I promise they are more interesting then I am.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is not your father's blog.  (I have yet to impregnate anyone, so don't come to me trying to get child support for your sorry ass.)  This blog will usher in a new day.  A day of sincere, honest, and powerful writing.  Writing of real people, for real people, and by real people.  Or it will suck and wallow in the mediocrity of almost every other blog out there.  But you can only find out if you read it.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>