<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I am going to a baby shower. For many young girls my age, this inspires glee and tidings of joy. Me...I would rather clean my toilet. Don't get me wrong. I am ecstatic for the parents and their new bundle of joy, and in this case, I haven't even seen this friend since she developed a plump appendage around her middle, but I just don't like baby showers. In fact, I don't really like babies too much. I love kids. Hey, I'm a teacher. But babies are a different story. In fact, I've always told my friends that I would like to adopt a two or three year old someday and just bypass the baby stage. I know that many of you are thinking that I am cold-hearted or quite insensitive, but really, I'm just telling you the straight and honest truth. I will enjoy myself today and love hearing stories about the newly decorated nursery and possible names, but I am not looking forward to sticking my head in a diaper to figure out what candy bar someone smashed inside of it, or wrapping the mother in toilet paper to guess the diameter of her stomach. I will enjoy the fellowship and sharing in the excitement of a blessing, a miracle from God, but don't ask me to participate in the antics, or speak in baby talk when the little guy/gal arrives. I'll pass on that. Send me a picture, I'll come and visit, but don't call me to babysit until the kid is potty-trained. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A Day on the Farm&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       About four days ago, the air conditioning in my classroom went out. This would not have been such a problem if there weren't 130 kids who go through my classroom each day. Take humidity, 80 plus degree temperatures, and then add 130 sweaty 8th graders. Not a good scenario. Today though, I entered the school to find the heating and cooling guy working feverishly on my unit. After various noises, smells, and flames, the a/c seems to be in working condition. In other news, I get a new cell phone today. It should be arriving at my doorstep around 4:30pm or so says the FedEx tracking service. I was in need of a new phone very badly. The other day the phone was on but the screen went blank. All I could make out was the battery meter in the right hand corner. I swear I never dropped this thing in the swimming pool.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Although I usually don't like to jump on the band-wagon with new trends, I have found something that strikes my fancy...that being a blog.  I have told myself that I will experiment with this new found technology and see what this blogging thing is all about. Hey, the cool kids are doing it. We'll see what happens.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>