<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So this weekend I bought a new tv for my bedroom so I could watch dvds in bed.  Which was what I basically did all day Sunday.  The new tv is a Toshiba, 14", flat screen, and I got it at Best Buy (it looks like this  urlLink http://www.bestbuy.com/site/olspage.jsp?type=product&id=1074787382974&amp;skuId=6304894  except mine cost less than this) Anyway, my little shopping trip got me thinking about how I am totally gullible and trusting of salespeople in Best Buy.  They could tell me that the tv i am purchasing would somehow generate enough energy to cool down my entire apartment (and as i don't have ac that would be heaven) and i'd probably believe them.  For instance, i was debating between the Toshiba and the RCA as the RCA was $20 cheaper.  So i asked, "is the RCA $20 less bc of it's brand name?  Am i essentially paying extra just to have the name Toshiba?"  So the guy tells me, "well, Toshiba puts more money into their parts, so therefore the TV lasts longer".  Now, that is, technically, a reason to pay more, but the guy could totally be making that up!  It's not like i asked him to show me statistical evidence that Toshibas last longer (and nor would i understand it if he showed it to me, i got a D+ in stat...thanks GW) and its not like i would ever attempt to call him on it - I would have no way of proving that he was wrong (nor would i want to waste the time, money, and resources on that experiment - i am far, far to busy umm...watching movies from my bed).  Apparently I was wrong, or rather  urlLink http://www.realitytvworld.com/  was wrong bc Britney and Kevin are not being tapped to take over newly weds, which is too bad bc that would have been hilarious.  I NEED daily documentation of Britney's downward spiral.  Incidentally, there is a funny little brief in this month's Rolling Stone (random tangent: when did tom cruise become such a crazy freak show?  He's telling people to fuck off bc they don't like scientology, but he won't talk about politics...uh...ok...yeah...keep filming Mission Impossible 3 - it's gonna do really well, i promise) where Brit and Kev go shopping for doo rags.  I'd link to it but i have issues figuring out how to get the little blurbs off of rollingstone.com and only seem able to link to large articles...sorry... Also, one of my roommates owns  urlLink http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0299591/  - which i watched selected scenes of.   My favorite part of the concert included the remix of "hit me baby one more time" bc Brit had a "thunderstorm" going on while she sang it, and she was dressed in jeans, a bejeweled boustiee, and a clear plastic cowboy hat (the hat was so her hair didn't get wet) - at the end of the song (this was the finale btw) she takes off the hat and stands under this jet of water getting completely soaked, and looking for all the world like some wannabee Jennifer Beals (yes i know that wasn't really J.B. dancing but do you remember the other woman's name? sigh...flashdance may be where i get my misguided idea that being a stripper wouldn't be so bad).  The second best part was during the "Slave for you" number (which was jungle-themed) bc at the end Brit actually pole dances (and awkward pole dancing is hilarious!).  It was at that exact moment that i finally understood why the mothers of 12 year old girls were put-off by the fact that brit wasn't the world's best role model.  As this concert took place prior to the Justin break-up (seriously...why would you EVER cheat on Justin?) Brit isn't entirely off the deep end yet, but the signs are there...oh, they're there...  Being from MA, i am interested in most things Kennedy, especially Ted Kennedy, ever since i was a wee lass and found out about Chappaquidick.  For those of you unaware, here is the short version: Ted, possibly drunk (but everyone KNOWS he was wasted), drove OFF A BRIDGE and ended up in the Chappaquidick River.  Fortunately, Ted survived, unfortunately the young, (i'd imagine buxom) woman who was not his wife, but in the passenger seat of his car did not.  Instead of going to jail, Ted became a senator.  Anyway, Ted is making headlines again  urlLink http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A17073-2004Aug19.html , this time, bc a terrorist is using the alias T. Kennedy...and this has slowed down Ted's commute time.  No news article of the day today - nothing is really heads above the competition...plus, it's monday, and i'm not awake yet, despite having been up for 4 1/2 hours now.     
     

        
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ok...so I live in DC and it's impossible to live in DC and not get caugh up in all the election stuff.  I'm a registered Democrat but only bc you can't register as an Independent in DC - you have to choose Republican or Democrat - how f-ed up is that?  Well, at least we can vote in the presidential election now, though the fact that our representative can't vote in ANYTHING is ridiculous...TAXATION WITHOUT REPRESENTATION!  Anyway, Kerry finally has taken a stand a la Kirstin Dunst and put his foot down re: the Swift Boat people who are questioning his military service.  "In his toughest response yet to questions of whether he deserved the honors he won in war, Kerry said if the president wanted to debate the issue of their respective battle records then "Bring it on.""  urlLink http://aolsvc.news.aol.com/news/article.adp?id=20040819205709990011  Even though i blatantly am anti-Bush i really thing the Republicans have stooped to a new low on this one.  Especially since Bush's military records just 'happened to be destroyed'.  In other political news the Republican National Convention is freaking out bc Anarchists are planning on protesting.  While I've never been a fan of anarchy in general (who wants to live in a world of chaos?) I really have to hand it to the Republicans for their attempt to dissuede the protesters by  offering free coupons  as a protest detterent.  i don't know but when a completely anti-capitalist, anti-establishment group is theatening you, i definatly think 1/2 off a Starbucks latte is the answer don't you?   urlLink http://aolsvc.news.aol.com/elections/article.adp?id=20040820071909990001   The other awesome part of this article is the quotes from the police.  "At the end of the day there is too much information,'' he said. "You need be able to decipher the wheat from the chaff and it is not clear. You can't overreact to the Internet because it can be a 16-year-old kid in Chicago mouthing off.'' And also: "We're taking the wheat as wheat,'' he said, adding that the threat posed by anarchists "is nothing the N.Y.P.D. can't handle.''  Talk about extending a metaphor too far.  News Story of the Day: submitted by my friend Stephen - All i have to say is 2 word "vodka vaporizor".  The rest of the article speaks for itself  urlLink http://www.nydailynews.com/front/story/224056p-192414c.html   Happy Friday to all - i am planning on getting wasted in Georgetown where i will make fun of college freshman getting their ids taken.  Hopefully also making a "connection" with my friend James' single guy friends.  One can only dream...   
     

        
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hey, this is my first entry. Exciting.  Basically I've decided to do this as a way to post links and stuff I'm thinking about that doesn't relate to my social life (ok, maybe some social life). The impetous for this came about bc for the past three days I have been searching for interesting/funny blogs to read and all the good ones I find are of people still in college. Which makes me feel old bc i am no longer in college (though I oftentimes like to imagine I still am...how else to explain the binge drinking?) and have to pay my own bills and go to work everyday. So I decided that instead of reading about all this fun I used to be having I would write about the experiences that I am currently having now, as a 23 year old, single female living in Washington, DC. And also bc my friend Aarron ( urlLink http://aaronmiller.blogspot.com/ ) has one of these and it was free.  So lately I've been watching a lot of the olympics. Mostly the swimming, bc it takes me back to my lifeguarding days when my fellow female guards and I used to watch this male guard Chris, swim laps on our breaks and talk about how hot...i mean, good at the butterfly he was. In much the same vein my gfs and I have decided that Michael Phelps has an amazing body, but an ugly face. On the other hand the Australian, Ian Thorpe aka "the thorpedo" wins extra points for a hot accent. All this being said, my fav. moment of the Olympics thus far was seeing the women's freestroke relay team kick major ass and break the world record last night. Natalie Coughlin, i salute you.  Another note re: Michael Phelps - i noticed that Mike (does he like being called Mike, who knows?) is always listening to something in his headphones prior to competing. I remarked, rather innocently to my roommate that i wondered what he was listening to - as if hearing my mental pleas for Mike's playlist, nbc commentators announced, to download Michael Phelps' playlist go to nbc.com and click on the Olympic athlete bios. So i went to NBC.com and found the athlete bios and i also found that you have to PAY to get Mike's (or any other athlete's for that matter) playlist, and that you can't even see what songs are on it until you buy it. Aside from the three they mentioned which are Usher (which i already own), OutKast (which i own but has kinda been driven into the ground - thanks dj of every bar i've ever been to), and Twista (while I do like that song "Celebrity" specifically bc of the part where Twista says, 'lemme be your manager' - it's so ridiculous and awesome - this is all i really know about the rapper). So basically, i'm going to give a big thumbs down to NBC for being too goddamn corporate to list songs. You can view capitalism at work here:  urlLink http://www.nbcolympics.com/phelps/5009163/detail.html   I just found out that my boss is going to sell me her old vcr and stereo for like, $30 together which is awesome bc I've been wondering what in hell i was going to do with the amount of vhs tapes i've accumulated over the years. Some of my friends have started replacing all of their vhs tapes with dvds one by one, but there are just some things i'm not willing to buy. For example, "Hoosiers"  urlLink http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0091217/  which has sentimental value as one of my best college guy friends bought it for me, or the various tapes i've 'inherited' over the years from roommates, ex boyfriends, etc. ("The Rock"  urlLink http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0117500/ , i'm looking at you). Do other people have this problem? i never thought i was much of a pack rat but apparently when it comes to audio and vhs tapes i just can't let go. And besides, i NEED that Debbie Gibson "Out of the Blue" as proof that yes, she is indeed way better than Tiffany any day.  urlLink http://www.allmusic.com/cg/amg.dll?p=amg&amp;sql=Bu2jm7i5jg76r    News Story of the Day:  (i'm going to try to post something like this every time, some may be funny, some serious). Britney Spears has been tapped (along with her white trash boy toy Kevin Federline) to host the next newly weds. My favorite part of this whole thing is that she's doing this so that Kevin can be "as famous as she is". Perhaps she and Kevin should have a chat with Nick Lachey before they sign any contracts.  urlLink http://www.realitytvworld.com/index/articles/story.php?s=2838   
     

        
</post>


</Blog>