<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Okay, for me this day is officially boring... OFFICIALLY BORING. Had it not been for the brilliance of our Philosophy professor, Dr. Co, I would have got out a lot earlier. At last I got a puncher. I just bought one off from Nat'l Bookstore in Recto. The walk, if you call it that (I would have referred to it as a pilgrimage ^_^ ), is really long and tiring. I bumped into two of my former classmates from highschool, they're from FEU by the way, and the other one really seemed like she was bumped(or maybe just surprised to see me again ^_^). There's a lot of things going on right now. There's our report, Pheobe's pending drawings that I need to make into a Flash Movie, my Philosophy Term Paper, there's also that unfinished Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire novel (that I borrowed from a classmate), the unfinished Queen of the Damned novel... i can't seem to get my hand around all this stuff. Time's awfully running faster than expected. Times like these I'm often reminded to get going a lot faster than usual. Zap! Gotta go!  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Haah... buong araw akong nag-computer kasi tinapos ko 'yung Flash namin sa Lit. ansakit na ng likod ko(!!!), not to mention, sumasakit na mata ko. What an exhausting day!!! Hanggang dito na lang siguro... bye! :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we had a practice for our Literature report. I woke up early only to find out that it's just 6 am or so. Anyways, I went back to bed and just woke up later. Before I depart from my extremely noisy home, I had to save the Matrix Flash that we're going to use in our report. I'll be showing it ot th guys later so they could have a glimpse of what the presentation i made would look like. When everything's fine and I'm ready to go, I just remembered that I had to buy extra art papaers that were going to use for the Lit. hand-outs. So off i went ot SM... When I bought the needed materials, I hurried across to the main road to get a ride. When bad luck strikes, bad luck STRIKES! The jeep that I was riding had to stop when I got inside because there were only two people, plus me, inside the jeep. When it started to run I felt okay, but it stopped for more than ten minutes just to get other passengers to ride it. It's really annoying coz I'm tryin' to hurry up.  When I got to Burger King, the announced meeting venue, both Phoebe and Jonet were there. Phoebe, she says, was early about an hour and half. Jonet, on the other hand, says she was early about an hour or so. Well... what can I do that freakin' jeep's a real loser? :) So I just bought my lunch and we headed on to Jewel's house by P. Florentino. When we got inside we started our little 'work'. Later on in the afternoon, when we were just rsting ourselves, Jonet found out that there were some missing details of the fiction in the hand outs. We can't do anything about it because we already have 45 copies of it photocopied. But juices came flowing inside our brainy brains and, ah... we did some ah... "editing". hehe! It was real work. Not feeling contented, I proposed that we finish everything that's needed to be done. Phobe also thought the same. So off we go compiling the hand-outs and the ahm... 'boards'. I and Phoebe were segragating the hand-outs, Jewel was punching two holes in them and Jonet was compiling them. We did real work! Teamwork! Teamwork! Hehe! Tiring, that's true, but it's fun nonetheless, not to mention the black stains that we have on our hands, that we got from holding the black art papers.  Later in the afternoon, we bid Jewel goodbye. And we bid ourselves goodbye to.  I went to SM NE to meet up wih my ex-girlfriend, going by the name of Katrina. We met up at Bearhuggs, says she's got to canvass some big(and she does mean big!)bear stuff toys. We chatted a little... his supposedly how th conversation started nd ended   She:  O, kanina ka pa?  Me:  Hindi (sarcastically)!  She:  O ano? Bakit ba kasi tayo nagkita?  Me:  Ah, ka punta muna tayong Bearhuggs 'di ba sabi mo magka-canvass ka? **We ent in and went around the store and exited, quickly.  She:  O ano ba kasi 'yon?  Me:  Ah, eh... may ibibigay ako sa iyo... (sabay hugot ng wallet)  She:  Ano 'yun?  Me:  Ito o... (sabay bukas ng isang parte ng wallet) 'yung binigay mong love-ltter dati.  She:  Ah ganun ba? (mukhang asar) **Lakad -lakad muna pagkatapos isilid sa bag ang letter  She:  (Parang na-asar talaga) "Wag mo sabihin sa aking mag-lilibot pa tayo?  Me:  Bakit? (Kunyari nangungulit na nangiti)  She:  Eh kasi naman po galing pa ako sa Proj. 2 'no? Anlalayo pa ng nilakad ko kanina... galing pa nga ako ng airport eh kasi hinatid 'yung lolo ko... tapos ako pa 'yung nag-bayad... binigay ko na lhat 'yung 1,700  Me:  one thousand seven hundred?  She:  Oo.  Me:  (kunyari interested sa sinabi) Huh? Eh bakit naman ikaw pa 'yung nag-bayad? Tsaka bakit binigay mo lahat?  She:  Eh kasi po, hindi ko binisita 'yung lolo ko kahit isang beses...  Me:  Oh pano sa'n ka na? (kasi gusto ko nang umalis)  She:  E pagod na ako, wala na rin akong pupuntahan kasi na-canvass ko na 'yung mga teddy bears... ikaw?  Me:  E ag-cacanvass ako ng mga cluth-bag... sa Human... (sabay turo sa papuntang Human)  She:  Ah o sig--  Me:  Ano ba-bye na?  She:  O sige-sige (galit 'to alam ko)...  Me:  Bye! Ingat! (sabay lakad palayo)  Ang totoo kung bakit ako nakipag-kita sa kanya, e dahil tatanungin ko siya kung baka pwede pa kami ulit. Ewan! She told m that I may ask her to meet with me anytime I want. She doesn't go to school right now because, she says, she was supposed to go to Canada but it didn't happened. So she's stuck here again and not going to classes. That love-letter i returned to her was her, I didn't want ot give back the othr one. Maybe, probably, she's angry with me because I asked her to meet up with me just so I can give her letter back. Haaaah.... Love, can't get my hand around it too well. :- 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       At long last i've got my own Blogspot! (hehe.. as if it's that hard to get an account) Today's an awfully stupid day. Woke up early and then slept again only to find out that I'm late for my class. I ended up missing two classes. So this means that I went to school only to attend one class. How stupid!  Were still working on our report for Literature on Thursday(next Thursday). There's something about that report that makes me quite nervous. I dunno... may be its just me. We will be taking the Matrix Theme as our concept. I hope we finish and succesfully deliver the report, I'm 'hoping' for the exemption on the finals examination. My grades on Literature  is  dismally low. If i should fail the finals exam, then it will be at my own risk. So I'm just 'hoping', nothing big.  I'm supposed to go to the Bb. QCA contest on my old school. Almost all of the alumni's at the school never fail to miss this kind of contest. It has been a tradition to select the Bb. QCA from the Third Year and the Fourth Year Classes. My former classmates wants to go, (actually I accidentally met one while riding an FX yesterday night). Andrew (si Lumasac) told me that the contest/pageant isn't today. Luckily I double checked on people. Hehe!  We had this extremely annoying essay-quiz on Journalism 201. I think I'll pass by luck on this one. ^_^        What I learned This Day:  Some people like to think about things that they think is right. It's quite annoying knowing that other people like to think about all they want to think about. (Labo!) It's quite hard even, to tell other people that what they think is wrong. Persons can be so stupid sometimes. It makes me think if they ever think about  themselves . You know, if they say this and that about another person then why can't they say this and that about themselves? It's like lying while doing another lie. Get it?   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>