<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing much happen this evening until Grace(Joan's sister) showed up. Had a really nice and fun conversation with her. Talk about lots of stuffs and asked her not to get too quiet with me. I would rather had her talking than just keeping quiet coz in my opinion, she has the vast potential to maintain a very good conversation. Hehe maybe she's shy and she needs the encouragement from people such as me? LOL okay okay, i know i'm being perasan here. Just joking okay?(Just in case you're reading, Grace haha). She told me she's really proud of Joan for being the Emcee for the Prefect lunch today and felt that she did really well in it. I would really love to see how good Joan is but too bad no chance, but oughta be good lar and congratulate her after she came online shortly. Compliment Joan about it but she say she kinda sucked at it. Nah, She's just being humble, i think she did really well although she didnt admit it LOL. Should have more confidence in yourself Joan coz i believe you have what it takes!  Talked to both of the Chong sisters, yeah not the Soong sisters by the way hahaha till 8 something and she send me one of the Planet Shakers song i've been longing to hear!! It's worthy to be praised. It's really a wonderful song. Been listening to it again and again. Went for dinner at Pantai Kundur with my fwens and guess what we ate. We ate ikan bakar, and we really chow the whole place up as though we've just came out from prison(I exaggerated on this part). Guess we were too hungry. Ordered half kilo of steam sotong cooked with extremely hot sambal, Jenak bakar chili, 4 packs of nasi lemak kukus, nasi pattaya, roti john and etc. I myself had 3 bowls of plain rice applying sambal on it. I really love spicy food and prefer to have them rather than chinese food. Not to say i dislike it but just felt jelak of eating it every day. The waitress gave us a weird stare for ordering such a huge amount of food and there's only 3 of us. But we can really finish every thing up. Nothing is impossible in malacca when it comes to food. Asked for the bill and we're really suprised that it cost us around 45 bucks for that amout of food. Very cheap and normally you'll get 'slaughtered' by other restaurants. We expected it to over be 60 bucks, and that's a really good bargain. Might go there for the 2nd time in some other day.  Left pantai kundur at 10 something and went back home to rest awhile. Gave Joan an instant message but she wasnt around. Went out again at 11 pm and chill out at the newly opened   Xuan cafe   at Melaka Raya. It's quite a happening place. Lots of young peeps hanged out there and the singer is really gorgeous!! *grins* Saw Lim, one of my old school mate there and chatted with him for awhile. I was really suprised and impressed that he's actually the owner of   Xuan cafe  . Cool stuff. He's the same age as i am and already own a business. Hope to get discount from him the next time we visit his cafe again hahaha. Aldrin said that where ever we go, there's surely lots of people  impressed coz he's actually the owner of who knows me and he says im like a politician coz i always greet people where ever i go lol. Well Malacca is really a small place after all coz there's chances to bump with each others along the way. We decided to go clubbing after leaving   Xuan cafe   and went to   'Pure Bar'   the most happening place in Malacca every saturday night. It was so packed as usual as we rammed ourself like sardines once we step our foot inside. Ordered a glass of orange juice and danced like monkeys once we reached the dance floor. It's been awhile since i went for clubbing since Quake left to Sabah to be reunited wif his gf and worked there. Saw lots of chicks there and we went 'gaga' when looking at them hahaha :P But it's just for side seeing okay? Please don't get the wrong idea. Wished Adelene was here with us coz she say she would love to go   Pure Bar   after her exams. Really missed her company!! Hope u're reading this, Lene hahaha :P Went back home at 2 A.M and feeling really tired + worn out. Guess dat's all for today folks. Will update this blog ASAP. Nites! 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I might sound a lil' outdated in the activity of blogging but seriously this is my first time of doing so. I knew it's already popular and has been around for ages but the reason i did not do so was because i've always felt lazy of writing anything, more ever posting it online!! LOL! It was changed after i've came across few of my friends blogsite and find it rather interesting with the idea expressing our thoughts. Well maybe it'll be my new found hobby of passing my time since there's nothing much to do online nowadays. I just don't feel as enthusiatic and over-hyped as i used to be anymore. I don't know. Started to blog right after i've created this account but i'm quite concerned because Adrian(my beloved god sister's boyfriend) told me i need to pay in order to use blogspot. Yeap, it's safe to assume that he knows all this because he's a former user of blogspot and experienced the event that i'm concerned about. Guess i'll switch to other domain if i really need to pay for it. Bah! So much for this s0-called "free" blog site.  Anyway's, went to makan at Wang's Footcourt and man!! Dad ordered tons and tons of food for us. We had chinese rice with one whole chicken(yeah, i know there's bird flu in the country recently but don't give a damn), grilled ikan pari, and 5 bowls of soup which is szechuan, some pork stomach, black beans, vege and some soup which i do not know what it's called in English. Went home feeling like a pregnant woman and watch a chinese drama while waiting for Malaysian Idol to start. Really had a great time watching MI although got a lil' irritated by the short commercials. What to do lar bro? It's sponsored by TMNet and it's a torture to see all of the stupid and irritating commercials promoting broadband. Most of the contestant were suprisingly impressive this week as some of them were quite a letdown last week. Saiful was doing utterly bad for the 2nd consecutive week with Fahmy forever singing his boring tunes, and both of them might get the boot this week. Haha anyway this were just my opinions and it's the public who decides who's to stay. Please don't chop me for that okay? Not to say i voted for each of them anyway *grins* Told Joan about it and she was so excited and can't wait to watch it. Hope she gets to download each of the clips later.  Aldrin came to my place shortly when i was just started talking to Joan. He invited me for yumchar session and suggested that we should wait for Jeffrey to come back from a 'date' with his supervisor some where around Pantai Kundur. Yeap, his supervisor is a male but don't get any ideas coz they're there to enjoy ikan bakar. Can't wait to eat there tomorrow coz it's Jeffrey's treat muahaha. The wait was worthwhile as we set our journey to a mamak stall at Kota Laksamana, not too far from my place. Once we reach there, we was wondering why it's so empty coz it's always packed on friday night and realised it's the 7th month on chinese calender a.k.a The hungry Ghost month. Sounds spooky enough.  We crap there as usual and we had a great time scaring Aldrin with our ghost stories coz Aldrin is going back by bike later. Huahuahua all alone!! Jefrrey got freak out shortly and we had to stop our conversation on that topic. Case Closed! Went on to crap till 1.50 AM and had to leave as Jeffrey was getting really sleepy. After all, he have to work tomorrow. Back on my pc and i'm waiting for Joan to come online again. I guess i'll end here for now. Laters!   
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Uchiha Sasuke  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello   
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys, this is my first time blogging here. Do come in and drop a few lines here. Thanks. God Bless you all!! 
    
</post>


</Blog>