<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm really bad at arguing, no matter how strongly I feel about a certain subject.  I never really understood the importance of health insurance until I got too old to be included in my parents' plan.  Right after I graduated college, I was on my own.  There was a 3 month gap where I was walking around without any medical insurance.  I was working in Manhattan, and the streets and intersections are always so crowded, and people's moods are on a sort of razor edge...I was wary of any situation in which I could've hurt myself or been hurt by someone or some taxicab.  I had no way of paying for hospital fees, doctor's visits, etc, so I had to avoid precarious situations.  And no, there was no way my parents could pay for me either.  I thought it was kind of funny the way I kept thinking,  "oh my god, don't step on my toe....oooooooooh be careful around me!  i'm fragile!"   I was also working with boxes of archived magazines and books for my job, and these boxes were stored on giant metal bookcases which could have easily toppled and squished me.  A simple accident could have landed me thousands of dollars of medical bills.        I understood the importance of health insurance even better the next year.  I finally bought health insurance through Columbia University.  It was a great deal.  Only $1500 for September 2002 until September 2003.  Luckily, I was able to convince my father to pay for that fee, because in February of 2003, I had a skiing accident.  My skis got stuck on a patch of really hard packed snow but the rest of my body continued as per the laws of momentum, and I tore my left anterior cruciate ligament.  It's actually a very common ski injury...but I racked up around $10,000 in x-ray, MRI, surgery, physical therapy, and various other doctor's fees.  I paid out of my pocket, maybe $250 total.  I was so glad for my health insurance.      This is where the arguing comes in.  Ever since I took a seminar on major topics in healthcare, I've developed an obsession for healthcare reform.  To my knowledge, my family has been very lucky with our medical bills.  The fees that came with my mother's stroke and rehabilitation was paid for by a sponsor who had a big heart.  Otherwise, we've had good health or have been covered by insurance.  Right now though, I'm not covered.  My father is not covered.  My sister was just dropped from the NJ FamilyCare Insurance plan which is a state program for low income families.  My mom qualifies for Medicare and Medicaid.  My brother has insurance through the hospital where he works, and he's a doctor (although he doesn't take very good care of himself).  It's sad that paying for health insurance is so difficult that we just ignore the importance of it.        Several of my postbac premed friends have also admitted that obtaining health insurance is not a priority to them.  I've put off acquiring health insurance because the Rutgers University plan doesn't really do as much as the program at Columbia.  There's no way I can afford insurance through a private managed care company.  I am not married so I can't rely on a spouse.  I don't qualify for NJ FamilyCare because I'm single and have no dependents.  Therefore, I don't go to the doctor for checkups, I don't get routine exams, I don't go to the dentist, I pay for contacts and eye exams out of my own pocket because it's necessary.  My teeth are fine, my general health is fine, thankfully.  Life was a lot more comfortable when I was insured and could go to the dermatologist, the dentist, etc.  And to think, millions of Americans are in the same place as me, or worse.  An alarming number of citizens are not insured or are underinsured.  These people can't pay for their medications, so they don't take their medications.  They can't go to the doctor for yearly checkups because a lot of insurance plans don't cover well visits.  These people then end up in the hospital because of an undiagnosed health problem, but they cannot afford their emergency room bills or the pills that they have to take.  The hospitals are forced to foot the bill because they cannot turn away people who are in need of treatment.  The hospitals then raise their fees, and everyone blames hospitals for the healthcare crisis.  Or they blame pharmaceutical companies for the healthcare crisis because no one can afford their patented, latest and greatest formulations.        The word "pre-emptive action" has gotten a very bad rap from its use in the war against Iraq.  But in the case of our nation's healthcare crisis, I think we should another look at the power of pre-emptive action.  Now, I don't know a lot about our nation's budget...and I may be a bit naive on certain topics, but I think we need to dump our current healthcare system.  I don't know what the solution is, but I think we need to PREVENT these emergency room visits, and this need for expensive drugs.  I haven't yet come up with a solution, but I wish everyone were paying more attention to this problem.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I decided that if anyone reads this and thinks he/she knows who I am, I would rather them not talk to me about what I write.  Anyone can comment, so long as he/she remains unnamed to me.  Many of my issues are topics that I do not like  talking  about to people.  Some of them may be important and interesting ideas, but I would rather not receive advice from friends or other people who actually know me.  Like I said though, those who think they know who I am or actually  do  know who I am are free to send me advice as a blog comment, but I do not want to know your real name or how you know me.  Thank you for your compliance to these terms.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm really having A LOT of trouble compromising with the hours of each day.  I hate that the majority of "life" exists during the hours of 9AM-5PM.  Everything should be operating 24 hours a day.  Doctor's offices, school, supermarkets, the gym, the DMV, EVERYTHING.  That way, night people don't have to be depressed that they can't function during "normal" hours.      My latest explanation for my "night operations" is that 7PM-6AM is when I have the least number of things/people to worry about.  I can't wake up at 8AM because I can't deal with the struggle of my egos.  "If I don't go to work, Mom can take the car and get out of the house."  (My mother had suffered a disabling stroke in November of 1997.  She can't work anymore.  We have 3 cars to share between 4 people.  My mother usually gets last dibs because the rest of us have to go to work.  Which means she is stuck at home).  I feel so guilty because the car belongs to my parents, it's a very good Honda Accord 2001.  And although I enjoy my work doing research for the medical school, it is not necessary that I be there everyday.  I can mostly work at home.  But once I relinquish my rights to the car for that day, I fall back sleep until 1or 2 PM.  I usually putz around until 7PM or so, when my parents are done with their days of work and cleaning and discussions.  Once they're done, I really wake up because the things that go on during their days stress me out like you wouldn't believe.  Once they're settled down in front of the TV, or ready to go to bed, I head out of the house to do my work.  I can't really work at home.  When they're asleep, it seems I am at my best.  No one to ask me questions, to ask for advice, to ask for favors, to yell things that I overhear and worry about...      So, what to do?  I'm supposed to learn to push those thoughts out of my head.  Until the world is open for business 24 hours a day, I need to learn to get my work done (AND NOT FEEL GUILTY) during the daytime.  Which means, I should try to buy my own car (ha) so I don't feel guilty about going to work everyday.  I need to realize my mother is an adult and doesn't need me to worry about her (especially since there's nothing I can do for her anyway).  Breaking the habit of worrying will allow me to focus on what needs to be done.  I should relieve some of the pressure that goes along with procrastinating (which happens because I'd rather keep my mother company and entertained than do my work).  I'm charting my progress by keeping a daily diary of occupations.  I try to mark down what I do by the hour and see if I can gradually become a "normal" day person.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>