<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This Friday night is going well I thought sub-consciously as I was carried into the zone--the zone that we all go to before we go into deep sleep. My brain was doing its regular check of my two legs that were my newly found babies, as I slept. Babies that I had taken extra care of since I started my training for my first marathon. Unconsciously I did the check 1 2 routine..I stretched my calf--fine, my Achilles tendinities (to the non-runners the tendon you find right above your heel). Ouch that hurt but not as much as last night. I bent my knee and pushed my snoring husband further to the other side of the bed.Not that I cared anymore-i was in "the" zone. Check 1,2 ,3 my brain said. All working except Achilles (achy for short) dear. she will be taken care of tomorrow by regularly stretching as we cruise mile after mile. I slept like a log that night not aware of the clock ticking away furiously next to me.I woke up feeling really refreshed unlike my other Saturday morning--without the jittery feeling and minus the usual tightness in my calf or a sore gluteus Maximus (to the non-runners again read butt) why won't it after what it was subjected at the gym, it had carried weights it had never imagined in its life time of 27 years! Anyways grabbed my chocolate drink pushed down a dry bagel and I was done. Ready to do my first 18 miller (gosh what was I thinking when I got into the program).The warrior me was getting ready, slathered the sun screen and Vaseline(to avoid chafing), reset my chrono watch. Sun glasses-check,watch-check,banana for the road-check,cap-check. My hubby gave me the look and gave me a sporty hug(yeah that's what sports guys do!--don't be surprised if they start giving you high five's!..I mean what more can you expect--c'mon yaar)..wished me luck.He had a look on his face that I didn't want to analyse. Infact i guess my brain was just trying hard to block away the future--tackle as it comes. I didn't want to be thinking of figures.No not today.I was ready to go...went through the check list yet again.My eyes caught my fuel belt lying there--feeling rather left out. Grabbed her (all my things are she's-don't laugh). All 30 odd sacrificial lambs were getting ready oblivious to what was in store. The coaches gave us tips one sentence remains in my head "till 16 odd miles you will be fine--after that EVERYONE hits the wall-the rest is all mental". I felt a shrudder going through me a she lamb squealed behind me and clung to her hubby she baaa'ed and said "now I am getting nervous". I guess she just realized what she was getting into.join the gang I thought!. One more nervous lamb among the 30 odd! We all started our jog, first we didn't have space to jog it was pretty crowded then we all spread around, the faster people took off the rest of us pretending not to know the obvious discussed issues that needn't be discussed. Exchanged views that needn't be exchanged. And kept asking each other how we were feeling every 10 mins!. Like I needed someone to remind me how my Achilles tendinitis was hurting(for the non runners sorry guys you will have to start from the beginning). But I religiously stopped every mile did my little stretch. I am sure my tendon was basking in the new found attention it was getting. that's one mighty way she has found out to show me she exist and resides right above my heel.I spent the next twelve miles appeasing her. We as a team(my calves,quads, hams,ms gluteus Maximus (she demands more respect) and her highness Achilles tendon (well well tendon ko bhi highness banana padtha hai-especially at mile 12!) were doing well. I had gulped down 2 gu's (ahem--that's a gel packed with carbs and what not a long distance runner needs--non runners please don't think otherwise).Then it hit, duh what happened I though. I found the sun enjoying it self directly focusing its rays at me. i felt I was the one targeted, i had the flash lights on me. And I had to perform. My feet was giving away it complained that I had iced the calves and Ms GM and payed respect to her highness so what about us they said. Well all i could do from mile 12 to mile 14 was drag myself. Humour them and promise then a good massage when they get home. I said I would rest them on a ice pack and massage them with balm--I begged them to drag me home. But they refused--outright without pardon I was punished. At mile 14 I sat down on the road....i tried my best, did my feet some massage and twisted my toes. some nice guy passed by asked me if I wanted water. I didn't want water damn it all i wished was that I had worshiped my feet before so they would act better now. Alas I had angered them.What could I do now I was 4 more miles from home. All I could do was stand and pretend to run --took baby steps. My team was accepting defeat. But I pulled on my team--my back up team my arms hands took over. They reminded me that I had not done enough for them, they made me realize that I had to do much more for them if they had to work the next time. Some how reached mile 15.All by myself trying to reach another limping warrior right in front of me, i was almost in tears now.I felt tears coming up..this was nothing but pure hell. I met another wounded warrior at mile 16. She was in a worse state than me...we decided to team up.We dragged ourselves for the next two miles how ...don't ask me. I could not break down since she was there....in encouraging her I felt encouraged , my team felt encouraged. That's what is called positivity, that is what is called a mental game. And yes we did it-- me and my team did our first 18 miles. You ask me how it was ...one word MARVELLOS.Will I do it again ? ..YES, I WILL. PS: Since this is a PG-13 I am not going to the gory details, of how I trodded limped my way back home, pushed open the door. and yelled my lungs out. how I self pitied myself. or how much i wanted to talk to someone when I got home!! In short --I am proud to me an 18 miller. And as a parting note...hats off to all the wannabe and pro runners over there. Cause only we know what it takes!  
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello there:  Just starting off blogging, I have blogs else where too so this is not new to me. I plan to put down some of my serious thoughts and opinions. So here I go. Later then adieu 
    
</post>


</Blog>