<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Moods are strange things for people. They affect us more than we can guess I suppose. Last night after I got off the phone with Jamie, my mood just dropped right out from under me, I totally crashed and I have no idea why..We had a fabulous conversation, so that wasn't the cause at all. I can no triggers at all. Sometimes its almost like my meds just stop working for some reason. I just can't pinpoint it. I got up this morning at 8am, had a small coffee, let the dog out and then went back to bed. I awoke in a bad mood again. I hate being this way. last night Iw as totally suicidal and I probably should have called emergency services, but I tried my hardest and made it through it. It sucks to live like this.. I am sick and tired of having these feelings, they affect me greatly, and everyone around me. I told my father: "I'm fucking sick of feeling this way' and he told which I'd rather do, Push up daisies or pull them up. Sometimes I'd like to push them up. He doesn't understand this at all. Not that I am blaming him or anything, he just doesn't get it.  Jamie is coming today and I wonder what will happen, what we will do??  My external voices were kind of raging this morning and driving me up the wall, which may just explain my mood. It has subsided somewhat, but they still remain.  I quit my Effexor cold turkey the other day and am waiting for the withdrawal symptoms to hit me. So far, nothing. I had nasty sexual side effects from it that I just couldn't deal with. I am still taking Wellbutrin tho.  Its not cool to quit meds without a doctors consent, by my dr doesn't understand that I DON'T care about the side effects and wanted me to taper off them. Screw that, I wanna be able to have sex!! lol  Its 3pm and Jamie just called and she is really close by now and my nerves are getting tattered a bit. I guess its normal to be nervous in situations like this.   
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi, I guess I should start with a little intro. My name is Chris, I'm 36 yrs old and I have been diagnosed by three doctors to be paranoid schizophrenic, schizotypal personality disorder, PTSD and finally, Bi-Polar. So, you can guess that my mind and my life are not a bowl of cherries. Suprisingly, I have been able to hide my symptoms for years until about two years ago when I let the cat out of the bag - I have been medicated since and have slowly been getting better. My current meds are 7mg risperdal (anti-psychotic), 20mg Zyprexa (anti-psychotic), 150mg Wellbutrin (anti-depressant that also relieves the urge to smoke!), 300mg Effexor (anti-depressant), 1500mg Depakote (Mood Stabilizer)..I also take a couple of PRN's (PRN=as needed) - one is Atarax (100mg), for anxiety and the other is 100mg of Trazadone, for sleep. The Depakote sucks, because I have to get my blood drawn every couple of weeks, to make sure the level isn't too high. If its too high, it can wreck your liver enzymes, which is pretty scary. I have been hospitalized twice and partially hospitalized once. I will probably end up getting hospitalized again someday...yeah, thats a negative attitude, but so be it.  Recently I had a breakup with my girlfriend of 8 years or so. I lied to her and was a lowlife, and she asked me to leave because she basically got sick of me/couldn't deal with me/found someone else. Believe it or not, we are still friends and I consider her my best friend. She literally saved my life by getting me help and I will NEVER forget that. I learned a lot in our relationship, more than I could ever state here. The only thing I wished she had done recently is to give me more credit for what I DID do over the years, instead of what I didn't do. Most of the things I did were an enourmous task for me, being sz and all..I must have done ten thousand little things here and there...BUT, I am not bitter about this at all, just stating how I feel.. I tried my hardest and I think she did too, but unfortunately, it just didn't work out. I like to think that someday things will be great between us again, but if I think realistically, we will never be a couple again, too much happened, too much didn't happen. Some friends blame her for me being hospitalized, but I personally don't think thats the case - it would have happened sooner or later anyway, regardless of the event of breakup. The same friends that see her as being evil, they fail to see her as the one who saved me... I miss her still, but the pain softens a bit everyday. One day I will be able to look at her as Julissa (LOL!!!!) instead of 'my old girlfriend' or 'my ex'.  I am currently partially hospitalized and the program is actually pretty good, we have 'group' all day and we are allowed to have smoke breaks throughout the day, so I never even get a nic-fit. The counselors are cool and the hospital food is real good too, especially the strawberry shortcake! Group ranges from life skills, to education, to music therapy which is real fun. I go to this place 5 days a week..they pick me up and drop me off every day. If for some reason I am not there when they pick me up, they will notify the police, they will hunt me down and I'll be locked in the psych ward. Sooo, as you can imagine, attendance is mandatory, even tho I volunteered for this program. Its sounds like fun, but it is actually pretty damn tough at times, especially when the counselors call you on your shit. Like for instance, I got busted today for smoking in front of the building and also for drinking a Coke (with caffeine)..I received 5 'points' for this. If I get five more points, then off I go to the psych ward. So, ya gotta watch your step or you can be locked up real easy.  I am currently receiving medical assistance and welfare. Now before all you people bitch that I am on welfare, please remember that I paid into this system too..I had very good jobs and a LOT of my tax dollars went into 'the system'. My goal is not to stay on welfare, but to become a productive human being again. I am signed up with this place called OVR which stands for Occupational Vocational Rehabiliation. They train you in a certain field of work, then place you, which is just great. I also plan on going to another place, which is a group home, where I can learn to get my act together and be a productive person. At this place, I have to pay rent and utilities.   ################################################################### ###################################################################   In Psychotherapy today, one of the guys talked about how he loves murder and death and gore and shit...He says that when he saw someone hit by a car and flung tthrough the air, he laughed...he said the same about the world trade centers. The other day he said something that really freaked me out, but I'll be damned if I can remember what it was. Anyway when he started saying all this in group, it totally flipped out the therapist..I can read her facial expressions like a book..I can almost smell her expressions. (I had this same 'sense' with Julissa) The poor therapist was mortified and I kinda giggled and she asked me why I was laughing and I just told her that her facial expression gave her away..She didn't like that at all, but I was just being honest. She called me into her office later and asked me what I meant and I told her that her face told me that she was literally scared of this guy. She actually THANKED me for bringing this to her attention! During our next session with her, she sat there as stonily as possible and I sat there with this big shit eatin' grin on my face cause she wasn't doing a good job of being stone cold..She asked me later how she did and I said 'better, but ya still need work'. This has obviously caused her GREAT concern...LOLOL It made me feel so good to get over on her and figure her out.  I am a bit of a pro on figuring people out. I figured out Julissa in about three weeks time. I could read her thoughts with no prob. When she had an affair on me, I knew it happened, so I just went and asked.. I figured out her new boyfriend, just by her emailing me thoughts about him, and I told her this, this, this, and this will happen and sure enough they all did. I never used my power in a bad way, I never used it to take advantage of people, I just use it to get to know them intimately. I like to know what people are thinking, I want to know them well. Shit, maybe I should use it in a bad way, everbody else fucks each other over, so why not me?  My eyes hurt, so maybe I should quit writing this now.. later.. 
    
</post>


</Blog>