<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Todae, another normal normal dae... hmmm... Todae wanted to see my honey so much... But when sae her she so quiet... haiz... nth to sae one lor we 2... so pai seh lor when nth to sae... haiz... Dunno why whenever we online we got alot of things to sae one lor... but when talk talk tt time... NTH TO SAE... Haiz... Saw the blog she wrote yesterdae?? Mi see le get beri angry lor... ThoSe CB senior bully my honey!HaiZ... So xin tong!!!!        Todae we had sci test... ok ok onli lar... mi nv study one lor... anyhow do? Noway... is throw dice lar!!! lolx... My honey dunno got study anot?? hmmm... she always sae she did her best but in the end... mi realli beri sad with her results lor... honey ar honey... plis get home early den do revision lar... and try ur best of the best... i dun see u doing so yet leh... no offense ar! i'm juz beri beri upset to see ur result... u noe... some how at border line... haiz... If u dun listen to mi will b realli reali realli disappointed de lor... haiz... I will support u one hor! And ask mi if u dunno how to do!!! Dun COPY!!        K lar enough of those craps... I followed my honey to mac... den i found tt i beri bo liao... walked back to sch... dunno for wat... i think see cassandra ba... HONEY! IF U SEE THIS, DUN ANY HOW THINK!!! MI TREAT HER AS SIS ONLI!! I ONLI LUV U!!!         Mi kind of wanted to see how they were doing mah... So went back... with some pie i bought at tmart... But too bad mi did not see the sec 1s perform... haiz... k lar... signing off...     I LUV U JO, U N ONLI U...  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hmmm... Todae woke up early in the morning go out wif cost to buy somethings den come back to my house do art project... den mi miss my honey so much much... always thinking wat she doing... I MiSs U SiA Jo... LuV U 4 EvER...  beri tired le... haha... sIgNing OFf...  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So SiAn... EaRly In tHe MoRninG WaKe Up... msG HoNey... AnD FouNd ThaT ShE wAs In ScH hvINg baNd... n I heArD ThAt ThEy DiD FoOt DrIlL... AnD KaNa PuSh UpS... So XiN TonG... HoNEy ToLD mi ShE GOT A SCRATCH ON HER LEG!!! HaIZ... ThAt Cb yaN LiNg IF I noT WrOng ASkEd TheM tO Do Push UpS... HaIz.... So StreSs SiA... OnE SidE Of My mInD tHinKinG OfF HeR, anOthEr PaRt tHinkinG Of The ComInG Up tEsTEs And UnDOnE PrOjEcTs... HaiZ... So TiRed Le... I MiSs U So mUCh Jo... LuV U SO mUcH!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Today woke up early in the morning to do my HE project... Dunno why, mayb i sensitive again ba; i kept having this feelings tt my honey have a crush on other boy... haiz... beri wierd hor? Then tt jin keat leh, wu yuan wu gu ask mi my blog's @. I gave it to him lor... so sian sia... still got so many stupid project not finished yet... I msg my honey this morning but she took so long den reply... mayb bz ba... I told her tt i going to concentrate on study 1st for this few weeks as i find tt a lot of testes are coming up... Wish tt this wont affect our relationship... or else mi realli dunno what to do le...       My feelings n luv for her is growing dae by dae... losing her would realli make mi beri deeply hurted... n surly would nid some time to heal one... SO! I WONT ONE TO LOSE HER NOW! I Luv her more then anythings else le now... even my dear com is behind her lor.... last time my com is my onli darling to mi... every dae use her... but now my com lk my second wife le... coz my honey is the 1st...         But sometimes i found tt luving jo is realli difficult coz she is realli a cheerful gal and... hmmm how to sae... aiya... she seems to dun hv stress on her daily life n school works... But mi alot of differents things to do... sometimes her attitude is reali bad... but tt's wat i lk... hehe...         One more things ar... she ar... everytime see boi one lor... whenever i see her in sch hor... she looking at boi lor... MAKE MI SO JEALOUS AND ANGRY.... but i trust her... so nvm.... Signing off...          I LUV U FOREVER JOANNE!!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hmmm... todae another normal dae lor... haiz... every time i go look for my honey, she seems to be so into someting else one sia... nvm... it's her freedom anyway... haiz... so worry of her lor... always dun listen to mi advice... JoaNnE ar Joanne why cant u juz... haiz... nvm... dun sae le... wat she did tis evening has made mi coughed non- stop le. I told her so many times not to play in the rain as i realli so worry tt she would b sick... den! wat she did!? She went to play in the rain!!! HaiZ... dun sae le... i realli cant stop coughing... haiz... signing off... bye...    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hmmm... Actually i created this acc yesterday... seeing my honey hv a blog and write all abt herself... mi den decided to copy her... hehe... Todae ar... hmmm.... nth much lor... went to sch ard 6.45a.m den wanted to go see honey one... but seeing the time going to b up le, then i did not go lor...          Haiz... dunno is i too sensitive or wat... it seems that honey is always ignoring mi sia... i was realli beri beri angry! But she talk talk to mi le juz now on sms... Dunno lar... dun care le... juz noe that i luv her n miss her so much... every dae, every hr, every min, i kept thinking of her lor... cant stop on sia... haiz...i miss her SO MUCH!!!!!!!! JOANNE I LUV U!!!!          Today during the com club hor.... my honey n qi hong they all was using the com in the lab to complete thier PW... Den this qi hong hor... SOT ONE LOR!!! Keep making Nelson.... Asking for stead, doing stupid stuffs.... and that oso scold mi stupid things... at that min i was realli beri angry lor... So idoitic sia... my honey leh? She talk to mi on msn, but one thing i dun lk abt her talking to mi that time was, she talk to mi as if she neglect how i feel lor... haiz... nvm lar... being a bf i muz always giv in to gf one... haiz... k lor until here le... SigNinG OfF....   
     

    
</post>


<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Yoz~!  Thanks for reading again...hmmm...I'll start off with today in general...happy day overall, except "some small" problems...but yay...who give a fuck 'bout 'em... Have to be used to it from now onwards...And yeh...I think I have an affinty with the number 6 today...I even saw a car with 3 6's in it's plate number...perhaps god is telling me to wait for 6 months? Bah. I'll wait forever.       "Determination and Patience bring success" Wee You(2004)      All right here I goes, at school, I jsut keep thinking bout da family..but who cares...as I said just now...hee hee...Life/Love is as complicated as how you make it into...and I'm gonna make it simple and clean...(this phrase give me the urge to play Kingdom Hearts again....omg....)      Had a whole day of basketball after school..man...saw the tall guy who diao'ed me yesterday...but yay...who carez...Basketball in my mind now..currently roks...relaxing and fun...but perhaps it is just a moment of thinking...that's what I do anyway...Shan Fen Zhong Re Du...hehe... but there is THAT one thing i wud not give up easily...hehe....me devoted guy....but sometime resistance only bring conflicts...ayarh donno don care....      Accidentaly hit EK's eye today...hmmm...to the public I apologise to the Chao Ji Wu Di Bai Ma Wang Zi Chao Yan Dao - Neo Na Bei....    My conscience pricks me severly for saying the wrong thing to the wrong person, maybe causing some damage to that person. So here, I also want to aplogise to Wang Sili,.     ~!~ I love you ~!~ 
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yoz~! I thought today would be a terrible day, but ironically, it turned out to be...well...okay day...juz like any normal day. Expected the aftermaths of yesterday's incident, which i wouldn't mention here, to happen today, but nah....yay~ I'm still happy, what'cha gonna do 'bout it? And well...I will wait. What do I mean? It's none of your buisness, but the person I'm referring to would understand, although I doubt she would take the time to read me blog :P      Can't believe that Xin Mei and Sili thinks that I should be sad...hmmm....why shud I? Sorrow only brings pain...yay...So I see it from a good direction. Can't blame me, I'm still da optimistic freak~    Okie...so what happened today? I'm not gonna explain it in details...we had a hard science test afta skool and after it we head to da Bball court for a day of Bball...a trio came down and wanted to play...and yeah, we did. The tallest one seemed AWFULLY familiar but I cud not remember who's him. Well well, we(En Kai, Zhao Kai, Me) lost to a 7-4, which in chinese...has a pronouncation of "go and die".      Bah..who cares...afta the game the tall one lik...keep diaoing us...I kept quiet bout it...then another person cum... I heard the tallde complain to that guy...who in turn challenged us to ANOTHER game...man...life's tired...but fun :P. I think that the tall one diao us b'coz...I lik...keep blocking him out from the...erm..."Red Area".... then no matter how hard he pushes I just stay there....Ayah...since he lik bueh song le...I lazy blk him oso...it was 5-7...yay...another loss for us....    Donno why...the tzll one knows that i dwwn go blk him...or maybe juz coincidence lah... Then he asked for another match...which we won in 11-10...yay...      Fun day overall..worsened my right leg's blister s ...left leg new blister... then my right leg de toe nail lik falling off le...but I still wun care...         ~!~ hApPy mE ~!~ ~+~ I aM tYcO...hEhE ~+~ ~-~oFfIcIaLly dEcLaReD cOnTeNtEd~-~ ~/~ i WiLl wAiT dE...i rEaLlY wILL de.... ~\~               
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Haiz....never expected me to type this all out...but...reli can't take it le lah.....a main family problem of mine is going to be posted to public....but who cares-.-"      Okie...here it goes...in a perfect evening at a perfect place called pasir ris...a inperfect accident happened...my uncle(Mother de sister de husband) and auntie(mother de sister) is involved in an accident, which caused my uncle to die and my auntie to be admitted to the hospital, which in turn caused her to be a vegetable..      Okie...I'm hurt by this incident of course, although i only see both of 'em during new year..or via coincidence...they are good persons who did  not  deserve this accident...but what can I do? Life is  that  fuckin' unfair...        All right...when all seems to be over, it is just a start of a problem involving with family bonds, trust, feelings and conflicts...here i go...  My mother and maternal grandmather si of course deeply saddened by this accident...especially when my grandfather and uncle(mother de brother) died in the past 5 years... which in turn caused my mother to be very hot-tempered...and my grandmother to be very depressed...blaming everything onto herself...    The relationship between my mother and my father is already not good...now my mother liddat..owaz use my father to "Chu Qi"...my father of coz will bueh song... then i predict more quarells after this le....haiz.....      Onto my grandmother's side...my mother need to cheer her up....but cannot show any anger to her... but as my grandmother is a very superstitious person...she refused to miove to my house, as she says my grandfather wud be at her house there when he cum bak....but she cannot possible stay alone le mah.....! she now in a depressed state leh..! then she keep saying about dying and all........haiz.....my mother of coz pek cek..then the more pek chek she   gets, the more anger she release on my father...as she cannot show anger to grandmother..whiich in turn will..haiz....      My auntie...now the only way to show expressions....is to show it by crying ...which she did...well....who wudn't...loved one died suddenly...suddenly unable to move...haiz.....pity her neh.....      that's not all loh... my uncle's side de family..... they  refused  to take care of my auntie...refused to visit my auntie..everything loh.....chee bye loh...the world where got so heartless people de....go to hell lah.....now my family don;t have the expenses and the space for my auntie...then impossible to throw to my grandmother rite?!?! Why so unreasonable de!! we dwwn to throw her into the nursing home rite?! she already very sad le u all stil liddat?! Are u still a fuckin' human?! the cats i see everyday have a betta heart than u!      And my uncle's assets and propeties...shud be going to my auntie de mah...but now she liddat...how she get.....?! according to the law the assets can only be changed if the person is totally immobolised...now my auntie can move the head there de...but so wad?! YOU DON FUCKIN' DESERVE ANYTHING IF U PUSH UR RESPONSIBILTY AWAY!        ~!~ PeK CheK! ~!~ ~-~ Why my family so complicated?~~-~ 
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Just came back from a whole day of basketball...so tired leh..I bet En Kai oso as tired as me le...whole day looking at Yan Hao's orange ball oso will sian.....  Early early wake up....then En Kai go down wrong stop...haha...Mu Tou Ren ish owaz Mu Tou Ren uh....! toot toot de...ayorh...then he bounce bounce bounce oso keep "Lau Qiu"...very sueh neh....  Not only he sueh nia...my bag oso sueh....kena stuck in a  moving bicycle  and the lift thingie...ayorhX...  Today...although having a lot of fun...but still very miss the...eh-hem...neh... why neh? Juz now Zhao Kai and En Kai dee siao...say the person u lik and ur ball will definitey go in....i keep saying her name...oso nv go in....then the Zhao Kai go say Patricia's name...then go in!!!! Qi Shi Wo Le!!!! En Kai oso sueh sueh de...  Zhao Kai dee siao siao go and say Dunice Tan Jelly....then keep going in sia...ayorhx....me and EK determined...then keep dedicating balls to the person we like :D  Today...oso see a lot of old frens....get back a lot of old memories... saw nicholas...got me back Primary School's band de memory...saw jun hao to get back the good ol' days where i just transferred to primary skool...oso saw Yumi neh...which indirectly let me tink of dat slut...     ~+~ BaSkEtBalL rOx ~+~ ~_~LoNgInG f0r t0m0rr0w~_~ ~$~ mIsSiNg dA oLd dAyS uH!! ~$" 
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Wow...a blog for me also...never expected this to happen....but actually i got one blog de...but long time nv go...forget pw le....hehe....    EeYer... today early early wake up for band...then do the foot drills...tired neh......! When it's break...i saw sili...den we tok crap together while the others keep saying that got a 1e3 de(    After band i see XM's dear play bball with jin keat they all...while waiting for sili...ayorh...why i want to wait for her i oso donno...maybe juz another excuse to take a glimpse of...erm...okie...    But in the end i still don see the...erm..okie...lah.. so i end up accompanying sili to the tampines mart...see her buy the socks and all...then after that send her home loh........    Do so many things.. already tired lik wad le... then go back home...get on com....and stare into space...haiz....i keep advicing sili to be daring and all...but am I? I thought about a lot of things....and...that slut come online....make me pek chek straight away...blocked her and went to sleep...but of course i can't....thinking of the past...me and her....ayorh...why I so stupid sia...    Then after that still accompany Zhao Kai play soccer...then my blister worsen.......ayorhx!? pain neh...on my way back home i saw Valerie...but i don tink she recognize me...so i juz walk past.......haiz.......    ~+~ TiReD ~+~    ~=~ Missing you ~=~  ~~ Fuck off, slut ~~             
     

    
</post>


</Blog>