<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      am feeling quite guilty for screaming at a teacher today. up till now, i still don't know if what i did was correct. i mean, i think im actually the first student who ever did this. i didn't even know if i was speaking for the whole class i was just being selfish.  selfish me. i only cared about my feelings.
      
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        want to get $80 to spend for prom nite gown or anything?  simple. philips is doing a survey on shaving, mainly at underarm n bikini line area. all u have to do is answer some questions n demostrate how u shave. not do the real shaving but just hand gestures. interested look 4 me or msg me. :)  
      
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Can't believe what we did on saturday. Mildly innane, Really stupid. We refers to Nexa and serene(3/4 03), Me and veliana (duh 4/6). We (nexa, clau, serene minus veliana) did the happy dance 2004 in front of a captive audience numbered one. THat one was Mr Low the one with the legend* and the revealed secret**. We wasted his time, to watch the entire second half, or rather, second 3/7th. And he wasn't really irritated i guess, at least he didn't seem so... By that, i believe he proved his mettle. I think he just earned himself the rank of funky*** MR LOW! YOU ARE OFFICIALLY FUNKY!  * Legend: Like -&gt; Devotion -&gt; don't like If in doubt, ask clau ** Secret: erhmmmm mmmarrriieee eeeerrrhmmmd *** Hierachy of (good)ranks from lowest to highest: Rock Funky Funkaay Other funkies:Mrs Low, Mr Lee 
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hee!! class blog!! damn cool manz.. hhaha..lets keep this for a very very very long time.. hopefully this one is blogged often unlike the yahoo groups thing.. that is almost dead.. then maybe 60 years later, we still have this blog..hmmm... 
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       haha!   finally figured this thing out! so fun! prelims coming le. work hard pple. really hope that everyone will do well fr the bottom of my heart. :-)   study hard k? then can really play and celebrate to your heart's content. haha!   won't be typing much today. very tired. just came back from king albert park studying.   opps... forgot that i haven't finish my ss essay... did it half way. i'll just complete during recess n lunch tomorrow. haha! okie. take care everybody!  
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      St. Margaret's from over the wall  urlLink     Elephance 
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hello blevery Hello 4e6 people. Hello It feels dead around here. SAy something people. RESPONSES! Pleassse For that matter, TDD is coming up, and can someone please volunteer a digital video cam, so that we can record our "swansong" and post it here maybe, so that the whole world can marvel (or laugh or otherwise) at our antics. Hello Oh yes, and a good way to stay awake to study is to study outside. It wouldn't do to fall asleep at a coffeeshop would it :P 
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Greetings, to all netizens of 4-6. I am bev(WONG), bev(WONG) am I.   Prelims are in what, 3weeks time?    Congratulations, a jubilation.. lalalala   Sorry la. I little hyper. No, Im just tired!    Does anyone have any suggestion   to keep yourself awake through the night to mug  ?  because I really need it, if not bye.. you'll prolly see me in ite jurong. So,  anyone has any good ways/secrets of keeping yourself awake? Share with me/us alright?     Thankyou, to one and all.    -Beverly(WONG)  
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      THIS IS clau. THIs is you lotsa people looking at chinese results.... HAHA... Cool pic huh..  urlLink     Elephance 
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Eberybodie, this is the 4e6 blog, please please post lots, then maybe we can hit 200 posts a week averaged. YAY. Okay, it is clau who set up this blog, and i have thios to say.. FIRST 5 MEMBERS GET ADMIN!!!! whooohooo., Everyone wants admin :) 
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      eh weird ah, who create this blog then nv post anything about who set it up!?! i suspect its either cLAU or negonisbeebs. (: OH WELLLLL. 
      
</post>


</Blog>