<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Rules that i discussed earleir were fraud, i mean they do exist but for time being. Rishi did something good today. He got a docs letter stating he is very ill and needs urgent medication. So Rishi won't attend any lectures till 1st. I may do the same in near future. Todays day otherwise was boring the only good thing about the day was that today it didn't rain. I can understand that north indians love rainfall but for me they should occur sometimes. Pune has been generously offered five to six showers of rain every day, sponsored by none other than your one and only Indradev. He's quite popular these days you know.But today it didn't thats the point. I am enjoying Pune weather, this makes me happy. What makes me feel opposite is Netra's killer looks, she is practically after me i won't be suprised if i get zero for my Business organisation project. I have found a nice way to submit it, if u are interested then go to this link:-  urlLink http://www.google.co.in/advanced_search?hl=en  , then change the file format to *.pdf, and type in the name of the company you want. I am sure you will end up with something funny though of your own benifit.  Keep thinking FK Way!!  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I knew it, Maddy was aware of the fact that we will be chucked out of class.....  reason  simple, we were not in coll uniform. I can uderstand the problem with school teachers but then we are in coll!!  Netra made some rules with BHAMA today they are as follows:  Rule 1: Every one in proper uniform  Rule 2: One class missed means attendance of the day gone (this one sucks)  Rule 3: No one keeps funky beards...whatever (I think Aman needs to shave of his so called funky  gotti)   These, i mean all of them really suck!!    BUT then RULES are meant to be BROKEN!!          
    
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Khan, Fahad Khan hai mara naam....  Bond liners still do well in public though you took it as a joke. Anyways i am writing this from pune. Sitting in Hub is like sitting in home..Saurab says so, i am feeling it, but then home was always better.  I am studying at symbiosis for all those who don't know symbiosis is the best or say one of the best col for B-commerce.  People say so, I believe it. And those who don't know Saurab, he is my friend--though a bit whatever, but a funloving guy.  I will be regular so keeb thinking FK way!!  P.S Ishchit's new hotmail account is  urlLink scream_in_skull@hotmail.com  add him to urs.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>