<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just went to ask my dad something, and that asshole drops a block of wood on my foot. That thing must have weighed at least 25 lbs. Painful, much.  Oh yeah, thanks to Bryan for helping me with my math homework. Saved me a detention, phone call, and grounding.
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Abogee. Its the newest word to hit the scene. Pronounced a-boh-gee, it means something (I don't remember), but its funny as hell. Just say it. Use it as an adjective, noun, verb and everything else! Example: "Hey I just abogeed that girl over there!" or: "I named my dog Abogee!" It can be used in all types of sentences and used as different parts of speech. Abogee is definitely the "it" word. Don't be caught not saying it!
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from my orthodontist, after being checked out early from school, and I got a good report :) Woot. Now I can actually live past tomorrow. If you had ever had an experience with those aweful people (orthodontists), post a comment and tell me about (like I'd care though).
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My friend Bryan has a  urlLink blog  also and a cool  urlLink site . They are awesome if you wanna check them out. Sign up for his BBS (bulletin board system). It's pretty cool. But mine's better...okay maybe not. But still, check it out it will be worth your while if you catch my drift ;) 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have insomnia. It sucks. Send me money so that I may buy pills to stop my insomnia. If you help me I will thank you very much, but thats about it since I'm broke. If you are an insomniac comment and tell me why you hate it so much.  After a while my posting will decrease after my schoolwork starts to increase. Remember kids: school blows. There isn't anything you can learn in school that you can't learn on the street. Just look at Albert Einstein. He grew up a poor German boy. Then he failed math, science, couldn't tie his own shoes... maybe I should have picked a better example... But you have to admit, that guy was a fucking genius. 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just finished my profile so now you can find some info on me (if you care), and well, if you are stalking me or something, theres a nice little snack for you. Well, its like 9:40pm and I gotta get going soon so I'll wrap this up right here. I'm done. (wow some ending huh?) 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I just got home from school at about 4:43pm. I was trying to get on here but the server must be bugging or something because it took it forever to load the page. Well, I got a ton of homework and little time to do it. But I don't care :) Theres always time (usually) for homework. Man, I feel pathetic :-S coming here, righting this, no one cares, its not like I have a stalker or anything... right? But still, its kinda fun and it gives me something to do in my free time besides watch T.V. and besides, there isn't anything good on right now.  I think...   Well, thats about it for this post, my dad is starting to yell at me to do my homework. 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, my friend told me to make a blog, so I did. I don't really know what to say. It's like 12:00am here and he woke me up while I was  trying  to sleep. But I never can. Fucking insomnia. Well, thats pretty much all I have to say right now. New post tomorrow, maybe. 
    
</post>


</Blog>