<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Mornin, y'all.      Interesting bits in the news this morning. First off, over 750 fell sick while visiting South Bass Island in Lake Erie this summer. They're not sure what to blame it on... hm... could it be partly because the Great Lakes are some of the most polluted waters in the nation? You stick your hand in the cesspool, you ain't getting it back. It's almost as bad just to breathe in the sea spray. Or- it could be a dirty restaurant worker who failed to wash their hands after a potty break... You see why I don't like to eat at restaurants so much anymore? A pube in the food is enough to turn any stomach.      In other news, the porn industry may require their participants to wear protection. And it only took how many outbreaks of the clap and AIDs to spark this course of action?       Well, another interesting night in the Olympic arena. A white man can  run , and fast. Hats off to Jeremy Wariner for disproving all sports analysts and 99% of spectators who thought a white athlete would never beat a sprinter of any other color.       And- would you believe it- a  raucous  night in gymnastics?       It seems that the crowds have gotten tired of the scores that the judges are giving. After a practically perfect vault from Romania's Marian Dragulescu, the judges almost  begrudgingly  gave him a 9.9- I can't remember the last time I've seen a 10 in this sport.   No one in the world can vault like Dragulescu. No one can stick a landing after a front triple like Dragulescu. A 10 wasn't in the cards, but he's supposed to be happy with a 9.9?    At that point, he was sitting pretty ranked #1. After his score flashed, he hid the disappointment, but fell on his landing on a vault that should have been a walk in the park. You tell me that he wasn't affected by his score.    Move to the parallel bars- same story. A flawless performance by Hiroyuki Tomita was surpassed by a gymnast who was far less powerful and daring. On high bar, Alexei Nemov completed an unheard of six- count 'em, folks,  six-  release moves and stuck his landing. What was his score? 9.7 . It was enough to rile up the crowd and boo the judges. It lasted for ten minutes, postponing Paul Hamm's routine, until Nemov stood up and urged the crowd to stop. Hamm's performance was nearly void of any discrepancy, but in my opinion, not good enough to surpass Nemov, which he did. Unsurprisingly. Hamm won the silver, Nemov's score was enough to send him home in 5th place.    It was a Malaysian judge who didn't think Nemov was good enough for a medal. Didn't you all know? Malaysia is the world's leading producer of first-rate gymansts! Sure are- they keep 'em all in a box underground and they're planning a release in time for the 2012 games.     In other news... I haven't suffered a wedgie yet today.    Peace.                             
    
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I'll be posting a link to my Ofoto albums (courtesy of Kodak) soon.   Once I post them, I'll pass along the user name and password via email.   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Hello again, y'all.  I can't resist making a comment or two about Svetlana Khorkina, the russian prima donna of gymnastics.  It seems that Svetlana is pretty sore about losing the all-around competition to America's Carly Patterson last week, and has taken to vocalizing her opinions to a russian newspaper. See, she feels that the judges had predetermined Patterson as the winner, and in her words, 'fleeced' her for the entire competition.  Let me take a step back. Khorkina is a product of the russian sports machine. They've churned out numerous gymnasts, divers, volleyball players, and wrestlers, among others. In a country that is too poor to support its once to be reckoned with space program, they invest everything they can into their athletes, and it has been paying off- until recently.  Alexei Nemov is the last man to my knowledge to win the men's all-round in gymnastics for Russia. Alexander Popov was 'The Russian Rocket' in Barcelona, Atlanta, and Sydney, but resolved to slink out of the pool after failing to qualify for events in which he'd previously been so feared in Athens. Rulon Garder defeated the russian wrestling favorite (can't think of his name, but this man was a BEAR) to win the gold medal. Now, don't get me wrong- these are all awesome athletes. They once dominated thier respective sports, but knew enough when they were defeated. I can't think of anyone who has acted as unprofessoinal and unclassy as Khorkina.  In Sydney, it was discovered that the vault had been set five centimeters too low and consequently sent Khorkina crashing to her knees. My heart went out to her. She fell off the parallel bars. Again, my heart went out to her. In Athens, she fell off the bars again. Guess what? My heart went out to her. When Patterson defeated her in the all-around competition, I felt a sense of sadness as I knew that it would be Khorkina's last Olympics. She paraded around the appartus, toting her flag, draping it over the parallel bars, acting like she has for the past ten years or so- the russian darling slash prima donna- a very fitting role.  She commented that the silver medal was grand, in so many words, and that it was the best day of her life. Yet, four days later, she's changing her tune and crying foul. Give me a break! Khorkina should wait to talk smack after the Olympics are over and stop falling off apparatus- then maybe she'd win the gold medal.  Anyone watching the competition can clearly see that Patterson was the most mechanically correct out of the entire field. She didn't fall, she didn't stumble. She deserved the gold and got it.  Khorkina has to realize that even though she is a sentimental favorite in the sport, it's not going to earn her medals. Near-perfect routines sometimes aren't even enough. It's a different scenario than Paul Hamm and the korean controversy- there, it was the judges screw-up. Here, it is Khorkina's screw up. Get over it, Svetlana. You're not the top dog anymore. The top dog won the gold, and even if she doesn't travel to Beijing to defend her title, she is still the Olympic champion.  However, feel free to come up with your own opinion.      If you're going to award gold medals to sentimental favorites because you feel they should get it, call Popov back to the pool and give him a couple. Give Jenny Thompson three. Hell, I have a lot of friends- give ME one.  Oh, wait- that's not how you're supposed to do it? Somebody had better tell Khorkina.        Peace.   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Mornin', Y'all.      Six a.m. and I am tired.  Just woke up a half hour ago and I'm ready to crawl back under the covers and snuggle with my pillows.  Anyone else feel the drudgery of life like a vicious, neverending cycle?  Eat, sleep, poop, something like that?        I'm too old at 25 to live on the edge anymore, and on the edge I mean spending all my money at clubs and staying out til dawn, only to stumble into work still smelling like smoke and alcohol.  I did that for a while.  Some of my friends still do that.  Number one, I don't know where they get the money because we all make the same amount, and number two,  it should be old to them by now.    It's like those 35 year olds who still try to pick up girls at the club, all spiffy in thier silk shirts and tapered pants.  Just  old .      I start a new job with FedEx soon, and I'll be working creature of the night hours- seriously.  11 p.m. to 7 a.m. Sunday through Thursday.  Hey, I'm not complaining.  It means that I'll miss all the lovely traffic down the 101 every evil morning and all the little shits coming back from nights of crazy partying.  I am no so much concerned with hours as I am with making enough money to feed my belly and Jess'.  And maybe get that guitar I've been eyeing on Musicians Friend for a while- a Squier Strat, all black and shiny.  But that's not important.      Wonder what shift I'll work when I become a doctor.  I watched a show where this ER surgeon had worked mids for three years.  Now that's just too much.  I'm hoping that if I specialize, I can  sort of  make my own hours.   Someone tell me I'm dreaming- I don't know how this stuff works!      Anyway, anyway, anyway... Off to the place where I stare at a computer all day.  Hope this finds y'all well and behaving yourself.      Peace.         
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Me. A doggy bed. Need I say more?  urlLink     
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Ah yes, the summer Olympics are now halfway over. I've settled into the familiar routine of watching absolutely nothing but sports for days on end until three in the morning. In about a week, I'll be at a loss as of what to watch for a while and then I'll settle into another routine- the same one that I had  before  the Olympics.      There's always stories that come out of the Olympics that inspire, anger, satiate even. Already I can think of three.      I enjoy Michael Phelps. Not only does he have bragging rights, he  refuses  to use them. He loves to be part of a team. He credits everyone around him for helping him succeed in a sport where it's all touch and go, literally. He's one of the most composed and humble athletes I have ever watched, and it's absolutely refreshing. He swims all year-round to give credit to everyone, himself last.       Paul Hamm is said to have won the gold medal in the men's gymnastics all-around on a judging error, and that the medal should have gone to a korean gymnast. First of all, shut up. Paul fell onto his ass during a vault, sunk all the way down to 12th place, and was able to pull it together enough to medal. The fact that he did  that  should be enough. It's always the fat assholes who like to judge our elite athletes behind a microphone as if it's easy to compete at world class competition level against the best of the best. Who the hell is Al Troutwig? Has he ever competed a day in his life in gymnastics?      And Jenny Thompson. I've followed her swimming career for as long as I can remember. Everyone makes such a huge song and dance about how she's the world's best teammate, helping her team members to the top of the podium, but has never won and individual gold medal. Do they  notice  how fast swimmers are at this level? How close the races are? They speak of a second as if it's an hour. Give me a break. Jenny has balls the size of Manhattan to swim competitively while she's immersed in medical school. She's also suffered heartbreak this year after losing her mother. Again, fat bastards behind a microphone make it so easy to judge and point out flaws rather than significance of strength and courage.      I'd like to start a pestering squad to urge Jenny to come back just one more time for Beijing. Then, her critics will have to shut up. How many of them can swim 50 meters in under 25 seconds? Assholes.      I love them all, all shapes and colors and religions. They are beautiful, talented, hard working, and they deserve every accolade we can give them. They also help to encourage me to work out pretty hard for two weeks out of every four years.      One more question- who is this chick who calls commentary during diving? I have literally seen ten competitors dive into the water, produce absolutely  no  splash, and this Elfie girl will say something like 'Oh, no, she was short of vertical...' , 'Nope, there were three drops of splash that landed on the forehead of the chinese judge...' Anyone give me some insight?      You gotta love sport.      Peace.        
    
    
</post>


</Blog>