<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dan- I'd fuck *Courtney*, but she's a cockteaser, so i wouldn't trust her   Me- Lol Zack still likes me, that bugs me   Dan- How?   Me- comes up to me and "tries" to flirt and stuff. was that guy snoring?????   Dan- yeah LOL.    Me- this skool is gay and i eat a lot   Dan- yeah u do fat ass JUST KIDDING   Me- ur so mean! i have no ass   Dan- lol u have more ass then me!   Me- My ass brings all of the boys to the yard, and they're like its better than your's.. damn right i could teach you but i have to charge   Dan- my dingaling brings all the girls to the yard... and they're like it's better then your's... damn right it's better then yours, i could teach you, but shit I'll just give it to u for free. lol. I want to go to ms. tarzan and pull on her tiger skin!   Me- her thong is cheetah print! ewww~ when i told Shaho that he was like THAT'S FUCKING SICK! You like it????    Dan- anyways, NO! I DON'T LIKE IT!   Me- her thong's all messed up! someone's been shopping at the salvation army!   Dan- yeah no shit, it's all torn up and stuff   Me- my thong says margarita and i got it from CR, not the donation place.   Dan- LEMME SEE!!! i'd show u my undies but im not wearing any. lol   Me- THAT IS JUST FREAKIN SICK. how u like it daddy, how u like it daddy... lol. freek-a-leek   Dan- I FUCKIN LOVE IT MOMMY! take it off! lol   Me- TELL ASH TO HER'S OFF, HELL NO. NOT MINE. I HAVE A BF THANK YOU.   Dan- I'm not wearing any. there's only one way to find out.....   Me- Dan, get a fucking life. STOP FUCKING VIBRATING MY CHAIR!!!   Dan- lol. meet me in the bath. in 5. JK   Me- Oh jesus   Dan- I'm not jesus, but i can be one   Me- Go screw urself   Dan- that tarzan looks goofy and she's fucking ugly   Me- awww.  that's mean!  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Me- Hey I'm bored, i writing to u, cuz no one else in this class is awake   Xak- ya me too. we should make out :)    Me- ZACK!!!! see! come on now! you now I'm with my bf   Xak- ok well let's strip then.   Me- I do that on sundays JK   Xak- invite me over sometimes   Me- YEAH RIGHT   Xak- We should play strip-tac-toe   Me- Let's not   Xak- ok, when r u gonna dump him   Me- prolly never   Xak- I'm a reall man   Me- yeah, a real man whore   Xak- psha! one of these days... just one of these days. u'll find out.   Me- And one of these days Eric will kick your sorry ass  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hi *GooGoo!   Hi how are you val. Ur a freakin alchy   I’m so not. I like how mr. a sys ur name. JK so wuts up   Nothing, u   What does it look like? Jk do we get daily planners here. He we get to take da new SAT   We usually do, but we would have had it by now. What new sat?   We have a new form. Renzo’s nuts.   Renzo’s nuts is our new form. That makes sense   Hahaha. I think *Allen looks like a blind dude. Nice cover for the food.   HAHAHA, me too, thank you. U know ur hungary   Hungary is a country, yeah I’m starving. Who the heck voted him as prez?   I didn’t, explain ur weekend.   Went over at my friend’s, got Jack’s and came back home, hid the bottle in my dresser, my mom found it. I got grounded.   Wow, fun weekend. Do u drink a lot.   No   …… do u have diarrhea?   NO! stop im gonna put tarantula on ur bed   I hate spiders so much. Ill shit on your pillowcase   Yeah well, I’ll piss on your face   I’ll fart in your mouth   I’ll ***in your mouth JUST KIDDING   Your dirty   And you like X-Tina   I’ll giz in your ass   Ur fuckin nasty! Skanky bastard   Hey you started it   Not the giz! Eww! I have to pee   You said *** go pee then   Which one should I do, JK   Well if you can get urself off that much then it’s your choice. Go pee or clog it with a finger.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        First of all, ALL real names have been replaced by other names. I will not tell you who the notes are from and who wrote them (well, most of all of them are between me and my friends).  
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Holy fuckin shit. Today went completely nuts. First thing in the morning Zack asked me if I wanted to fuck with him. Second hour, Renzo burst out water from his mouth cuz I made him laugh and I went to the bathroom and my ass almost fell in the fuckin toilet. I didn't eat my freakin lunch cuz I had to take my English pre-test. I dropped out of AP class- didn't do my summer reading. I'M SUCH A REBEL. AHAHAAHAH. Anyway, in English class, Mizz Wenz started singing kumbaya and we started reading our stories in the dark, which was pretty cool, cept some kid threw up. Oh! and stupid Drew told me "You're so sexy I'm gonna fuck you upside down". HE IS SO FREAKIN UGLY. And in Dance, which is my last class, Mizz Garner told me that I have an excellent hip rotation and pointe. COOL COOL. Oh, never will I go to the bathroom ever again.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>