<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today was a regular school day. I got to school and survived through Mr.Perez going on about Jewish law. Then I went to Web Design and watched a pretty interesting video on the history of the internet. After a short break I showed up for Biology and did really good on our quiz. Thats when things started going down hill. When I got into fourth period I had a really bad headache. Then at lunch by the time i got my food it was time to go to class. Spanish and Algebra were easy. Then came AVID. I had to listen to my new AVID teacher talk about how things are going to be different this year. We've been going over this for the past four days. It's getting pretty old. Well after that I came home did my homework and started on this. Thats about everything that happened to me today.  
    
</post>


<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today was actually a pretty good day for me. I did well on my Biology quiz and was great during Spanish. I guess i got enough sleep last night. I was pretty tired. When I woke up this morning i wasnt very crabby about waking up at 6:30. Today my Web Design teacher (Mr.Briggs) assigned us a project. We have to keep a blog for three days and then email the address to him so he can see how it's going. My Bio teacher has to be the most boring man alive. He wont look at anyone when he is talking and his voice is monotone. He told us today that one of his hobbies is to go to southern California to catch spiders to keep in the class room. He also told us that his job before he was a teacher was to go through a jar of goop takeing out all the fish larva and fish eggs. he seemed pretty proud of it. I think it was pretty pathetic. Oh well thats all that happened to me today.  
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today started like anyother monday. I woke up crabby becuse I didnt get to sleep until about12:00. I know that doesnt seem late but I need about 9 hours of sleep in order to be in a good mood. When I got to school my I heard an announcement that we had to meet in the gym at fourth period to listen to our new vice principal ramble on and on about all the new rules. Then when I got to seventh period my class got in an argument with our teacher about how to organize our binders. After I got home I did my homework and then BBQed some hamburgers for dinner. Now I'm starting a blog for the first time.  
    
</post>


</Blog>