<Blog>


<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      this guy...this guy right here with the two opposable thumbs is exhausted. just got back after a day at work. long in actual time, but short in what it seemed. i ran out of bus passes today so picked up a new booklet. 30 dollars for 10 days. too much money. in seattle public transportation is awful...the only choices are a) buses, b) taxi's or c) the monorail built in 1967 for the world fair when it was in seattle that goes a full seven blocks in downtown no where near where i live, but it caught on fire recently and so it doesn't work anyway. taxi's cost too much. it all comes down to the bus. ive been looking through craigslist like mad for a bike, but every time someone writes me back with an offer, part of the deal is that i need to come pick it up. yet i dont know seattle and have no way of getting there. if i had a car i could, or even a scooter maybe. i actually got close to acquiring a bike the other day--Hugh told me he'd bring it by the office (which i agreed to out of desperation not even thinking about where i would keep it for the day). it was only twenty dollars. a damn good deal for a bike. so i asked him to tell me about the bike (yeah that part mattered less to me than just having it). he told me it didn't have any wheels. the chain is rusted completely through. one of the handle bars was slightly bent which kind of affected the steering. oh, and it was purple. i told Hugh: "i think im going to abort the mission." he wasn't too happy but he agreed to cancel. i feel somewhat isolated. the u district is no island...but my inability to get where i want when i want can frustrate the hell out of me. waiting for the 74 has become an art. i air drum a lot. sometimes i pace in off time signatures around the bus stop. i look away for a good ten seconds and then turn quickly around thinking that my spontaneity will increase the likelihood that the bus will round the bend. it's worked only once. but it was a good once.  im going to sit at my desk for a little while longer...look at things, listen to some music, maybe talk to myself a bit. being alone can be liberating (that's what they say at least) but it can also be damn boring.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      this one came out a few days ago but couldn't pass it up. its witty interesting a-okay:  http://www.nytimes.com/2004/08/22/arts/television/X22ZENG.html  this editorial in the ny times is important to read:  http://www.nytimes.com/2004/08/24/opinion/24tue2.html 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday I had a day off so I took the 71 downtown to the Seattle Arts Museum to see the Van Gogh exhibit. The line was long and when I got to the front of the line, the tickets cost more than I had. I told the woman I was a member of the American Association of Museums, which wasn't a total lie as I was a full, card carrying member for a year. It was actually incredible. Any museum: bypass the lines, get in for free. You could be with five other friends. Everyone in for free. Discounts on meals in any museum. Small, pre-packaged sandwiches and bottles of water! Discounts on stuff in the museum store. Postcards, big coffee table books, Picasso shot glasses! My membership expired two months ago and I lost the card though. Yet even in death...the American Association of Museum's spirit lives on: after I mentioned the bad timing ("I can't believe this...and not two months earlier...") the woman smiled, gave me a ticket and pointed me to the entrance to the exhibit.   Van Gogh makes me feel really strange. When I look at his paintings I get anxious. Uneasy. I dont want to move when I am standing in front of any of his paintings. I feel like I can't spend enough time looking. Looking at what? Those damn thick brush strokes. The freaking vibrant colors. The fucking lines! It drives me crazy. It's just too good. If I leave and go onto the next piece, I feel guilty. Did I stay long enough? Did I miss something? I desribed this feeling to Pike this way: when a little girl sees a puppy and just wants to attack and squeeze it because its so cute. I mean, I wouldn't go as far to say his paintings are cute, but I want to squeeze the hell out of them.   I did eventually make it out of there and on the bus ride back there were two women of note. One was a black woman, about 45, whose lips were injected with botox and who looked like she was on the cusp of death. The other, an overweight deaf woman with seven oversized stuffed bags that probably carried her life in them. The former, carried a McDonalds bag in one hand and a crushed McDonalds paper cup with a straw in the other. She was shaking. At one stop, she stood up abruptly and threw the cup out the door onto the pavement. Sitting next to her was a young bald guy, dressed in tattered clothing, but for style. They didn't know eachother. The woman started laughing at his tatoo covered arms. He reached into his bag and pulled out a binder, which had his drawings that looked like tatoos or something you'd put on your arms. She laughed harder. Then he started to laugh too. They stepped off the bus together and as the doors closed behind them, they held hands nervously and started laughing. We turned the corner and lost them.  The deaf woman sat down and stared at the ground. She hadn't said anything when the driver asked for her fare. Then she looked up, startled. And began to sign. Sign and sign. Sign toward the back of the bus. But no one signed back. She was talking to herself.  Work tomorrow is early...and I will be there late...where will you be?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I am in Seattle....don't really know how I got here. But I am here. For those of you who don't know, I'll fill you in. For those of you who do know...read on anyway. My whole game plan, long term plan, whatever,  was basically to wait tables in DC and try to get involved in the Kerry campaign in any way that I could. About a week and a half ago, I was ready to give up. I couldn't find anyone who wanted to hire me. Everywhere I turned, they would say, "We could always use volunteers." I told myself, one more week of searching, sending resumes, coverletters and all those other stupid things that we were supposed to learn how to do in the career centers of our colleges, and then I'm giving up. I'll wait tables and volunteer. Then out of the blue I got a call from Seattle. A few calls and few writing samples later, I was hired as the press assistant/deputy press secretary for Senator Patty Murray of Washington State's reelection campaign. I was to fly out to Seattle in a only a week and a half. I scoured Craigslist and quickly found a cheap sublet in the U District...bought a plane ticket and now all of a sudden I am in Seattle. I have no idea how I got here.  When I first got here I stayed in the Jet Motel across the way from the airport. Without my bags. American Airlines lost them. I ate dinner at 2 in the morning at Denny's. I have definitely not taken advantage of that restaurant. I don't care what people say about it. Food poisoning? Fake eggs? Doesn't faze me...and it shouldn't faze you either. Do it. Eat at Denny's.  In the morning, a rather heavy set woman, with brown caked-on make-up named Sharon picked me up in her brand new silver Mercedes convertible and drove me into Seattle to meet up with the landlord at my apartment. Sharon had sat next to me last night on my flight. She turned out to be the Secretary of the Washington Democrats. She also turned out to be a serious talker. I tried everything...headphones, pretending to sleep, reading my book. She didn't stop. Something good did come of our "conversation" though: she told me that she would do anything to help Senator Murray, even if anything meant driving thirty minutes away to pick up a stranger at 8 in the morning at the shadiest hotel in the Seattle area. She sped us into Seattle with the top down and the wind blowing through her blow dried hair. I was freezing....she seemed totally comfortable.  Seattle, for those of you who have never seen it...is really beautiful. The air is crisp and clean...the views are spectacular....water is all over the place...snow capped .mountains peek out in the distance (kind of)...and according to Sharon, it doesn't rain as much as everyone assumes. She seemed like she knew. And I believe her.  My apartment is small, but fully furnished. It's perfect for me. I even have a catholic church that faces me as I look out of my window....so while I am sleeping or just vegging out in my apartment I can feel closer to Jesus. They were singing "Gloria" today, and as I thought back to Mr. Payton's middle school music class, I instinctively started to sing along. It was really a glorious moment. Me in my underwear (i had just gotten out of a shower and was air drying because my towels were in my lost luggage) looking out of my window singing along, them dressed up in the Church, me a Jew, they, Catholics...the juxtaposition of faiths and backgrounds...I almost cried.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>