<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, while driving fast up I-88, I was thinking. I was thinking about heaven, now as we all know heaven is a "place" that you go when you die, and through faith, trust and obedience in Jesus Christ will get you there... Here is the kicker, or perhaps I just like to play devils advocate?  Say (for instance) that I am a perfect Christian and when I die I'm going to heaven (SAY IT!!!). Now also suppose that around me I have a group of people whom I love dearly and have strived throughout my whole life to bring them to God, and I also believe that these people are going to heaven, because I love them, and I believe they believe in Jesus Christ... Now now I die, I'm going to heaven and it turns out that the people whom I loved dearly managed to get a one-way trip to hell and they will be spending an eternity in pain and anguish.  When we go to heaven, arnt we supposed to be re-united with those whom we love? If all those who we love go to hell, isnt it a little bit of a raw deal. Sure, you have an eternity to spend with Jesus Christ (which dont get me wrong, is pretty darn great), but you also have to come to terms with the fact that you will never see those people who you loved ever again... for eternity.  Now given all that, doesnt that make it kinda sour in heaven...? Wouldnt it be just "dandy" if everyone went to heaven. I really loved the movie  urlLink What Dreams May Come , and I think that the my idea really goes in tandem with this movie. The problem with the movie is that I dont think (I dont know for certain) that we can leave heaven, go to hell and bring back those we love? Wouldnt that be nice?  Which leaves me to my second thought? (Maybe it should be points to ponder). Ok, so I died and find myself in hell (and pretty surprised too). Wouldnt it be feasible to continue to try and make a peace with God? Perhaps our cries of pain and desperation would be heard by God and he will take pity on us, and reach down to save us? In fact, to further the mindless direction, perhaps in the same vein, we could be like preachers in hell and preach the gospel to those perishing in hell... If I understand Christ as I think I do, his love is unbounding, and perhaps maybe those in hell CAN be saved. Just think of the metaphor of the lost sheep, think of how many lost sheep are toiling in the depths right now. Wouldnt it be a glorious time in heaven when we trully get to be reunited with all those we loved...  Or perhaps heaven will be an eternity without your friends...   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so I spent far too much time today checking out another website and reading it throughout.  The website in question is  urlLink Things My Girlfriend and I Have Argued About . I found the whole thing to be funny and oddly familiar. I dont argue too much but...  Also I want to mention  urlLink Wikipedia , which is my most favourite site of all in the past few weeks. I find myself going to the homepage, clicking on a article about say, "The Spanish Civil War" and end up going in-depth into why the Americans "REALLY" entered into WWII on the European front... Or read an article about George W. Bush or John F. Kerry, and end up reading about secretive orders that aim to control society by putting the wealthy in power... That doesnt happen in reality does it?  I continue to scour the web for things that make me go "uh". To infinity and... well thats far enough isnt it?     
    
    
</post>


</Blog>