<Blog>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you been watching the Olympics?  I have.  I got really nervous before the 100m Hurdles today.  They were putting SO much pressure on the Canadian to win.  I kept seeing specials on her and everything.  So I kept flipping the channel while they were setting the race up.  Then I HAD to watch, and our poor Canadian FELL before she hit the first hurdle.  It was SO sad.  The local channels had set-up cameras where her family was watching the race, and they were so devestated, poor girl.  very sad.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So what's new to tell everyone about.  Well, it is mainly just me and Ridley around the house no adays.  Colin and I rescued a kitten at Colin's uncles on Saturday night.  Brought it home, and the cat was SO CUTE!!  I called up Lexie and said, I have a new kitten in my house, but if you want it you can have it.  So Lexie is the proud new owner of a little girl kitten she named Potter.  Hopefully Lexie can tell us all how the vet visit went today.  I am still looking for work, I had an interview with the National Ballet on Monday, they are making it REALLY difficult to get into their organization, which hopefully means they would be good to work for eventually.  They said they would call people back on Thursday whether you got the job or not, cross your fingers!!  I start volunteering with the 'word on the street festival' preparations on Thursday night.  Hopefully that will be fun.  I was at the library today, and they were holding this tea and books 'event', which I stuck around for.  The director of my library told us a list of her favourite new books, and read bits of each of them while we sipped iced tea, it was nice.  I sat next to this lovely elderly woman who I spoke a bit about the books with after the event finished.   Girls night at the Drake on Saturday night, I have no idea how to get there, since its so far West on Queen.  But should be fun.     And its the MTV Video awards on CityTV Sunday night, I hope someone I LIKE performs for a change.    Got tickets for the Franz Ferdinand concert October 1st, I am terribly excited about that, my new favourite band.  Maybe I will get a t-shirt at the concert.  The Toronto Film Festival movies are posted on the web now, www.e.bell.ca/filmfest.  The movie I was hoping to be at the festival this year wasn't chosen, so I am sad about that.  Sandy is ecstatic that the new John Waters film will be at the fest.  I am a little scared of it myself, but hopefully it will be fun.  Ladies get your choices in for the Visa Screening room movies you want to see.  Kirsten, what nights did you want again, Monday and Thursday I think, at the Elgin.  Wow, I guess I did have a lot of things to talk about.  Well, hopefully you didn't skim or fall asleep reading about my life!!  Let me know what is going on with you.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>