<Blog>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       how cool is this?    urlLink     Maxim magazine is my favorite :o)  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      as I noticed him singing along to the obscure jukebox selection I didn't tell him I made, a goofy smile uncontrollably broke across my face.  In came the sappiness.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   1/27/2002 6:24 PM PDT   in the future, people need to remind the wench that too many alcoholic beverages tend to cause her to say things she feels are witty and alluring to the males seated near her, (translation: shots and beer make me flirt WAY too much, and that's not ALWAYS a good thing...)  No harm was done this time (that I know of) but maybe the lack of physical release in my life also attributed to the rampage of drunken flirting attempted last night. we need to remedy that situation. drastically.  -wench
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1/26/2002 9:24 PM PDT     who said being sober is the way to be? I am SOOO drunk right now, thanks in part to PPGoddess, and also in part to 2 of the men I lust for but can't have. Matt bought me a beer, Dom refused his shot... I told dom, brandon & matt more than I should have. and I'm having trouble typing more tommorrow, when sober, -beerWench
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   1/24/2002 6:25 PM PDT   Why must I always long to be with the men I can't have? Matt, Brandon, Ryan, Drew, Dominic, Jeff, Charlie (not so much anymore of course), Gideon Yago, the host of Beat the Geeks... New information will help past my past, Dominic was wise to share exactly as much as he did. He got the point across, but didn't make it hurtful. For a moment, I almost cried, but as I've said all along, since I've met him, I just want him to be happy. And now, he is. It's sad that I made the situation such that he and I can no longer be friends. I do miss hearing his opinion on things. Without his influence, I would've never checked out Kittie, wouldn't have heard of Jack Off Jill, or much of the punk I now enjoy. If I hadn't gotten my punk foundations from hanging out with him, Ray and I (and therefore Chris and I) wouldn't have had nearly as much to start talking to eachother about, and I would have missed out on 2 good friends, AND a formal dance date. So now, starting today, January 24, 2002, I have exactly 7 months to find an amazing date to Paul and Mindy's wedding. Either absolutely gorgeous, or, fawning at elbow, bowing to my every whim... wonder if I can pay someone to act either of those roles out? A combination maybe? And by then, maybe the slight pain I'm masking with 'happy-for-him-that-he's-happy'ness, will be truly gone. In 7 months, *I* could be ab
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   1/23/2002 7:49 PM PDT   I love it when my friends are happy, really I am... but lately, it seems all my friends get to be happy, and falling in love, or already madly in love, and I get to have a lot of good friends. I'm not complaining, but it'd be nice if I could get some good lovin'. For heaven's sake, it's been over a year now! I'll be ok, maybe I can persuade a particular writing friend of mine to see things in a different light.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   1/20/2002 4:16 PM PDT   As much as I try not to miss him, unless I'm let back into his life I still will, that's not going to go away. Trying doesn't make it easier, only harder. And now, new info. And I want to do something about it, but my hands are so tied on this. I don't want to overstep bounds, but I don't know what those bounds are. How do you deal with the death of an ex's parent, especially whent that ex is seeing someone new?
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1/8/2002 9:02 AM PDT     Still no kiss in 2002... But I have had the chance to hang with some really cool friends, some of which I don't appreciate enough, and others which I just underestimate. Hanging with Becca tonight, haven't seen her for quite some time. I feel loved lately, even without the lovin'. It's a nice feeling. Not that I'd turn down the lovin' should the right offer come along :o)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   1/2/2002 7:50 PM PDT   Still no kiss in 2002... New Year's Eve was almost just like any other night, except Mulligan's gave us each a free glass of champagne to drink at midnight. While my roommate and her boyfriend kissed as the ball dropped, I took that glass down like a shot, and then, when time came for us to toast, I had nothing left but a massive mug of beer... ah well, I had nothing in particular to toast to anyway. At least I didn't get pseudo-dumped again. :o) 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, with Christmas coming, I figured I could give this a shot...  urlLink Buy Me Stuff Link   hey - it worked for PPs birthday...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      11/27/2001 9:55 AM PDT     I like him a lot. I'm honored to know him in any capacity, which for now, is acquaintance, bordering on friend... someone to hang out with at mulligan's and talk over a beer or two, and hang out and watch movies with. even if things don't progress beyond that point, I'm a happy person for having the chance to know him :o) 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      11/19/2001 3:48 PM PDT     ok, it's time to take a few steps back and take some time for myself, to figure out what *I* want, and where I'm headed with myself, so until I get my own head straight, I am keeping myself away from any and all boys in any capacity beyond friendship. Staying away from the alcohol has really helped with that. tomorrow will be 2 weeks (minus one night of cheating, but as I said, he MADE me - thought it'd help him out once he got me home... hee hee, :o) nothing happened that wouldn't have sober) Thanksgiving should maybe change the abstaining, from one or the other, my family will drive me to it... Further updates ahead.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      11/13/2001 7:52 PM PDT     argh! He made me cheat! That crazy boy made me go against my alcohol abstinance, and split a pitcher with him. Granted, him kissing me later probably had something to do with it... he should know that the same exact events could have occurred without me drinking... Silly boy. How could he NOT know I've been into him for months? Honestly, he had all the signs...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      11/11/2001 8:35 PM PDT     The beerWench is taking some time off from the bottle. Call it abstaining, call it a test of will power, call it a mini-diet (so many empty calories...) call it I'm broke, call it what you will, but little to no alcohol will enter my system for an undetermined period of time... Wish me luck, though I don't THINK I'll need it :o)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      11/1/2001 5:16 PM PDT     too much to say... boys are evil, in general... when I think they aren't, they are, and while I'm thinking they aren't, I hurt the ones who really aren't... sorry for being cryptic  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      10/9/2001 1:42 PM PDT     Hey gang... that  urlLink KDS  urlLink   show downtown was kinda lame due to technical difficulties beyond the control of the band, but they more than made up for it this past saturday at the Intersection... The next night, we saw a few bands play, again at the  urlLink Intersection , the headliner being my newest VERY favorite band  urlLink - Lucky Boys Confusion  Great show, lots of fun... I danced as much as I could, then laughed at the pathetic attempt at a mosh pit, and can't wait til they come to town again. After the show, I even got a few of the band guys to sign my cd case :)  Off to class now - GR AT&T Broadband cable channel 28 from 6-9 pm tonight...   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      9/21/2001 8:29 AM PDT     Anyone in the Grand Rapids, MI area should head downtown around noontime tomorrow to the Monroe Center ampitheater to watch Knee Deep Shag with me!   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      9/20/2001 6:52 AM PDT     I found a new friend. It's name is vicodin. It keeps my mouth from feeling the pain I should be feeling from having my 4 wisdom teeth yanked out of my head while I lay completely unconscious yesterday. That's about all that's new that's happened to me in recent days, outside of my friend Jeff burning me a really really cool cd of music, most of which I've never heard, but all with a nice little happy beat :o) 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      9/19/2001 7:07 AM PDT     Soon, you will no longer see the same backdrop behind me when my cam actually *does* work... soon, in less than a week, I will have a new home, a new bedroom of my very own, one less roommate, but a happier apartment. I think the move will drastically improve the friendship between myself and the roommate we are abandoning to move off on our own. I feel a little guilty because she has to get a second job, and her mother to co-sign on her new apartment because we up and told her we're moving out, but she's known this was coming for quite some time...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      9/10/2001 8:57 AM PDT     well... you can't see me on my cam yet - modem driver's still jacked, BUT - if you live in the Grand Rapids area, and get AT&T cable, you can watch me sit through a boring class every tuesday from 6-9 pm... channel 28 people! how exciting. yay.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      8/14/2001 7:41 PM PDT     I'm done with Paul for forever now. He's moved back in with Mom in Kalamazoo, which, granted, isn't too far away, but he has no car. Thank god. There's one closed chapter to my life. I'm over Ray. Way over. Not his cute cousin though ;o). I'm very into Jeff at the moment, but fear I'm too *bad* for him... we'll see. I hope not. I really like him. He's nice, sweet, fun, and very very cool. In MY opinion...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      7/26/2001 8:52 PM PDT      urlLink Shag  was fun. Shagging the lead singer would have been more fun. That's a semi-longstanding crush. What happened last week... Meijer doesn't carry darts in the summer, what's up with that? The Saturday party was kinda lame, Paul being the only guest coming to see me (besides  urlLink Kate  of course) and Jeremy just thinks I hate him. Paul, on the other hand should hate me, but keeps freaking calling. I give him no indication that I'm even mildly interested in his company when he's present. What's his problem? When I did want his attention, running, beer, and the guys came first. Now that I realize how boring he is and how mismatched we are, I can't get him to leave me alone. Anyway. That's highly irrelevent. Tonight was chillin' with Min & Paul. Tomorrow night, is a pseudodate with 'little Jeff' as Mindy calls him. Update on that soon :o) Didn't get the balls to call Matt and let him know I'd be in town... Wouldn't have had time for him anyway, it seems. Ray's been acting funny lately. I hope I didn't do anything to piss him off at the concert. He seems rather disturbed when we talk. And doesn't seem to want to hang out. Further research needed for that issue though. This is long enough for now.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      7/19/2001 9:10 AM PDT      urlLink Blink / urlLink NFG  concert was awesome. Ran into Matt from  urlLink GMI  there too, very cool. they played some good songs... wish I could have maybe spent more time hanging with musicians... any of them... but it was still fun. Ray & I are good at hanging out with eachother. He's a really nice fun guy. Wish I could make myself like him more. But MATT! I got digits :o) I wonder if he thought Ray & I were *together* Hmm... I guess we'll see. That's IF I have the balls to call him at some point. Tomorrow night is Shag at the 'section. Can't wait for that! :o)   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      7/16/2001 8:09 PM PDT     Ray & his cute playa' cousin Chris stopped by randomly tonight. Ray's been to my dirty nasty apartment before, so he wasn't shocked. Chris on the other hand, walked around with this fascinated expression on his face. I couldn't tell if he was dumbfounded that we live here at all (he is 20, lives with parents in an awesome house) or just that it was so dirty, and he didn't expect that from me. I couldn't explain to them in front of my roommate that the mess was mainly contributable to her. I hope Chris doesn't think I'm a pig. They left quickly. I think they thought they were interrupting me. Interrupting my boredom, that's about it. Damn.   Ray and I are leaving for New Found Glory & Blink 182 in 35 1/2 hours. That will be an interesting day. We'll see...   Debating whether I should call Little Paul back. It's been a week now since he called me. Did I make him wait long enough, or is it not long enough until he gives up and calls again? Games suck. But if I'm going to have to learn them, this is the one to practice on I guess.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      7/13/2001 6:54 AM PDT     Party at Ray's tonight. Julie's leaving me for over a week. As much as I hate to admit it, even though I don't actually want to be with him now, and couldn't even start to deal with that thought, I'm missing the ex... missing just hearing from him every once in a while. Won't call though. That wouldn't be good. Stay strong. As for the other ex, hearing from him too much, and satisfied that it's still bothering me that he wants to hang with me. When I start thinking it's ok, that's a problem. When I come in here and say *Paul and I had so much fun last night* that can't be a good thing, take me in to get psychoanalysis. I really need to remember my diaryland password so I don't have to spill all this for the general public, who I'm sure don't give a flying fuck. I took " urlLink The Gay Test " at  urlLink theSpark.com  - turns out I'm 44% gay. Females taking the test average 32% I guess. Hmm...   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      7/11/2001 5:41 PM PDT     why do I do things that complicate my life? why why why why why?   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      housewarming rocked.  Kate posted pics at her  urlLink MSN community .  I didn't get there in time to make it into any of the pics, no girl-on-girl action for me until we were broadcasting much later in the evening (and many drinks later).  More updates to come, but needed to get that link in there.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, Valentine's day has come and gone.  Still haven't been kissed in 2002.  Did get my chest  happily  molested in public, and was told what someone would do to me if I was his slave.  Still hung up on a particular Monkey King, even though it won't happen, but now with even more encouragement, why must everyone tell ME that we should be together, I'm the one that gets it... fucking tell  him  that.  Saturday's housewarming party should be interesting.   Brandon .  Hmm...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that Thursday evening, Kate and I will be throwing ourselves a pity party after I get out of work. Another lonely V-day. At least this time, less lonely, because I'll have my favorite girlie-girl with me :o) We better get wasted, and we better get sympathy drinks from the men at our favorite pub. Maybe the Monkey King will be back from abroad, and feeling generous... I miss that boy, crazy, isn't it?  He's only been gone a week.    *hugs* to everyone who has someone to make *every* day like a sappy romantic holiday... if you know anyone, send 'em my way.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love my friend Kate. Who else would go with me to the Red Barn & Velvet Touch AND buy matching stuff with me :o) (and loan me a few bucks to do it). I'm sure K8 and the Brain will have just as much fun as me and Tyler Durden will have in the future. It's great to have good friends, that are comfortable and trusting enough to go sex toy shopping together...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not much to talk about lately...  Spending way too much time on line, and therefore not expanding my off-the-net social life.  Need to work on and submit a resume.  One job in particular in mind.  Working for a church though, not sure I can pull that off.  Kinda low lately, damn holiday on the horizon making me feel less than perfect.  Nationally recognized holiday reminding me that *Oh yeah, I'm STILL alone* not that going to bed alone every night isn't reminder enough...  aargh, enough whining, at least I have good friends to love me...  and I'm working ALL day on V-Day, so I don't need to sit home irritated that no one asked me out.  But, that means no Red Barn shopping trip for me and Kate if she doesn't have plans...  We'll go soon though. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      he hugged me.  what the fuck?
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok. I know the BEST way to depress yourself is to evaluate your life based on all the things you DON'T have, but that hasn't stopped me from doing that lately.   All I really need is a date.  One date.  Someone to pick me up, tell me I look nice, hold doors for me, take me to dinner, hold my hand during a movie, kiss my cheek at the door, say goodnight, and tell me they'll call me. Even if it's a lie.  Last time that happened to me?  June of 2000.  I've had some non-traditional dating adventures since, and that last one WAS the start of a pleasant six month relationship, (he wasn't lying when he said he'd call) so I can't complain about that. After that date, I'm sure I'll then need one night where mr fabulous and I rent a movie neither of us really care if we see, curl up with each other, and nervously distract eachother from the screen.  Damn, that'd be nice.  Sex would be cool too, but I can do that on my own.  It takes a really good imagination to have someone hold you, when they aren't there.  Wake up with strong arms around you that aren't really there...   I need to find someone who will be connected to those arms.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I've known my friend  urlLink Mindy  since  urlLink kindergarten .   This August, she's getting  urlLink married .    I've known this since Christmas, but as more and more plans are finalized, it's seeming more and more real to me.  I've seen a few of my cousins get married in the past few years, and a few friends as well, but none are hitting home quite as much as this one.  I guess none of them have seemed so... permanant.  Min & Paul have been together 2 years, and for a girl who's normally nauseated around *cute* couples, I love watching them be snuggly.  I love that Mindy's as happy as she is.  I'm glad that through her, I got to meet Paul, who's a pretty cool guy to talk to.  I love watching a couple who, in my mind, there is no doubt will *work*.  The idea of marriage in general terrifies me, maybe because I doubt I'll ever find someone that doesn't make the word *forever* seem like such a bad thing.  So, on August 24th, I'll be watching someone I used to play hopscotch with, sell girl scout cookies with, talk about *Pop Can*s with (had to be there), get drunk with, quote Monty Python, and sing to Violent Femmes with, commit herself to a life with Paul.  The only scary part about that union - I don't think I'll EVER be able to spell his last name right :o)   ~~~   One afternoon, my friend Sarah started asking me what plans I'd made for my wedding.  My first thought was, I'm 9, do I really need to think of these things yet?   She seemed insistant, so, in order to not be the only freak girl without my wedding planned in the 3rd grade, I made up some details about a dress, and that satisfied her enough, mostly because it let her start going on about ALL her plans...  Months later, she asked me what I was going to name my children.  "Children?" I thought, "  I'm   still a child!"  But I decided that a boy and a girl was a standard answer, so I picked random names for one of each.  I never understood the point in planning some of those things so far in advance.  Why start thinking about weddings when you're not even dating someone?  Why start naming kids, when you're not ready to have them, or sure you'll want them?   Instead, I sat and thought about what I'd name my band when I formed one.  I didn't care that I didn't yet know how to play an instrument, that, to me, seemed irrelevant.  I guess in the same way Sarah, at age 9, didn't need to know the name of her future husband to plan their wedding and children.  I planned my band's style, image, and am just now, at the age of (almost) 23, taking the steps to learn the guitar.  We'll see if the band that had originally been named *Awesome Rainbow Sunshine* (since altered to Fingercuffs, yes, I still daydream about it all)_ever makes it into the spotlight.  Our first album will no longer be named *Boys are Stupid* (though that's not a bad idea, hmmm...)  I'm not a normal girl.  I'm not ashamed of that fact. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can no longer say I haven't kissed anyone in 2002.  I thought that would be a good thing.  It's not.  I shouldn't have.  I'm sorry.  I tried to fight it, but between the allergy meds, all the alcohol, and the months and months of chastity, I couldn't.  That doesn't make it any less evil, but it's the truth.  I shouldn't try to rationalize, but I'm human, we learned in communication classes, this is what we do.  I love you, I don't want you to stay mad at me, though you have every reason to, and are well within your rights if you do.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok.  He still gives me those comfortable butterflies, but I really am giving up this time.  I came to a revelation the other night.  When I stop wondering if he's EVER gonna realize I'm perfect for him, and just start having fun hanging out again, I realize how much I'd miss him if we DID fool around and that screwed up the friendship.  I've known all along that can't wait for him forever, it's just NOW that I'm realizing I can't wait any longer, and I'm not gonna push it.  I'm gonna let what ever happens to me, happen.  When I feel a connection with someone, I'm not going to hold back just in case he some day comes around (I felt myself doing this once or twice in recent months).  In the meantime, I have someone in my head, but I'm keeping this one to myself, because I have no idea what's in this boy's head.  Can't wait for Jell-o Night at Kate's, then an evening in D-Town.  I get to hang with family, friends, and people I haven't seen since christmastime.  Long drive for one night, but they're worth it.  Most of them are, at least...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      when julie and I moved into our apartment, not only was I disappointed in the small size of our bathroom, but also at the lack of storage they provided us in the room.  we even had one of those industrial toilets - no tank, just pipes, like I had back in the dorms.  so one less spot to place things.  the other day, I came home from work, and all our rugs and a few tiles were soaking wet, and in the tub, the floor a little damp, and the room smelling musty.  I immediately blamed my roomie's bf, assuming he flooded the toilet, or didn't close the shower curtain, or something.  Thursday I came home, and the maintenance man stopped me on the way into the building to tell me the water was shut off for a couple hours, he was doing work downstairs.  I was irritated, but I dealt.  Until all of the sudden, with no one around, the toilet started flushing wildly all on its own, and then flooding into the bathroom.  Julie ran downstairs, grabbed the man, he tightened a pipe, and it was better, for the time being.  Yesterday, I came home, and we have a BRAND NEW TOILET!  with a tank so we can set things there, a normal shaped toilet seat (not oval, with the slit at the front) which we can now switch and use the glow in the dark toilet seat our wonderful friend becca gave us for christmas!  YAY!  Who knew a low flowing water closet by American Standard could bring someone such joy?
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Still haven't been kissed in 2002. Whenever I have what I guess could be called a  crush  any time I spend not with that person, I second guess myself, I wonder if it's  them  I really like, or the  idea of  them. Sometimes, (Joe) as much as I hate to admit it (Mark), I just enjoy being noticed by someone, (Dan) and decide that I'm attracted to them for a while, (Paul) even if I'm not (Josh), until I'm bored (Nate).    Other times, like now, I just REALLY enjoy every moment spent with them.  It's like... comfortable butterflies.    I feel completely myself, and completely at ease, but still all that giddy nervousness and excitement you feel when you spend time with that person you just really dig. At one point this evening, while harmlessly glancing over during a video, I glanced aside, and just noticed his hands. At that point, I couldn't help imagining those hands on me, on my back, my face, my chest, my hands, his lips on mine...  but restrained myself from jumping on him. I keep hearing people tell me I should do  just  that, but I'm SO terrified of a) rejection, and b) ruining a GREAT friendship. Ugh. I need to get my head straightened out. Or maybe I just need to jump someone else entirely  (any volunteers?) , and hope he eventually comes around, and timing doesn't suck. I really DO think this boy could make me happy for years to come. Ani will be a chance... we'll see.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to high school with the newest member of urlLink  Our Lady Peace .  I've loved that band since I first saw them in concert in May of 1997.  I was grounded for a month for going to that concert.  This is so fucking cool.  I went to see Steve's old band Nancy Boy play at Richmond High School gym.  I let him cheat off me in Spanish.  My brother and I got him a potato gun for Christmas one year.  I hope he remembers us :o)   I saw OLP again 2 years ago here in GR at the Intersection.  At one point during that show, I floated out of my body, the music was so moving to me.  Last Easter, I won tickets on the radio to see them (on top of being the right caller, I could also answer the trivia question) but couldn't go due to family obligations.  But I got a shirt.  My roomies went, and Julie brought back a shirt.  It says *masturbating* on it.  Actually, it says "Talking is just masturbating without the mess", but it still says that word.  I know that's why she picked it.  She does things like that, even though she denies knowledge.  I almost didn't believe Mindy when she told me.  I love her.  *hugs*    urlLink (wish list)   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok, again, this is nothing new.  EVERY time I think I'm over him, I get sucked back. (See March 15th)  Why must he ask ME what he should do about the girlfriend he's not sure he wants to keep around, while telling me how much he values my opinion, intelligence, etc AND flirting like crazy?  Grrrrr...  It'll happen.  I might be 73 years old by then, but it'll happen.  Good, horny old people lovin...  Mmmm, can't wait.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am an honest, straightforward, and for the most part, open person, but also a little shy.  Because of this, I assume nothing less from those I choose to spend my time with, and I choose to spend my time with people I feel I can trust.  My first instinct is always to believe - in my mind, that's a much better way to live life than a doubting, and pessimistic worldview.   I had some very sweet words whispered to me this weekend.  I wonder if the speaker has  any  idea how much they meant to me.  It was a major impact in a positive way.  In a weekend of peaceful love, trust, and happiness, you moved me more than you could imagine.  I've been holding my head higher, and had a brighter smile on my face, and people have noticed.  I think they assume it's the weather.  If you read this, know that you are a truly beautiful person, in every sense of the word, and I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Such a fun night...  felt much love, all around the room.  Thanks for making the trip, all of you, everyone...  And thanks for the hospitality...  I haven't had that much fun in a while, and I can't wait for the next party.  Love you all. *hugs* -wenchie
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm a very happy woman.  Details wouldn't bring justice to my joy, so I won't even bother.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been weeks since I've entered anything in here.  I'm not quite sure why.  It's not like my life has come to a grinding halt.  That's hardly been the case.  Just a week ago, I went and saw Ani DiFranco with someone who's becoming more and more one of my closest friends.  A week before that, I went out 6 out of 7 days in the week to celebrate my 23rd birthday.  Since then, I've hardly spent a night home that I didn't have something I've been working on.  I guess  that's  why I haven't written, I haven't really been online as much (except at work, but I can't really pour my heart out there, bad bad idea).  I haven't been home to do so.  And when I have, I haven't been in a creative mood at all.  Socially, I have a lot going on, I need to learn how to schedule, for the second weekend in a row, I've considered driving out towards my parents, and then decided against it, and that I should stay in Grand Rapids.  I keep calling all the people around my parents', leading them on, making them think they're going to get to see me, then I yank that rug out from under them, and just get lazy and stay.  Next weekend, I won't have that choice, I'll be working my first Saturday in months.  And I'm sandwiching the work day with Knee Deep Shag shows!  Friday at the 'section, and maybe Sunday in K-Zoo...  we'll see.  I should call Paul.  He needs another bit of hope, even though there's no chance.  God I'm evil.  But only to him.  That is all for now.  I'll catch it all up later.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's amazing how heart ache and rejection caused by one insignificant man I once-upon-a-time loved (and almost equally if not more importantly, the family, also at one time beloved) can be so simply (though most likely temporarily) cured and I can be comforted by closeness with a much sweeter, much sexier, flat out better man.  Today started off as a really bad day. It ended a spectacular night.   You may or may not know what you were doing for me, chances are you had an idea.  I just hope you DO know that it's because of YOU that any of this evening happened, the pain he caused me was just a coincidence.  Had today's circumstances gone any differently, I still would have wanted you to be with me tonight.  As reluctant as I am to admit it, I like having you around in a more than friendly way.  I'm always happier after having been near you.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm...  Sorry I've been so lax in updating this.  I think the 40 + hours a week I spend on a LAN with faster internet discourages me from jumping on at home... I only really do when I have something that's filtered out at work, or I really have nothing better to do at home.  Netflix is another culprit.  I have the computer and the DVD player in separate rooms, and I've been watching a LOT more movies lately, and trying to spend time with real world people, enough excuses.  Time to sleep!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When you lay life out for anyone to stumble upon, you can't be too shocked when someone does.  I've had my first encounter with having to edit my weblog.  I don't mind doing it, especially to protect the parties involved, it's just kinda weird being told that someone found it...  if not for the others, I would have left everything alone, but that's being selfish.  I'm still not sure I removed enough, but I can't bring myself to further condense it.  The purpose of this is to spill out how I feel, and if I entered any less, I wouldn't be true to myself.  and someone recently told me not to hold my tongue, to speak my mind, and not worry about what people think.  I guess that would only apply to me speaking about myself?  Anyway, I guess I'll just have to be a better self-censor in the future, and hope I can catch my own drift months, years, later when I reread these entries...    I'm not sure what anyone but me gets from this, but knock yourself out.  And here I thought my life was pretty boring...  I've moved urlLink ...   archives will remain here.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yup, still here.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      2 days til the wedding.  7 hours before I leave for my parents to prepare for the wedding.  I feel like crap and hope these drugs kick in SOON!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, things seem to be going better with a certain friend of mine I was concerned about, but appearances can deceive.  We'll see.  Being vague is fun.  Its gloomy outside today, just the kind of day I like to spend laying on my bed, staring out the window, reading or watching pointless stuff on tv.  Its got that eerie look like its trying to be sunny, but its equally darkish everywhere - makes me wonder if there's a tornado coming.  Wow, that was boring.  Oh well.  No one told you you had to read this.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It sucks when someone you consider a friend starts distancing themself from you, but tries to get all close with one of your closer friends, at the same time.  It almost feels like SWF, but not quite.  Hmmm.  Maybe I should post over here more often.  Its kinda neat over here...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot I had this thing...  I borrowed the colorscheme for my LJ, if you can find it, check it out :)
     
    
</post>



</Blog>