<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      me...farthest i'm going..will be....ottawa??? maybe, altho unlikely, quebec city...  do stm ppl get access to internet and computers?  or do i have to wait .....9 more days?!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      chips ahoy..  oh oh  oh oh oh ummmmm i'm so bored ........ violin exam!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! who's going where for summer..
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think everyone's gonna like this place:  urlLink "Welcome to Homestarrunner.net - It's dot com!"  I highly recommend checking out Strong Bad's E-mails.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey ppl!! nice group site --- my blog page is "koolkolibri.blogspot.com" so visit that too and comment...(i just changed from xanga because no one uses it). 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink CHP Election Campaign Site   check if there's a candidate running in your area and find out about them!!! even if you can't vote---at least find out about them....talk about this to your parents, etc....an interesting option.  don't know yet whether we can agree with everything they run for, but worth looking at, i believe.  so, take the time to read
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      as some of you may have noticed, at the bottom of the left hand navigation bar i have links to a bunch of ppl's personal blogs...basically teh church ppls' ones that i know of.  If you're not in the list (i.e. that includes Jacqueline cuz i don't know it!) please tell so that it can be added!!!! :)  and WELCOME EVERYBODY!!!  and if you find yourself with too much time on your hands and you feel you really really really want to be admin so you can mess with the template and what-not...feel free to ask, and i'll make you one :)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      la ddeeeee da     wow we are gaining members!! ahahahaha *____*
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hehe...I joined this thingy..;)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      #!/usr/bin/python print "Hello World!"
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      super private.... duhhh.... yeah we all adoooore gossiping about ppl...and their love interests??? uhh -________- RIGHT.    let's say...... ummmmm random stuff :P rants? or you hoimin pearest can supply us with nerdy info, or then poopie lists!:D
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      eh, what do we write about in this thing? just normal everyday things? super private, hush-hush, i'm in love with your second cousin's best friend things? i'm so annoyed with life and everyone things? or... nothing in particular...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey! talking from hello messenger thing with bloggerbot---hoping this will work :) so how is everybody who can read this? btw dorkinda says she's having trouble joining....herman did you have any problems? karmel?   We could not find the invitation you requested. Please confirm that you copied the exact URL that was sent to you by email. Also note that an invitation can only be used once before it expires. If the invitation was sent to a mailing list, somebody else may have responded first.  thats what dorkie's getting..well.i'm trying several things now...  YAY my last exam was today!!! hahah no more chem or anything else for 2 months...:) :) :) big smiles!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yooo does that mean i have to pretend to be a boy??  ahh hoimin today you had an inside-out orange shirt...looked REAL funny ^____________^ bahahhaa.... okay this is a post just for the sake of posting.... let's see what else i can talk about...  HISTORY!! (without the "francais" accents)    Les causes des revolutions de 1789:   - crise financiere, (financement de la guerre en Amerique - independance en 1776, 14 juillet) - crise paysanniere --> mene a une crise d'artisan, etcetc.. - modeles anglaises et americaines (no need to re-explain)   modele anglaise  - monarchie absolue : Jacques 1 - tyrannie : Charles 1 qui renvoie le Parlement - guerre civile: parlement vs. Charles 1 - dictature de Cromwell + fils: "Republique", institution de "l'ordre moral", reconquete d'irlande - restauration : Charles 2 accepte le Bill du Test, Habeas Corpus, (1679) ??  - glorieuse revolution : le Bill of Rights (1689) Guillaume d'Orange = monarchie temperee   Revolutions francaises   1789  - 5 mai : ouverture des Etats generaux a Versailles - 17 juin : Assemblee Nationale - 20 juin : Serment du Jeu de Paume - 9 juillet : Assemblee Nationale Constituante - 14 juillet : prise de la Bastille - 4 aout : abolition des privileges --> fin de l'absolutisme/Ancien Regime? - 26 aout : Declaration des Droits de l'homme etc..  1790  - 14 juillet : fete de la Federation  1791  - 20 juin : fuite/essai de fuite de Louis XVI, attrape a Varennes - 3 septembre : monarchie constitutionelle (avec suffrage censitaire)  1792  - guerre contre Boheme, Hongrie, Autriche, Prussie?  - 10 aout --> x___x gouvernement - 20 septembre : victoire a Valmy - 21 septembre : proclamation de la Republique  okayyyyy this is just for my studying, but blogging at the same time!!  so...  a WIN WIN situation???? maybe??? okay sorry! -___-" haha  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      do i have to pretend to be a girl?  i'm contributing as contributors should.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hoimin i hope you bought the pikachu prize..  carnival looked so funnn!!! the dunk tank.. hahaha
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      how do you all like the new template? if i find a nicer, more orignal picture, i'll use that instead of this lighthouse thing.hahhahaha or you guys find something nicer....
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hmm...NEONE isn't a bad idea!!! esp when ppl start disappearing to univ...can keep talking, not exactly their entire life story, hahah but still....  so how are we going to publicize this?? lol...just ask on msn?or send out invites...you're free to invite anyoen you feel like LOL..but i don't ppl to feel left out either....  today was my last day of school!!!! yay!!! last 2 weeks of june? piano piano piano piano...july? piano piano piano.....LOL
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      exam-time for me..... :(   i wonder what we should do in the last two weeks of june...i might be going up to someone's cottage...that should be so cool...but knowing me i'd not be able to go because i'd just get lazy and not want to go :s   blahhhhhhhhhhhhhh :p
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      annoyed?  hahah me? learning to DRIVE yum you might not want to car pool to anywhere with me this summer!!! lol not that i can drive on highways....  and i AM doing my ARCT....  yah we need more ppl..who do you think??? stephany even tho she already knows everything in our lil lj community...what about like, 'your' group? like grace???  also...dorkie, jacqueline, janice..hahah anybody???? LOL who knows...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i seriously think we have to start inviting ppl into this thing...but while we're at it, today is sunday! first sunday of juuuuune, which means summer! what are you doing for summer....swimming and instructors stuff? blahhh i wish i wasn't doing so many things this summer....gonna miss hosanna camp, retreat, and all that fun stuff, like the trail mix camp!! -___________-"  i'm really annoyed lately *______*
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      HELLO DARLINGGGSS..... well ppl who are eventually going to join this........bahahahaha
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      let's see how this is working...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Yes, it's probably breaking the page because it's full size and you 56kers probably hate me.  BB4Win Minimal theme, Gentoo Linux wallpaper (because I'm in the process of making this a Gentoo box), no icons, Y'z Dock on bottom, Winamp, you can see that I'm listening to Hillsongs' To the Ends of the Earth CD.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    my present desktop..hahahah the random things i post and do..enjoy!!!! rofl...yes notice the tan-colored bottom taskbar thing...i love the color..the maple scheme...and highlights are tan-colored too!!! or brownish---anyways..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      it workssssss =D hahaha.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      while work does afford more anecdotal funnies, it also carries some  measure of fatigue, in which blogging becomes rather difficult.      what compounds this difficulty with this long, obscure french url is  that it doesn't really have a theme. so i suggest we come up with some  manner of blogging form. is it about personal stuff (no)? is it about  funny things you found on the internet? can we make this place into a  newspaper of sorts, each contributor writing a column on the topic of  his or her choice? or maybe a mad chain story. those seem hilarious.   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      let me quote...."even shirleys abandoned this blog"  i have NOT :O LOL hahahaa so maybe i'm not so active...well i need help, DON'T i?! LOL but yah...maybe i should try inviting dorkie again..since everyone else's link worked...:D   haha been for a 3-day so-called tour these last 3 days...i'm gradually going to type up my "travel diary" into this.... urlLink http://swirleetravels.blogspot.com so yah....like...um...enjoy?! LOL and *cough* no false accusations, thank yous very much  you can all get me that "avast" CD for my b-day then :D hahahahahaha
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Anyone still alive?  I say get Andy Hunter's Exodus.  It's the rave CD from the van in Atlanta.  I like.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Welcome Moyee to the boring hello friends with a long french url blogger community!!!!!! LOL  plz to enjoy the wonderful randomness of previous posting...and we want to see some of yours too!!!!!  and lol that must be the worst grammar i have ever used in my life :(  must be the after-effects of that in-class driving lesson this morning...4 hours of bad english punctuated by random remarks in cantonese......
     
    
</post>


<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rurouni Kenshin is up there on my list of favourite animes already.  Just that phrase.  Oro? O.O  Kenshin's pretty funny considering he's the most feared manslayer in all of Japan a few years ago.  Ahh.  Also finished NWN.  The ending was kind of bleh.  The ending "changes" depending on your alignment.  What this means is that Haedraline throws in a paragraph or two about you.  "OH NOEZ!! YUO ARE TEH POWAR-HUNGRY!! PREPAER YUORSALF 4 OTHARS WHO WILL DEFAET YUO LIEK YUO DID TO MORAG!!"  So much for alignment-based ending.  After I get back from STM, I'll have some fun with SoU, Kenshin, and Star Wars mods for Homeworld!  3D space combat, finally with Star Wars!!  YAEF!  And in a few hours, I leave for Nashville for STM.  Wow.  How that has crept up.
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really wish I could get Slackware 10.  But I can't.  I don't have the space for it.  So, I thought, how do I join the oss revolution without having an opensource os?  Why don't I use opensource software anyway!  So that's what I did.  I got openoffice.org and gaim.  They are currently replacing MS office xp and trillian.  They are working just fine.  And of course, Firefox and Thunderbird are my IE/OE replacements.  I'm going to look into the GIMP and of course either emacs or vi.
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Hitler vs. Stalin 
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From  The Best Page in the Universe : Imagine a movie about an honorable samurai clan filmed in New Zealand and starring an American. Am I the only person who sees a problem with this? Where do we draw the line? I mean, why not make a movie about Zulu warriors starring James Hong? Or a movie about US Marines starring drunken kung-fu master Simon Yuen? If I had a chance to remake "The Last Samurai," it would star that chick who played Miranda on "Sex and the City," and the setting would change from ancient Japan to biblical Japan when it was submerged under water. The movie would mostly consist of her drowning. Oh man that would rule so hard. I love myself.  My thoughts exactly.
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love BitTorrent.  It's great.  I can download at speeds of 100-300 kb/s.  That's better than the 30-60 kb/s I've been getting on other p2p programs.  There's one thing that annoys me though and that is the fact that it takes an enormous amount of memory to run.  Each torrent that I have downloading is taking about 13-14 megs of system memory.  I just had three torrents open.  System performance shot down.  Even with two torrents open, I can see the difference just typing this thing up.  It's probably because it's written in Python.  Python isn't the fastest language out there.  I guess I'll just wait until the C port comes out.
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The 43th Annual Awards for Teachers who are on my Timetable   1. The "Watch movies every other class and still manage to teach us well, all the way into the Cold War" Award  This one goes to Treleaven. Yeah, he cancels half the tests for the year and half the entire course was made up of movies, but the classes he was there and actually taught were good. I can't believe I got an 88 first term in this class. Ah well, I redeemed myself.   2. The "ZEE MARK IZ MEIN!" Award  English is hard. I can accept that. But having a teacher think 80 is the Holy of Holies makes it slightly more difficult. Only slightly. Okay, I lie. Mitsopoulos is a nice teacher, really. It's her Mark Nazi marking schemes that make us all weep.   3. The "One to three, a, e, g, four, a to c, and 7 to 9" Award  How Voves assigns homework: she picks her three favourite letters of the day and three favourite numbers of the day and puts it together somehow so that it comes out as a string of questions for the day's homework. Needless to say, it's preferable to the lazy teachers who just assign 1 to 263257.   4. The "Good morning to each and everyone of you" Award  Mirkopoulos is nice. REALLY nice. And REALLY easy. Her happy-ness (that's deliberate) and hand gestures make everyone feel safe from overly difficult things. She had to make the civics exam slightly harder, and it was as easy as invading  urlLink France .   5. The "I wish I could get to know my brother more" Award.  Beswick is a depressed guy. He's easy. He's emotional. Apparently, he broke down into tears because of a reaction from his students to one of his tests. And he's away every other class. The man has problems. It's best to leave him alone.   6. The "My dog is better than you" Award  Hybs is amazing. Hybs is smart. Hybs will make you look stupid. Hybs will create fear in you. Hybs will then mark in such a way that you will be rejoicing. Yep. That Hybs is crazy. One of the greatest teachers, evar.   7. The "Everything that can go wrong will" Award  Music is so fun. But alas, there is always something going wrong. There's always some amusing "you won't believe it" type thing going on in Ms. Moroz's life. I'm glad she's our music teacher and not some other schmuck.   8. The "I'll bump you up to 99 and just to be fair, I'll bump everyone up the amount I bump you up too" Award.  Khorshichehr is a really good teacher. He makes computer engineering easy. Even better is the fact that he bumps the highest student in the class (me!) up to 99 and does the same for everyone else too. Ah yes, I like that. My average has never been looking better.   9. The "Useless retarded hypocrite who should have been fired a few years ago but hey the stupid teacher's union has to protect the lives of dangerous stupids so we can't do a damned thing about but at least the principal and department head agree with us" Award.  Zayit is the most incompetent retard in the entire world. If I did not need to take computer science, I would have dropped it in a heartbeat. I do not care if I'm getting 100 in that class. The waste of time and intelligence in that class has been devastating. I will be seething with hate when I hear that accursed name. And all will cry woe as those vile letters are pronounced throughout the air. Oh how we wish we could push her out that window when she opened it in the middle of the bloody winter. Oh how we wished we could have handed her the pink slip for her incompetence. Only then shall we have victory. But until then, avoid TIK2O1 for the life of you. If you heed not my warning, only death and destruction await.  And that ends this year's edition. Please come back for the 65th Annual Awards for Teachers who are on my Timetable next year, slightly different time.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, I'm not American, but I support  urlLink them  all the way.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Allow me to enlighten you today.  I'm sure 99% of you who are reading this are doing so in the comfort of Internet Explorer.  You're probably not aware that Internet Explorer is really not good.  Allow me to explain.    There are standards set by W3C for the Internet.  Standards are good.  They make sure everything is the way they should be.  IE ignores these standards.  Developers have to jump through hoops of fire to get their pages to work in IE.  Also, IE is a buggy little piece of crap and has many many security exploits, not to mention spyware, malware, adware, and the fact that Microsoft has pretty much stopped development on IE.  Now, you're all probably thinking even if there is an alternative, you wouldn't know how to use it.  Mozilla Firefox, the open-source, standards-compliant, secure, fast browser is the answer.  Get it, install it, use it.  It's like IE, but better.  As a person who has built sites, I can say that I loathe developing for IE, but I have no choice, since it get's rammed down everyone's throats and they use it just because it came with Windows (which also is not great, but that is another day).  Not to mention that my IE broke.  And it couldn't even go to windowsupdate anymore.  How pathetic.  It will make IE fall, I say.   urlLink    [/rant]
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I was bored and I watched the election debate for about an hour. The second topic was interesting though: Canada and the World, or more like Canada and the US. So the leaders all get into a little fight over NORAD and NAFTA and all sorts of treaties that I thought everyone loved because they were good. And I also saw for the first time, two parties agreeing on something (Duceppe and Layton were having such a wonderful time agreeing with each other's points). Of course, Harper was being made fun of for wanting Canada to beef up its military 570943265 times. "Mister Harper and his invasion force." Meanwhile, Duceppe is hammering at Martin who's ducking the NORAD and missle defence thing. Then Martin says it: "We will never participate in the weaponization of space!" o__O What exactly is   weaponization  ? So I go over to Google. Weaponization isn't in the dictionary, but according to the results on google, it's been used exclusively so far for space militarization (which would have been the word I chose instead of creating new stupid words like weaponization). Who comes up with words like "weaponization?"
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It looks like I'm back.
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       HAPPY SYSADMIN DAY! 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So what has happened in the past few days?  I've managed to get the courage to switch to Linux. Let's have a recap of what has transpired with my efforts to ditch Windows over the years:  2002: Installed Mandrake 8. Deleted it within hours. 2003: Installed Red Hat 9. Forgotten and eventually deleted in favour of more space. 2004, a few months ago: Installed Slackware 9.1. Permissions problems and lack of gaming support led to deletion. Today: Gentoo Linux. Compiled everything from source. Used Portage to manage software. Uninstalled every non-essential app in Windows, repartitioned drive to make room for future Linux exploits. Gaming support, printing support, graphics and web design, OpenOffice for PowerPoint stuff. Life looks good on this side of Linux. There is no shortage of apps and whatever I can't find, I'll just use WINE or Cedega to handle those Windows apps. There are still some kinks in the system, but this is more stable/fast than anything Windows could ever scrape up. I believe I have truly switched.
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I come home to find that none of those four had actually compiled.  It turns out that I shouldn't be compiling huge apps at the same time, like OO.o.
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it took me about one day to make Gentoo useable for me.  Here I am on Mozilla right now, waiting for Thunderbird, Firefox, Gaim, and XMMS to compile.  Ah.
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well then, to install Gentoo's base system, it took me about 12 hours in total.  Compiling everything is extremely time consuming.  Also, if you thought Slackware was evilly hard, then you'll die on Gentoo.  Die.  As long as you follow instructions, you're alright.  Luckily, I had another computer, so I didn't have to print out 109 pages that is the installation handbook.  Of course, where it takes forever to compile stuff, it is easy to install software on Gentoo.  None of the packages are on the CD, so you have to download your entire system, minus the install stages.  I've got the base system down, but now it needs X.  So to get X, all it took was # emerge xfree .  I love Portage.  Amazingly easy.  Want a package?  emerge it.  That downloads and compiles it and it's installed.  Now, I just have to get Gnome and the desktop should be ready.  After that are apps and stuff.  Yaef!
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever want to kill a process, tell Windows to kill it, and it  doesn't ?  Yeah.  And now that stupid process is spiraling out of control taking about 60 megs of resources.  When I want you to die,  you die!   Thank goodness I'm switching again.
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once again, I have begun to put together a plan to rid myself of the spawn of the devil: Windows.  Last time, I got comfortable using it until a kernel recompile went awry.  This time, I'll make it.  I'm still debating on using Slackware or Gentoo.  But this time, I cannot leave any reason to go back to Windows.  I'll be taking everything with me this time: games, apps, and docs.  I'm also hoping of reducing the size of that NTFS partition so I can actually move all of my stuff.  If all goes well, I'm hoping that I can reduce the NTFS down to about 5 GB and have everything else be for Linux.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's time for redesign!   urlLink blkmage  will be undergoing a redesign very soon.  It's in the planning stages right now.  I've always wanted my site to be as standards compliant as possible.  I design in Photoshop and truck them out in ImageReady, so I'd always used deprecated HTML and tables.  Just now, I discovered that I could export my stuff in XHTML and CSS.  That means validated site for me!  At first, I was going to redo my current site in XHTML and CSS, but that turned out to be too much work.  So I'm going to make a new design and it's finally going to be in XHTML and CSS.  Ah.  Good ol' standards.
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Whatever happened to capitalization It used to be so cooool"  "Y-O-U-R Y-O-U-Apostrophe-R-E They're as different as night and day Don't you think that night and day are different? What's wrong with you?"  "Ohhhhhhh If you want it to be possessive, it’s just “ITS” but if it’s supposed to be a contraction then it’s I-T-apostrophe-S. Scalawag."    urlLink Source  
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some of you may be wondering why there's not much personal stuff in this here blog.  Well, the answer to that is simple.  I have two so-called blogs.  This blog is for my public declarations and place to put oddities and weirdness and other stuff I think is important for people to know.  My other blog is a LiveJournal.  It's for those not too lazy to go to  urlLink here .  That's where all of my personal stuff goes.  On the rare occassion of course, stuff will be placed in both.  In conclusion, my blog is my soapbox and my livejournal is my, uh, journal.  And for those of you wondering about xanga, I've never had a very high opinion of xanga or its users.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I felt the need to comment on some of the CDs I, uh... "got" because of listening to them in Atlanta.  First up is Passion's Hymns: Ancient and Modern.  This CD made me love hymns even more.  They sound awesome when contemporary-ed by the likes of David Crowder, Matt Redman, Chris Tomlin, et al.  There's a distinct way to the melodies and lyrics that makes it so cool sounding.  Secondly is my favourite CD so far: Andy Hunter's Exodus.  BOD put it on in the van and I loved it.  The first track, GO!, just owns.  I love this CD.  This is the reason I got into Christian techno/electronica over the last few days.  I want to go back to Atlanta to have another rave in the van :(  I miss them.  And then, Relient K's Anatomy of the Tongue in Cheek.  I already have Two Lefts Don't Make a Right... But Three Do, but I love Pressing On.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well then, now for the all of the super funness of my STM trip.  The day that we left for Nashville, I couldn't believe that the trip had actually crept up like that.  I felt so uncertain of myself.  But, nothing I could do then, right?  So I got on a car and went off to Pearson International.  There, my little encounter with US customs was not happy: - What are you doing there? - Visiting friends - How do you know these friends - Church (???) - Okay, who are you going with? - Uh, friends - How do you know  them ? - Er... we're all from a church - which church? - Toronto Jaffray Chinese Alliance Church - Ah, what're you doing down there with a church? - Er, just working with them - Are you being paid? - No - Where are you going? - Nashville - It says here you're going to be in Adams, or at least that's what I think it says... - Yes, that's Adams... - What school do you go to? - West Hill - Grade? - 11 - Alright, have a nice trip.  Phew. So two flights later, we were in Nashville. We drove up to Adams to the YWAM base, where we would spend three days for training.  Training was a really intimidating word, seeing as how we didn't really work that much.  I can see now what it was for though.  First of all, we learned our dramas, and kind of learned testimony writing-ish thing.  But really, the three days was for spiritual preparation.  Throwing yourself right off the bat into a missions trip will kill you.  The training was time to get closer to God, worship with others, focus on Him and Him alone, and discipline yourself in Him.  Even though it wasn't gruelling, it was soooo important.  And that brings me to the theme for this trip:  WORSHIP  Every Knee, Every Nation  All the nations you have made, will worhship You oh Lord They'll bring glory, oh glory to Your name   And matching bags and shirt to go with theme!  But yes, the theme in summary is that missions is not our goal.  Worship is.  But since the goal of worship hasn't been reached, we need missions.  Y'see, Christ is only coming back after every "nation" has heard the Gospel.  And that is why we need missions.  So yeah, for three days we met some really cool people at the base, like Bryon, BOD, etc.  We learned our dramas (Decision Time!) and had fellowship with one another (pool!).  Then for the next seven days, our TJCAC crew split up.  I went to Atlanta.  For six hours I honed my evangecube skills because it was the most interesting thing to do.  In Atlanta, we stayed at this extremely nice youth centre owned by the Roswell United Methodist Church.  Over those seven days, we did loads of stuff.  Of course, I can't go through all of them, so I'll talk about some interesting ones.  First was with the Atlanta Children's Coalition at Little Five Points.  Even though I'm not a big fan of kids, I didn't care, and neither did the kids there.  A bit later, we met a guy who called himself the Professor.  A little into the conversation, he tells us that he took theology.  Of course, we were all "oooooohhh."  Halfway in, he reveals that he's Muslim and he believes Islam and Christianity are the same.  So then our team leader Rebecca who was with us tries to politely point out that they're not the same.  We do this carefully for about half an hour at which point the guy "invites" us into this creepy bar.  Of course, we go in for a few minutes, say bye and run out.  That was the first "thing" that happened to me.  Monday was an amazing experience.  We went to Edgewood, one of the poorest neighbourhoods in Atlanta.  There, we handed out bread and invited people to watch our drama.  Even though the people there looked very gangster, they were really nice.  We did it, and all the kids came out and everything.  Just seeing how much the kids loved it and how much happened just that morning was so amazing.  Of course, it sucked a lot when we had to leave and all the kids still wanted balloons.  Tuesday was working at the food bank.  Sorting, packing, screwing around.  In the afternoon, we went to a nursing home and talked a bit with the people there, played bingo with them, and then we did our drama thing and sung a few hymns after.  There was one lady who came in to visit her parents and went on about how wonderful it was for the people here and how we  had  to go to Stone Mountain, to the point of pseudo-threatening us into going.  That was also really great, and I can see how it must be hard.  I had a really hard time trying to hear what they wanted to say to me in my conversations with them.  The last night was fun.  Techno rave in the van!  Beat Satan down!  Yeah.  Thanks for introducing me to Andy Hunter.  Now I listen to it all day.  Until I get bored of it, anyway.  I used to be deathly afraid of other people.  Now I can at least talk to strangers.  God has also forced me to be tons more dependent on Him than before.  Going into the trip, I was really worried whether God wanted me to be on this trip and whether He was going to use me.  I can see now that He has a way of getting what He wants regardless.  He's in total control.  Even though I didn't get to really evangelize, I can safely say that God has accomplished so much on this trip in me and working through me.  Experience?  Psh, If I went and all that I got was the experience, it would have been a ripoff.  No, my friends.  The real prize was having God orchestrate and work through this entire thing and being able to  see  it.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh how great that ten days was down in the States. I'll go over it in more detail later on, but wow. Even if I didn't get to share about Christ, God still worked in everything that we did. And working with everyone on the team was so great. What's also amazing is that you have no idea how much you grow until people notice.  There was something else i wanted to put down, but I forgot. Guess I'll wait until I write up a big thing.
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today, I had nothing to do, since  no one is giving me anything to put in the handbook, wink wink nudge nudge .  I had finished Rurouni Kenshin and that was greatness.  So I decided to finally start watching the Kenshin OVAs starting with Reminiscence, the one that talks about Kenshin's past.  So I took the discs and reorganized them, since the OVAs were under Gundam Seed, Lain, .hack//SIGN, Record of Lodoss War, etc.  Still in working order, good.  So I start up my trusty mplayer and find that the subtitles don't work.  AHGHAGHAHGAH.  I find out I have to use the console.  Okay, that's weird, but it worked.  But it also turned the audio track to English.  AHGHGHAGHGAH.  So then, I start mplayer with GUI and I switch audio back and fix the subtitles.  YAY.  I must say that this OVA is 5948237952 times more violent than the anime, ever.  I mean, just at the beginning, it's a really different atmosphere than the fun one you get from the anime.  But it is still AWESOME.  Yes, it kicks the stuffing out of Naruto, but I've held that view ever since the Kenshin-Saito fight at the beginning of the Kyoto arc.  Amazing stuff.  Kenshin > Naruto in every way possible.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Here. 
    
</post>


</Blog>