<Blog>


<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      piss off bitches
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Goddamn. The end.
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah that was SUPPOSED to say 'ass' but it doesn't so go cry about okay!!??!!
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah so I was just in I thought I'd talk to myself some.  Blah!  


                            OOO          OOO         OOO
                         OO     OO    OO     OO   OO     OO
                         OO     OO    OO     OO   OO     OO
                         OO     OO    OO          OO
                         OOOOOOOOO     OO          OO
                         OOOOOOOOO       OOO         OOO
                         OO     OO           OO          OO
                         OO     OO    OO     OO   OO     OO
                         OO     OO    OO     OO   OO     OO
                                         OOO         OOO

Do You have any Idea how long that took me, now i'm sober...dammit
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ummm high and stuff ....uhhh wanna get some sausage hmmmm no i dont wanna get sum sausages i dont even know what i am typing i will kill dustin baker ...wait no no i will make him suffer ...i will make him a steak a really really good steak and then put him in a life size gerbil reel with the steak in front of it so he cant get it mwhahhaahhhhhahahahaha
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tittie grabbing is out

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a while since I've really let out all the anger that has benn seeping to the back of my head for the past year.... happy temperament ....so I've decided to change the Blogname to Quietly Ticking, until the back of my head blows out all over the wall and I freak on someone....don't be scared... Happy   temperament ....eat cheese it is  GO o D .

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have also found that drama sucks, and always has.&nbsp; Being a nice guy gets you screwed over, because you can never seem to pleaase everyone at once

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah so this is the first time I have had a little quiet time to myself without someone looking over my shoulder&nbsp; oh nevermind.&nbsp; ok they're gone.&nbsp; yeah I'm just hanging at Mattimeo's house right now for something to do.&nbsp; I've been thinking a lot ove rthe last couple of days and it is apparent the I will not have someone to be truly close to for a long time, because nobody really seems to noticde me in that light.&nbsp; All I really want is someone that I can go to sleep beside at night, and can confide in and not have any drama put on about what I say or do.&nbsp; BGut it is now obvious that nobody is interested in getting close enough to me to be that person, except for Jimmy, and he is the best, closest friend that I think I have ever had, but I need someone even closer, I just feel lonely.......SHIT..,...don't pity me bye

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quietly Ticking

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let me just tell you a little bit about this kickass game called Zelda.&nbsp; It is my favorite game of all time.&nbsp; I weighed myself last night and I lost about twenty pounds since I started not eating so much.&nbsp; But I am still fatty.&nbsp; Yeah I don't like the rain at all because I do not like being wet, unless I am taking a shower.&nbsp; That was pretty useless.&nbsp; But okay then bye. 


    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      NOT QUITE
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah I'm having a bunch of fun now...YAWP!!...Barbaric YAWP!!!  Yeah I'm happy, I'm feeling good cheese is GOoD!!...eh?
    
</post>


</Blog>