<Blog>


<date>27,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      What a weekend. We drove around the city looking for houses for sale. There is precious little out there.  Saturday our agent sent a short list of homes for sale, 1/2 of them not even built yet. We looked at four properties on Sunday, and are poised to make an offer on a 1/2 built home. There are several more houses on our 'must see' list, but I have the feeling that we will buy NEW. What that means for ME is thet I'll be able to install CAT 5 (ethernet) cable throughout the house before the walls go in. Tonight we'll see that last few houses and make a choice ... if all goes to plan...
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Good news. If I sounded a bit depressed yesterday it was because our selling price was too low. Well, it turns out that I didn't take into account how much he had paid off on our present mortgage since the beginning of this adventure. The big advantage to taking a whole year to sell your house is that in the meantime you've made a whole year of payments on your present house. Our initial goals are still on track because of this. yabba dabba doo!    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm sitting here celebrating with a Corona and a bowl full of nuts. The cause for celebration is that we sold our house ... finally. We first put it on the market, let's see ... about 12 months ago? Where is this sellers market we heard about? Seems to me that the housing maket is not nearly as desperate as we were led to believe. Anyways, the condition on the offer was met, and the buyer's financial institution's assessor is coming tomorrow.  Then the deal is done. I am not totally happy with the offer, but what can I do now? Cut corners, compromise, eat KD for a few months. The fun part is that we get to start house hunting in earnest tomorrow. I'm just looking forward to getting into a bigger house and the opportunity to unpack boxes that have been stacked in the basement for the last eight years. Cheers.
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, yesterday was the Big Smokeout with the Big Honey. We changed the spelling of Honey to distance ourselves from the origin of the word : Winnie-the-Pooh. In tribute to the original use of the barrels, we re-dubbed it the Big Honey. Anyways, there is a new blog dedicated to the Big Honey and those that will use it. It will be at  urlLink bighoney blog . The original webspace  and storage for the pictures is in  urlLink my webfolder .
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was the assembly date (over beer and pizza) for our new smoker barbeque dubbed the Big  Hunny  Honey ... named after the two BeeMaid Honey barrels it is made of. Thanks again to the  urlLink Peters Honey Farm  for supplying the old barrels. Today is the inaugural "smoke" with dry-rubbed 6-inch back ribs. Once the  urlLink Big  Hunny  Honey  has a chance to cool down, we will empty 6 cans of black high-heat stove paint on it.
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the house sold AGAIN ... this time for much lower than I wanted, but (if you want to look at it this way) we will get $2000 less than the last offer we accepted, which, in the Grand Scheme of things, is not a whole lot of money. I could spend more than that on a suite of ADOBE products... at least I wish I could.  Anyways, some background: We have been trying to sell our house since Fall 2001. Various factors kept buyers at bay ... namely our high price because we were not serious about selling at first, the condition of the foundation in our 1911 2-story house, and the fact that we are located right next to a big-ass apartment block. Then we changed the factors that we could to generate interest: We lowered our asking price by $8000 and we started fixing up the joint.  We got a conditional offer in March or April, subject to the appraisal of a building inspector. He could not recommend the house, so the buyers backed out. We fixed up the house some more by replacing the worst shingled areas on the roof, and overnight the showings seened to pick up. Within a week (today in fact) we got our second offer. Lower than we expected anyone would even dare offer. We countered with $2000 more, and they accepted within several hours. Now their only contract OUT is if the furnace is in such bad shape it needs replacing. Stay posted to find out how our house-selling saga ends.    back view   
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This  urlLink Calendar    and  urlLink Web Color pre-Visualizer  are  contest entries for web pages  under 5 Kbytes ... my title jpg alone is over 19 kb! Check out other entries at  urlLink www.the5k.org/  
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Everything you ever wanted to know about Canadian Grain from my current employer: The  urlLink  Canadian Grain Commission  
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Some of my geek friends and I have decided to get into the shop and get our hands dirty. We concluded that if our wives could have countless 'girls night out' 's, then the men were entitled to a weekend to ourselves. We decided that a fitting venture would be a 'weekend welding workshop' ( or WWW for those of you that didn't notice the clever pun), in which we would build the ultimate smoker barbeque. For a glimpse of what we are attempting to build, see:  urlLink  The Big Baby . So far we've cut one barrel in half (noisy), ground some rust off (messy) and drawn some pretty lines where the wood-stoking door will be. The WWW is a bust though as the wives made their own plans again and left us men with the kids. We'll have to do it after bed-time.
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Another issue I have came to light today while I was examining the contents of my pockets. Among the bits of paper, post-it reminders and receipts, were some brand new yet crumpled up $5 and $10 bills. Now what is keeping me from storing these things in my wallet, where they belong? The answer, of course, is because that my wallet no longer  fits  in my pocket. I have gone through my wallet so many times, trying to cull the crap that gathers there, but no matter how much I throw out, what's left is still too much for my back pocket. What gets me is that with the technology we enjoy today, it still takes 1/16 of an inch x 2-1/8" x 3-1/4" of plastic to store a name, a number an expiry date and a signature. If you have 16 credit cards/debit cards/bank cards/club member cards/air miles(tm)/phone cards/blood donor cards ... you already have 1 inch of your wallet thickness. On top of that I have the (much smarter) thin plastic coated public library card/insurance plan cards (at least 3 or 4 of them)/wallet calendar/BlockBuster/a few pictures of the girlies (my own, not the GUESS girls ... well maybe them too ...) My wife health insurance plan cards (for dual coverage)/ several business cards I use all the time, Subway coupons, Public Transit tickets, Driver's Licence, postage stamps, 1 free with 10 whatever ... CD's, Popcorn, Power Juice, Coffee, Haircut, car wash, film developing ... etc. In the end I have room for everything  except  money. I might as well carry a purse. I don't see  why   companies couldn't offer barcode stickers instead of full sized credit cards for discounts and '1 free with 10' offers. Air Miles, the Library, Chapters, and my health plan could all be stuck on the same card. Those forward thinking companies (like Safeway) that accept my phone number instead of a barcode are even better. Those cards I can leave at home or in my wife's purse. Who can I call? Where can I take my beef? Do you think that VISA(tm of course) and MasterCard(ditto) are aware of this problem?
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa, I just ran 200 miles [+/-198]. Waiting for the rumored endorphins to kick in. Maybe they can be coaxed out with a hot shower. Last week I thought I'd die after 1 mile. This week I ran 2. It ain't much, but   am  improving. Gotta go now and log my progress at  Runner's World's   urlLink  free   Training Log.
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, I admit it. I'm out of shape. I was supposed to go running Friday and Sunday, but I was not able to get out. Instead, I decided to reroof part of my house. My brother came over Saturday and helped me out (with his carpentry expertise) and we got half of the job done. Now my hands feel like sandpaper, and every muscle in my body is screaming for A-535. I didn't run, but I feel like I got a workout. After a few finishing touches, I'll be ready to do the back roof next Saturday. All this just so we can sell the house.
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      HAHA ... HUGE water-main break at Pioneer and Water today (that's close to Provencher Bridge). Cars of all sizes are pushing through water up to 2.5 feet deep. The ONLY stall was a businessman in his fancy BMW. I was going to comment as I drove by on my bike, but the look on his face told me I'd be better off keeping my thoughts to myself. 
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  What IS it with some people? If this blog had a theme it would have to be that. There will be a good long rant coming about the quality of service in the retail and so-called  service  industries, but first lets talk about today.   The date is May 9. The weather is damp and cold. Tons of wet snow has been falling since late last night and the city is dripping. Transformers are shorting out because they're filling with slush, and traffic is crawling because, between today and three weeks ago, people have forgotten how to drive in the snow. This morning, as each of my coworkers arrived at work, they took their turns describing the fights they had with their significant other. Throughout the day these normally good natured people proved  how scrappy they can get. Somehow the snow had completely demoralized them. What's up with that? Granted, we are not supposed to have blizzards in the month before June ... but it  happens . I can remember many ice storm in May. This one is just a little warmer and wetter. It's no reason to stomp around and pout. We work in an  office  building. We don't even  go  outside for heaven's sake. Weather is weather. It is unpredictable and uncontrollable. Don't let it ruin your life.
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
          Daryl's Blog is active   May 8, 2002  
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The inlaws wanted to see the inside of the house yesterday, so they called us up. We met them there last night, got a key from the show home, and took a peek. All the wood trim and oak pantry door is installed. The top coat of paint was also finished - but it is the wrong color!. I suspect that the paint supplier forgot to add the tint, since it was just a flat white. It was supposed to be the same as all the other Hilton homes ... a darker cream color. We told the builder and they are looking into it. While we had the builders key, we stole a look at the neighbors house across the street. It is identical to ours but a little further along.  Their basement is poured and their cabinets, lights, some flooring is installed, and their paint is the right color. I outlined my plans for the basement, and Janet and her mother agreed with them. All systems are 'go' and the hi-tec basement planning pushes forward.     right color (in the neighbors house):     wrong color:      
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday was a day of fun for the kids. The Red River Ex -- a 10 day fair and amusement park -- is in town.       
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      We borrowed a key and took a peek at our house again on Saturday (June 22). As was on an earlier pass in the rain (Wednesday), the tar paper and wire mesh has been added to the outside walls in preparation for the stucco. Now the inside plastering is completely finished and primed, ready for painting. The front concrete steps were poured yesterday and the interior woodwork ... door and window trim, wall caps, sills, were brought in for installation.        Last Sunday was the Manitoba Marathon. I ran the shortest run available - the 2.6 MILE SuperRun - 1/10 of a Marathon. The guys are gearing up for another Marathon in Walker North Dakota in Fall. I have agreed [in principle] to join a relay team and run 13 miles. Time will tell if I can adequately recover from my 2.6 mile ordeal. My official time was 29:51, but that was from when the gun went off. I spent several minutes folowing the crowd to the start line after the gun fired. MY watch time from startline to finish was 27:17. After the Marathon we had a little birthday party for:   Janet told him that we were singing HAPPY BIRTHDAY for him. He nodded and smiled. A few moments into the song he asked her who we were singing Happy Birthday for... It's not his memory, it's his hearing. I don't believe he has any batteries in that hearing aid.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      On Thursday the inside walls of the new house were covered. Our new home is beginning to take shape.       On Friday the wall guys started taping and plastering and added the rounded corners. Also on Thursday, we picked the lighting fixtures that will go into the house. All of the interior lights will be of [faux] Italian (marbled) glass with pewter hardware. Tomorrow is the Manitoba Marathon, and then a picnic/barbeque for Father's Day and my Grandpa's birthday. Don't ask me how old he is ... I've lost track.
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      In case you are curious, I have heard from area residents, that the street name "Braswell" Rhymes more with "Maxwell" than with "Roswell" ... if you can imagine the 'x' being a hard 'z' sound. Maybe "Braz-well" would be a better way to put it.
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This past week was a busy one. We choose carpet and vinyl flooring colours for the new house. I drilled the cable holes for my future Leviton Integrated Network [I found out that 1 14-volt drill battery lasts for 2-1/2  1" holes through a 2x4, and 2 layers of subfloor]. I found plans for the house in the house, that some contractor left behind when he was done ... so I scanned them into my computer. I can now plan our basement layout with more precision.        The house now has fascia, soffits and brick installed. The rough plumbing electrical and framing has been inspected and the walls are ready to be covered. The Doors and Windows are installed and the garage floor is poured. 
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      What a rush! The last time I posted was a week ago. It seems like yesterday. What has happend in the intervening days might qualify as the biggest rush in recent memory.         As I expected, we decided to buy a brand new house. After scouting around to see what was available in the used houseing market, we decided that for about $15,000 more, we could have a  brand new  house. We found the biggest lot (longest dimension, 210 feet) with an adequate sized house (1188 ft/sq with a full basement) in our price range ($130,000 give or take $20,000), and put in an offer. We offered a little more, and added a lot more 'built-ins' than the original price offered. For example, we asked for all appliances to be included in the asking price, as well as air conditioning and some landscaping. The builder counter offered $1100 more, and we countered again ... to meet him half way. The deal was then accepted and signed.        Since then we have been choosing colors for the house, planning how and when we will move, planning my  urlLink Leviton Integrated Network Structured Media System , and driving by the house every day to video tape the progress. My dad, a builder for many years, came and looked at it, and gave me a few points to complain about. We are happy because even though it is a small house, it has 3 to 4 times more space than we have now, it's in a low traffic neighborhood with lots of young kids, and it will be  new, brand new !
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      It took a while but I'm back online. Our Internet service was installed into our new house on Saturday, but I JUST got the wiring to the computer hooked up now. The installer was not interested in doing that for me since he had never seen a Leviton BHN* box before.  Neither have I, which is why it took me till now.      This is a picture of my Cat5e Ethernet jack wiring (before trimming):            The move 8 Kms south went amazingly smoothly. I got an early start by loading all of my books magazines, collections, etc. early in the morning. As soon as the sun hit us the temperature soared to 30 C, so the early start saved my life. I'm sure I would have had heat stroke if we started later. Our U-Haul with Arizona plates had to be boosted twice. The U-haul guy later told me the battery was brand new, so the charging system must be faulty. No problem though ... we all know how to boost cars in the Great White North. We had just the right amoount of ppeople over to help us. Not so many we tripped over ourselves, but not so few we had to do it alone. at noon there was a turnover of people, so we got fresh muscles to do the heavy lifting. I must have drank (drunk?drinkin?) a couple gallons of water that day, but I made not one trip to the toilet. It all came out as sweat.  We unloaded all of the basement boxes into our new garage. There they still sit. It will be a while till we can afford shelving to unpack it all.  It  seems that every task I set out to accomplish now is an excercise in circular reasoning: I need to unpack boxes to get to the items I need. But I need shelf space to dig through the boxes, but I need to move the boxes to build the shelves, but I need room to move them too ... When it gets too frustrating I just go and sit on the couch in my new living room, and smile. We love the new neighborhood so far. Our neighbors are great, the train is much less intrusive then we imagined ... much less than living in an airport air lane, next to zero traffic, NO noise at night.       Everybody workin', no one  to take pictures... this is all we have for  moving day pictures ...               Break time               *see previous posts
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess it is now officially Wednesday July 24. This afternoon we see the bank to sign mortgage papers. Then tomorrow we get an 'official' walkthrough at the new house. I believe it is to voice any concerns we may have missed to date, and for receiving special instructions on how to care for a new house ... yard regulations, new concrete care, telepost adjustment, etc... Then we see the lawyer's assistant to sign papers. Next morning, Friday, we see the lawyer again to collect the front door key. Then the real work begins!
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         The house as of July 23 ...  3 days before  possession day:                             Our current basement:      
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         Vacation instructions:           
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      One working day until vacation time! Today I felt MUCH better. My recovery is well over the hump. Now since Janet is at work all day, and the kids are at the grandparents, I just might go shopping. Did I hear Home Depot is having a 70% off sale? Mac users might find this of interest: urlLink dotMac 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Three working days till vacation!  6 days after wisdom-tooth surgery, and my face is still swollen. My antibiotics run out today. I have 3 doses of painkillers (mood-improving) drugs left. The stitch-holes feel inflamed and sore ... like I bit both cheeks really hard. I cannot eat fast enough to get full so I have a perpetual hunger-headache.  
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The weekend of pain is officially over. The discomfort is not, however. The 'pain' was really far from it. I tasted no blood. I felt no real 'pain' from the missing teeth. I stopped taking painkillers after 14 hours. The real inconvience is the swelling around the jawbone and the burning around the stitches when I try to eat. I have nothing to complain about and I think the procedure went remarkably well. Now I am waiting for the stitches to dissolve so the holes can heal over. I tried to eat steak yesterday. Ha Ha. Without functional cheeks to position food between my molars, I ended up swallowing most of the pieces whole.  New in the house today: bathroom sinks, Leviton Basic Home Network media panel.    Kitchen sink:               Bathroom sinks:     Leviton BHN panel:      
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      2 news items: The incredible progress made in the new house earlier this week; and my wisdom tooth removal this afternoon.    Vinyl and Carpet:     Measuring for Window Coverings:       1) We visited the house on Wednesday. Last time we looked (on Saturday), they had just poured the basement floor and moved some wall materials into the basement. They had mistakenly installed the kitchen vinyl flooring in the bathrooms, and had correctly installed the underlay for the carpet.  Monday and Tuesday saw all the vinyl properly installed, all of the carpet installed all the way to the bottom of the basement stairs, all of the ductwork, A/C, and furnace componants, sump pump and pit installed, and basement walls (perimeter only) framed and insulated. There must have been three different sub-contractors at the house during those two days. We measured for window coverings. On the way out we also noticed that the garage door was installed.    My Bottom Molars:            2)Wisdom Tooth (x4) removal... This happened today. I was scheduled for 12:45 pm, but the queue was pushed back for a few hours. i got out of surgery at 3:30, and Janet picked me up at 4:00. The drugs they gave me put me to sleep (or rather, I just fell asleep, since I stayed up till 2 am last night ... I wanted to fall asleep on the table), but I did wake up in the middle of the third tooth. I tried to yell "you got the wrong tooth" ... twice, but both times they told me to try not to  talk : ) ... I honestly thought they were drilling on my second molar, not the third.  After the surgery -- I felt great at first: no effects felt from the drugs, I was walking right away with no dizzyness; my lips and chin were numb and felt like they doubled in size -- a mirror proved otherwise; I took an ice pack and painkillers right off the bat, but when they wore off after 3.5 hours, I took some more. In the 4th to 5th hours, the freezing wore off, and the new dose of painkillers hadn't kicked in yet the pain was... exquisite... I suppose 8 years of treating migraines with Tylenol with codeine (T1's) has made me a little tolerant of the drug.  I'm taking T3's now and they're not having the desired effect. I'll have to increase the dose, or put them closer together. I also received drugs to decrease swelling (Dexamethasone 2mg 2x/day for 4 days), and antibiotics for 6 days; so far, 5 hours later, swelling is minimal. All in all, I am pleased that the surgery went quickly, and that there was no nerve damage of any kind.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Dilbert for Wednesday, July 10 2002  ^^                               ~~ () ~meet with our vendor         () ||  and come up with a plan.     J|     I�ll do the same with      their executives  ^^       ~~ ()       () ~Can you see any reason ||       J|  why MY meeting might be               a complete waste of time?  ^^                           ~~ () ~Sure, lots of them,      () ||  but I�m planning to      J|     spring them on you      during your performance     review.  
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      We spent the weekend packing. Although the official possession date for the new house is July 26 (3 weeks minus 3 days), an they may let us in a week early... Next weekend is my  urlLink Weekend Of Pain , so I'm not expecting to do much more than lie on the sofa and watch TV. That would leave a week or two before the big day. Packing is going well, but I feel like I'm living in a warehouse.   The basement is poured!. We looked on Wednesday, and there was that pile of gravel that was being used to support the underfloor plumbing and weeping tiles. They must have brought the crushed rock on Thursday, packed it down, and then poured the floor on Friday. Now it is ready to walk on and the furnace and duct work can be installed.  We had been talking to the builder about installing the deck-header at the back of the house. The chemically treated rot-resistant 2x10 is bolted to the outside wall, and is used to secure the deck to the house. This board does not come standard with the house, so we were going to have to pay for it. Alternatively we could install it ourselves after the stucco is on the house. This would involve a lot of stucco removal, or an unstable header bolted to the outside of the stucco. The price was $140 for a 20 foot deck-header. We were going to pay it, but then remembered that the framers forgot to install a small 4 foot wall between the living room and the front entrance. Although we like the omission, we used it to trade for a deck-header.  
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Performance Review. Phew.
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      We visited the house and insepcted the new changes. The tile guy was there so the doors were open. We found a roll of carpet underlay on the floor -- it seemed to be too soft for 'upgraded' underlay, so we took a sample to the carpet store to make sure. All is OK. We just got a soft sample. The rest should be fine. They found it strange that there would be a half-roll in the house at all, since the underlay and carpet are usually delivered on the install date... next Monday. We are pleased with the new kitchen colors and the paint job. Possession date is in 3 weeks and 1 day, so we are starting to pack up at the old place.Have a Safe and happy July 4 those of you south of the [cdn] border.     New Kitchen:            new paint job right color:     Becky in the Big House:        
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was the last fireworks display we will get to enjoy from the comfort of home. Yesterday was Canada Day and the evening fireworks take place in the middle of town, six blocks away and across the river. This year was more extravagent than ever, with two displays taking place on either side of 'The Forks' where the Assiniboine meets the Red River. Becky says "Happy Birthday Canada", and Jenny says "Thanks, Canada for the beautiful fireworks".    Fireworks Canada Day, 2002     From the kids Bedroom Window       Today the painters are fixing the mistake made last week in our new house. I don't know who made the goof, nor do I care to know. The important thing is that it is fixed. Our cabinets were also installed today, and they are prepping the basement for the pouring of the concrete.
    
</post>

<date>30,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Who-hoo!  We are finally able to park in the garage. I have officially finished moving everything  into the house that belongs in the house. The only junk left in the garage is future shed and yard stuff  and garage/workshop stuff. The basement is now a little crowded and disorganized, but that will change  as we unpack. This A.M. as I walked to the bus-stop in the dark, I heard a blood curdling screeech. I looked in the  direction of the scream, but saw nothing. The second screech came from behind me so I knew that  what I had heard the first time was an echo off of a house in front of me. I looked back toward my  house, and sitting on our neighbors roof was an owl sitting  at least  two feet tall. For my benefit  the owl stretched his wings, and jumped off of the roof and landed on a roof closer to my position.  I took out my camera with the intention of shooting the owl if it flew over me, but I didn't get the chance.  This would be the second wildlife I have seen since moving to this area, the first being a deer on the  railroad tracks.
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Finally! The day has come  ... After returning from Grandpa's lovely funeral, we discovered that our driveway had been poured. This marks an end to the muddy feet that come from little feet slipping into the gaps between construction site sidewalk blocks.     Driveway form, Tuesday August 20:           Poured Driveway, August 21  (color cast due to evening light)         
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday at 4:15 am Grandpa went to his reward and rejoined Grandma. We grandkids have 'missed'  grandpa (Henry F Siemens of Altona) ever since his hearing went, and will miss him even more now.  Grandpa will be remembered for his 'sermon-in-a-prayer' style grace before family meals, His unending  string of new cars every two years, so he didn't have to worry about repair costs and family safety, his  strong opinions about local matters -- and his arguments with grandma over the details, all of the practical  furniture that came out of his basement woodshop, his Hammond organ playing at Christmas, his sense  of humor and his smile.     At the age of 91, Grandpa (at his birthday party above) suffered a 'silent' heart attack,  a condition only diagnosed after blood tests. After a brief recovery, he developed  pneunomia and died peacefully August 17 4:15 am.  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Phew... I made it home ...  I drove home from Steinbach with one eye closed, listening to  Boom, chucka luckalucka, chuckaluckalucka boom boom ... waiting for the dinosaurs We rented a movie, and had some pizza with these great sprinkle-on toppings that added extra flavor. One was a mild Italiano, and the other was blazing hot Chili Peppers. All was fine and dandy until, on the drive home, I absent mindedly rubbed my left eye. Youch! I'm glad the deer decided to stay in the fields tonight. I would not have seen them on the road. BTW, thanks D for letting me use your only cup, and sit in the captains chair.
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       wow, what an eventful week so far ...  Jenny turned five and got her new bike on Sunday. I immediately put training wheels on the new bike and took the training wheels off of the old small bike. Two days later -- Jenny is driving the old small bike [without training wheels] unassisted. We had no part in teaching her how to drive a bike. Like Becky, she just did it. Nike would be proud. The next day [sorry Paul, you're too late ...] Becky lost her second front tooth in a week. Guess what's all she wants for Christmas now? Today we left the old house for good. Everything we want to keep is moved out, the final meter readings were made, lawn mowed for the last time, and the keys left behind. Good luck to the Anders, the new owners as of tomorrow morning.
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Everybody welcome Jenny to the Five Year Old Club. And the Big Girls Bike Club. Both achieved the same day, August 11, 2002! 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Paul bought a house, Paul bought a house...   (sing to the tune of nya, nya nya, nya, nya) 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      We've been in the house for a week now. So far there have been a few surprises.  For starters, and to our complete surprise, a garage door  opener  was  not  included in the price of the house. I suppose it's because everyone has their own idea of what a garage door opener should do, so it's left up to them to go out and purchase them ... but I think it should have been handled the same way as the lights and carpet and appliances: you get a base model unless you go to the store early and upgrade. As it happened, we went to the Sears website and got their top-of-the-line model for a cut-price. At least $100 less then the competition name brand [that probably MADE the Sears model]. It came with 2 remotes, a wall switch, infrared beam safety feature, and an external keypad entry system. Next, a hand rail for the basement stairs  fell off  the wall at a moment when I was depending on it greatly. It was glued to the paint, and fastened with screws  so short  that the tips only just barely penetrated the underlying wood 2x4. I replaced those screws with ones 1 inch longer. THEN ... someone brought us red wine for a h/w gift ... then proceeded to spill some on the carpet (see our carpet color in the archives). The  ladies  poured their own white wine on the red spill, and diluted it enough to remove the marks with detergent and water. I think there is now a  light  spot on the floor. Then I was BBQing beef back-ribs, salmon and steak, and I  dropped some back-rib grease on the garage steps and garage-entry door... (and  then  I burned the steak while showing the guys the rest of the house (namely the basement). There was only one steak, so it wasn't missed). At this rate the house will look totally lived-in in a few weeks, then we won't have to worry about it any more.     new dining room     Jenny and Vinnie     new front yard        up the street     new garage door opener     temporary storage        Jenny's new friend     our new friend     Becky losing her first front tooth         
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
              I am Marvin the Martian!  
</post>

<date>25,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       The time is Eight, Thirty-one a.m. -- The temperature is minus one degree centigrade.   This morning is the first time this season I've seen the temp drop to below freezing. We're still waiting for the stucco guys to do our house ... and the three neighbors around us.  Yesterday we installed a few curtains and a basement doorbell chime. With any luck I'll get a  urlLink 150" target=king>   before winter storms in. We have a lot of furniture and shelving to build to make our new house a  home! 
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       B ig headache at work the last few days. last minute changes leading to cascade failure throughout all of our systems. Comedy of errors, whatever you want to call it. After 3 days of overtime and forfeited days off we have finally caught the tiger by the tail. To remain positive, we have hijacked the theme song from the kids show 'Bob The Builder' ... "Can we fix it?  YES WE CAN!"  
    
</post>

<date>19,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I added two moving day pictures to the post of 7.28.2002. I could not believe how hot and tired I got that day. I do not want to do that again in the near future. 
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I just changed to a more space-efficient blogger template. Sorry to you who need reading glasses to see the new text size, but I was always bothered by the humongous proportions of the other template. If you feel nostalgic, you can always review the archives, which I will leave alone. Now I'll have to re-do my customizations...
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Update for September 16, 2002:  Todays news is that there is no news.  Nothing worth sharing happened last week. Our house was not stuccoed.  Our yard was not levelled and landscaped. I did not fill up the film containing  the photo of BBB (see the Sept. 9 entry -  man, that was fun).  We  did  get the money from our old house ... but that wasn't too exciting  as we ended up about $1000 short ... so we will be staggering for a few paydays. I  did  also find a quick easy way to index my new photos to make them  available (for viewing only) online. If you're interested, check out my  webserver (if it is turned on) at    urlLink  http://webfolder.sawatzky.info/   sawatzky.info no longer active   I will be distilling, renaming, and moving the files available to the general public,  so you may have trouble with bookmarks of a specific item. Any movies you  find require the Apple Quicktime plugin. 
    
</post>

<date>10,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Dang it, just when I thought I licked this racist thing, some nigger come along and prove me wrong ...  urlLink take a looka dis ...   How did I find this you ask? Well I ... welll ... I was searching for lyrics to a song I was listening to  ...  
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       After a fairly uneventful week, came BBB day.   Boys Being Boys is what we dubbed the events of Saturday September 7.  In the evening we changed our acronym to GONADs, for Going Out Night for All Dads.  This of course is in response to (and some would say 'revenge for') all of the GNO's  we've been seeing recently. Girls Night Out is of course at least a monthly occurance,  so we have to make the most of our BBB's and GONADs.      Saturday started at 6 am Saturday A.M. when we all had to drag ourselfs out of bed, despite it being a weekend.       We all (7 of us) met at (get this) 'Bacon and Eggs' Restaurant for breakfast downtown. B&ER is a small one-man operation downtown with super-cheap  big breakfasts, as the name suggests.      After breakfast we strolled through a China-Town grocery where a few of us picked up food and snacks for later in the day.       One of the seven departed for the rest of the day, to rejoin us later for supper. The other  six of us spent the next hour or so at the S.I.R. outdoor store, and then the Lee Valley  Woodworking store.      After a stop at Tim Hortons for another coffee, we headed for St Laurent's 'Paintball Paradise', an hour and a half north-west.     At PbP we shot at our opponants with 280 ft/sec paintballs for about 5.5 hours in the great  outdoors. A great time was had by all and no lost eyeballs. Our games were played in the forest with dense underbrush and a light drizzle coming down from above.       After changing our of our thoroughly drenched clothing into something respectable, we headed  for Muddy Waters smokehouse at The Forks. This is where the GONAD part of the day began.  We called a few others to join us, but only the one who left us at breakfast rejoined us for an  amazing dinner of: Pork Ribs, Beef Ribs, Pulled Pork, Roast Chicken, Baked Beans, fries,  veggies, bread and butter, beer, coffee, cheesecake, apple-crisp, and pecan pie.      After dinner six of us went to the Cheap Theater and saw  Minority Report  for $2.95 each. On Sunday we each nursed our aches and pains, and today the pain is a reminder of the great time we had during the BBB weekend. [Come back next week for Pictures]
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The kids are out now... augmenting their candy supply for the long winter ahead.   urlLink      TRICK OR TREAT!!!  
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     Happy Halloween!  Congratulations for surviving the coldest October in HISTORY!  Play safe this Halloween.
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       PayDay!    Let's see if we can't crawl out of our hole this time...
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Janet has a new (additional) job! There is no way to put this delicately so I just tell it like it is...     She will now be collecting and processing your bodily fluids for new life insurance applications. If you are in the market, there is a small but not impossible chance that you will run into Nurse Janet.
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Oops, we did it again ...  In a bungled WindowsXP ad  urlLink Microsoft  throws pie in its own face ...
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      -11c this morning ... Brrrrrr.    I will be on a 3 day course starting today, at the CanadInn on Pembina. That means I won't be back at work till next monday. WooHoo! 
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Good day all you canadians eh?  Have a nice Thanksgiving weekend? All stuffed full of turkey?    I wrote this as a comment in PABLO's blog, but it bears repeating here: I would boycott Tim Hortons if I could find a better [and more convienient] cup of coffee somewhere else. Their whole rational for not having debit machines is SPEED. However, the only place you see speed is through the drive-thru. Why not then offer debit card service INSIDE where service is already turtle's pace, and leave the drive-thru cash only? (some Robin's Donuts do this already). If I don't have cash, I refuse to go to the bank machine to get money just for Tim Hortons. I'll drive out of my way instead and get a good cup of java at Starbucks (who DO take Interac).
    
</post>

<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        EXTRA  THIS JUST IN!   The photo evidence is all here  ...  urlLink    The five mennonites and one sympathizer who escaped their accountability peers for a day of secret carnage in the outback have been identified, thanks to a photo leaked to the press by an unknown informant. The names of the alledged anarchists are as follows, from left to right: Myron K, Martin P, John W, Kevin S, David S, Daryl S.   Click on the small photo for a larger one. 
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Will the real Slim Shady PLEASE SHUT UP?!?  This may be old but I still find it funny:   urlLink   Will the real Slim Shady PLEASE  SHUT UP ?!?   
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Snow      
    
</post>

<date>04,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       A few house blues  ...  the builder is sticking us with the cost of a permit we thought he took care of long ago ... the animal services branch is cruising new neighborhoods ( such as ours) and forcing all dogs to be licenced (we got away with no tags for 8 years, and the dog is already 12 years old) ... the same dog had an 'accident' on the new carpet, not totally his fault ... and although I have the new saw, I have no money for wood, and the weather is turning very cold.
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       I bought the saw!  Sunday afternoon I finally got the table saw. There was no picture available on the Delta site, so I took this one which is almost the same. [update: this is now the right picture]. I could not be happier with it. So far I have not cut any wood with it. I spent one night assembling it, another adjusting it, and listening to the whirr when I turn it on. Every time my hand brushes that razor sharp cross-cut blade, I lose some blood.  Hopefully tonight I will be able to make a few cuts on wood.    urlLink     Congrats to Pablo on his first day of  HOME OWNERSHIP !!!
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         If I was a U.S. city I'd be Seattle, the Emerald City.  What US city are you?  urlLink Take the quiz  by  urlLink Girlwithagun .
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Halloween is a distant memory, the snow has arrived and Christmas is in the air. The kids are putting together 'Operation Christmas Child' packages, and Christmas concert practices dominate our calendar. This season induces in me the kind of feeling I get when I see my VISA bill ... that sinking feeling in the pit of my stomach. Maybe the two causes are in reality the same thing. I'm fine by summertime.   
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Its four days past Halloween. There were no incidents in our new neighborhood that I have heard of. Last night though, I had to put on my candy cop hat. One of the girls decided that she didn't need real food anymore. She was happy with her new diet of  flavored sugar. I had to tell her that, just like at McD's, BK, and Wendy's -- if she didn't eat her real food, the prizes were mine. Once she realized I was serious about placing the candy on the top shelf, her appetite suddenly returned.    
    
</post>

<date>30,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
          Today was my first day back to work after a wonderful Christmas week off. Ugh! I seem to have picked up a cold during the Christmas break, something I was resistant to for the previous two months, while everyone else in our house was sick. On the bright side, Tomorrow, New Year's Eve, is a 5 hour workday for us Gov't types. Can't complain about THAT.  Santa was kind this year. Mostly $$$ and shop tools. Janet got a FREE **1/3** Megapixel Vivitar Emage 100V digital  camera with her recent cell phone purchase. With 8 MBs of RAM, it can store up to 26 full screen* photos at reasonable Quality. With compression on that number rises to almost 100 photos! The photo of my messy cubicle (above) was from that camera, but I scaled it down by 75%. Of course nothing is truely free, and the price I paid was the camera's software now causes Photoshop 7 to crash on startup. Doh! Well, we have an evening of  food and bowling planned for our New Years Party. Take care, and remember ... when you drink and drive, you lose! ; )   *if you have a VGA monitor!
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        Merry Christmas everybody!  (or all  one  of you that reads this with any regularity!)  With only 4 days to go I wanted to get this note in before it was too late. All four of us have at least the next 12 days off. We will visit family, play with our new toys, and continue the cleaning up process we have been involved in since we've moved into this house.  MOST of our Christmas shopping is done. If anything, I want to go look for alternive grab-box gifts so I can keep the ones I bought -- they're too nice to give away. Or maybe I'll but a few more of the same to keep!  As a Christmas present, my boss let me know [early] that my work term was extended another 3 months from the end of January. Yay. I know it's not his fault, but our terms at work have been short, and we usually only hear the day before they expire, that they have been extended. 
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Birthday Janet. Janet gets 35 bumps this morning. She can count them on her newest business tool from Palm Inc while playing Giraffe, the Grafitti learning tool.  urlLink      
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The Geniuses in Apple's marketing dept. have done it again... you can now buy a classic G3 iMac, snow white in color, under the moniker of 'Classic' for a mere $1249 [Canadian dollars]. This iMac is identical to mine in all ways but one ... it does not include a CD burner. Yes, now you can Rip and Mix, ... but you can no longer BURN.    urlLink     What confuses ME is that I bought mine a year ago as a 'Special Edition' for < $1200, with the same HD size (40 GB), RAM config (128 MB), processor (600mHz G3) and video card (32 MB ATI). Why would they now leave out the CD-burner, and charge MORE?!? Shouldn't they now be trying to get RID of the old style iMacs -- now that you can get a G4 flat screen iMac for < $2000? I don't git it.
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a DOOZER of a wipe-out on the way to the bus today. I hit the ground so hard it was funny. I slid down a small hill at the edge of the park. Since I had a lot of forward motion, and the hill was still moving down and away from me, when my feet slid out from under me my upper body hit the ground well before my feet did. I landed on my side, so I'll have a good sized bruise on my hip, and my left wrist. Fortunately nothing hurts now. Just a little tingling in my wrist. And I made it to the bus just as the last person in line was stepping on.     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Believe it or Not: Some holiday make-up tips from the experts can be found at   urlLink http://www.lifewise.canoe.ca/LifewiseBeauty0211/1126_makeup.html  Before:      and After:        
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      And from the wacky world of candy and drugs:    from WIRED magazine Feb '03 
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been reading (while  not  on the bus) Cory Doctorow's futuristic Utopian novel,  Down and Out in the Magic Kingdom . The unique thing about this book is not so much the  content , but the  medium  in which it is published: while the book is available in the bookstores in hard copy, it is also freely available in just about  any  format you can imagine ... PDF, Palm, HTML, Plain Text, LIT (Microsoft's Window's LE Reader), etc. Click on the book to go to the complete list, and start reading! It is really a rather good story.  urlLink     Cory claims that there have been over a million downloads, but I have at least three or four of them so I can read the book with whatever hardware happens to be available.  Correction: This was posted at Cory's site Feb 10 ... "A month after releasing Down and Out in the Magic Kingdom,  over 75,000 copies of the book have been downloaded from the site ..." I read a million somewhere, but that was not from Cory's site.  I apologize for the gross inflation. I took a wuffie hit on that one.
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      How many Nestle products do you buy in a week? Do you have any IDEA? The dollar figure would probably surprise you. Anyways, Nestle is caught up in a  urlLink lawsuit  with the Ethiopians Government over a livestock firm owned by Nestle, but sold by the Ethiopian Government to a local business for $8.5 million. OK, I can see their point, but they are essentially sueing this 3rd world Government for 6 million US dollars, which is the profit above and beyond the true value of the farm. It's true. A company that made over 3.9 BILLION US dollars in the first 6 months of last year, is sueing for 6 million over a $1.5 million dispute (that's how much the business was worth to Nestle) with an impoverished country whose GDP is about $100 per person per YEAR. Can you say NASTY GREEDY INHUMAN ... Just take 2 million, and start over ...   urlLink     So, I guess I'll be looking at labels till this comes to a satisfactory end. No more Quik, no more Dairy Milk Bars, KitKat, Nerds (We have kids you know), Tollhouse products, Libby's products, Stouffers, Lean Cuisine, Perrier, Nescafe  ...
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Wow.  This has been a typical January so far. Nothing new happening here. No money to spend, Christmas bills stacking up, COLD. I rented a bunch of DVD's, cleaned up the basement - trying to prepare for framing, relaxed. Tomorrow is payday # 2 of 3 for this month.  In other news, Apple this week released a beta version of their new web-browser  urlLink  Safari   based on Konqueror, an open-source  standards based  Linex KDE file and internet browser.    urlLink     =   urlLink     The beta is free, but of COURSE, Apple is trying to force my hand into buying the new version of OSX (Jaguar) by making Safari incompatible with my version of OSX. It'll cost me $200 (CDN) to upgrade to Jaguar. So far the upgrade has not been worth it for me, but as Apple develops more Jaguar-only apps, the change is becoming more tempting. When iSync was announced, I had no use for it. But now that we have a Palm device, iSync and Jaguar's new addressbook and iCal are looking better than ever.  Since the Pro version of Quicktime is included with Jaguar, I can take the price of that license off of the Jaguar tag (I've been putting off that purchase for some time now). A release of iMovie 3 would just push me over the edge!  Added to my template today: A.Word.A.Day. I get A Word A Day and WorldWideWords as daily/weekly email. I find that I really didn't know the meaning (or origin) of words I hear only occasionally. These lists will help me know what I am reading and (hopefully) give me an edge at party games!
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever wonder what your phone number could be if you turned it into text? Mine wasn't too exciting, but yours might be! Click my number below and find out!    urlLink      Here is an  urlLink alternate  site.   
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I sent an email to Saucony asking why I couldn't find ANY information about my new shoes on the internet. Here is there reply:  Daryl Thank you for your email. The Grid Legacy are very comparable to our Grid Jazz 8 which is on our web site. The reason you found no information is because we did not put any marketing dollars against this shoe, hence the lower price point. We basically manufacture the shoe and ship it directly to retail. We don't warehouse it, market it, put it on our websitek, so all you are paying for is the shoe itself. There are not as many bells and whistles as our higher prices shoes, but it is technically sound and biomechanically correct for you to run in. This is a cushioning shoe for a neutral runner. If you are a runner who tends to over-pronate and is seeking a stability shoe, we do recommend you exchange this shoe for a stability shoe. Hope this helps. Saucony, Inc.  I think I will keep 'em.
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I broke down and replaced my MIA running pants. For some reason my first pair decided to go AWOL during the move to our new house. Since these pants had magic properties, motivating me to get out there and run when I put them on ... when the pants disappeared, so did the magic. I kept thinking that if the magic pants could disappear so easily, than they could reappear at any time. But alas, the weather is showing signs of warming. I've been through every box in the house trying to find the magic pants MANUALLY, but they are no-where to be found. Only time will tell if the replacement pants, also Nike but not nearly as Cool as the first pair, have any magic in them. I also replaced my worn out Nike running shoes for a size larger pair of Saucony shoes.   urlLink   Saucony Grid Jazz8   Just to clarify: These are not the shoes I bought. I cannot find my shoes (Saucony Grid Legacy) unless I go to European websites ... and pictures there are either non-existant or too small to see any detail. My shoes have red accent coloring and reflective grey panels stitched in. The bare canvas color is navy instead of the white shown here.
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Happy Valentines Day! Seems this Valentine's will be all about friends. For the rest of the weekend we will be back home for a Valentine's Weekend wedding. Congratulations Tara and David!    We will also be meeting Wes and Angie for breakfast, and just yesterday, I ran into some old friends, Harold G. (last seen 1987), and Brent A. (last seen ... i don't know ... '84? '85? ... before he had a  beard  anyway...) Good to see you all! 
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        *** NewsFlash!*** This site has a new domain name!  urlLink darylsawatzky.com  ******************************  
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hats off to all the fine folks and families at NASA on their terrible loss this morning.   urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      What  is   the sound of SILENCE? To me it sounds like ... a running refridgerator ... and nothing but ... and yesterday it was driving me a little crazy. To explain lets just say that Janet and the kids are travelling out west this week, so it's just me, Sam and the cats. Sam is pretty quiet until someone walks by the house.  Yesterday Sam alerted me to the presence of someone on our property. I looked outside and sure enough, the SHAW Cable guy was sitting in his van outside ... which prompted me to look up my cable bill ... which made me real nervous ... until he left, leaving my cable (and internet!) service intact. Pheeeww! I think I have a bill to pay today. Anyways, back to the silence... it's really quite unnerving. I must be a genuine city-slicker already. I'm used to cars and busses, and people yelling at each other. In our new neighborhood I hear nothing of that. There's new construction during the week, but yesterday ... Sunday... there was nothing. No cars, no tractors or trucks, no kids (I blame that on the weather). Finally I went to Leanne and Vince's to watch  The Sum Of All Fears  and play with their PS2... Grand Turismo 3 and LOTR.
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       I have recently discovered that precurser to the World Wide Web, the Internet of the Airwaves ... Shortwave Radio.             Miniworld 100 PE by GRUNDIG     So far I have listened intently to a Japanese station, Spanish (SA, or Spain, how would I know? or even USA for that matter), an English religious station discussing the Book of Revelation (how appropriate),  and BBC, country of transmission unknown. So far though, 90% of my radio time has been with  urlLink CJOB 68 AM radio , available world-wide via the Internet, not shortwave.   
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       The long anticipated WAR has started.  The talk on CJOB talk radio has been centered on the response of Canada to the US-led invasion of Iraq. Our Prime Minister, Cretien, and stated categorically that "Canadians are against this action". Many people who previosly  thought  that they were Canadians, are calling in to the show to show that, in fact, not all Canadians are against the US and are furious at their PM for not supporting our neighbors and friends.  While I have posted an anti-war sentiment on this website, which I believe most people would agree with   in principle , I do not believe that it is prudent to disassociate with the US. I believe that war with Iraq was decided in 1991 when the UN imposed sanctions against Iraq. I believe that the UN, not the US has made this war inevitable. In fact, if you want to go waaay back, I believe that the idiotic body of governers that invented the concept of  sanctions  is to blame for the conflicts that ensue when the sanctions inevitably fail.  The good book tells us that "Perfect love casts out fear". This concept has a LOT of power. Even a small smidgen of 'love' can go a long way. I am not talking about a christian invasion of offending countries, and I am not saying that this is even possible in our world because people are just too selfish, but the principle is valid.  Take the example of the madman down the street, who has been ignored by his neighbors, beats his kids, killed his wife, and struts around his front yard with a loaded shotgun. The arguement is that someone should DO something, but WHO? The neighbors, who have an interest in keeping peace with the neighbor? The authorities who are equipped to handle people like this? Who? We would say, obviously, that the police would have to move in, and the neighbors should lie low. MY arguement would not suggest walking up to this guy and giving him a hug...it's too late ... Some might try, and might even be successful in calming the guy down. More likely they would end up with a hole in their chest. I would argue, like the US in their current position, that it is too late for diplomacy. In this case, the time for diplomacy was when the 'guy' was a friendless chap in your high school, who you never cared to talk to because he swore to much. The time for diplomacy was when he moved to your street and got married, and had kids your own kids age. The time for diplomacy was when they had their first big fight, and the whole neighborhood knew about it, but everyone  kept to themselves .  With Iraq, the time for diplomacy to start was before sanctions were imposed, was before Iraq felt that they could invade Kuwait and get away with it, it was at the first sign of trouble, wayyy back when Saddam attacked Iran and showed his propensity for attacking his neighbors. The key to stopping conflicts is to make it harder on the rulers if they step out of line. How do you do that? Apply sanctions that weaken the innocent population, and empower the dictator? Yeah, like  that  will work. Look at our favorite case study, and nearest neighbor Cuba. Do sanctions drive out dictators? What would have happenned to Cuba if the US hadn't applied sanctions on Cuba? It would be a US State by now! The US would be Castro's biggest cigar and tourism customer. The US would make it IMPOSSIBLE for Castro to play his games with the US. Capitalism would defeat Communism in a heartbeat. Of course every country is different, and every dictator a different story.  What would have kept Saddam in line, with his bent towards middle east domination? Maybe nothing. I believe that his goals were born out of the Israeli occupation. I don't think there is a lot you can do to prevent  prophecy . I don't see a diplomatic solution, even if it was started at the beginning of conflict with Iraq. I don't mean to be fatalistic, but even though I don't believe in fighting to resolve conflict, I don't think that fighting is avoidable. Eventually we have to choose to be watchers of horrendous deeds, or preventors of those deeds, however violent the methods are. I remember in high school, while being beat up on by a 'friend' I did everything I could to avoid the conflict. Finally it took a surgical strike (to his face) to end the conflict. I suppose I could have let him finish and stop on his own. I would have lived up to my own ideals, and he would have felt what? terrible? satisfied that he taught me a lesson? What would  I  have felt? I would have felt that I needed to taunt him to prove that his beating meant nothing to me. Or I would have shown him what true love meant, that it means not returning violence for violence. I will never know if my actions would have made a difference in our relationship.  However, I have difficulty applying that experience to the situation in Iraq. In my case I was only taking a few punches. In Iraq, whole groups of people have taken mustard gas bombs, and have been imprisoned, with thier kids tortured in front of them. How does one walk away from that kind of violence? In this case a 'surgical strike' looks mighty appealing, if it can stop the violence. Walking away and applying true love ... lifting sanctions, increasing the foreign tourist population, adding more UN 'eyes' to the country ... could have worked just as well, though with more long-term effort. It would have made Saddam rich beyond his wildest dreams, but it would have made the Iraqi people rich as well ... friends with the world, with a LOT at stake if their ruler steps out of line.   SO the bottom line is that ...  love  is the only true ANSWER to the worlds troubles. However that approach will never happen in this society because the nations of the U.N. (including Canada) will NEVER agree to make an evil dictator rich beyond his wildest dreams, and today's society is too selfish to make any kind of long-term commitment to a troubled country if they have no stake in that country.   I think that we should support the US in what they are doing because this conflict has been a long time coming, and Canada has NOT done the right thing by showing Iraq  true love  by becoming involved and intertwined with those people. Last minute moralisms do nothing to resolve our national guilt over this issue.  If this sounds convoluted, wishy-washy, and disjointed, it is because  I  am convoluted, my opinions are torn, and I'm writing this at work where some people actually expect me to be working!
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         Ouch Oww Owwie ... Exactly one month after I purchased my new running shoes, they went on their maiden voyage. Five-point-five kilometers (2.6 miles) of slush, mud and ice in 1 degree (C) weather took its toll on my poor overburdened knees, but the run itself went amazingly smoothly. I actually enjoyed it. Although I haven't run since the last Father's Day Marathon (where I ran the 2.6 mile fun run) ... which was about eight months ago ... I experienced none of the startup pains of last time. No burning lungs, no spitting up blood, no pounding headache. In fact, by the end of this run, Sam, who was keeping me company, was dragging on his leash behind me because he was too pooped to keep up. If you feel sorry for the dog, at least do it for the right reason -- this 13 year old Golden Retriever has been cooped up in the house all winter. It's time for both of us to get in shape. In fact, I think I should put HIM on the scale and keep track of his weight!   
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
          I heard it from the source ... an Irishman ... St. Patrick was a SCOTSMAN!!! Abducted at age 14 from his native Scotland to tend Irish sheep, St. Patrick later escaped back to Scotland, joined the ministry, and voluntarily moved back to the people that abducted him. Takes a Saint to do that!        urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I just found the  urlLink  BLOG  of one of my favorite authors. Even though I have read only ONE of his books, I knew he would be a favorite even before I read that one (see my bus book page). I bought another of William Gibson's books yesterday, 'All Tomorrows Parties', his fist post-netizen book. I was a little surprised to hear that the person who coined the word 'cyberspace' in his  first  book was a internet luddite until after writing his sixth (?) book! Now he's caught the  urlLink 'bug'  and has his own fairly sophisticated  urlLink  web site , hosted (and presumably designed by)   urlLink  AuthorsOnTheWeb.com    
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's entry is a link to a rather humourus piece  allegedly  written by John Cleese ... at the very least it follows Monty Python tradition, which is good enough for me....  urlLink  AXIS of Just As Evil  
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       We got a new vacuum at Costco today, a Euro-Pro Fantom Twister HEPA filter bagless upright. Got the picture? Then try urlLink  this  Apparently the Fantom line went into credit protection last year, and the Euro-Pro company bought them out. The Twister line is the first of the Euro-Pro line. All other Fantom models are no longer under warrantee (Thunder, Cyclone, Fury, Lightning). 
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It happened a lot faster than we expected! In 2 days we got our stucco scratch coat  and  our final color coat!    color: Suede     The dark parts are wet stucco. It will all dry lighter. Hopefully when it rains the wet spots will get dark again. I like that look.
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      We got a bit of a scare last night. Sam seems to have had either a) a really bad dream where he was falling through thin air, or b) he had a full blown seizure. I'm not sure which it was, but the poor guy was flopping around on the floor at 2:30 am. We thought that one of the cats had startled him awake, and he jumped, but a few seconds later a second wave hit him. He spilled his water pail, and when we turned the lights on, we saw the tail end of the episode. It looked like he was trying to get up but had no control of his legs. It ended with a loss of continence. He immediately appeared to be normal with full control of himself as we were cleaning up. Today a leg seems a little stiff perhaps from overstretching. Sam is our Golden Retreiver, born 1990.
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
          Well, well, well. Today was a DAY OF FIRSTS... 1) First Coat of stucco on our house 2) First Bon-fire in our city-approved wheeled fire-pit 3) First visit from the fire-dept, tipped off by an overly-concerned neighborhood resident with poor eyesight. 
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
           Happy Easter everybody .  Just don't be fooled into thinking that  chocolate  has  anything  to do with Easter.  
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Why are kids so cruel? I got this from a couple of high school girls on my run tonight ...  them: "hey running man, got a lighter?"  me: "No" them: "Didn't think you would being all healthy and all... Nice BOD for, like, a 45 year old." me, thinking: that's 37!  If I were THAT old, I'd be able to retire in ... 2018!
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Woo hoo!!! According to my Statement of Pension and Group Benefits, I can RETIRE with an immediate annuity on my birthday in  2025 !* That's sooner than that of a lot of my co-workers who have been here a lot longer then I have.    *that is with 2% of my average salary per year of service, or in this case, 50% of the average of my best 5 years' salary.
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "For God's sake why? It's already there in IE"  URL handling is integral to OS X - therefore the ability to change which applications handle these protocols is also integral to OS X. Currently the only way to do this is through IE.  Therefore in order to configure something that is integral to the Mac OS you have to use *a web browser* that is built by Microsoft - If that doesn't seem wrong to you then you've already given your soul to Bill Gates.   urlLink       On to another subject:  We (or rather, Janet) bought new living room furniture today. Excited doesn't  begin  to describe her. This new leather sofa and loveseat will be our first new furniture in ... nine years. 
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally got a transparency scanner on Saturday. A 2400dpi HP 4570c Flatbed scanner with transparency adapter. I've read mixed reviews, and so far, I know where the reviewers coming from.   urlLink      Quite frankly, the scanning software sucks (the OSX version, haven't looked at the Windows version yet). So far I have not found a way to make preferences  stick  between sessions (destination directories, file formats, scan sizes in actual pixels, etc), for full functionality HP requires the use of two or three applications (preview software, image editing software, and an iPhoto-like program that I would rather just use iPhoto for), the scans are automatically stored as huge TIFFs in the application directory if you are sending you scan to an editing app like Photoshop, and the software is not intelligent enough to preselect all of the images on the scanner bed, and store your scan preferences for each picture, and then scan all at once, the scanner doesn't work with third party scanning software like Vuescan and SilverFast. HP, ... Look at Agfa's Scanwise software. That's what scanning software should do.   I am a little surprised at how dull and lifeless a scanned slide looks compared to the original. If any transparency experts would like to give me some scanning hints, I would appreciate that.  However, the price was right ($250), and at the moment I am confident that I can persuade this thing to fill my needs, as long as it doesn't completely break down. 
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      We were alarmed yesterday. Literally. Don't you try sneaking into our house, cuz you'll hear a big big noise.   urlLink     urlLink http://www.adt.ca/en/residential/safewatch/demo   
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      SEE WHERE I WORK! Although I couldn't see this on MY work computer ... there could be a number of problems with my Java and IE relationship ... I have seen this work on other computers. This is a user controllable web-cam across the river, pointing this way. Between us and the camera is the new bridge, which is the main reason the camera is set up: To find me, start the camera, then click one page to the right of the bridge. I'm in the middle of the 'mushroom-shaped' building.  urlLink www.winnipeg.ca/publicworks/Engineering/ProvencherLiveCam.asp 
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been busy designing the layout of our basement. I procured a program called 3-D Home architect Deluxe V 3.0 the enables me to draw the basement in 2-D with standard materials libraries, and then render the drawing in 3-D with the push of a button. The image below is one sample with default colors. Textures can also be applied to each surface to bring the design closer to your vision.    urlLink      3-D Home architect Deluxe V 3.0 is published by  urlLink Broderbund . Their current version is 5.0, so I got version 3.0 from a clearance source, Dave's Dwellings Inc.... for $17 US. Version 5 apparently uses a more powerful CAD engine, but is harder to learn. For $39 US though, it might be worth a try.
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Mama's Day!      In other news from the last week: A few weeks after stucco, and after some preliminary grading, and the exterior is looking more and more like a home.      
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday, the 29th of April, the  parging  was finished on our house. Parging is the process of conditioning the cement of the foundation, and then applying a layer of stucco on top of the cement. The color is a nice even grey. Now final grading of our yard is scheduled for next week. All that is left to do on the house is evestroughs. The rest is landscaping, and my own activities in the garage and basement ...
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I've finished the none-too-small task of scanning all of the slides I found several years ago. There are approximately 340 of the buggers, depicting some very interesting looking hiking trips and group campouts. Some also appear to be a wilderness movie shoot or something.   urlLink     If these photos belong to you, please email me with a description of how and where I may have come across them. You can have them back.  Now I will be moving forward with the MONUMENTAL task of scanning my 1987 Europe slides ... all 1,296 of them. After that there are another couple of hundred more that I took after Europe. I did the found slides first, knowing that once I was finished the 1,500 of my own, I wouldn't want to touch the others. Then there will be dad's slides ...
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow ... Apple just introduced the next gorgeous computer I could not possibly afford until it's too late ... the G5:   urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, we've had a semi-busy couple of weeks. Last weekend (Father's day) we sat around the Manitoba Marathon route, cheered and took pictures of friends as they ran by.   urlLink     This week we were told we were to be getting our front lawn installed (included in the price of our house), so we waited, and waited ... but so far no lawn.   This weekend we went camping for 3 days at a provincial park just north of the city (Bird's Hill). I foolishly figured it was time to get rid of my farmers tan by wearing sleeveless shirts (and for a while, no shirt) all day Saturday. Sunblock would only counteract my efforts, so I wiped the kids down and put the sunblock away. IF I took off my shirt off at work today, (assuming people wouldn't run and hide) the lobster jokes would fly. After seeing the beautiful tan the kids got WITH sunscreen, I'd hope to be a little wiser next time I take my shirt off.  
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      HERE is my radio...   urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh man, I've been meaning to post since last Friday, but TIME ... time is ticking away.  Last Saturday our neighborhood had a massive community garage sale. Fortunatly for me, I had to drive Janet to work at 7 am, so when we got home, the other three of us hopped on our bikes and got an early start on the garage sales. Within 10 minutes, my arms were loaded with DEALS. First I got an external frame hiking backpack, used once and a fish scale, $10. Then the girls got themselves a few stuffed animals and a change purse. Then I got a nifty vintage, classic tube radio, from the late 50's or early 60's for $3.    urlLink    This is NOT my radio, but looks the same. Mine says BEAVER on the face plate, while this one says RINCAN. Mine has a dark woodtone cabinet, where this one is white.  Next we got a Nintendo64 gaming console with 3 games for $45, a Stanley router from the 60's $7 (a woodworking tool, not a computer periphial), a Kite $5, and some wood veneer $1. For me, the Radio rates as the coolest find, while the N64 is the most used. The radio must be super rare, since I cannot find even one mention of it on the internet [well, now I obviously found one, but it's just a picture with zero info]. None of the dozens of vintage and classic radio pages mention the apparent maker ... Beaver. There is ONE radio called the Beaver Baby Grand, but it is nothing like what I have, and is the only Beaver Radio mentioned anywhere. Inside the radio, the speakers have "Philco" marked on them. Philco was a MAJOR radio maker of the day (Phillips Co.) and are still around, but again ... a search of Phillips radios yields no matches to mine. If anyone has information about this radio I would appreciate an email to fill me in. 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm almost finished our new shed. The long tedious part is rot-proofing the cedar. I have to soak every single siding board, trim board and cedar shingle in this  urlLink mixture  that instantly ages the cedar and supposedly protects it from any further deterioration.   Now after going through all the pieces of this kit, I have some mixed feelings about it. The kit is made by a company called BGYardkit (?!?) from BC. The design itself is adequate. However, I feel that they must have taken greater care when picking the pieces of the demo units that the Windsor Plywood stores put together. The collection of sticks that I received were sub-standard to say the least. I would have bypassed 3/4 of the wood if I were picking it myself at the lumberyard. In contrast, the demo shed at Windsor Plywood has almost-clear cedar siding (no loose knots) perfect timbers, and cedar front fascia instead of the 1x6 pine I got. Many of my 1x4 trim pieces are twisted, warped or cupped or are bark pieces. SOMEONE is making a killing selling off their scrap wood in these shed kits. 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we are having our new shed delivered. It was precut in B.C. and shipped to Windsor Plywood. We have to put it together. The dimensions are 10x8  feet (10 being the front) and is all cedar (except for the 2x4 frame). A smaller example can be seen on  urlLink  page 3 of this pdf .
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      After two days of intense labor WE HAVE A DECK! Thanks dad for levelling and framing on Friday, and Janet for  screwing  all day Saturday.        These are the only pictures of the finished deck I have right now. Taken from video shot late in the evening.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     I must thank the guys at Windsor Plywood on Pembina Hwy for their excellent service. I got a quote for a deck on Monday. It was closing time, the store was busy, but James took the time to use the computer program to design a deck, explain the plans to me, and print out the list of parts I would need to build it. Total cost: $1,573.03. I went back to order the deck this morning, James wasn't there, so a fellow named Dave helped me. One glance at the parts list, and Dave could tell that something didn't look right. For starters, He knew that the end-cut treatment came in smaller quantities than what was printed on my estimate. He also knew that if he added one pound of deck screws to the estimate quantity (from 17 to 18 pounds), I would get the box price, which was $20 less. Excellent start. Now for the big savings, in price and design ... Dave reduced the joist size from 8 to 6 inches. He added three 2x6 3-ply beams which will reduce weight while adding strength. Total cost of the improved design: $1,408.00. Thanks guys, and I'll be back for a shed   urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      We Got Grass!    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's link is a bone for all you Adobe Photoshop fans out there ... a gallary of work that will leave you wondering "How did they DO that?!?" I even let the pop-up ad play through several times -- a Stadium Anthem ad willl cool tunes ...  Check it out:   urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I registered for Family Camp ... the final activity of our holidays for the past few summers. The  urlLink picture  in the banner above was taken at one of these occasions. This year Janet will be staying home as she has to work, but the girls and I will be roughing it in a tent. Hopefully it won't rain, or we'll be sleeping in the van.
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Block Party!   urlLink     The birthday party for Gabi, Jenny, and Michael was a hit, with the air castle, hot dogs and chips, cream soda and the candy "Pik*a*Prize" candy wheel.
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Microsoft vs. GM ================  At a recent computer expo (COMDEX), Bill Gates reportedly compared the computer industry with the auto industry and stated, "If GM had kept up with technology like the computer industry has, we would all be driving $25 cars that got 1,000 miles to the gallon."  In response to Bill's comments, General Motors issued a press release stating: If GM had developed technology like Microsoft, we would all be driving cars with the following characteristics:  1. For no reason whatsoever, your car would crash twice a day.  2. Every time they repainted the lines in the road, you would have to buy a new car.  3. Occasionally, your car would die on the freeway for no reason. You would have to pull over to the side of the road, close all of the windows, shut off the car, restart it, and reopen the windows before you could continue. For some reason you would simply accept this.  4. Occasionally, executing a maneuver such as a left turn would cause your car to shut down and refuse to restart, in which case you would have to reinstall the engine.  5. Macintosh would make a car that was powered by the sun, was reliable, five times as fast and twice as easy to drive - but would run on only five percent of the roads.  6. The oil, water temperature, and alternator warning lights would all be replaced by a single "This Car Has Performed An Illegal Operation" warning light.  7. The airbag system would ask, "Are you sure?" before deploying.  8. Occasionally, for no reason whatsoever, your car would lock you out and refuse to let you in until you simultaneously lifted the door handle, turned the key and grabbed hold of the radio antenna.  9. Every time a new car was introduced, car buyers would have to learn how to drive all over again because none of the controls would operate in the same manner as the old car.  10. You'd have to press the "Start" button to turn the engine off. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, the shed is done. Dad came over last Friday and helped me square up the walls and brace the shed. Then we finished the trim and shingles. It looks nice now, but I'm looking forward to the color change as the wood ages. I like that nice even silver tone.  We got a few shrubs for the front yard and trees for around the rest of the yard. We don't know what we like, so we are winging it. We got a Burning Bush, two Dogwood bushes, a BuffaloBerry bush and a Pin Cherry bush. For trees we got a Shubert ChokeCherry tree, a Silver Maple and a Linden tree. The big problem for us now is knowing where to plant them. We have no formal plan for the yard, so anything we do may have to be changed later. More on this as it develops.  Yesterday was my birthday. To celebrate we got the  urlLink  smoker  and roasted a ton of meat: two pork roasts, a beef blade roast, some pork spareribs, and a chicken. the meat was fantastic and the guests enjoyed it. Despite the rain, everyone found a semi dry place to sit -- either under the tent on the deck, or in the house.
    
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have started the long and tedious process of scanning, color-correcting, rotating cropping, annotating ... etc. of my collection of kodachromes. Expect to see a link to the results in about ... oh ... maybe two months.  
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I got about twelve photos back from our 20th anniversary high School Reunion. To see them, click the graphic:   urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I was out at the lake last weekend where I took advantage of the darkness and clear skies: below are four views of Mars as it moved across the sky. The pics were taken with a Sony SteadyShot Digital8 video camera on a tripod.   urlLink    urlLink     urlLink    urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My Photos from Germany are ready for viewing. There are only three pages of 20 slides from Germany, but they include the beautiful Black Forest, a few pictures of the kids at Black Forest Academy (in 1987 of course), and the U2/Pretenders/Lou Reed/B.A.D.... concert I got to see in Basil Switzerland. These photos span the weeks between June 15 and July 15 1987.   urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't believe it's been a month since my last lame post. What has transpired since then?   Well, I have been researching my next largish purchase ... a new digital camera. After extensive research in to the strengths and weaknesses of the various cameras in my price range, I've almost decided to go with my first instinct -- Canon. I say 'almost' because anything could happen between now and when I actually have money-in-hand ... new Christmas pricing, new cheaper models in the other leading brands, my choice sold out ... but we'll cross that bridge when we get there.  I've also finished scanning my 1987 British Isles tour slides. You can view them here    urlLink      We've also been busy in the 'new' house: We moved the last of the river rock to the back yard where we built a 'dry' river bed to guide run-off water from the west side of the yard dowm to the east side. We also planted three new trees. With any luck they'll survive the winter and the deer and rabbits that like to eat their bark.   My last outdoor task will be to re-pack the dirt around our window well to try to stop the flow of water down our foundation every time it rains. The well fills up with water and overflows in through the window, causing some wetness in the kid's play area. That has to stop. The excess groundwater we already experience has burned out our first sump-pump [well, actually it was a stone caught in the impellor that did the damage]. I replaced it with a better unit which hopefully will last a few more years than the first one.  The basement is now rearranged and prepped for work I intend to do this winter: wiring and drywalling. The basement feels more open than it ever has since we moved in.  
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
          urlLink      
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      We've got a few broken links today, because I've let my .info domain name go.   I'll place all my marbles behind the darylsawatzky.com domain name,  so the photo pages below will be inaccessible until I rewrite those posts.   Please keep checking back for updates though. This effect is only temporary.
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My Photos from Hungary are ready for viewing... only 16 years after the fact. Oh well... hopefully those involved will be able to find and enjoy them.  These photos span the weeks between July 15 and August 30, 1987.   urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        -40 c     as reported today by the Winnipeg Int'l Airport weatherstation   
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Once again you'll notice a few broken links ... This time due to a major accident on my hard drive. Among the casualties (the only casualties, really) are 4 GIGABYTES of scanned photos and slides , and all my digital photo files since January 1.  (found backups) 
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          urlLink create your own visited country map 
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After several weeks of flakey computer performance and severely cold weather, things are starting to look up. My computer problems were self-inflicted, and are now completely reversed, well, except for the re-scanning of hundreds of slides.  One positive piece of news since the last post is that I got the 'letter' announcing the eligibility list for promotions at work. There are three positions up for grabs, and I made the list. I will not say more about that here, in case you-know-who reads this. 
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My solar system got bigger today, and I got corrospondingly smaller. I always assumed that the solar system more or less ended at Pluto. I knew there was controversy whether it should have ever been termed 'planet', that it was just the biggest of the rocks in the Kuiper Belt,  but whatever. I thought if a rock was big enough to be seen from here, it deserved the title... even if just honorary.  There is now another Pluto-ish sized rock, dubbed 'Sedna' (after a goddess of the cold sea), tracking beyond the orbit of Pluto. Although it also travels around our sun, it follows a highly elliptical orbit, nearing the planets only once in it's orbit. The scale diagram below (four scales actually) put the size of its orbit in perspective, and also that of the Oort cloud ... made up of objects that orbit our sun. In comparison, WE are living in the face of the sun, just beyond her nose, while Sedna is on the other side of the continent, and the farthest objects in the Oort cloud are close to our moon.  urlLink    Right Click picture and "View Image" to see full size
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink         If you see the Deep Cranberry van ... it's not us. We got new wheels on Tuesday.  
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink    I've found a great source of classic texts for reading on the Palm ... its the  urlLink UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA'S E-BOOK LIBRARY for the MS READER and PALM Devices   
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For all  one  of you that read this blog ... I'll list the latest:   Janet's mom has cancer. Everyone is being very brave, doing what they can. She's, what? mid-seventies, and is now training dad to fend for himself should the worst happen. Our whole neighborhood is having a big garage sale this weekend. We have been cleaning out our basement, looking for things to sell. We have a small pile, but more importantly, this search has forced us to reorganize this pile of boxes down there.  In my search I found two undeveloped B&W films from the year we got married. There's a bunch of zoo pics, some of Janet in our first apartment together, and some picture I took in the park. Nothing special, but still ... who-da thunk that film could be developed after 15 years?!?  In one month B & J will be finished Gr. 1 & 3. This year has flown by.  In the workshop this spring I have made several end tables. One was a commission from Janet's mom, made from Ash and bird's-eye Maple, the other an end table for us with a tile top. In the plans are a tiled or mosaic coffee table to match, and some comfortable deck chairs. 
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, June 27, felt like the first day of summer! It was the second dry day in a row, and the weather broke that magical 20 C. Yesterday I sprayed Roundup(tm) on the weeds in the back, and hopefully we can proceed to sod in the next week or so. Unfortunately, the "hot" weather also encourages the mosquito population, but that's a tradeoff I am willing to make. There's always Muskol (also tm), and strong  cigars" border="0" /> to hold them back (thanks Tom).  
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I know it's  just water, and it really does not bother me much that it has been raining since  the snow melted -- However ... I wish it would dry up for just one week so that             a) the    farmers could get their crops in and thus not jeopardize my job and             b) I    could get into my backyard to kill to weeds and then sod the    yard.        After that  is done, it can rain all it wants, I don't  care.   
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       SIGH .   IITT  (that's programmer lingo for  It Is Time To ) change the template for this blog. This one is having some degree of difficulty. Add that to the growing list of things to do.  At home every minute of the next month is spoken for. We have the materials I need to insulate our garage. We have the funds to sod our back yard, we're just waiting for suitable weather. The van needs an oil change (its first), and of course, I need to win the lottery.
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     Ahhh... the last two days of my holidays, sleeping in, shorts and muscle-shirts (obviously named after someone else), and the hot noon sun. Back to khakis and collars, closed shoes and flourescent lighting. Ah well, at least I'll have access to  my  other computer and a laser printer again.     Saturday the afore-mentioned friend came over to help me with the garage ceiling. After he left I also drywalled one wall, and got the garage door opener working again. All that's left are the five sheets on the west wall. I'll leave the taping and painting project for another year I think. Unless I get ambitious later this summer or fall.     Today (Sunday) we drove to Winkler to my parents place where we deposited the kids for the next three days. The pain from my mid-back has travelled up my spine to my shoulders and now my head. Nothing a handful of drugs can't handle. And an Icepack. We had a nice game of Bocce on the lawn, surveyed plants dad has that we could add to our new backyard, bbq supper, then came home.  Mom and Dad just got back from Calgary so they had our IKEA order ready for us.  Always a good day when we get an IKEA order...   
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              Ok, so the daily log idea didn't work so well... today was the last official day of my summer holidays. Day Eight was last Wednesday.     Thursday was a hot day, and I spent it ... I forget.     Friday was a family day. The kids cast their vote, Janet and I cast ours. Although the results were a tie (zoo/tinkertown) we gave more weight to the kids votes because, well, we want them to like us ... As it turned out, Tinkertown was remarkably quiet and lines were short. The day was coolish, and they added a new coaster that actually has an excitment rating. It was so rough however that I believe that it started a chain of events that ended in some damage to my back. But that's another story.    Saturday and Sunday Normal weekend days. I believe I drove my bike to Home Depot on Saturday and bought a hand shower for Janet's parents. We went to their place for supper and installed the shower head. Last I heard, Dad didn't like it, but it was for Mom, who is quite sick. Her surgery was scheduled for Monday morning, so it was the last time I would see her.     Sunday the girls went over to visit one last time before surgery.   
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink    Oooo ouch ... another Sunburn day. I started the day by going to Home Depot to get replacement parts for our aging grill. I replaced the rusting tin burner with a  heavy cast iron version.   It's been two weeks since we installed the lawn, so it's time I mowed the lawn. I had ruined the last blade by mowing the weeds and rocks before we layed the sod, so I got a new blade at HD. The 6000 sq feet took two tanks of gas, and about an hour in the hot sun. The new grass was so long the task more closely resembled haying, leaving a blanket of clippings behind. SO I spent another hour  or so raking the clippings together into piles. I had to sit under the sprinkler and drink litres of water to recover.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     Monday Day Six: Finished the insulation work in the garage, next up is vapor barrier. Went to Blockbuster later to get a movie. Rented The Last Samurai, bought the finales of LOTR and The Matrix for much less than what I was going to pay at CDPlus. Also picked up Tim Burton's latest, Big Fish. Tuesday Day Seven: Lazy day. Took the girls to Starbucks while Janet went shopping with [one of] her sister[s]. While at the mall I looked in London Drugs at computer equipment: personal HP laser printer $299, LaCie external DVD-RW drive $279, iMac 20" $2999. I need the DVD drive cuz without it I cannot install Garage Band, which I desperately want to try out.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I suspected, I have fallen behind in the holiday journalling. The reason, I'm sure, is because I've been working in the garage late into the evening, and then going straight to bed after a quick shower. No time or energy for playing on the computer. So here is the play-by-play: Wednesday:  Worked on the garage, Janet felt that she needed more summer clothes, so we made a family trip to Old Navy. That little trip cost us $90. Thursday: Watched the back-yard neighbors lot get their final grade. Guarded the lawn to keep those workers from walking all over our new mushy lawn. Worked on garage. Friday: Major thunderstorm overnight. No need to water the lawn today. Worked on the garage. Saturday/Sunday: I have finished with the garage strapping and I'm ready to move on to insulating the second half of the garage ceiling. After that I can start on the drywall. Saturday we went to The Forks. Of all the times to forget my camera at home ... The Forks was a bee-hive of activity. There was a wedding in the ampitheatre, a native dance in full costume about a hundred feet away from the wedding, The Manitoba Fish Festival where Becky forgot to take her artwork home with her, The  display railcars which have been converted into retail space, most notably the Sugar Mountain Candy Store... Later on our deck we had an ad-hoc birthday bar-b-q for Leanne's-boyfriend-Vince's 40th birthday. ***newsflash ... The number of the day is ... 19! /newsflash*** Don't ask ...  On Sunday went to Tims Hortons for the first time this week. Mom and Dad took us all out for Dinner to Tony Roma's for dinner and aforementioned 40th birthday. Then back to our deck for dessert and coffee.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I stayed in all day, watered the lawn, and "concentrated" on cleaning up the computer area in the basement. That turned into cleaning up my hard drive, AND a friends ten-year-old computer that is at our place for service.  In the end, their computer is ready to go back, my desk looks OK, and I came to the unfortunate realization that I would not be able to host my photo albums from my computer any longer because I have just simply run out of disc space.  I have so little drive space left on my 40 GB HD that I cannot even BURN CD's at the moment. I am now rendering raw movie files into MPEG4 movies so I can delete the disc-space-wasting source. So far I have freed up more than five gigabytes.
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was the first day of my first three-weeks-in-a-row vacation. I've been entitled to three weeks for 10 years but I have never taken them all in a row. To prove to myself, when its all over, that I didn't just add to my mosquito bite collection, I am going to journal each day here. So, first, the weekend: Saturday: -- Rained, so we didn't have to water the lawn.  -- Had to get the girls out of the house because Janet worked nights, so I rolled the lawn one more time,and returned the lawn roller to Home Depot.  -- Went to the mall and got a haircut at Aura, then some more summer clothes at American Eagle, who had given up on summer and was clearing a bunch of stuff out at 80%off. Then Starbucks for my Venti Darkroast with shot of toffee-nut, Disney store for the kids, London Drugs new store to drool over the Mac section (and pick up Panther/iLife) etc.    --  Installed Panther, amazed at 'new' features (I upgraded from OS  X.0.5). Sunday: -- Slept in  -- Took the girls for a drive to Transcona, where I photographed the future Habitat for Humanity eight-home site for the church's web page (they're sponsoring one of the homes and are building in August)  -- Had supper at Applebee's with Tom and Carol. I had double order hot wings and a huge plate of nachos... Appetizers 1/2 price!  Today, first official vacation day: Never left the house. Didn't shower. Watered the lawn all day. Downloaded games for the Mac. Made supper ... Mmmm ... sweet & sour farmer sausage on Mashed potatoes ... Watched ... Uncle Buck.  
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CANADA DAY! ... was 2 days ago. And it was the most exhausting Canada Day in my short history. You see, it started at 7:30 AM when I realized that if I didn't get up NOW, I would never get the topsoil in our backyard packed down in time for the delivery of our back LAWN! Sure enough, the moment I got out of the shower, I got the phone call that the sod was going to arrive within 1/2 hour. I quickly ran out and started rolling the soil with the water roller, and within 1/2 hour the sod was here.  I had them drop the sod right on the yard, spaced so we had to do as little carrying as possible to lay out the sod.      Just as I was finishing up with the levelling, help started to arrive. By lunch time we were 2/3 done, and by 3 PM we were totally finished. I was amazed by two things: 1) How fast we were able to completely sod 6200 square feet, and 2) how totally useless my sunscreen was. Today I returned the roller, and all we have to do now is water, water, water. We totally love our new insta-lawn.
    
</post>


</Blog>