<Blog>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Cafe La Florida at Place du Capitole in Toulouse 
    
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Early morning in our street. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Driving past the local market. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Earling morning driving to work. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    A cafe at Place Saint George in Toulouse. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    A small castle in Mont Beron north of Toulouse. If it wasn't a hospital for mentally ill and we had won in Lotto, we'd buy it! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The church of Mont Beron north of Toulouse. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Market at Place du Capitole. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Place du Capitole in the rain. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Ready for the ten kilometers of Blagnac. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The minitel still works! 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Karine just accepted my proposal for marriage! Champagne in a cupid's capsule in the London Eye. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Picture from Toulouse plage Saturday night. It's a great place, but sadly it closes already at one o'clock. Now that the neighbours have started to complain about the noice they are playing music at a very low volume which is a bit sad. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Cafe de la Concorde, our local cafe. It is one of the oldest cafes in Toulouse. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    I am neither embarrassed nor tired, but simply relaxing after having walked around Toulouse an entire day. When you have visitors you get an effective work out by walking around the entire town and explaining some of the history of the town. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    A view of La Garonne which runs through Toulouse. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The salle des illustres in Capitole. Do not miss this place if you visit Toulouse. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Original building. From a walk around Toulouse. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    It's great to walk around Toulouse and enjoy the incredibly charming old houses. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Last beer on the way home from a night out in town. A nice picture even though my facial expression is a bit weird. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    French erotic novel. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    It looks like Lance Armstrong is going to win the Tour de France once again. Here's a photo I took of Lance last year when the tour passed Toulouse. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    No, this picture is not from some sort of morbid sex shop, but from a shop for hairdressers. I wonder how people react when someone walks out of the shop with one of these heads under the arm! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    On our way home from the 14th of July fireworks, we passed Place du Capitole where there was a concert. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    It was crowded at the Garonne tonight. People gathered to see the 14th of July fireworks. The show was beautiful. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Some lunatic has put a red substance in our fountain and sprayed the text "prison kills" on it. I have no freakin idea what good that serves and the person doesn't even have a clear message. Put that person in jail and then it'll be his/hers problem whether or not prison kills. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Walking through Camden after visiting the lock market. Though very crowded, Camden remains a place I visit every single time I'm in London. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    A view of London from the London Eye 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Now this is something you don't really get to do in Denmark. Hanging out by a pool at night is great and the fact that it can be open about half of the year is just so darn sweet. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Ok I know that it's a bit unclear,but it's a picture of a message board at a French bus stop. The nice bus people have indicated how the customers can get in contact with the company and one of the contact options is mail. Great, but what the heck is up with the lack of an email address? They simply write www.semvat.com, which either means that they have no idea what the difference between email and websites is or that they want to hide the email address on their website to avoid getting too much customer feedback.  
    
    
</post>



</Blog>