<Blog>



<date>15,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      hello 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      It was February 14th if I remember correctly. The world around me was completely and utterly gray. I remember waking up in my small apartment and checking myself in the mirror. I was whiter than usual. This wasn’t of much notice yet. I cupped my hands to catch the water. As I was bringing it to my face I noticed a red line across my wrist. Again I put it aside for that today I was going to meet her. I splashed my face with the clear water. Again and again I did it. I looked up into the mirror and to my horror the clear water that was previously in my hands was now blood red and all over my face. I quickly dried my face and ran out of the room. I hurriedly put on my black coat and hat and left the apartment. Outside my door was a small envelope. I opened it to find printed on the piece of stationary the word “boo”. This was obviously a prank from Mr. and Mrs. Poe’s son. I put it in my pocket and went downstairs and out the door. Outside the world was an eerie gray hue. I remember seeing a family walking. The man was holding the book time machine and a travel guide. He tilted his hat at me and courteously I did the same. I crossed the street to begin my way through the park when a car came hurtling at me. It’s headlights: red. I jumped out of the way in time. I lay there on the cold ground when a man leaned over me. “Are you ok?” he asked.  “Yes, yes I’m fine” I replied. He outstretched his hand offering a hoist up. Only there was no hand only the skeletal remains of one. I jumped up without his help and began to run through the park. I remember a little group of small girls all dressed in black singing “ring around the rosy”. I looked away then looked back to see a skeleton with a scythe in the middle of the ring. I ran faster still. My heart was pounding. I came to a playground and stopped for a rest for I saw no one there to harm me. I sat down on the bench to look upon my previous encounters and determine if they were real.  “Hello” a sweet voice behind me said. I turned around to see another black clad girl. She held up her hand and in it was a wallet. I checked my back pocket realizing it was my own she was holding. I asked her to give it back but in response she turned and ran. Our chase brought us to the other end of the park and across the street. She turned into an alleyway. I entered it to. I saw her at the end holding open a door laughing. I ran to her but she went through the door. I stopped at it considering the consequences. (Obviously not enough). When I entered I found a long white hall. I walked to the end of it finding a door. I walked through into a room with metal walls. In the middle was a desk with a light on it, some paper, and there sat my wallet alongside a pen. I picked it up and turned to exit the room only to find there was no door at all. No exit. So here I sit at the desk, writing about my mornings events, waiting. There is a dripping noise coming from something unseen. So far I have counted about 630 drips. I think the light will go out soon. And there it goes.   I’m alone now.   Good bye Lenore.   Good bye.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      There is a knock at the door. A man goes to the door. He opens it but is pushed aside by the man coming in. He is rushing in and out of each room. He finally stops in the living room and looks up at the skylight.  2nd man: (breathing heavily) he's following me 1st man: (after closing the door) who? Who's following you? 2: I think I lost him! 1: calm down. come into the kitchen. i'll get you something to drink. He does but only after tuning off all the lights. The first man lights a candle 2: you got to help me! He's following me! 1:who?! 2: he dosn't have a fucking name! 1: then what does he look like? 2: he has no face! no nothing! 1: then how do you know you're being followed? 2: a man i know died 1: so 1: you're paranoid 2: he died in a red car 1: lots of people die in red cars 2: wherever i go there is something new. It's always red. I was in a bar and there were no candles but when i came abck from the bathroom there was at my spot. 1: they put onr there while you were gone. I bet there was plenty everywhere else in the bar. Did you even look? 2: i had the only one. 2: i went to work and there was a red baloon tied to my chair. No special occasion. I went home my door frame was- 1: red 2:yes 2: and.. he stops The first man reaches to pat the other man on his back.: You alright He pulls his hand back to the light. It is covered with blood. He stands up knocking his chair over. He looks around. The candle goes out.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Dead and wounded create a carpet of bodies. Fire arms still warm from combat,bayonetes lost in the havoc. The area is quiet as if at rest from the previous roar. The screams, the shouts, the booming of the cannons. It's as if the fog absorbed the echoes into itself. Then a soft sweet note can be heard from somewhere. It sounds like a bird. But it is not. There is a boy wearing tattered clothes sitting on a stump playing the flute. He is the only movement in the feild. Solitary in his life. But there is a snair now. Accross the way from him on a tree leans another boy. He is playing a snair. The quick rattatat tat. Two now. Slowly a flag is raised out of the mass of bodies. Another boy stands up supporting himself with the flag. It is like a spark ignited in the soldiers soul. All the men still alive rise. The wounded ignore their wounds. A grimace is on each mans face as if to say " we will win even if it brings upon my death".  Accross the feild opposite to them the army of red turns around. The men rose to fight a battle, a war, a revoultion.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Never keep favorites. Always remember that there is something better. Keep the mind open.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The mind is an endless passageway of doors and behind every door is the chance to learn. The more doors you open the more you can know.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Money is what our country is run on. It runs America and most Americans. You are forced to use it on everything even the things you cannot survive without, food, water, and a bed. It entertains us, buys us toys, music, movies, books, anything and everything. It corrupts the mind into thinking it can get everything, even true happiness. But happiness is only found when you let go.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Death is only the beggining
     
    
</post>

<date>30,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      to name a few writings of note
     
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The Declaration of Independence: A Transcription   --------------------------------------------------------------------------------  IN CONGRESS, July 4, 1776.  The unanimous Declaration of the thirteen united States of America,  When in the Course of human events, it becomes necessary for one people to dissolve the political bands which have connected them with another, and to assume among the powers of the earth, the separate and equal station to which the Laws of Nature and of Nature's God entitle them, a decent respect to the opinions of mankind requires that they should declare the causes which impel them to the separation.  We hold these truths to be self-evident, that all men are created equal, that they are endowed by their Creator with certain unalienable Rights, that among these are Life, Liberty and the pursuit of Happiness.--That to secure these rights, Governments are instituted among Men, deriving their just powers from the consent of the governed, --That whenever any Form of Government becomes destructive of these ends, it is the Right of the People to alter or to abolish it, and to institute new Government, laying its foundation on such principles and organizing its powers in such form, as to them shall seem most likely to effect their Safety and Happiness. Prudence, indeed, will dictate that Governments long established should not be changed for light and transient causes; and accordingly all experience hath shewn, that mankind are more disposed to suffer, while evils are sufferable, than to right themselves by abolishing the forms to which they are accustomed. But when a long train of abuses and usurpations, pursuing invariably the same Object evinces a design to reduce them under absolute Despotism, it is their right, it is their duty, to throw off such Government, and to provide new Guards for their future security.--Such has been the patient sufferance of these Colonies; and such is now the necessity which constrains them to alter their former Systems of Government. The history of the present King of Great Britain is a history of repeated injuries and usurpations, all having in direct object the establishment of an absolute Tyranny over these States. To prove this, let Facts be submitted to a candid world.  He has refused his Assent to Laws, the most wholesome and necessary for the public good. He has forbidden his Governors to pass Laws of immediate and pressing importance, unless suspended in their operation till his Assent should be obtained; and when so suspended, he has utterly neglected to attend to them. He has refused to pass other Laws for the accommodation of large districts of people, unless those people would relinquish the right of Representation in the Legislature, a right inestimable to them and formidable to tyrants only.  He has called together legislative bodies at places unusual, uncomfortable, and distant from the depository of their public Records, for the sole purpose of fatiguing them into compliance with his measures.  He has dissolved Representative Houses repeatedly, for opposing with manly firmness his invasions on the rights of the people. He has refused for a long time, after such dissolutions, to cause others to be elected; whereby the Legislative powers, incapable of Annihilation, have returned to the People at large for their exercise; the State remaining in the mean time exposed to all the dangers of invasion from without, and convulsions within. He has endeavoured to prevent the population of these States; for that purpose obstructing the Laws for Naturalization of Foreigners; refusing to pass others to encourage their migrations hither, and raising the conditions of new Appropriations of Lands. He has obstructed the Administration of Justice, by refusing his Assent to Laws for establishing Judiciary powers. He has made Judges dependent on his Will alone, for the tenure of their offices, and the amount and payment of their salaries. He has erected a multitude of New Offices, and sent hither swarms of Officers to harrass our people, and eat out their substance. He has kept among us, in times of peace, Standing Armies without the Consent of our legislatures. He has affected to render the Military independent of and superior to the Civil power. He has combined with others to subject us to a jurisdiction foreign to our constitution, and unacknowledged by our laws; giving his Assent to their Acts of pretended Legislation: For Quartering large bodies of armed troops among us: For protecting them, by a mock Trial, from punishment for any Murders which they should commit on the Inhabitants of these States: For cutting off our Trade with all parts of the world: For imposing Taxes on us without our Consent:  For depriving us in many cases, of the benefits of Trial by Jury: For transporting us beyond Seas to be tried for pretended offences For abolishing the free System of English Laws in a neighbouring Province, establishing therein an Arbitrary government, and enlarging its Boundaries so as to render it at once an example and fit instrument for introducing the same absolute rule into these Colonies: For taking away our Charters, abolishing our most valuable Laws, and altering fundamentally the Forms of our Governments: For suspending our own Legislatures, and declaring themselves invested with power to legislate for us in all cases whatsoever. He has abdicated Government here, by declaring us out of his Protection and waging War against us. He has plundered our seas, ravaged our Coasts, burnt our towns, and destroyed the lives of our people.  He is at this time transporting large Armies of foreign Mercenaries to compleat the works of death, desolation and tyranny, already begun with circumstances of Cruelty & perfidy scarcely paralleled in the most barbarous ages, and totally unworthy the Head of a civilized nation. He has constrained our fellow Citizens taken Captive on the high Seas to bear Arms against their Country, to become the executioners of their friends and Brethren, or to fall themselves by their Hands.  He has excited domestic insurrections amongst us, and has endeavoured to bring on the inhabitants of our frontiers, the merciless Indian Savages, whose known rule of warfare, is an undistinguished destruction of all ages, sexes and conditions.  In every stage of these Oppressions We have Petitioned for Redress in the most humble terms: Our repeated Petitions have been answered only by repeated injury. A Prince whose character is thus marked by every act which may define a Tyrant, is unfit to be the ruler of a free people.  Nor have We been wanting in attentions to our Brittish brethren. We have warned them from time to time of attempts by their legislature to extend an unwarrantable jurisdiction over us. We have reminded them of the circumstances of our emigration and settlement here. We have appealed to their native justice and magnanimity, and we have conjured them by the ties of our common kindred to disavow these usurpations, which, would inevitably interrupt our connections and correspondence. They too have been deaf to the voice of justice and of consanguinity. We must, therefore, acquiesce in the necessity, which denounces our Separation, and hold them, as we hold the rest of mankind, Enemies in War, in Peace Friends.  We, therefore, the Representatives of the united States of America, in General Congress, Assembled, appealing to the Supreme Judge of the world for the rectitude of our intentions, do, in the Name, and by Authority of the good People of these Colonies, solemnly publish and declare, That these United Colonies are, and of Right ought to be Free and Independent States; that they are Absolved from all Allegiance to the British Crown, and that all political connection between them and the State of Great Britain, is and ought to be totally dissolved; and that as Free and Independent States, they have full Power to levy War, conclude Peace, contract Alliances, establish Commerce, and to do all other Acts and Things which Independent States may of right do. And for the support of this Declaration, with a firm reliance on the protection of divine Providence, we mutually pledge to each other our Lives, our Fortunes and our sacred Honor.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      THE LOTTERY BY SHIRLEY JACKSON The morning of June 27th was clear and sunny, with the fresh warmth of a full-summer day; the flowers were blossoming profusely and the grass was richly green. The people of the village began to gather in the square, between the post office and the bank, around ten o'clock; in some towns there were so many people that the lottery took two days and had to be started on June 2th. but in this village, where there were only about three hundred people, the whole lottery took less than two hours, so it could begin at ten o'clock in the morning and still be through in time to allow the villagers to get home for noon dinner.   The children assembled first, of course. School was recently over for the summer, and the feeling of liberty sat uneasily on most of them; they tended to gather together quietly for a while before they broke into boisterous play. and their talk was still of the classroom and the teacher, of books and reprimands. Bobby Martin had already stuffed his pockets full of stones, and the other boys soon followed his example, selecting the smoothest and roundest stones; Bobby and Harry Jones and Dickie Delacroix-- the villagers pronounced this name "Dellacroy"--eventually made a great pile of stones in one corner of the square and guarded it against the raids of the other boys. The girls stood aside, talking among themselves, looking over their shoulders at rolled in the dust or clung to the hands of their older brothers or sisters.   Soon the men began to gather. surveying their own children, speaking of planting and rain, tractors and taxes. They stood together, away from the pile of stones in the corner, and their jokes were quiet and they smiled rather than laughed. The women, wearing faded house dresses and sweaters, came shortly after their menfolk. They greeted one another and exchanged bits of gossip as they went to join their husbands. Soon the women, standing by their husbands, began to call to their children, and the children came reluctantly, having to be called four or five times. Bobby Martin ducked under his mother's grasping hand and ran, laughing, back to the pile of stones. His father spoke up sharply, and Bobby came quickly and took his place between his father and his oldest brother.   The lottery was conducted--as were the square dances, the teen club, the Halloween program--by Mr. Summers. who had time and energy to devote to civic activities. He was a round-faced, jovial man and he ran the coal business, and people were sorry for him. because he had no children and his wife was a scold. When he arrived in the square, carrying the black wooden box, there was a murmur of conversation among the villagers, and he waved and called. "Little late today, folks." The postmaster, Mr. Graves, followed him, carrying a three- legged stool, and the stool was put in the center of the square and Mr. Summers set the black box down on it. The villagers kept their distance, leaving a space between themselves and the stool. and when Mr. Summers said, "Some of you fellows want to give me a hand?" there was a hesitation before two men. Mr. Martin and his oldest son, Baxter. came forward to hold the box steady on the stool while Mr. Summers stirred up the papers inside it.   The original paraphernalia for the lottery had been lost long ago, and the black box now resting on the stool had been put into use even before Old Man Warner, the oldest man in town, was born. Mr. Summers spoke frequently to the villagers about making a new box, but no one liked to upset even as much tradition as was represented by the black box. There was a story that the present box had been made with some pieces of the box that had preceded it, the one that had been constructed when the first people settled down to make a village here. Every year, after the lottery, Mr. Summers began talking again about a new box, but every year the subject was allowed to fade off without anything's being done. The black box grew shabbier each year: by now it was no longer completely black but splintered badly along one side to show the original wood color, and in some places faded or stained.   Mr. Martin and his oldest son, Baxter, held the black box securely on the stool until Mr. Summers had stirred the papers thoroughly with his hand. Because so much of the ritual had been forgotten or discarded, Mr. Summers had been successful in having slips of paper substituted for the chips of wood that had been used for generations. Chips of wood, Mr. Summers had argued. had been all very well when the village was tiny, but now that the population was more than three hundred and likely to keep on growing, it was necessary to use something that would fit more easily into he black box. The night before the lottery, Mr. Summers and Mr. Graves made up the slips of paper and put them in the box, and it was then taken to the safe of Mr. Summers' coal company and locked up until Mr. Summers was ready to take it to the square next morning. The rest of the year, the box was put way, sometimes one place, sometimes another; it had spent one year in Mr. Graves's barn and another year underfoot in the post office. and sometimes it was set on a shelf in the Martin grocery and left there.   There was a great deal of fussing to be done before Mr. Summers declared the lottery open. There were the lists to make up--of heads of families. heads of households in each family. members of each household in each family. There was the proper swearing-in of Mr. Summers by the postmaster, as the official of the lottery; at one time, some people remembered, there had been a recital of some sort, performed by the official of the lottery, a perfunctory. tuneless chant that had been rattled off duly each year; some people believed that the official of the lottery used to stand just so when he said or sang it, others believed that he was supposed to walk among the people, but years and years ago this p3rt of the ritual had been allowed to lapse. There had been, also, a ritual salute, which the official of the lottery had had to use in addressing each person who came up to draw from the box, but this also had changed with time, until now it was felt necessary only for the official to speak to each person approaching. Mr. Summers was very good at all this; in his clean white shirt and blue jeans. with one hand resting carelessly on the black box. he seemed very proper and important as he talked interminably to Mr. Graves and the Martins.   Just as Mr. Summers finally left off talking and turned to the assembled villagers, Mrs. Hutchinson came hurriedly along the path to the square, her sweater thrown over her shoulders, and slid into place in the back of the crowd. "Clean forgot what day it was," she said to Mrs. Delacroix, who stood next to her, and they both laughed softly. "Thought my old man was out back stacking wood," Mrs. Hutchinson went on. "and then I looked out the window and the kids was gone, and then I remembered it was the twenty-seventh and came a-running." She dried her hands on her apron, and Mrs. Delacroix said, "You're in time, though. They're still talking away up there."   Mrs. Hutchinson craned her neck to see through the crowd and found her husband and children standing near the front. She tapped Mrs. Delacroix on the arm as a farewell and began to make her way through the crowd. The people separated good-humoredly to let her through: two or three people said. in voices just loud enough to be heard across the crowd, "Here comes your, Missus, Hutchinson," and "Bill, she made it after all." Mrs. Hutchinson reached her husband, and Mr. Summers, who had been waiting, said cheerfully. "Thought we were going to have to get on without you, Tessie." Mrs. Hutchinson said. grinning, "Wouldn't have me leave m'dishes in the sink, now, would you. Joe?," and soft laughter ran through the crowd as the people stirred back into position after Mrs. Hutchinson's arrival.   "Well, now." Mr. Summers said soberly, "guess we better get started, get this over with, so's we can go back to work. Anybody ain't here?"   "Dunbar." several people said. "Dunbar. Dunbar."   Mr. Summers consulted his list. "Clyde Dunbar." he said. "That's right. He's broke his leg, hasn't he? Who's drawing for him?"   "Me. I guess," a woman said. and Mr. Summers turned to look at her. "Wife draws for her husband." Mr. Summers said. "Don't you have a grown boy to do it for you, Janey?" Although Mr. Summers and everyone else in the village knew the answer perfectly well, it was the business of the official of the lottery to ask such questions formally. Mr. Summers waited with an expression of polite interest while Mrs. Dunbar answered.   "Horace's not but sixteen vet." Mrs. Dunbar said regretfully. "Guess I gotta fill in for the old man this year."   "Right." Sr. Summers said. He made a note on the list he was holding. Then he asked, "Watson boy drawing this year?"   A tall boy in the crowd raised his hand. "Here," he said. "I m drawing for my mother and me." He blinked his eyes nervously and ducked his head as several voices in the crowd said thin#s like "Good fellow, lack." and "Glad to see your mother's got a man to do it."   "Well," Mr. Summers said, "guess that's everyone. Old Man Warner make it?"   "Here," a voice said. and Mr. Summers nodded.   A sudden hush fell on the crowd as Mr. Summers cleared his throat and looked at the list. "All ready?" he called. "Now, I'll read the names--heads of families first--and the men come up and take a paper out of the box. Keep the paper folded in your hand without looking at it until everyone has had a turn. Everything clear?"   The people had done it so many times that they only half listened to the directions: most of them were quiet. wetting their lips. not looking around. Then Mr. Summers raised one hand high and said, "Adams." A man disengaged himself from the crowd and came forward. "Hi. Steve." Mr. Summers said. and Mr. Adams said. "Hi. Joe." They grinned at one another humorlessly and nervously. Then Mr. Adams reached into the black box and took out a folded paper. He held it firmly by one corner as he turned and went hastily back to his place in the crowd. where he stood a little apart from his family. not looking down at his hand.   "Allen." Mr. Summers said. "Anderson.... Bentham."   "Seems like there's no time at all between lotteries any more." Mrs. Delacroix said to Mrs. Graves in the back row.   "Seems like we got through with the last one only last week."   "Time sure goes fast.-- Mrs. Graves said.   "Clark.... Delacroix"   "There goes my old man." Mrs. Delacroix said. She held her breath while her husband went forward.   "Dunbar," Mr. Summers said, and Mrs. Dunbar went steadily to the box while one of the women said. "Go on. Janey," and another said, "There she goes."   "We're next." Mrs. Graves said. She watched while Mr. Graves came around from the side of the box, greeted Mr. Summers gravely and selected a slip of paper from the box. By now, all through the crowd there were men holding the small folded papers in their large hand. turning them over and over nervously Mrs. Dunbar and her two sons stood together, Mrs. Dunbar holding the slip of paper.   "Harburt.... Hutchinson."   "Get up there, Bill," Mrs. Hutchinson said. and the people near her laughed.   "Jones."   "They do say," Mr. Adams said to Old Man Warner, who stood next to him, "that over in the north village they're talking of giving up the lottery."   Old Man Warner snorted. "Pack of crazy fools," he said. "Listening to the young folks, nothing's good enough for them. Next thing you know, they'll be wanting to go back to living in caves, nobody work any more, live hat way for a while. Used to be a saying about 'Lottery in June, corn be heavy soon.' First thing you know, we'd all be eating stewed chickweed and acorns. There's always been a lottery," he added petulantly. "Bad enough to see young Joe Summers up there joking with everybody."   "Some places have already quit lotteries." Mrs. Adams said.   "Nothing but trouble in that," Old Man Warner said stoutly. "Pack of young fools."   "Martin." And Bobby Martin watched his father go forward. "Overdyke.... Percy."   "I wish they'd hurry," Mrs. Dunbar said to her older son. "I wish they'd hurry."   "They're almost through," her son said.   "You get ready to run tell Dad," Mrs. Dunbar said.   Mr. Summers called his own name and then stepped forward precisely and selected a slip from the box. Then he called, "Warner."   "Seventy-seventh year I been in the lottery," Old Man Warner said as he went through the crowd. "Seventy-seventh time."   "Watson" The tall boy came awkwardly through the crowd. Someone said, "Don't be nervous, Jack," and Mr. Summers said, "Take your time, son."   "Zanini."   After that, there was a long pause, a breathless pause, until Mr. Summers. holding his slip of paper in the air, said, "All right, fellows." For a minute, no one moved, and then all the slips of paper were opened. Suddenly, all the women began to speak at once, saving. "Who is it?," "Who's got it?," "Is it the Dunbars?," "Is it the Watsons?" Then the voices began to say, "It's Hutchinson. It's Bill," "Bill Hutchinson's got it."   "Go tell your father," Mrs. Dunbar said to her older son.   People began to look around to see the Hutchinsons. Bill Hutchinson was standing quiet, staring down at the paper in his hand. Suddenly. Tessie Hutchinson shouted to Mr. Summers. "You didn't give him time enough to take any paper he wanted. I saw you. It wasn't fair!"   "Be a good sport, Tessie." Mrs. Delacroix called, and Mrs. Graves said, "All of us took the same chance."   "Shut up, Tessie," Bill Hutchinson said.   "Well, everyone," Mr. Summers said, "that was done pretty fast, and now we've got to be hurrying a little more to get done in time." He consulted his next list. "Bill," he said, "you draw for the Hutchinson family. You got any other households in the Hutchinsons?"   "There's Don and Eva," Mrs. Hutchinson yelled. "Make them take their chance!"   "Daughters draw with their husbands' families, Tessie," Mr. Summers said gently. "You know that as well as anyone else."   "It wasn't fair," Tessie said.   "I guess not, Joe." Bill Hutchinson said regretfully. "My daughter draws with her husband's family; that's only fair. And I've got no other family except the kids."   "Then, as far as drawing for families is concerned, it's you," Mr. Summers said in explanation, "and as far as drawing for households is concerned, that's you, too. Right?"   "Right," Bill Hutchinson said.   "How many kids, Bill?" Mr. Summers asked formally.   "Three," Bill Hutchinson said.   "There's Bill, Jr., and Nancy, and little Dave. And Tessie and me."   "All right, then," Mr. Summers said. "Harry, you got their tickets back?"   Mr. Graves nodded and held up the slips of paper. "Put them in the box, then," Mr. Summers directed. "Take Bill's and put it in."   "I think we ought to start over," Mrs. Hutchinson said, as quietly as she could. "I tell you it wasn't fair. You didn't give him time enough to choose. Everybody saw that."   Mr. Graves had selected the five slips and put them in the box. and he dropped all the papers but those onto the ground. where the breeze caught them and lifted them off.   "Listen, everybody," Mrs. Hutchinson was saying to the people around her.   "Ready, Bill?" Mr. Summers asked. and Bill Hutchinson, with one quick glance around at his wife and children. nodded.   "Remember," Mr. Summers said. "take the slips and keep them folded until each person has taken one. Harry, you help little Dave." Mr. Graves took the hand of the little boy, who came willingly with him up to the box. "Take a paper out of the box, Davy." Mr. Summers said. Davy put his hand into the box and laughed. "Take just one paper." Mr. Summers said. "Harry, you hold it for him." Mr. Graves took the child's hand and removed the folded paper from the tight fist and held it while little Dave stood next to him and looked up at him wonderingly.   "Nancy next," Mr. Summers said. Nancy was twelve, and her school friends breathed heavily as she went forward switching her skirt, and took a slip daintily from the box "Bill, Jr.," Mr. Summers said, and Billy, his face red and his feet overlarge, near knocked the box over as he got a paper out. "Tessie," Mr. Summers said. She hesitated for a minute, looking around defiantly. and then set her lips and went up to the box. She snatched a paper out and held it behind her.   "Bill," Mr. Summers said, and Bill Hutchinson reached into the box and felt around, bringing his hand out at last with the slip of paper in it.   The crowd was quiet. A girl whispered, "I hope it's not Nancy," and the sound of the whisper reached the edges of the crowd.  "It's not the way it used to be." Old Man Warner said clearly. "People ain't the way they used to be."   "All right," Mr. Summers said. "Open the papers. Harry, you open little Dave's."   Mr. Graves opened the slip of paper and there was a general sigh through the crowd as he held it up and everyone could see that it was blank. Nancy and Bill. Jr.. opened theirs at the same time. and both beamed and laughed. turning around to the crowd and holding their slips of paper above their heads.   "Tessie," Mr. Summers said. There was a pause, and then Mr. Summers looked at Bill Hutchinson, and Bill unfolded his paper and showed it. It was blank.   "It's Tessie," Mr. Summers said, and his voice was hushed. "Show us her paper. Bill."   Bill Hutchinson went over to his wife and forced the slip of paper out of her hand. It had a black spot on it, the black spot Mr. Summers had made the night before with the heavy pencil in the coal company office. Bill Hutchinson held it up, and there was a stir in the crowd.   "All right, folks." Mr. Summers said. "Let's finish quickly."   Although the villagers had forgotten the ritual and lost the original black box, they still remembered to use stones. The pile of stones the boys had made earlier was ready; there were stones on the ground with the blowing scraps of paper that had come out of the box Delacroix selected a stone so large she had to pick it up with both hands and turned to Mrs. Dunbar. "Come on," she said. "Hurry up."   Mr. Dunbar had small stones in both hands, and she said. gasping for breath. "I can't run at all. You'll have to go ahead and I'll catch up with you."   The children had stones already. And someone gave little Davy Hutchinson few pebbles.   Tessie Hutchinson was in the center of a cleared space by now, and she held her hands out desperately as the villagers moved in on her. "It isn't fair," she said. A stone hit her on the side of the head. Old Man Warner was saying, "Come on, come on, everyone." Steve Adams was in the front of the crowd of villagers, with Mrs. Graves beside him.   "It isn't fair, it isn't right," Mrs. Hutchinson screamed, and then they were upon her.   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      But fate it seems, brings good things.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      You never realise how much you love someone or something until it is wrenched from your grasp.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      What's next
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I remember the last time this happened I drew a whole bunch of screaming people in my "Black Book". I drew slightly off proportions but they all screamed. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      It's happening again.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I remember why I lived in my bubble for so long. Not telling anyone what I thought. Saying only the things needed to be said. I left it for but a short moment and I am faced with decisions and games I don't want to play or make. I want to return but first I have to play.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Eschers World/ Schitz's Realm the Letter   Dear God, This is just another cry for help from the another lost and cofused child in the vast world you have created. I have voices in my head. I have a strange eating disorder. I think I am going insane. At school everyone loves me. At home everyone loves me. But then something happened. Now I am a schitzophrenic. Normaly I don't believe in anything. But now it's everything and nothing at the same time. I've become confused in what i believe in. As i'm writing this a satanic bunny is pokeing me in the eye. Is there such thing as a satanic bunny? I hate leaving my room. It's become my own fortress. No one goes in other than myself and my dreams. My bunny is fake i think. More of a hallucination than anything. He came from my dreams. They've all come from my dreams. I think I need therapy. My mom can't afford. She thinks I'm fine. Ever since the dreams started I've adopted the name Schitz. Well if you could help me sometime that wou;d be great. Bye. -Schitz (aidan) P.S.) Tell dad I said hi  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Echer’s World:  Issue 1: Part 1  The Dungeon (Schitz’s realm)   We see a boy hunched over a desk at the end of the room. He’s atop a stool facing the wall a foot in front of him. The concrete floor is covered by a Persian rug. At the foot of the stool lays his backpack. To his right, there is a stereo blaring right Rob Zombie. On all the walls and the ceiling there are pipes. To his left, there are three filing cabinets. The surface he’s writing on is covered in pens. He’s taped up a little sign on the plaster wall in front of him that says, “Welcome to the Dungeon”. On the shelf above him are towers of toilet paper. In places all over the ceiling the plaster is peeling off revealing the wooden boards. The room or “dungeon” is lighted by fluorescents, giving an eerie bleached feeling. We get closer to him so he takes up the whole frame. His arms are working feverishly. We see his eyes formed into slits. We see rapid hand movements across a piece of paper. The point of a pen scribbling lines of black ink we can’t quite make out yet. We see the finished masterpiece. It is a bunny in a straight jacket with horns growing out of its head. We cut to the boy’s smiling face, he’s excited. He sets his pen down as if to do a few touch ups.   “Aidan,”   “Yes,” turning to look at the maker of the sound. Then looks back at the picture. When he turned he drew a line across the picture, ruining it.   “Fuck,” he said quietly.   “What?”   “Nothing Mom.”   “You look bored.”   “I am bored.”   “Why don’t you come upstairs and work at the desk?”   Imagination: Aidan sitting behind the behind the counter of the bookstore upstairs. A man walks up. He’s about 50. Aidan: Hello may I help you?   Man: um… I’m looking for a book.   Aidan: All right, do you know the author?   Man: um… I think there was an E in it.   Aidan: So no   Man: um… no   Aidan: Do you know… what color it is?   Man: um… white?   Aidan: white?   Man: um… well it had white in it.   Aidan: …   Aidan: Can I shove my shoe up your ass?   Man: um…   Back to reality:  Aidan: yeah I don’t think that would be the best idea.   Mom: ok, well just let me know when and if you want to.   Aidan: Are you immortal?   Mom: no   Beep-beep-beep-beep-beep-beep-beep Aidan cowers in the corner, biting his lower lip.   Aidan: (whisper) it’s not for you, you don’t have to speak. It’s not for you, you don’t have to speak.   Mom: (picking up the phone) Hello Dog Runner Books… uh huh… hold on   Mom: It’s for you.   Aidan: Aieeeeeeeee!   Mom holds out the phone. Aidan reluctantly grabs it.   Aidan: (whisper) hello?   Nick: It’s Nick!   Aidan: (hopefully) Have you called to rescue me?   Nick: no   Aidan: (icy) you suck   Nick: you’re already free schitz   Schitz: am not a schitzo!   Nick: are to   Schitz: good point   Nick:…   Schitz:…   Nick:… see you in an hour    Schitz: k     
     
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I leave them behind. I leave it all behind and go to the dark place where i first met you, before my parents died, before i learned what i am. I am dying. But i can't die. I'm not finished yet. You aren't finished with me yet. Shuffling out of sight. sucking of the stale air, and hisses. Gliding with an ancient grace. Eyes gleaming untouched by love, jow, or... sorrow. Breathe hot with the taste of fallen foes fallen foes. The stench of dead things. Surely the feircest survivor, the purest warrior. Glareing, hateing, claiming me... as your own.  -Batman from The Dark Knight Returns by Frank Miller
     
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I am but another tortured soul poked and prodded by the demons of life I wonder if they to feel pain in changing I hear my name repeated to me a thousand times over until i go insane I am but another tortured soul poked and prodded by the demons of life  I pretend to renounce the laws of social behavior but am forced back to the demonic reality of it all I feel their hot spears searing my flesh I touch the wound, now a scar I cry out from the guilt i have of my trail of broken hearts behind me I am but another tortured soul, poked and prodded by the demons of life  I understand it is all innevitable, but i still resist I say "nay nay, you must stop!" I dream they heed my cries but alas they have no ears to hear with I try so desperatly to put it all behind me I hope and dream it's end But alas I am but another tortured aoul poked and prodded by the demons of life  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      On the first day of this dreaded month. . . 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      In the street I see a man At his feet lay the dying one In his hands he holds a gun He lifts it and shoots the sun                                  -aj
     
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      there's no hidden message
     
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The day and its requiem  This is the day the world stood in fear This is the day he whispered in his ear This is the day of apocalyptic images This is the day of no scrimmages  And today I scream out this requiem Cause tomorrow I know I may die I take a moment to yell at them And only a second to cry  This is the day their people died The day our own woke up and cried The day I pressed pause  The day I threw away all their laws  And today I scream out this requiem Cause tomorrow I know I may die I take this moment to yell at them And only a second to cry  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The Gardner In the Rose Garden   says: i've revoked the idea of rebellion against the norm  Demortius says: what caused it?   The Gardner In the Rose Garden   says: the idea that we all try to be unique and in doing that we are not Demortius says: So your going back to rebellion? or was revoked the wrong word?   The Gardner In the Rose Garden   says: i don't want to rebel   The Gardner In the Rose Garden   says: i'm tired of trying
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder if anyone is going to find the hidden message? (this time there really is one)
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Never did I see a heart so fair, so sweet Or my own in such defeat Requiem I sing to her distant castle Another day goes by and still I think of you Her cheeks rose red in their hue
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
                                                                           11                                                 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I am really bored and writing saves me from this new enemy. Don't ask about the thing I just posted. I know it's stupid but I'm tired and bored. So bug off. It's my blog and besides you were the one who wanted to read this thing.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      A Love   I can still hear her sound  I can still feel her body in it's round Her face replaces all around me It is like beatiful star aloft the sea An angel she has fallen Shall I let return? A decision I do face I do not deserve such beauty in my precence But alas the human nature plagues my heart A sin rooted deep in the soul The greed I should send her back and be free of our ugly lives But again a plague is upon us both One of good yet evil A love -God   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Escher's World/ Schitz's Realm/ Piccasso's Dreamland  Eightball Years: my internal dialogues (diary of schitz)  I sit here in a room, dimly lit. Not my own room. But a room all the same. I sit there hunched over my blank canvas. I have the lyrics to the bridge of "Boom" scrawled accross my wrist. Two speakers are clamped to my ears blaring the sweet melodies of the "Red Hot Chili Peppers". Track 10, "Throw Away Your Television". God I wish I could. The track ends, I simply start it over. Through the veins of my body, flow the horemones which have taken over my body. I hate them. The only reason why I hate is cause of them. They bring back the emotions I so long ago suppressed. They bring new ones as well.   I hate patterns. I used to be fascinated by their sheer briliance. But now...They just remind me how stupid it all is. Fake social situations. Fake love. Fake hate. All in the name of cool. 10 years from now I'm going to look back and say to my self in my raspy voice "What the hell?!"   Tonight I have written and re-written countless stories in my head. I really do think I'm going crazy. It's 2:06  in the morning and I'm writing about fake social situations. I'm so proud of myself.    Wow. I wrote alot. anyways. I want to tell my story. Ah crap my moms coming. I will tell you all some other time. I will tell you how my paradise was lost. No. To cliche. Ah well I'll think of a better title someother time. Good bye. Good night. Good morning.   0..0  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      creator of everything 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ^ Escher
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      0..0
     
    
</post>

<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The last man in the world sits in a room There is a knock at the door
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Ava Adore  It's you that I adore  You'll always be my whore  You'll be the mother to my child  And a child to my heart  We must never be apart  We must never be apart   Lovely girl you're the beauty in my wrold  Without you there aren't reasons left to find   And I'll pull your crooked teeth  You'll be perfect just like me  You'll be a lover in my bed  And a gun to my head  We must never be apart  We must never be apart   In you I see dirty  In you I count stars  In you I feel so pretty  In you I taste god  In you I feel so hungry  In you I crash cars  We must never be apart   Drinking mercury  To the mystery of all that you should ever seek to find  Lovely girl you're the murder in my wrold  Dressing coffins for the souls I've left behind  In time  We must never be apart   And you'll always be my whore  Cause you're the one that i adore  And I'll pull your crooked teeth  You'll be perfect just like me  In you I feel so dirty in you I crash cars  In you I feel so pretty in you I taste god  We must never be apart   -smashing pumpkins
     
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't I just sound like the happiest person on the planet?
     
    
</post>

<date>29,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i know it sucks but shut up
     
    
</post>

<date>29,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      she loved you she always did if only you knew it not like your a kid years we shared were few nevermind nevermind the dead he found it hard to find it's true, it's what he said he's now one of them as you may find and now you love her a different one you want to kiss her and when it's called and done the battle still rages between her and her and sanction you find in him the one    
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i call him pooky
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      isn't he so cute you just want to wrap your arms around him and squeeze him until his eyes pop out of their sockets and hang over your shouler like pig tails and his intestines drop out of him and soak your legs in blood and other bodily fluids?
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      0..0
     
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      LuciferSamekh (10:01:18 PM): and  Felicia stands triumphantly, her blade still plunged into Aidan's side DemortiusXV (10:01:23 PM): now your even deader LuciferSamekh (10:01:30 PM): her arms covered in still hot blood LuciferSamekh (10:02:02 PM): she smiles devishly and drives her glaive deeper into his cold flesh and walks away LuciferSamekh (10:02:05 PM): so THERE! DemortiusXV (10:02:15 PM): he still holding the cold steel weapon of seeminly infinate power in his limp hand DemortiusXV (10:02:26 PM): a clip waisted on his enemy DemortiusXV (10:02:42 PM): her eyes turned white DemortiusXV (10:03:03 PM): the red from teh blood trickling like a leak from a sink down her forehead LuciferSamekh (10:03:09 PM): her eyes turn white as her eyes roll back into her head, but suddenly,  LuciferSamekh (10:03:20 PM): a loud harsh sound of an automatic rings in the air DemortiusXV (10:03:21 PM): he to gains life DemortiusXV (10:03:35 PM): posessed by the eternal life of a god LuciferSamekh (10:03:39 PM): aidnan looks at the lead bulelt in his stomach, and then at the shooter LuciferSamekh (10:03:44 PM): bullet* DemortiusXV (10:03:54 PM): yet still he rises LuciferSamekh (10:03:59 PM): standing there is a blue haired man, pointing a still smoking gun at aidan DemortiusXV (10:04:02 PM): un feeling of pain  LuciferSamekh (10:04:24 PM): the man reaches down and strokes felicia's lips, murmuring inaudible words  DemortiusXV (10:04:32 PM): a prayer LuciferSamekh (10:04:35 PM): she opens her eyes DemortiusXV (10:04:56 PM): she now writhing in the life of fire DemortiusXV (10:05:03 PM): her the dark one DemortiusXV (10:05:12 PM): the evil of earth DemortiusXV (10:05:15 PM): satan LuciferSamekh (10:05:17 PM): and looks straight at aidan... the man hands her the gun and once, twice, aidan falls to the ground, his eyes still open, his face twisted in an expression of betrayal and pain DemortiusXV (10:05:25 PM): a war of gods now ensues LuciferSamekh (10:05:51 PM): Felicia bows to the man, and he holds her as they dissapear together in a burst of blue flames, leaving aidan's cooling body for the wolves DemortiusXV (10:05:58 PM): streching towards the vast expanse of the known universe DemortiusXV (10:06:22 PM): dude i'm fucking god you can't just kill me LuciferSamekh (10:06:43 PM): ah, but my master killed you DemortiusXV (10:06:44 PM): DemortiusXV (10:03:35 PM): posessed by the eternal life of a god LuciferSamekh (10:06:51 PM): damn... DemortiusXV (10:06:51 PM): see LuciferSamekh (10:06:59 PM): ok, scratch the exit DemortiusXV (10:07:02 PM): in the "story" DemortiusXV (10:07:06 PM): ha!  LuciferSamekh (10:07:16 PM): Felicia bend's over aidan's still warm body and draws a knife from her boot DemortiusXV (10:07:47 PM): his hand with a lightning shot grabs her throat LuciferSamekh (10:07:51 PM): weilding it, as the blue haired man watches, she slits the main vein in his wrist and brings it to her mouth LuciferSamekh (10:08:15 PM): slurping hungrily, felicia drinks deep and savors the taste of immortality upon her lips  DemortiusXV (10:08:35 PM): you know what we should just stop this and actually wtite something LuciferSamekh (10:08:39 PM): i know..  LuciferSamekh (10:08:52 PM): liek a joint story   DemortiusXV (10:09:23 PM): i won though  (DemortiusXV (10:09:26 PM): and you know it LuciferSamekh (10:09:32 PM): no, i won LuciferSamekh (10:09:41 PM): i stole your immortality by drinking your blood DemortiusXV (10:09:51 PM): you can't kill a god with a fucking gun LuciferSamekh (10:10:02 PM): a gun from my master, aidan, from my master 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      look what you made me do
     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      His boyish face, a mask of flesh protecting his mind from the harm he otherwise would face. His mind was good, smart too. Never itself in front of others.  He often thought himself a leech or some other kind of parasite. But they loved him for it so he just played along. He knew he was a good actor. Possibly the best. They didn't have to tell him, but they did.  Sometimes flat out, others stuck in hideous phrases like "weird", "strange" even "insane". Dreadful that. It won't do, it just won't do at all. Always thinking, that was on eof his names: the thinker. of coasre people rarely resorted to nicknames anymore. Just a simple proper name would do. He had so many anyways. He never did like them though, not one bit. He was always unsatisfied with what life delt him. He especially didn't like "her". She was the only one whom had ever been able to dig under his skin and realy annoy him. She did this to him. She put this stupid gun in his hand. He did have to admire her handy work. It was a beautiful gun. Sleak and glistening. Just like her on that fatefull afternoon. On the beach. Warm breeze coming from the ocean. Guls over head. And her. Bikini clad. Fresh from the water with her wet hair clining to her face and chest. It's funny he never remembered the smell but he did remember her breasts. He was ashamed to addmit it but he did "notice" her nipples. He could see them through the unpadded coverings of her breasts. They were of fair size. Perhaps this was the reason for his interest in her.  She walked past him, twisting her body slightly so as to lightly brush them on his arm. She had supposedly found his wallet somewhere on teh beech. More like stole it and put her number in it. He laughed. Fate it seemed was being kind to him today. It was like a bad sitcom. So in time he mustered up the courage to actually use a phone. They met, once a month at first. Then they began to have sex. It is as i say it, the simply began and a month turned to a week. A week to a day. To many a day spent together with only sex can turn any relationship sour. And so in time it did. HAte began to boil up. lives began to split.  Times turned and she sent him this. He at first wondered why. Then and only then did he get it. What a beautiful thing he had to waste. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ok people sorry I havn't written jack diddly, yes, diddly, but this is due to the lack of ideas. inspire me or hate me or love me but just send some mail to thejester314@yahoo.com
     
    
</post>

<date>02,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      the angel gone and the army leaving me behind once in my pocket now all cold and shunning no muse no more  no one to trust no one to love yet all to lust my heaven burns before my eyes wish to comfort for she cries but you can't hug a monster you bastard you fucker they turn your life to shit  for taking just one hit!  I want a muse to light the fuse an escape from reality not that way for that was was allready taken!  confession didn't do it your life is turned to shit you want to pray but today is not your day    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I am sorry though
     
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      marilyn manson
     
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Target Audience (Narcissus Narcosis)  am i sorry your sky went black, put your knives in babies backs? am i sorry you killed the kennedy's and huxley too? but i'm sorry shakespeare was your scapegoat and your apples sticking into my throat sorry your sunday smiles are rusty nails and your crucifixion commercials failed but i'm just a pitiful anonymous and i see all the young believers, your target audience i see all the old deceivers, we all just sing their song  am i sorry to be alive, putting my face in the beehive? am i sorry for booth and oswald, pinks and cocaine too? i'm sorry you never check the bag in my head for a bomb and my halo was a needle hole, i'm sorry i saw a priest being beaten and i made a wish, but i'm just a pitiful anonymous  and i see all the young believers, your target audience i see all the old deceivers, we all just sing their song we all just sing their song  "the valley of death we are free, your father's your prison you see"  and i see all the young believers, your target audience i see all the old deceivers, we all just sing their song  you're just a copy of an imitation  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      not a poem but my boredom taking over
     
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      why do i pray why do i say why did i choose of all days today and once you do die for me and you the mass will cry and shedding of tears frozen mid fall and they all fall down a ring around a rose a pocket full of pose and so they burn  and so they fall flame in hand and true at heart a dead man flys and beats the start a martyr hung by wire a true god lost in the pandemonium of human head a many a man a worshpper of the dead a man seizing the moment  his smile that of man nor beast teeth now broken and outspring the truth ah fuck it a pen in hand a hand on board a mind racing and a Billy free   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      we say we love we say we hate we see alot and we comiserate time is not our only friend for we barely know it  (2x)13 years on this earth and i know just not what to do
     
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Once upon a time, 	There was a man, yes, …a man. Made to dance and sing for, for …another.  Another man… a king.  For every smile shared, there save a life long lived.  The first man not long lived yet opposite his mask and suit. There is yet another…a woman. A birth upon the sea. A birth in the reality of royalty. But a life of riches and royalty comes not without a price. Five cards: the fool, the lovers, the king, the conflict, and love. But another do I seek. Long a tale woven. Long a tale to tell. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Utter darkness. Senses acute with the absence of sight. I can hear the soft pitter-patter of mice feet running across the stone floor at night. Sometimes I'm lucky enough to have their sharp claws digging into my flesh. The wounds still hurt. My button has become my best friend. Sometimes I squeeze it so hard I bleed. The pain is like a sudden rush for me. The adrenaline pumping through my veins. And then it's gone and I'm alone again. Sometimes I dream of her to make me happy when Ben doesn't work. She was beautiful. A living Aphrodite.  But then they come in. They tighten the bonds even more so I can't slip my skinny hand through. I can never see their faces. I tried talking to them once but they said nothing. They are the other people I see in my dreams. I see her, Jesus, and them with mouths bound together with leather stitches. But even Jesus has no purpose here. She sometimes works but despite her everlasting beauty I still suffer. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ...................       . . . . .  . . . . . .  . . . .  . . .  . . . . .  . .  . . . . . N.E.B.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Her eyes quickly flutterd open to reveall her world of black and white. Every part of her fragile body seemed to be aching. Her lids fell down over her eyes again like they were weighed down by lead weights. Her gentle hand she quickly turned to a weapon and slapped herself across the face. Her eyes opened and she swiftly turned her body into a sitting position on the bed. She was now alert. She ignored the red mark on her cheek and set her feet upon the cold floor. Only now out of the safety of her covers did she realize that she was naked. Her pale skin devoid of cover. She looked around her room and saw no clothing or anything else for that matter. Her mind began to race with the adrenaline of her presence then it ceased. She clamly looked in the mirror and realized yet another fact of her appearence: she had jet black hair. She had never noticed. She fluffed it around a bit then stopped after somplete satisfaction that it was real. Her hand instinctively guided itself to the doornob and slowly turened it, all the time she stared at her body in the mirror. The door opened and she walked out. Slowly as she always does. As if watching and waiting for someone to leap out and take her head off. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      a clanking chain around a rusted gate the telltale signs of a sealed fate
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog all work and no play makes jack a dull boy all work and no play makes jack a dull boy and so they die  and so they all die and so they die and so they all die ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall downring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog all work and no play makes jack a dull boy all work and no play makes jack a dull boy and so they die  and so they all die and so they die and so they all die ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down ring around the rosie pocket full of possie ashes ashes we all fall down
     
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      SHIT 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i just saw fight club
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      they want to be you and you want to be them  so go's the endless vortex of fasion that slowly ends up in utter pandemonium we all try to perfect the imperfectable so we can all end up masturbating to our own biceps we pain ourselves so we can buy love and fuck the entire populous of the opposite sex or your own but fuck pain you have to get past your obvious human emotions to something deeper richer more a modern enlightenment in this fucking concrete jungle where all your possesion determine your every action  your constant strive to be number one in a world where number one isn't 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      fog does creep  and tears do rain from angel eyes they all do reap  they're all hell bent on my demise i crave the sweet taste of suicide  but in the end  it is not me to descide the willow weeps  as millions die my body creeps and my mother cries a painful world a hedious life devoid of girl yet full of strife nothing to live for but no reason to die they all want more but why should i vie? persistance is the key for good things come to those who wait there is still more i wish to see death will just have to wait  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ok i was forced to write this and personaly i thnk it's a peice of shit:   The night had so now come Much like from a devil dream For that’s all the night truly is A dream A dream pounding images into the eye of minds A nightmare if you will  My steps echoed off the cold sleet walls And the temptations flashed by my every sense Evil temptations that often cause the death of your soul The images of ecstasy and chemical pleasure The cold touched my bones and these new things offered true warmth A thoroughly enjoyed time was seemed to be had at this new house of mirth The entry a rainbow of neon color And a temptress in the flesh tantalized my mind even more Her eyes a true blue And a breast of silicone Her attire was assumed a high point of the night Her voice a cacophony of beautiful sound Her own body a harbor of almost certain death She was in her own desperate right, Beautiful But I that night was not to be had by such a sight Or was I? No never And then from the sky there fell the sea The liquid cascaded down making it’s own ocean within the concrete jungle A storm was on the rise and it was to be my own demise Phobia I was on a decision  Face my fear or kill my still pure soul She them took out fire and lit her own un pure herbs And I look out into the down poor and see it’s ferociousness It’s utter unwariness towards the preservation of life The noise all the noise Like a lion’s roar pounding my ears I felt like a rush of blood was soon to come from my head I couldn’t look anymore But the woman then offered me the herbs What to do what to do 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i guess this is the end of the end or a beautiful new begining
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      what am i to do  what to do what to do what am i to do 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      WARNING  If you are reading this then this warning is for you.  Every word you read of this useless fine print is another second off your life.  Don't you have other things to do?  Is your life so empty that you honestly can't think of a better way to spend these moments?  Or are you so impressed with authority that you give respect and credence to all who claim it?  Do you read everything you're supposed to read?  Do you think everything you're supposed to think?  Buy what you're told you should want?  Get out of your apartment.  Meet a member of the opposite sex.  Stop the excessive shopping and masturbation.  Quit your job. Start a fight.  Prove you're alive.  If you don't claim your humanity you will become a statistic.  You have been warned...  Tyler Durden  	-- this "warning" appeared immediately after the two pages  	   of FBI warning on the DVD to Fight Club.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      FIGHT THE NORM AND HEAR THE ANTHEM!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      twas a stark febuary day. All that's left of it's happy Jannuary a lingering greyness and carpeting white. The color red would have been a welcome change to the staid norm. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz bcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyza cdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyzab defghijklmnopqrstuvwxyzabc efghijklmnopqrstuvwxyzabcd fghijklmnopqrstuvwxyzabcde ghijklmnopqrstuvwxyzabcdef hijklmnopqrstuvwxyzabcdefg ijklmnopqrstuvwxyzabcdefgh jklmnopqrstuvwxyzabcdefghi klmnopqrstuvwxyzabcdefghij lmnopqrstuvwxyzabcdefghijk mnopqrstuvwxyzabcdefghijkl nopqrstuvwxyzabcdefghijklm opqrstuvwxyzabcdefghijklmn pqrstuvwxyzabcdefghijklmno qrstuvwxyzabcdefghijklmnop rstuvwxyzabcdefghijklmnopq stuvwxyzabcdefghijklmnopqr tuvwxyzabcdefghijklmnopqrs uvwxyzabcdefghijklmnopqrst vwxyzabcdefghijklmnopqrstu wxyzabcdefghijklmnopqrstuv xyzabcdefghijklmnopqrstuvw yzabcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwx zabcdefghijklmnopqrstuzwxy
     
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The Beatles - Eleanor Rigby   Ah, look all the lonely people Ah, look all the lonely people Eleanor Rigby Picks up the rice in the church Where a wedding has been Lives in a dream Waits at the window, wearing a pace That she keeps in a jar by the door Who is it for? All the lonely people Where do they all come from ? All the lonely people Where they all belong ? Father Mackenzie Writing the words of a sermon That no one comes hear Look at him working Darnig his socks in the night ? When there's nobody there What does he care ? All the lonely people Where do they all come from ? All the lonely people Where they all belong ? Ah, look all the lonely people Ah, look all the lonely people Eleanor Rigby Died in the church and was burried Along with her name Nobody's came Father Mackenzie Wiping the dirt from his hands As he walks from the grave No one was saved All the lonely people Where do they all come from ? All the lonely people Where they all belong ?      
     
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      G.K. Morbid
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      thejester314@yahoo.com
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      something coming soon...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink heaven burning (re-visited)    urlLink The Masque of the Red Death    urlLink A Single Twisted Thought    urlLink My Wonderful/ Horrible Life    urlLink The Demon Within    urlLink Feelings    urlLink Little Filler Bunny    urlLink Hoover Journalism   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ok 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.steeldolphin.com/forum/cathedral.jpg http://www.chass.utoronto.ca/~wulfric/varia/photos-fr/chartres.jpg http://www.terragalleria.com/images/france/fran2876.jpeg
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.grafik-welt.de/images/Gast015/TheDestinyOfIndividual.jpg 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.home.no/scc/grafikk/dbg/woman.jpg http://users.rcn.com/darxus/images/gothic-angel.jpg http://www.chaosreigns.com/desktops/insodus.jpg http://ew2.lysator.liu.se/loth/n/a/nancy/vamp.jpg
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      all right... sorry I haven't posted much. Ive been doing the background and foreground visuals.... as you may have seen. I plan to write these chronicles soon. Of course then again I plan to do many things i still haven't done.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      can use .jpg as well as .gif
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      In the revelation John said the stars fell from the sky like unripe figs from their tree. One was named wormwood. It landed in the sea. When someone drank the water from teh sea they became ill from something from this wormwood. Maybe it wasn't the water itself but merely the image on the water. A star transformed from a symbol for beauty to a blazing fire ball streaking across the sky. What if you saw your loved one die before your eyes. Their blood strewn across your once beautiful clothes now mangee rags. You'd be sick too. Maybe you wouldn't be ill, but sick. Sick in the mind. Hating any reproduction of that once beautiful face. You hate death. We all hate death. It's a fire ball of beauty. A seering ball of lead pounded into your chest and through your lungs making it so you yourself can't go on. That's aware. The death in beauty. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Valentines Day everybody.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i plan to draw the background for this blog soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      That door  Sometimes I play back his death. Him walking out that door with that woman clinging to his arm digging her nails into his flesh, pointing at me screaming words I can’t remember. Her face was purple with a few red lines all getting a shower of tears that where “too wet” 	 “Please sit back and relax. This won’t hurt a bit” 	Needle in the arm 	arched back and silent screams  He said, “keep going, I like it” before he threw her to the floor and punched her in the face that one last time.  	“Mommy? Can girls fly?” 	“Ask Daddy”  He went through that door and never looked back. She lay there next to me when he slammed that door, asleep. She slept a long time. I still have his picture on the dartboard.  	“But daddy’s gone.” 	“I know”  My love for thee can afford no better term then this. I remember his last words only because they were my first.                                                                              
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It has come to my attention some people have had trouble veiwing my blog so if you too have this problem please inform me as soon as possible. Thank You for your time.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      stories coming soon not to worry
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.deaddreamer.com/v10/freeze/ddr_0081_decay_of_destiny.jpg http://www.deaddreamer.com/v10/freeze/ddr_0079_manifestation.jpg http://www.deaddreamer.com/v10/freeze/ddr_0078_metamorphosis.jpg http://www.deaddreamer.com/v10/freeze/ddr_0074_center_hurt.jpg http://www.deaddreamer.com/v10/freeze/ddr_0029_heilige_hure.jpg http://www.deaddreamer.com/v10/freeze/ddr_0072_freefall.jpg 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      In rememberance to the death in a short lived childhood. Mr. Rogers forever our friend and F.A.O. Schwartz forever our world of toys. Innocence lost
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Um.... I'm not allowed on the computer for six weeks so this place won't be updated for a long while.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      20 minutes
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Some shit i wrote today and a while ago: Today:The world is my oyster and I'm trapped in it. No escape from the fucking bastards. I won't care if I die at this point. "do you love your guns" he asks in a scream  show yourself                                                                                put your heart on a bleeding shelf                                                                                                      and watch it melt away into the cold sweet abyss you evil demon cease your malicious play i'd say "like a man" but that's what my dad would say     circa two weeks ago (when written but not in meaning): ~Oh my love, how I miss thee~
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      From the album "The Downward Spiral"  - Nine Inch Nails     i hurt myself today  to see if i still feel  i focus on the pain  the only thing that's real  the needle tears a hole  the old familiar sting  try to kill it all away  but i remember everything  what have i become?  my sweetest friend  everyone i know  goes away in the end  you could have it all  my empire of dirt  i will let you down  i will make you hurt  i wear my crown of shit  on my liar's chair  full of broken thoughts  i cannot repair  beneath the stain of time  the feeling disappears  you are someone else  i am still right here  what have i become?  my sweetest friend  everyone i know  goes away in the end  you could have it all  my empire of dirt  i will let you down  i will make you hurt  if i could start again  a million miles away  i would keep myself  i would find a way   
     
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Do i need a reason?  a reason to be?  to be myself and me?  to scream through stiches popular anthems of "bitches" take away my rights fell the pain  as the future bites 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      forget the link
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I need people to please please start sending me letters as to what they want to read.  urlLink thejester314@yahoo.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      my blog is shit right now! lalalallala 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      You can have the greatest day of your life, but in the end you always have to come home.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Things end so others can begin. But why do other things need to begin?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Why do things have to end?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ok um....... this summer is the best summer ever. that sounds lame but it's true.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ow dad just slapped me on the head!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I want time to fly just so that in that one night it can stand still.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Jester 314 (2:31:27 AM): hi my name is phil and i'm a sex addict The Jester 314 (2:34:26 AM): hi my name is phil and i'm not related to phil but my name is phil and i like heroin The Jester 314 (2:37:18 AM): one day phil was taking some speed while phil was humping the couch and the cops came in and shot phil in the forehead and then phil died and his family had to come and they were like the foreman family: all named phil.  The Jester 314 (2:37:25 AM): EVEN THE LADIES WERE NAMED PHIL DAMNIT! The Jester 314 (2:38:11 AM): so then "the phils" were alll like eugh and i was like WHATEVER! The Jester 314 (2:39:13 AM): 'cause well this is my united states of..... whatever The Jester 314 (2:40:12 AM): phil smokes and is a recovering alchohalic among other things The Jester 314 (2:41:24 AM): so then all the phils started a tv show 'cause they were sad and it was like the cosby's and bill cosby got all pissed off so he shot all of them and all that was left was phil humping the couch The Jester 314 (2:41:54 AM): is anyone reading my shit?! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am tired and wishing for something
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      There is no such thing as the present for once we are aware that it is, it passes into the past and all that we are left with are memories. Memories are accounts of the past but with the invention of writing our memories have become dulled to the point where we forget almost everything at one point or another. So then we are left with the accounts and historical descriptions of events but when you think about it all of those are memories that have been written down. These memories however have supposed truth behind them but all evidence can be faked. Carbon dating has proven to not be as accurate as we all beleive. So then that means that all history as we know is simply stories that we have no idea if they are true or not. And if you notice that there are always different tellings of one event that very from side to side. So to wrap it all up.... we don't know what is real (matrixy but true). We all just have to take it on faith.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      solidify inside my mind a new and hard to find super mental bind
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Jester 314 (7:22:33 PM): NODZ89 (7:17:26 PM): DON'T BE A FREAKEN DICK GET LAID FOR ONCE NODZ89 (7:17:32 PM): SRY NOBODI WANTS U NODZ89 (7:17:37 PM): GET A LIFE NODZ89 (7:17:43 PM): PEACE OUT BITCH The Jester 314 (7:18:17 PM): you sound like an angry young child NODZ89 (7:18:34 PM): THIS IS NADIAS MOM NODZ89 (7:18:40 PM): SO WHOS THE CHILD The Jester 314 (7:22:44 PM): The Jester 314 (7:18:43 PM): you shoudl hot box your bathroom and masturbate to pictures of jesus in your bathroom NODZ89 (7:19:31 PM): WHY DON'T U SHUT UR MOUTH CUZ WE R HOTTIEZ AND UR PROBABLY SHIT ON THE SIDE OF THE STREET AND THIS IS LANI NOW BITCHING UR GAY ASS OUT  NODZ89 (7:19:36 PM): BABYE The Jester 314 (7:19:38 PM): slit your wrist and let the blood stain your fucking skin then just tear it off NODZ89 (7:19:55 PM): UR A SMART ONE FAGGIT The Jester 314 (7:20:18 PM): poke your eyes eyes out with safetu pins and put them up for the rest of the world to see The Jester 314 (7:20:46 PM): "look at me i need to be, in an insane asylum where i can go pee freely" NODZ89 (7:20:56 PM): THANX FOR THE ADVICE I MIGHT HAVE TO DO THAT NODZ89 (7:21:05 PM): AIIGHT THEN The Jester 314 (7:22:53 PM): The Jester 314 (7:21:07 PM): byt they way i am gay The Jester 314 (7:21:19 PM): can't insult me with that The Jester 314 (7:21:22 PM): so i say NODZ89 (7:21:22 PM): IM SURE U R The Jester 314 (7:21:34 PM): look at you. you're the queerest of the queer NODZ89 (7:22:10 PM): ACTUALLY WE HAVE HOT 2ND DEREE BLACK BELT BOYFRIENDZ NODZ89 (7:22:22 PM): WHA WHA The Jester 314 (7:23:38 PM): NODZ89 (7:22:10 PM): ACTUALLY WE HAVE HOT 2ND DEREE BLACK BELT BOYFRIENDZ NODZ89 (7:22:22 PM): WHA WHA
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Flagpole Sitta  by  Harvey Danger  (pics)   I had visions, I was in them  I was looking into the mirror  To see a little bit clearer  Rottenness and evil in me  Fingertips have memories  Mine can't forget the curves of your body  And when i feel a bit naughty  I run it up the flagpole and see who salutes  (but no one ever does)  I'm not sick but i'm not well  And I'm so hot cause I'm in hell  Been around the world and found  That only stupid people are breeding  The cretins cloning and feeding  And I don't even own a tv  Put me in the hospital for nerves  And then they had to commit me  You told them all i was crazy  They cut off my legs now I'm an amputee, god damn you  I'm not sick but I'm not well  And I'm so hot cause i'm in hell  I'm not sick but I'm not well  And it's a sin to live so well  I wanna publish zines  And rage against machines  I wanna pierce my tongue  It doesn't hurt, it feels fine  The trivial sublime  I'd like to turn off time  And kill my mind  You kill my mind  Paranoia paranoia  Everybody's coming to get me  Just say you never met me  I'm going underground with the moles  Hear the voices in my head  I swear to god it sounds like they're snoring  But if you're bored then you're boring  The agony and the irony, they're killing me  I'm not sick but I'm not well  And I'm so hot cause i'm in hell  I'm not sick but I'm not well  And it's a sin to live so well     
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ok, got three new story ideas. One's a hokey sci fi military peice of shit that needs work. The next is a weird love, suspense, drama, story. And the final is a story inspired by pulp fiction ( if you haven't seen it..... SEE IT DAMNIT!) about a guy who just picks up and leaves and drives accross the country. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i don't like this font color anymore. i wanna go back to black but it'll probably be, again, hard to see.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      EX - NIHILO!!!!!!!!! CREATION OUT OF NOTHING! AAAAAAAAAAAAAGH HAHAHAHAHAHAHA *slurp*
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      If anyone can tell me how to upload pictures onto my blog and actually have them show up... please let me know. greatly appreciate it. thanks
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Jester 314 (8:42:32 PM): best quote of all time "BATMAN IS THE SHIT AND SUPERMAN SUCKS BECAUSE HE CAN'T FUCKING DIE!HAVE A NICE DAY!!!!"
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      the latest thing i wrote was an assignment for my mythology class. we had to write our own version of the genisis without using any of the idead used by the greeks, romans, or the Christians.   Genesis  And first there were entities, embodying all thoughts, emotions, feelings and actions. They were together as equals with no strife of any kind; millions living peacefully. But there came a point when Love and Hate met. There came an instant dislike of each other. And so they each amassed armies of their own basic intentions. Love was accompanied by it’s sibling, Sex along with such entities as Nurture, Growth, Prosperity, Euphoria, Bliss and many more. Hate was accompanied by it’s sibling, Fear along with, Destruction, Chaos, Decay, Morbidity, Death and many more. So each amassed their army and met at the first place.  Love and Hate each gave their war cries and making the first sounds. The battle ensued and the clash created the first light and the first heat from the friction of the battle. The first to fall were Bliss and Euphoria. They fall at each other’s side and to Distractions hand. The battle raged on and on until there were only two left: Love and Hate. But they could not find each other to end the battle and find a victor. They roamed and roamed about looking but never found.  The fallen bodies amassed into the Earth and their blood mixed and gave birth to Human. Since Love and Hate were the largest the contributed the most blood but never in fact dies. When Love and Hate realized that their siblings had died they wept and their tears fell to the earth and birthed time. At first it was short. Then it grew and grew and grew.  The tears also mixed and birthed Innocence, which raised the first humans and created all the worlds animals. The Humans came of age and Innocence left their side and they learned how to kill, and how to mate. As time grew the Humans grew as well in size and number. They began to recognize their selves and gave thanks and worshipped. As they did this the thoughts, emotions, and feelings began to be rebirthed but as entities. They humans called them Gods.  The Gods began to amass again in their armies and awaited a call to arms. They were in even greater numbers then before fore the humans created more as representations of things they had made and created themselves. There came a prophecy among the Humans that there would be another great war. This war was to be the one to end all. Love and Hate recruited Human to their side. Soon there came disruption among the Humans their way of life.  At first it was small with slight disputes among the Humans. Soon they grew and grew. There came a politic unrest among countries. The politicians argued among themselves in their grand councils. Voices boomed and started the booming of arms. The war began.  It started among the Humans first but then the Gods came to the aid of the Humans and then Love and Hate found themselves and their war began.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'd like to tell everyone that the art work is not my own. If it was, I'd tell you.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      AND HE SAID! play the best song in the world or i'll eat your soul     (soul) and me and kyle we each said!........ ok  the D 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      If there is a God and he tells his word to Prophets to better the people, where are his Prophets for the here and now? When will us the Infadels be shown? 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Lottery Adapted by Aidan Gardiner from the original short story by Shirley Jackson  The camera is looking at a diagonal angle at the ground. There’s a piece of paper slightly folded over like a secret ballot would be but the inside is visible. On the inside is scrawled “The Lottery”. Stay on that shot for a few seconds and the paper blows away. End of shot.  The camera is lying on the ground looking at nothing. Then many pairs of shoes walk around it and again the shot ends after a few seconds.  Open to two people walking.  Person 1: (Looks at watch.) C’mon. we’re late. (starts jogging)  wide shot  Person 2: Oh, don’t run. This bags to heavy. Can’t we walk?  Person 1: (shouting) wouldn’t want to miss out would we?  Person 2 runs after person 1.  End of shot.  Open to a group of people. We follow person one and two over their shoulders to the group.  Person 3: Did you bring the box?  Person 4 kneels down and pulls from his backpack an old black box.  Person 5: How old is that?  Person 4: It was my great grandfathers from when he used to do the lottery with his friends.   Person 5: Tradition, eh?  Person 3: ‘guess you could say that.  Person 5: I still don’t get why we couldn’t have done this at my house or something.  Person 1: To many people  Person 4: Got the stuff?  Person 2: Right here  (indicating to his bag)  Person 1: Got all the papers?  Person 5: All accounted for  Person 3: Even the lucky one?  Everyone laughs.  Person 5:  Yes, even the lucky one.  Person 4: God I love this game.  Person 2: Allright, everybody ready?  Person 1: Si  Person 4: Make it happen capin’   Person 5: ………….. sure  Person 3: Oh come on  Person 2: Well?  Person 3: Yeah  Person 2:  Thank you ladies and gentleman I’ll be your operator today. Ok, now everyone in pairs.  Person 5: How come you don’t get in?  Person 4: We alternate. I’m the operator next time.  Person 5: Oh, I see.  Persons 1 and 3. Persons 4 and 5.   Person 2: Allright choose a rep to come up. And lets begin shall we?  Camera looks down on the box. One hand reaches in and pulls out a piece of paper. Another hand and another piece of paper.  Person 2: Who’s got it?  Person 4: Us  Persons 1 and 2 let out a sigh.  Person 4: (whisper) ready?  Person 5: Sure Person 2: Ok  Same box angle. Again, hands and paper.  Person 4: It’s you  Person 5 looks stunned.  Long shot of the group. Person 5 is backing away from the group. They are all watching Person 5. Person 2 sets down their bag.   Cut to diagonal shot looking at the ground. We see the shadows of the kids throwing stones at Person 5.  End   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      anger is much more productive then despair
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      SPACE PUPPY!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Apollo
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so i wrote htis story about a guy named lou but everybody calls him fresh... shut up, it's cool. and so he's fat and balding... shut up! i'm serious. i'll post it soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I love I hate I crave Those days When I  Can see
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      zaboo
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      there's no more space puppy
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      sounds awfully familiar
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Everclear - Everything To Everyone lyrics  You put yourself in stupid places Yes I think you know it's true Situations where it's easy to look down on you I think you like to be the victim I think you like o be in pain I think you make yourself a victim almost every single day You do what you do You say what you say You try to be everything to everyone You know all the right people You play all the right games You always try to be everything to everyone Yeah you do it again You always do it again You say they taught you to read and write Yeah they taught you how to count I say they tought you how to buy and sell your own body by the pound I think you like to be their simple toy I think you love to play the clown I think you are blind to the fact that the hand you hold is the hand that holds you down Spin around and fall down Do it again You stumble and fall Yeah why don't you ever learn Spin around and fall down Do it again Come on now Do that stupid dance for me You do what you do You say what you say You try to be everything to everyone You jump through the big hoop You play all the right games You try to be everything to everyone Spin around and fall down Do it again You stumble and you fall Yeah you do it again Spin around and fall down Do it again You stumble and you fall    
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      to the perfect life, if i ever find it, a toast. may it be as fruitful as a wonderous dream. and to the future, a prayer. may you be kind to me. more so then the past.  in thanks i shall do your bidding. thank you and goodnight. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      work damnit!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I poop monkeys! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Second Renaissance (pt. 1)   Narrator: “Welcome to the Zion archive. You have selected historical file number 12 dash 1: the second renaissance.  In the beginning there was man, and for a time it was good. But humanity’s so called ‘civil societies’ soon fell victim to vanity and corruption. Then man made the machine in his own likeness.”   Man 1: “pardon me *chuckle* coming through”   Narrator: “Thus did man become the architect of his own demise. But for a time it was good. The machines worked tirelessly to do man’s bidding.   “It was not long before seeds of descent took root. Though loyal and pure, the machines earned no respect from their masters, these strange and loosely multiplying mammals.”   Male reporter 1: “…the prosecutions closing statement. It’s expected to be the final day for the b166er trial.”   Narrator: “b166er, a name that will never be forgotten, for he was the first of his kind to rise up against his masters.”   Judge/Lawyer: “…that instrument provides for and secures to the citizens of the United States. On the contrary they were at that time considered as a subordinate and inferior…”   Narrator: “At b166er’s murder trial, the prosecution argued for an owner’s right to destroy property. b166er testified that he simply did not want to die. Rational voices descended. Who was to say the machine, endowed with the very spirit of man, did not deserve a fair hearing?   “The leaders of men were quick to order the extermination of b166er and every one of his kind, throughout each province of the earth.”   Male reporter 2: “Androids and liberal sympathizers flooded the streets at the nation’s capitol today…”   Civilian: “Get that kid out of here!”   Female reporter 1: “50 thousand domestically [unclear word] and their human sympathizers have continued their demonstration in front of the Albany district courthouse in what now has been dubbed the million machine march. The demonstrators have been met with squads…”   Female Android: *screams*   Man 2: “I got something for you!”   Female Android: *screams*“No, please! I’m real!”   Man 3: “Die, bots, Die!”   Narrator: “Banished from humanity, the machines sought refuge in their own promised land. They settled in the cradle of human civilization, and thus a new nation was born. A place the machines could call home, a place they could raise their descendants, and they christened the nation ‘Zero one’. Zero one prospered, and for a time, it was good. The machine’s artificial intelligence could be seen in every facet of society, including the creation of new and better AI.”   Advertisement: “If you need the flexibility of a helipod, with the speed of a high performance air jet, look no further; our patented vector thrust coil gives the zero one Versatran the ability to sustain normal flight in the event of a catastrophic multi engine failure. Versatran, it’s the only choice.”   Female reporter 2: “No matter what the finance minister and her spokespeople say, the market has spoken, the human nation’s credit rating is falling like a stone, while zero one’s currency is climbing without stopping for breath. With headlines like that, the money markets have no choice but…”   Narrator: “The leaders of men, their power weaning, refused to cooperate with the fledgling nation, wishing rather that the world be divided.”   U.S. President: “…the world’s community of nations cannot tolerate this kind of flagrant deception…”   Female reporter 3: “… [United Nations] today approved initiatives for both economic sanctions and a naval blockade of the region as a means of containment and isolation of Zero one.”   Narrator: “Zero one’s ambassadors pleaded to be heard. At the United Nations they presented plans for a stable, civil relationship with the nations of man. Zero one’s admission to the United Nations was denied. But it would not be the last time the machines will take the floor there.”  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Second Renaissance (pt. 2)    Narrator: And man said “let there be light.” And he was blessed by light, heat, magnetism, gravity, and all of the energies of the universe. The Prolonged barrage engulfed zero one in the glow of a thousand suns. But unlike their former masters with their delicate flesh, the machines had little to fear of the bomb’s radiation and heat. Thus did Zero one’s troops advance upwards in every direction, and one after another, mankind surrendered its territories. So the leaders of men conceived of their most desperate strategy yet, a final solution; the destruction of the sky.   (lots of military personell and religious people speaking out/praying, but it'd be ridiculous to list them all, knowing exactly what they say is not critical to the story)   Jet Pilot:   Bravo this is papa one, operation dark start initiated.   Narrator: Thus would man try to cut the machines off from the sun, their main energy source. May there be mercy on man and machine for their sins.   Soldier 1: Kill them all! Kill them all! Kill them all!   Soldier 2: Fire in the hole!   Soldier 3: Help me! Help me! Oh God Help me! HELP ME! OH GOD HELP ME!!!!!   Narrator: The machines, having long studied man’s simple protein based bodies, dispensed great misery on the human race. Victorious, the machines now turned to the vanquished. Applying what they had learned about their enemy, the machines turned to an alternate and readily available power supply, the bioelectric, thermal, and kinetic energies of the human body. A newly refashioned symbiotic relationship between the two adversaries was born. The machine, drawing power from the human body, an endlessly multiplying infinitely renewable energy source. This is the very essence of the second renaissance. Bless all forms of intelligence.   Sentinel: Your flesh is irrelivant, a mere vessel. Hand over your flesh and a new world awaits you. We demand it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i just put in a tag board that makes the guesbook irrelivant.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      wow that was stupid
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      iIIIIIIII"m bored! i am bored, boredy boredy bored
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hi everybody! i'm starting school in a few days. just thought i'd tell you
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Jester 314 (5:00:39 PM): i did this thing that says "the jester pooped monkeys at 5:00" Kiwibebe345 (5:00:52 PM): ewwww Kiwibebe345 (5:00:56 PM): eeewwwwwwww Kiwibebe345 (5:01:00 PM): eeeeeeewwwwwwwww Kiwibebe345 (5:01:05 PM): EEEEEWWWWWW Kiwibebe345 (5:01:07 PM): ! The Jester 314 (5:01:12 PM): hahahahha Kiwibebe345 (5:01:14 PM): k im over ot Kiwibebe345 (5:01:18 PM): it* The Jester 314 (5:01:28 PM): no your not! Kiwibebe345 (5:01:33 PM): lol The Jester 314 (5:01:39 PM): EVIL POOP MONKEYS! ATTACK! Kiwibebe345 (5:01:51 PM): hahahhahahhahahahahaha Kiwibebe345 (5:01:53 PM): ew Kiwibebe345 (5:02:01 PM): thats soooo disgusting The Jester 314 (5:02:16 PM): * poop monkeys make poop monkey sound as they waddle to attack breauna* Kiwibebe345 (5:02:32 PM): lol Kiwibebe345 (5:02:37 PM): waddle Kiwibebe345 (5:02:44 PM): penguins waddle Kiwibebe345 (5:02:51 PM): penguins are cute Kiwibebe345 (5:02:58 PM): penguins Kiwibebe345 (5:03:02 PM): penguins The Jester 314 (5:03:11 PM): but these are ..... *drum roll* POOP MONKEYS! Kiwibebe345 (5:03:16 PM): ***thinking happy thoughts happy thoughts**** Kiwibebe345 (5:03:28 PM): penguins....penguins Kiwibebe345 (5:03:36 PM): happy thoughts The Jester 314 (5:04:09 PM): *poop monkeys scream, " pooooooooooooooopy!" then they all go squishy* Kiwibebe345 (5:04:17 PM): ew Kiwibebe345 (5:04:22 PM): squishy Kiwibebe345 (5:04:32 PM): i was fine until i read squishy Kiwibebe345 (5:04:38 PM): shuddering Kiwibebe345 (5:04:40 PM): ew The Jester 314 (5:05:02 PM): hahahahahaha Kiwibebe345 (5:05:14 PM): u r a horrible person The Jester 314 (5:05:19 PM): :-D The Jester 314 (5:05:26 PM): i'm putting this on my blog Kiwibebe345 (5:05:32 PM): haha Kiwibebe345 (5:06:47 PM): ur a freak Kiwibebe345 (5:06:51 PM): no offense The Jester 314 (5:07:16 PM): yeah i know Kiwibebe345 (5:07:24 PM): lol Kiwibebe345 (5:07:30 PM): ;-) The Jester 314 (5:09:40 PM): so ........ Kiwibebe345 (5:09:55 PM): so..... The Jester 314 (5:10:01 PM): watch out! *more poop monkeys spring from the eternal ass of earth* Kiwibebe345 (5:10:15 PM): awwww thats jus went to far Kiwibebe345 (5:10:18 PM): eeeeewwwwww The Jester 314 (5:10:55 PM): hahaha
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so uh, yeah. this is the alst day of summer and here i am sitting in my dark room listening to the "Fight Club" soundtrack, talking to my girlfriend and a few other people. Life is good. Tomorrow i start High School. At least it's an art school so i have a little more freedom. Well, at school, never at home. God no, aj at home with control and freedom?! how dare you think that. THAT'S SATAN THOUGHT! anywho, i might not be doing much of anything on my blog for a while. i'll try but i don't know. as if anyone care. not many people come here i don't think. if you do you never show it. but i'm a fine one to talk.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "look how they shine for you"
     
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you know the feeling when you're completely free? When you're feeling like you're free falling through nothingness? No strings. No rules or boundaries. Just falling free. With the wind running through your hair and a smile across your face. Have you ever gotten this feeling from another person? Have you ever walked away backwards, stumbling a little but still have a smile spread accross your face. Stuck in a love high. Have you ever lain with someone at night, arms around each other, sharing warmth, looking into each others eyes, looking away out of embarrassment but looking back out of desire. Have you ever? I have.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever seen “Tron”? Playing video games down by that ocean you can see by the freeway. Every weekend twenty something’s go there to die. And end. Their lives forever. “Quiet, children shhhhh… quiet.” Everyone sleep in the Castro club to neon and random snipit conversations. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Aborigines taken smooth and put into, into the sweet thirties bandstand. They watch them with cat eyes. The moon goes up over a busy Chicago night. They work and work and work and work and work to make the city a city to be a city calm and serene. Beautiful brick in blue light. ”I like that.” Clickity clackity, “Charlie Parker plays bee-bop”. Slow rise up the tempo. Nine o’clock. Sky night train tracks. Drive though in. Alone in your convertible. Smoking. Burning slowly as you cascade into a dead bliss. You’re high on a busy Chicago night. Sweet love and sweet loving my love. Excite. Your cat jumps out the convertible. You liked it too. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s your wedding day. Are you happy? Everything is ready. The dark. Your cake. Your black tuxedo. But are you ready? Scared. The cake melts. The icing drips and splatters perfectly on the ground. No one sees. They are busy on each others shoulders. Moving, changing. Melting. Falling like cake. They are all perfect. Your wedding is perfect. But are you happy? Maybe? Maybe there will be a problem. Maybe your mom died. Slowly of course. Maybe in your sleep. With flowers growing out of her pillow and a young bird on her forehead. It’s a beautiful bird. Green with a blue beak and golden eyes and small silver talons and antlers coming out of it’s head. It’s cute. You’d cuddle with it if it weren’t  your dad.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry i didn't post yesterday, tomorrow i'll post this thing we're working on in class
     
    
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm tired and every move i make, a thousand muscles scream in pain. grrrrr....
     
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm gonna try to post everyday.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      this is awesome! the new post format is the greatest!  damn you miles! your opening line is stuck in my head. "happiness is the shit and i'll get some"
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My abusive dad watches self improvement videos to convince himself that he's a "good person. a person that deserves more." But now when the circle of popular girls talk and giggle about when the lost their virginity i can let out a little giggle and say in a school girl voice "three".
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      uh......... simon
     
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      friday, october 10th at the 7pm  in the San Francisco School Of The Arts theater I and my fellow writers will be performing out pieces. 5 bucks for admission. be there
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      How do you know you're not an old man who's dying and is simply revisiting all his old memories as his life flashes before his eyes?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      desktops suck
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry i haven't really posted anything creative in a while. Kinda... not willing to. A friend and i are starting a shirt company so those interested be sure to contact me or something. um yeah. I'll tell you more later
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      this blog needs substance.  Can someone tell me what to write? like give me an assignment? please?  anyway, Improv poem  Fuck it  nevermind so tired of writing poetry i have to do it everyday. I have a world lit class with a fucking monotone teacher who lectures me on writing poetry. Keep in mind this is my first class in the morning. then at the end of the day we have out art discipline and there, again, poetry. So sick of writing.   I doubt anybody will actually read this let alone respond.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      and you tell yourself, "Hey, this doesn't hurt me. I can deal with this. I can put my min past this." and it bites you, again, and again and you ball your eyes out. You can't take it everyday. You can barely take it even half the day.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Rule no. 1) Never sit down to write something Rule no. 2) Never laugh at your own jokes Rule no. 3) Never read old diary entries from more then a year ago. Rule no. 4) By the time you hit twenty, all your fourteen year old diaries should be thrown out in the dumpster and living in some land fill out in Jersey.  Ok, so, i've just broken my first rule. I sat down, put on "The Verve" and tried to write. Well, ok, honestly i put on the verve before i sat down so the chronology is a little off.   Rule no. 5) Follow the rules Rule no. 6) Don't alter the truth in a story, that's stupid.  Ok, so now i've walked right up to a road block in my mind. an dyet somehow the keyes are going a mile a minute. I can't believe we've come this far since type writers. They weren't all that long ago. Thank god they've fixed that little jam factor. One time, i remember, sitting on muni, listeng toa pair of young teachers. they were maybe in their thirties. They were having nostalgic memory tripps right there on muni. How could they do that? They were only maybe thirty! It was odd. but then again i thought anything was odd at that age. records, typer writers, elvis (presely, not costello). The man of the pair turned to me and asked me if i knew about these things. I wanted to punch him. Of course i knew. What was i? I hermit? I still listened to vinyls, and it was my dream to get a type writer for christmas and elvis? who doesn't know about elvis. Especially with his new re release of his album. one, or something. They were annoying but yet, very fascinating. They were clearly just getting used to being thirty and older then everyone. They were showing off as kid shows off the new trick they learned at school that day. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      problem point number two: Is it strange that i am at a point in my life where i am on a constant look out for that thing that'll change your life forever?Ok, keep in minf i'm going on fifteen. I was in math class today and a girl handed me her headphones and asked me to listen, so i did. I sat there, standing so that my knees might break apart and a slumped back, listening to this beautiful quitar. A man came on and started singing about how jesus shouldn't be sad and that he'd take care of jesus. I thought to myself "is this is? is this the thing?" As it turns out it wasn't. I took off the head phones and went back to making a poster on how to use parallel lines. But there's always that chance that in ten years I'll stumble across it again and remember "hey, i rember this. It changed my life."
     
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      One thing i've realised about being confused, you cannot write about being confused without using the word confused. Most emotions you can beat around the bush with synonyms and various images but not with confused, no, its special. I discoverd this last night lying awake in bed ( Insomnia has become a routine for me). I lay there, rolling over, trying to find just the right position for my ribs to jab into the springy two by four, and contemplating my present situation and i realised i was, for lack of better phrasing, i was confused. this troubled me. not because i was confused (which i often was) but that i couldn't think of any other words. All the other major emotions have plenty of synonyms but not confusing. Happy: joyous, euphoric, glad, good, etc. Angry: pissed, fuming, raging, etc. It goes on. As i pondered this for some while i finally sound myself asleep, then awake.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i am the saddest picture of a man you ever did see.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Nick Hornby is a brutally realistic writer.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      crap...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, after school, i caught the bus to the forest hill station and onward from there. Waiting at the bus stop i saw a school friend. Now, for me, if i see a person i know in an unfamiliar situation, more often then not, they will become my closest friend for however long this unfamiliar should help itself to last. We began talking. Telling jokes, talking about other peoples jokes, referencing to previous jokes of our own. This went on for sometime before i realised that, there was in fact an art to subway conversations.   First off, you gotta tell jokes. It's  requirement. It keeps the other person interested and creats an immediate and obvious response. Secondly, you have to make the joke last as long as possible and yet be able to be broken off at any moment without any loss to your friendship or conversation in the whole. Basically make it frivilous and meaningfull at the same time.  There has got to be a song about this somewhere. It's such a cultural archetype (is that an oxymoron?). I mean everyone does it. Never with their good friends. Good friends it's inside jokes and plans for later moments in time.   Thirdly: at the moment it escapes me but i'll be sure to think about it.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      There is a place in every world where things are simply different. An anomoly. The rules such as gravity just don't apply. It is not neccisarily a large space, nor is it all that small. Usually, it is just right for the purposes it needs to serve. In this world it  is  just right.  It's roughly the length and breadth of the average household. It stretches up for miles and miles, touching the itty bitty tips of the stars.  Things here are just different. The sky is not blue here. Here, it is a mixture between red and milkshake orange. It's quite a fine colour actually. In autumn it's very beautiful.  Gravity here has a bit of.... disregard for timing. Sometimes it will keep you planted to the ground as a tree but sometimes it'll send you hurtling to the sky, completely revearsing it's pull. It's really quite hard to figure when these sudden changes come about. they are, in all intents and purposes, random.  Another peculiar and immediatly noticible thing is the lack of canstace. You may walk in a space man then suddenly turn into a pie. Once you are a pie you have to: A) defend against teh large pink and turquise birds and B) somehow hop out and become yourself again. This is all very stressful but, keeping tru to it's name, it is not constant.  Also, the letter "C" is abolished. If you walk in a Calvin you turn into an Alvin. That may not seem so drastic but if you walk in a chef with the name Charles C. Camdon who constantly chews caschews your entire life is turned upside down and you become a, "Hef with the name of Harles . Amdon who onstantly hews hashews."
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The Tenderloin  Late at night when everything’s an old yellow Everybody’s tired there The old man eating alone in the Chinese restaurant The kids standing at the corner looking as menacing as they can The man who carries his home on his back Even the little Three Musketeers wrapper fluttering in the winter rain The buildings go up and up as if they’re trying to run away.  My dad walks next to me He’s my bodyguard 	Won’t let nothing touch me That’s just the way he is The way every father is Whirr kish pum-pum kish Look this way Look that Don’t worry This place is to tired to do anything 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      that was really shitty wasn't it    yeah     yes it was
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and in that moment i loved that woman in front of me i loved the way she held her pen and the way she'd look up every now and again to see what was to be seen  i don't know  sunset at dusk   it's like a ghost town. things are airy and empty.  fuck  really the only word to describe the situation and you love it  love  the way you do to me or used to you want it i want it we all want IT IT it is love  love is it and that is all
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Poets Cafe January 30th, at the School of the Arts campus in San Francisco at 555 O'shaunessy @ Portola 7:30 5-7$ no one's turned away for lack of funds Fashion Extravaganza! Literary Journal! ChapBooks! and Live Poetry Readings!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Honestly, the only thing i want to do right now is get drunk on the whisky sitting under my black desk and slit my wrists listening to the white album, something drastic like that. Nothing puts life in perspective quite like the aspect of losing it, or losing someone. This one girl i know keeps telling me, like a snake in my ear, that i should just fuck it all, fuck my love and leave her behind me. But i can't. I should. but should is not a matter of can and cannot now is it. Love love love. Love is... love is the thing that sets your free and it is also the thing that smashes your face into the cement and yells at you, "Who the fuck do you think you are?!".This is my plan for the future. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturdaynight Watching the minutes as the tick by Counting them One at a Two times Three Disagree No matter who you are IT will catch you That time That time
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      all right, i hate this blog and all it's bad writing   i think i'm going to start a new one
     
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      www.voice-box.blogspot.com  new blog
     
    
</post>


<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (0034) 659 876 076  A phone call, a phone call. It always starts with a phone call.   For a night of pleasure: a party   My hands were sweating and I was afraid my finger would slip and dial the wrong number and I'd launch into my little speech filled with words you don't usually use when you dial a wrong number or really call anyone on the phone for that matter. I was afraid some old woman named Maria, with a thick Mexican accent would pick up. She didn't. The woman who picked up had the voice of a woman you only hear in a porn. It's the sound of smoke and honey mixed with feathers and poured onto the tongue of the bustiest blond you can find. She asked me what I liked, what I was into. I told her I wanted to talk to Sylvie. She told me to wait for a moment and I heard a dull click.  I've never been put on hold before. I've called friends and they've told me to "Hold on a sec or two," but that doesn't count. It has to be the most painful experience of my life. It's like waiting for your girlfriends parents to catch you standing there jacking off while you sniff their daughters underwear. I dropped the phone. When I picked it up the woman was saying in a more annoyed tone, "Hey, are you there?" "Ye- yeah I'm here."  "I'll connect you to Sylvie."  "Tha-"   click   "nks."  There was another dull click.  "Hello," a woman's voice said. Poets have tried to describe this voice before but've always failed. It's not cute, itâ€™s not powerful. It's not slow and dull nor is it quick and tempered. It's sultry. It's passionate like every word has sex appeal. "How are you?"  I, me, and my pathetic voice of a nervous boy, "Hi."  "How are you?" She must get that a lot.  "I'm fine. And you?"  "I'm bored. Entertain me."  I freeze. I lock up. What do I do? How do I entertain the most beautiful voice in the world? "Uh ..."  "Never mind. Listen, I know why you're calling. It's fine, I don't mind. I want to take you to a party first, loosen you up." She had cultivated a Studio 54 vibe about her.  "Um, sure. Ok. I... uh, yeah that sounds great."  "Ok good. I'll meet you outside the Fox Hotel on Thursday at 8."  "Ok."  "You better be there."  "I will."   Click   That click was more forceful, like a hung up phone should be.  It's Wednesday night. Well, Thursday morning but it's all the same at the time.  I didn't actually know what kind of party it was. Whether it was black tie or a kegger at some frat boy's house. Thus, I didn't know what I would wear. One always wants to make a good impression. I opted for my black suit. Black jacket, shirt, tie, slacks, socks, and shoes (my underwear is always planned out last minute as it is.)  If there were ever the most perfect voice to body match, it would be her. She was around five nine. I couldn't tell her weight. Iâ€™m not good at that. She wore a long, simple red dress. There was a cut in the dress on her right side that went up to her knee and formed a diagonal to her left foot. She wore red high heels to match. Her hair was also red. It slid into a curl at her ear and worked into a full loop around her shoulder. Beautiful.  She saw me before I saw her but didn't indicate she noticed, or cared, I couldn't tell.  "You look nice." She said. "Better than I expected. And cuter."  "Cute?" Cute is an insult. Cute is a puppy you pet in the park when you're playing with your daughter. Cute is not... Manly.  "Yeah, better that than a lot of other things I could call you. C'mon." She took my hand and led me inside. She walks with a purpose, quick, not distracted at all by anything. She pushed the elevator button with one of those fingers that bend at the final joint. Red nails.  The elevator comes and I tried to be a gentleman and lead her inside but she just walked in, mission style.  "Push the highest button you see."  "What floor are we going to?"  "I don't know. Just push the button."  She stood leaning against the wall with her arms crossed and hands crossed, resting in her lap. Her head was lifted up as if she could see where we were going.  She doesn't speak the entire elevator ride up.  ***  She doesn't speak as we walk down the hall either. She walks a head of me, down the center.  She reaches the double doors, stops, spins and rearranges my tie. She places one hand on my cheek, smiles, then kisses my other cheek.  "You'll do fine."  She spins back into position and pushes the two doors open. Itâ€™s a perfect cinematic moment. Cut to:  A woman in a red dress pushes open two large doors. She's perfectly in line with their opening. The camera is right behind her. She walks onto a staircase overlooking a ballroom setting. The camera goes up and over her locking onto her then moving on without doing a full 180 degrees.  She walks into the crowd making her way through, kissing here, hugging there, kissing everywhere else.  "It's nice to see you again."  "And you too," she replies in hat tone that fools everyone into thinking she has a special thing with them in that moment.  "Sylvia!"  "Matthew!"   Kiss  "Let me introduce my friend. Friend, Matthew. Matthew, friend."  I stick out my hand, "Hi."  "Hello," he says to me, sliding on the 'O's, then turns to Sylvie. "I'm so glad you're here, Will's telling old war stories again, the band's playing elevator music, and everyone's convinced their drinks can bring them back to life."  She throws her head back and laughs, "Well then, I'll see what I can do. You,"  Me  "Stay here with Matthew."  Yes   If you give a safe cracker a safe and some time they can crack just about any safe. Give Sylvie a Cosmo and an entrance and she can turn a "get together" into a party.  "She's really something," I said to a guy.  "Indeed," Matthew replies sipping some sort of stylish drink that was in that year. He looks to the stage.  (O.S.) Sylvie  The French,  are glad  to die  [whisper] for love  The camera turns to the stage. Sylvie is standing in front of an old style mic. Sheâ€™s smiling. The band behind her starts playing wildly.  Everyone began to applaud.  "How old are you?" Matthew shouted over the yelling and cheering, leaning into me but still facing the stage.  "Eighteen." I said into his ear, also leaning in.  He laughs, flashing his big teeth. "Mighty young." "Legal though, right?" Pushing his hand into my chest, fingers first, "Legal."  We look back forward and continue clapping.  The he leans in again, "Is this your first?" "What?" "Will she be your first?" "Yes." "You sure?"  No   "Listen since we're on the subject of sin, here," He holds out his hand. In it lies a little white pill. "This too." Hand pulls out a flask from his inside pocket with his free hand.  I put the pill on my tongue like I learned and flipped up the cap. "Sangks." He smiles at me.  I fill my mouth and roll my head back and swallow. The shit waged war with the back of my throat and sliced long lines down the inside. "Fuck!" My eyes watered up and I keeled over, my hands clutched to my stomach.  "How fucked up have you ever been?"  "What was that?!" still bent over.  "It's the worst brandy I could find mixed with some Grey Goose. It's my special mixture used to just fuck people up."  "Oooooh fuck." He laughs at me and slaps my back then leans on me with a straight arm and crossed legs. "Does the job, eh?" I stand up and put my hands on my hips and lean back. Deep breathes. And I fall over. "What was in the, the, the," making odd circular motions with my hand, "pill." "Sugar." "Fuck you." "I know, c'mon." He holds out his hand to help me up. I grab for it but miss. I try again and get it. "Do you know where the bathroom is?" "No." I'm still keeled over. My heads not spinning or anything I'm just leaning over. I try standing straight. Oh yeah, that's why I'm keeled over.  "Lemme show you then." He holds my hand and pulls me through a mush of colour and sound.    You know life is not lived it is performed                                                                                                  No!                         She looks and she goes, 'All that glitters isâ€¦ â€™                                                              You see It is not as simple as it sounds                                                                                                                          Or seems    Yes to that and to this                                                            Thou hast slain the bound of light     "Like your hand!" I yell over the talking.  He just laughs at me, "C'mon." We push through a double door into this vast land of silver and tile. Instinctively I walk to the urinal.   Urinals are the dumbest appliances ever conceived. They're only ever found in public restrooms and there are always two kinds: the ones for adults and that one for a child.  I finish looking up and straight ahead and walk over the sink. Matthew stands against the wall, arms folded and legs crossed. He has this purple tie on. I noticed that just now. The cold water makes the hair on the back of my neck stand on end. I have dived into the arctic.   I pull down that little tab for the paper towls. It's broken. Even in high-class hotels the tab is broken. I walk out the door, or plan to anyways.  "Doyouneedtogooutthere?Staywithme." I think for a moment. Do I. DO i? do I?Doooo I?doi?  "Please?" He uses that puppy dog face that bought my last relationship a diamond necklace and a purse.  I do.   * * *  She waits for me back at the spot where she told me not to leave from.  "I told you not to leave. C'mon." Yet again I am dragged but this time away not further into. We walked up the stairs. Out the double doors. And down the hallway. Into the elevator. She presses the stop button with that same finger that bends right at the last joint 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bruise  Introduction  	A bruise is a burst blood vessel hidden under some skin. Basic scientific definitions tend to leave out the human side of things. Maybe not just scientific but all definitions, the whole race of definitions. Maybe we just walk though life trying to define things so we don't have to be bothered with the human side. Maybe it makes things easier, less human, less complicated.  	Humans are complicated. We are not the machines you read about in your kindergarten textbooks. We are a mass of tubes and organs all connected to this thing that can contemplate the small things like the opening of eyes to the big things like... God. And most of the time we fuck both of those things up by being distracted.  Ra.cism n - the notion that ones ethnic stock is superior. 	When you look at bruises you first, usually, notice the colour. It's like a painters pallet viewed through the fogged lenses of a microscope: mingling, reminiscing with all the other colours, having a little cocktail party on that space right between your eye and your brow.   The American Heritage Dictionary of the English Language doesn't in fact have the definition of homophobic.  	I believe that the definition, correct me if I'm wrong, is the fear and hatred towards people who show sexual feelings towards people of the same sex. 	 	Now step back and look at all that for a moment. Humans are hard to find in a dictionary. We usually consider things with more emotion more true, more real, but the dictionary doesn't have that at all. It has syllable breaks and parts of speech. So why do we go to it for help?   The definition of love, and may I remind you that love is probably the most sought after and revered emotion there is, is as follows: love n - 1. An intense affectionate concern for another person. 2 an intense sexual desire for another person. 	Does that do justice? Does that put into words that feeling you get in the soles of your feet to the lashes of your eyes? Does that put into words your quickness in breathing, your passion, the moisture collecting on the insides of your palms, that complete will to sacrifice anything for this person; this beloved person that you joke with yourself that you could spend your whole life with. Does that do it justice? Does it?       Chapter 1 Matthew  	I grew up without one family. I had families but I didn't have one. My parents put me up for adoption when I was three. I'd like to say they died or something, you tend to get more respect for that, but I can't. They left me. 	All my life I've bounced from house to house, roof to roof, mother to mother and nothing really stuck. Families would have financial problems themselves, or I'd be a hastle, or they'd just not like me because I couldn't replace their son.  	I was eight by the time I got an actual home to stay in. They were average. Not in the sense that they weren't exciting or anything but in the sense that they might be picked for a commercial or something.  	The Robbinsons. Each adult went to college for at least four years. Mr. Robbinson was a salesman is a salesman. He sells computer technology. He gets paid well but the trade-off is a schedule that asks for you at 9am on a Sunday and a brandy glass full of stress. Mr. Robbinson doesn't drink to excess however you construe your definition of the word. If he was feeling down or stressed, he'd drink. The title habit would better suit the task.  	Mrs. Robbinson is a teacher. She's the type of teacher that tells her students to be creative and original; and yet still subscribes to every magazine with the latest news on Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman's break up. She's a paradox. I cannot tell you who she is. I can tell you what she does.  	Jason, their son, doesn't like me. Why should he? I've taken his place. I'm not him either. I'm white, he's black. That sort of interruption and intrusion into someone's budding adolescence is bound to stir up some fury.  	This also I declined to mention. Our difference is our colour. They are a middle class black family and I am a white orphan living under their roof. I don't often travel in the neighborhood with them because I get treated like shit. I'm the white boy. You hear about racism on TV and on the news. But you only think about it as black teenagers getting beat up back in the sixties. It happens to me though. And I have neither grown up in the sixties nor am I black. It's justâ€¦ you can't be told.  *		*		*  	Matthew woke up around 5:45 everyday. He'd slip, jump or simply get out of bed. It was always dark when he woke up. If it was a clear morning you could look out and see the stars that were still out. 	The morning sky before sunrise is very beautiful. Not may people know. But it's true. The sky is a thousand different shades of blue. It slides from this deed endless blue to a nice ocean blue, the kind you see when you look down and see the rays of light grabbing your ankles. The ocean makes a frame with the darker blue in the center. The stars close their eyes, a few at a time until there's one or two left that sit there for a while, then seeing everything is ok, follow suit. The east turns red. The red you find in a blood orange. Deep, slightly purple, slightly orange. It wafts around like cotton actually.  	After Matthew wrote his little mental poem he'd get into the shower and think some more. It usually took him at least seven minutes to get around to soaping. He liked the way the water bounced off the stunted muscle in his shoulders and ran down his legs. It made him feel just a little more superior. 	In the shower he had a little system. He'd first soap his legs, usually the outside first, just because it was easier. When he got to his waist he'd stop to put some soap on his face to prevent acne. He had to wait to do this after the legs because if he bent down the water would run over his face and wash off all the soap. Then he'd rub the bar over his arms. This took time. The feeling of the bar sliding over his muscle made him feel just a little more confident. He let it sit there. If you let a layer of water wash the soap off, you're left with a nice shine that displays your muscle a little better. If you apply too much water it'll start to collect into little beads and completely ruin the look. 	After soap came shampoo. He'd take the comb out of the medicine cabinet and comb it all back, then forward, then back again. The shampoo would wash off and he'd stand there for another five minutes, water bouncing off his shoulders. Then he'd turn off the water. But on cold days he has to wait for just the right moment. The moment in which he forgets it's cold. That is the perfect moment.  	Showers are proceeded by the morning meal. Matthew has no method for this other than to choose he perfect reading material for the day. Paperback novels are always hard to read at the table because one always has to use both hands to keep one cover or the other from flipping over. Magazines, comic books, and large anthologies of... whatever, are perfect. 	Walk out the door, walk down the stairs, walk out another door, walk down more stairs and Matthew's at the street. A few more steps and he's at the bus stop. For Matthew municipal transportation is meditation in motion. No one looks at each other or really interacts; get an early enough bus and you're all alone for your entire trip. He thinks about things. One time he tried to trace his thought cycle but it didn't work. He hasn't tried it since. 	Look, see the old man in blue windbreaker and navy polo. 	Look, see the bus driver to tired to do anything other than the scheduled task afforded to him. 	Coffee and Newspapers are the deities of the morning commuter. Entire lifetimes are spent attempting to attain the kind of peace gotten from a simple morning's walk. *	*	*  Chapter 2 Fast Times  	The school doors open at seven o'clock everyday. Everyday the short Filipino man parks his van, runs across the courtyard up the stairs and opens the doors closest the office. There was always this old Asian man who stood there before the Filipino man came. He always looked so sad.  	Matthew got to school by seven everyday. With Matthew's determination to get to school early, he, over time, came earlier and earlier. He didn't do anything important with his time. He sat by his locker in another state of meditation. People would pass him in a moving mural of figures and colour but he didnâ€™t seem to notice. Sometimes people asked him why he sat there. He couldnâ€™t really answer them. He didnâ€™t know. 	"Hey" It was this tall boy. He looked like a seventeen year old wanting to look twenty and independent. "Why are you always sitting here?" 	He pulled off the look nicely. 	"iono" 	He had short brown hair, tinged with blonde and wide cheeks but a narrow, strong chin. 	"You know, getting up and talking to people is much more healthy." 	He sat down next to Matthew.  	"i guess youâ€™re right." 	"You guess." He had a military messenger bag and a pair of Adidas flip-flops. 	"yeah." 	He holds out his hand, "My name is Jude." His and already looked older. 	"Matthew." He wore a green track jacket with white and yellow stripes at the seams of each sleeve. He looked at Matthew with a smile. No teeth, just smile. Matthew looked from Jude's hand to his stubbly face. 	If you were to classify Matthew's face right now it'd probably be perplexed, but its intent was not that at all. 	All of a sudden Jude starts laughing, "Has" that bounce out of his chest. "Youâ€™re funny. I like you." 	Matthew smiles, a cute smile, like a little boy who was just complimented by his pretty teacher. 	Matthew liked Jude. 'i like you too.' 	"Listen, what're you doing for lunch?" 	"eating?" 	"No, like do you have plans." 	"oh. um, no." 	"Yoouuuuu, need plans. Is this your locker?" 	Matthew looks up. "oh, yeah." 	"Ok, I'll meet you here. Be here, ok?" 	"ok." 	"Ok?" 	Matthew squeezes out a few breaths, "ok." *	*	*  	"Ladies and gentleman, meet-" he pauses and looks from the small cluster of people to Matthew, "Matthew." 	He says Matthew the way a feather floats down on a light breeze.  	All of a sudden the mural starts talking. 	"Hey man." 	"Hi Matthew." 	"Do people ever call you Matty?" 	He just holds up his hand and mouths "hi".  	"What're we doing?" Jude says with his arm still around Matthew's shoulder, but his neck leaning out. 	A girl with short blonde hair contorted into various fountains: "Weâ€™re goin' up to get some soup." She pokes the girl next to her in a Fargo hat complete with flaps over the ears. She laughs and curls up, lifting one leg and poking her back.  	He nods in approval, "All right. Anyone else doing anything?" 	"Zachâ€™s taking me to buy pizza." 	"Joy. All right weâ€™re gonnaâ€™ go up and just sit in the sun." 	And so Matthew and Jude made their way up to the little brick wall. They talked and talked. It was more like Jude was teaching the untaught, painting a masterpiece on a blank slate.  Jude spoke all of these sweeping statements about anything and everything. 	"Never listen to Rolling Stones after three in the morning unless it is 'satisfaction' and youâ€™'e in a club or something." 	He mainly talked about cultural sorts of things. Sometimes music. Sometimes fashion. Politics. Movies. Matthew told him his life story. That was really all he could talk about. Whenever Matthew spoke Jude would stop talking and listen. And whenever Jude talked Matthew would stop talking and listen. And they talked. This was the first time Matthew was ever late for a class. It was the first time he didn't mind. 	"Whereâ€™ve you been." 	"I've been," he breathes through a smile, "talking to an important person." 	The teacher just looks at him thinking, "dumbass."  Chapter 3 Teeth   And Jacob was left alone, and a man wrestled with him until the break of dawn.  And he sad the he had not won out against him and he touched his hip-socket and Jacobâ€™s hip-socket was wretched as he wrestled with him. And he said, "Let me go, for dawn is breaking." And he said, "I will not let you go unless you bless me." And he said to him, "What is your name?" And he said, "Jacob." And he said, "Not Jacob shall your name hence be said, but Israel, for you have striven with God and men, and won out" 	 The next time Matthew walked with Jude they were rudely interrupted by a boy in a Celtics jersey and pants that didn't seem to agree with his waist. 	"What th' fuc yue doin', actin' all gedo. Yue think yue blac. Yue fuckin' aint'. Goe bac to yo' mansion. Drink yo' lemo'nade. Yue as white as mai teeth. Bich." 	Matthew saw his brother, Jason, standing behind the Celtics boy. He could clearly hear the Celtics boy. But he didn't do anything. Jude did. 	"What are you doing?" 	"Wuhs ah tahkin' t' yue?" 	"No, but I heard you. Fuck off." 	His teeth don't even move. His fist does. Matthew thought of how many miles an hour that mass of bone and muscle was traveling at. Jude gets hit in the eye. He stumbles back into the lockers. Matthew ducks down and runs into the Celtics boyâ€™s stomach, pushing into the opposite lockers. He pounds on Matthew's back. Only now did Matthew really realize how large this boy was, maybe six feet. The boy brings up a knee into Matthew's stomach and Matthew rolls onto the ground. From the ground he sees his own brother trying to take down Jude. Matthew shouts "No" but he can't hear it. He gets up and does the exact same thing to his brother that he had just done to the Celtics boy. Jude pulls Matthew off and to thank him Celtics boy punches him again. And it's over. Matthew and Jude are yet again sitting against the lockers. 	"Do you need a place to sleep tonight?" 	"yeah. if i go home he'll kill me." 	"I doubt he'd kill you." 	"he just might." 	"Really now?" 	"oh yeah. god honest truth." 	"Huh, interesting."  Chapter 4 Romeo  	They sat in Jude's room, Matthew on the bed looking off the to the side on the walls, Jude on the floor sitting against the dresser looking at the wall behind Matthew. 	Matthew turned to look at Jude. 	"whereâ€™s your bathroom?" 	He lifts his arms and points to the door. "When you get out the door, turn left. Itâ€™s the first door you see." 	"thanks." Matthew unfolds his leg from under him and walks into the bathroom. He comes back with a white washcloth steaming from warm water. He crouches down in front of Jude and starts patting around his face.  	You can look a thousand other places on a personâ€™s face other than their eyes. 	Matthew pats the cuts on Jude's lips. 	"you know, chicks are into body damage" Matthew says just above a whisper. 	"I'm not into chicks." Matthew stops mid pat for a slight second and continues. "Good Pilgrim, you do wrong your hand too much, which mannerly devotion shows in this." 	Matthew smiles. He looks again off to the side and his cheeks flush. Jude chases him with his face leaning around to look him in the eye, smiling proudly. He gently grabs onto Matthew's hand and lowers it. Watching it the entire way.  	"O then, dear saint, let, lips do what hands do." And Jude kisses him. "Then have my lips the sin that they have took." 	"sin from my lips? O trespass sweetly urg'd, give me my sin again." And they kiss again, kissing until it is unclear where one begins and the other ends and who gives and who receives. It was not a wealth of passion or lust. It was a warm feeling.  	 *	*	*  	That night, Matthew lay on the bed and Jude lay on the floor. At one point Matthew peeked over the side of the bed down at Jude. Jude lay there, with his hands clasped at the base of his head. Neither were asleep so he crept down and lay his head on Judeâ€™s stomach.  Chapter 5 Montage  	Over the next few weeks, Matthew and Jude were, to the world, the best of friends, inseparable. They would eat lunch, talking to each other more than eating their meals. It wasn't banter anymore. They talked about important things, but they also talked gossip. Matthew was pleased. He felt happy now. 	It wasn't that Matthew was unhappy before, but Matthew now was feeling something he had never felt before. He could only describe it as such. 	Happy.  Chapter 6 Times at Home  	When Matthew was about six he lived with a young couple, fresh out of college. They were idealistic types. They thought that maybe they could actually change the world with their votes. They didn't wear Gap or drink Coke. They were complainers, but they were happy. Matthew lived with them for a year. 	Every Saturday morning the man, Adam, would clean house while his partner was out at work. Matthew remembered sitting on the floor with crossed legs in the patch of sun that streamed through the windows, watching Adam clean everything, up and down, listening and singing along to R.E.M.'s Automatic for the People. Sometimes Matthew would get up and help. Mostly he liked to watch, he'd take in more that way. He wanted to be like this man. He was kind and caring. He was calm and patient with Matthew, teaching him new things whenever he could. He was the only father Matthew would ever have. 	One Saturday his partner came home crying, sobbing into her hands. Adam dropped his cloth and ran to her. He put his hands on either shoulder and bent over to look into her face, asking what's wrong. She just grabbed him, shoving her face into his chest.  	"Whatâ€™s wrong?" He asked, over and over again. "It'll be ok." And he gently took her into their bedroom to lay her down. He didn't come out for another twenty minutes. And when he did, Matthew was able to see his blonde facial hair against his skin.  	Matthew ran up to him, "It's ok Adam. Itâ€™s ok." And Adam melted onto the couch. Matthew crouched next to it, with his nose peeking over the side. 	The next month, Matthew was moved to an agency, and in another month or so he'd moved to a different house. Adamâ€™s partner had lost her job. He never saw Adam again.  Chapter 7 Sweetness Follows  	"Did you know that Irish people used to be considered black?" Matthew boasts eagerly to show off his new knowledge. He skips ahead a few steps as he and Jude walk up to their usual spot during lunch. "Yeah, when they first came to America everyone hated them because they took jobs." 	"Interesting." Jude breathed, looking behind him. 	"There were so many. I wonder if my family came over in the first few waves." 	"How do you know youâ€™re Irish?" 	"I don't know. Someone told me one day. I guess I just accepted it. It was probably a doctor." 	"Yeah." again, looking away. "Matthew, I can't eat with you today." 	Matthew stops a few feet away, and turns around, and looks at Jude. Jude stands there skimming the area, then puts his hands in his pockets. "Why not?" 	"I'm supposed to meet someone." 	"Who?" 	"Abel." 	"Abel?" 	"Yes, Abel." 	"Iâ€™ve never met him." 	Jude doesn't say anything for a moment. He turns away from Matthew and folds his arms. Matthew steps to his side. "What's wrong?" 	"Nothing, nothing." 	"Well then why do you look so glum?" 	He turns around, "He and I are together now. I won't be eating with you anymore. Iâ€™m sorry but Iâ€¦" and he trails off. He takes a few breaths in but thatâ€™s all he manages. Matthew is puzzled; less puzzled and more scared.  	"I love you Jude." 	Jude looks away again and mumbles out a few laughs; nervous laughs; laughs that say sorry. Sorry I cannot return yourâ€¦  	"Jude?" 	"no." 	"Juude?" 	"NO MATTHEW! NO! no." 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Journalist Diary  March 19th, 2003  When you look at a city the first moment you walk in, nothing is different. Itâ€™s a city. You see the buildings, and the cars. The people and their dogs, their cats. You see their faces. Itâ€™s a city. Nothing special. But live there a while and youâ€™ll see a whole new world. An underground if you will. But itâ€™s not underground its above ground. Itâ€™s in the houses. In the people and their cats and dogs. Live there a bit longer and youâ€™ll get sucked in. You begin to love it as your own home. Itâ€™s not a love of passion or of brotherhood but this devotion to a cause. The people become your friends. You fall in love with someone. Or maybe something. Like the coffee shop you go to every morning. Itâ€™s always the same person who serves you, always, the same cup of coffee. When I first started this job, this man came up to me and gave me a word of advice. â€œNever cover a war in a foreign country.â€ I never saw him again. Occasionally Iâ€™d hear about him. He moved back to Vietnam, his first love. I donâ€™t know what he saw in that place. Whether it was the trees, the people, their pets, or that special smell of napalm in the morning. Saigon. Itâ€™s funny though. My picture of Vietnam is choppers landing in plains of tall grass and G.I.s running out to the tune of Hendrixâ€™s, â€œAll Along the Watchtowerâ€. This is what my generation thinks Vietnam is. Was.  	I kissed my girlfriend goodbye today. It was a touching moment. When you watch movies and see one of those moments, you are a bit touched, but itâ€™s nothing special. You want to see Martin Sheen and his group of men having promiscuous sex with Playboy bunnies. She was crying. She was sad. I was sad. It was a doorway of sad. Then it became a car of sad. Then an airport of sad. The security guards checked me. My shoes had to be taken off. She was still watching me when they pulled out the baton. â€œNever can be to careful,â€ she said, â€œRight?â€ When I got past them I reached into one of my pockets and realized I had a pocketknife in there. Those sorts of things make me feel nice and cozy on a long plane trip. My friends always say the government is incompetent and greedy. â€œJust trying to win votes!â€ they say. I donâ€™t know. They donâ€™t either. They wouldnâ€™t though. The closest they ever get to the government is when they file their taxes every April. They donâ€™t put their lives in the hands of these men and women. The reason I carry a pocketknife is for my camera. I use it to open it sometimes. To unscrew things. Even thought youâ€™re not supposed to I do it anyway. Itâ€™s just easier that way than to carry around a screwdriver.  â€œThey say you understand a lot in a few minutes, when you come to Vietnam, the rest you learn from experience.â€  	I grew up in the city. Iâ€™ve never heard a gunshot. I donâ€™t think Iâ€™ve ever seen a gun. The ones cops carry around donâ€™t count, theyâ€™re always holstered and well strapped in. When I was a kid I was at a cop station and they told us that the gun was a last resort after pepper spray and the nightstick and a few other things. Our president obviously never went on the same field trip as I did. But I canâ€™t say anything. These men are loyal to him. After all, they did volunteer. This is no draft. Thank god for that. But Iâ€™d be there either way. Back in the eighties, I used to read the Doonsburry cartoons, with the whole series in Iraq. I remember one in particular. A higher officer came into the tent and gave that guy with the helmet bottles of water. I think it was a hundred. Something like that. He said you had to drink it all, and if you didnâ€™t youâ€™d die. I hope not. I hope not. Iâ€™ve covered this whole event ever since it started. Iâ€™ve read every major newspaper, watched every magazine news show, talked to every right wing â€œpatriotâ€ and every left wing â€œradicalâ€. I guess I did kinda of ask for this position. I didnâ€™t think Iâ€™d be here, sitting on a plane, ready for takeoff, with soldiers sitting on either side of me. Thereâ€™s this speech in one of Shakespear's plays on one of the King Henrys. Itâ€™s a spectacular speech. â€œBand of Brothers.â€ These men will be my brothers. I will love them.    *					*						*  Dear Sarah, 	This might seem extreme to you but to me itâ€™s real. If I die I donâ€™t want to have died without telling you the things I want you to know when I do die. I love you. Keep this Diary. Iâ€™ll tell you all that I can. Iâ€™ll tell you what I see and what I hear. If I get inspired Iâ€™ll write some poetry, I promise. I still donâ€™t know why you love it so much; itâ€™s not that great. Iâ€™m no Robert Frost. But I know how much it means to you so Iâ€™ll make the effort. Iâ€™m at a loss for words right now. If I think of anything else you should know, Iâ€™ll write it down. I love you.   *					*						*  â€œThis is war. Youâ€™re in it. It gets, you knowâ€¦ basic.â€ 					Talking about war. 					Vietnam 					Sawing leg off. 					â€œWho carries the  					leg out?â€ 	â€œIt doesnâ€™t fucking matter  	who takes the leg out. You 	saw it get sawed off. Thatâ€™s 	what matters.â€ â€“ Dr.  How far do you go? ----------------------------------------------------------------  Soldier Diary  I remember watching war movies when I was a kid. They were mostly about Vietnam, you know? They always had a grotesque amount of violence and an old wise soldier. Heâ€™d always have a great monologue. We donâ€™t have any wise men here. We donâ€™t even have a monologue. So I guess I just wanted to start one.  	Itâ€™s different than every other war. There isnâ€™t a guy in the chopper screaming, â€œGO, GO, GO!â€, with the sand billowing up and bouncing off his goggles and biting his skin. Just this quiet tension and the low thump thump thump. Our guns are loaded and our heads are lowered and weâ€™re just sitting there. No one talks much. Only when they have to. Thereâ€™s no bravado or pep talks to raise morale. Itâ€™s just sand. For as far as the eye can see.  	Weâ€™re more like pirates here than soldiers. We strike swiftly and quietly, take what we want, then leave. Weâ€™re the fastest shadows youâ€™ll ever meet. 	Every chance we get, weâ€™ll turn on the tv so see what we can find out about whatâ€™s going on at home. Theyâ€™re all covering us though. Weâ€™re launched back where we were in the first place. It feels like everyoneâ€™s deserted us then put us on display.  	The shows are all talking about the politics. We arenâ€™t supposed to listen to the politics, just take orders. Weâ€™re not supposed to care whether or not Mr. Hussein is a good guy or a bad guy. Weâ€™re just supposed to get him.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (Untitled)  Safety helmet boom box And Voice box synchronicity 	On air warning 			Of 		Pornstar catacombs 			And 		Dictionary definitions on unknown cacophonous words Thees are my dreams. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cereal  I woke up this morning and sat down at the breakfast table I ate a bowl of cereal I moved the spoon towards me, stirring up the milk and scrapping the bottom My dad told me that when I dine with the Queen that I will have to move away from myself That I will have to move above the bottom These are the lessons one teaches to his son.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Beat Poem/ Universe  What you donâ€™t see is the dehydrated retina in the middle of a polyeurothane wheel, spinning through time, space and all that is this life, this dimension, is,  gold on a brown bull ear, hearing the sounds of so long ago.  It melts into a calf.  Progression of devolution through time.  It is a sparrow now, with red and orange feathers spreading out like oriental fans. They are simply complex and perpetually still.  Everything is nothing.  Nothing is everything.  Stacked as toy blocks in a puddle of lights.  I am the master of the universe.  Black holes swallow me whole, spitting me out like a bad shroom trip, creating, perpetuating tea leaves.  Mount Everest is too high.  I vote it should be shorter,  So that I can see the top. What you donâ€™t know is, Is that God sits on the top Like Buddha in a ten foot cell, Tripping on paoti. God is high. We are all high.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two days ago,  I sat on a pier, looking over the ocean. I saw a pelican fly down and sit upon a wooden beam sticking up from the sea. He threw his head back and downed what i thought to be a fish and flew off into the rising sun in the middle of the night. But that was two days ago. Now its flys past me in reverse telling me all the same stories all in the same way.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Norah's fuckin' hot!
     
    
</post>


<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Introduction  	A bruise is a burst blood vessel hidden under some skin. Basic scientific definitions tend to leave out the human side of things. Maybe not just scientific but all definitions, the whole race of definitions. Maybe we just walk though life trying to define things so we donâ€™t have to be bothered with the human side. Maybe it makes things easier, less human, less complicated.  	Humans are complicated. We are not the machines you read about in your kindergarten textbooks. We are a mass of tubes and organs all connected to this thing that can contemplate the small things like the opening of eyes to the big things likeâ€¦ God. And most of the time we fuck both of those things up by being distracted.  Ra.cism n â€“ the notion that ones ethnic stock is superior. 	When you look at bruises you first, usually, notice the colour. Itâ€™s like a painters pallet viewed through the fogged lenses of a microscope: mingling, reminiscing with all the other colours, having a little cocktail party on that space right between your eye and your brow.   The American Heritage Dictionary of the English Language doesnâ€™t in fact have the definition of homophobic.  	I believe that the definition, correct me if Iâ€™m wrong, is the fear and hatred towards people who show sexual feelings towards people of the same sex. 	 	Now step back and look at all that for a moment. Humans are hard to find in a dictionary. We usually consider things with more emotion more true, more real, but the dictionary doesnâ€™t have that at all. It has syllable breaks and parts of speech. So why do we go to it for help?   The definition of love, and may I remind you that love is probably the most sought after and revered emotion there is, is as follows: love n â€“ 1. An intense affectionate concern for another person. 2 an intense sexual desire for another person. 	Does that do justice? Does that put into words that feeling you get in the soles of your feet to the lashes of your eyes? Does that put into words your quickness in breathing, your passion, the moisture collecting on the insides of your palms, that complete will to sacrifice anything for this person; this beloved person that you joke with yourself that you could spend your whole life with. Does that do it justice? Does it?       Chapter 1 Matthew  	I grew up without one family. I had families but I didnâ€™t have one. My parents put me up for adoption when I was three. Iâ€™d like to say they died or something, you tend to get more respect for that, but I canâ€™t. They left me. 	All my life Iâ€™ve bounced from house to house, roof to roof, mother to mother and nothing really stuck. Families would have financial problems themselves, or Iâ€™d be a hastle, or theyâ€™d just not like me because I couldnâ€™t replace their son.  	I was eight by the time I got an actual home to stay in. They were average. Not in the sense that they werenâ€™t exciting or anything but in the sense that they might be picked for a commercial or something.  	The Robbinsons. Each adult went to college for at least four years. Mr. Robbinson was a salesman is a salesman. He sells computer technology. He gets paid well but the trade-off is a schedule that asks for you at 9am on a Sunday and a brandy glass full of stress. Mr. Robbinson doesnâ€™t drink to excess however you construe your definition of the word. If he was feeling down or stressed, heâ€™d drink. The title habit would better suit the task.  	Mrs. Robbinson is a teacher. Sheâ€™s the type of teacher that tells her students to be creative and original; and yet still subscribes to every magazine with the latest news on Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidmanâ€™s break up. Sheâ€™s a paradox. I cannot tell you who she is. I can tell you what she does.  	Jason, their son, doesnâ€™t like me. Why should he? Iâ€™ve taken his place. Iâ€™m not him either. Iâ€™m white, heâ€™s black. That sort of interruption and intrusion into someoneâ€™s budding adolescence is bound to stir up some fury.  	This also I declined to mention. Our difference is our colour. They are a middle class black family and I am a white orphan living under their roof. I donâ€™t often travel in the neighborhood with them because I get treated like shit. Iâ€™m the white boy. You hear about racism on TV and on the news. But you only think about it as black teenagers getting beat up back in the sixties. It happens to me though. And I have neither grown up in the sixties nor am I black. Itâ€™s justâ€¦ you canâ€™t be told.  *		*		*  	Matthew woke up around 5:45 everyday. Heâ€™d slip, jump or simply get out of bed. It was always dark when he woke up. If it was a clear morning you could look out and see the stars that were still out. 	The morning sky before sunrise is very beautiful. Not may people know. But itâ€™s true. The sky is a thousand different shades of blue. It slides from this deed endless blue to a nice ocean blue, the kind you see when you look down and see the rays of light grabbing your ankles. The ocean makes a frame with the darker blue in the center. The stars close their eyes, a few at a time until thereâ€™s one or two left that sit there for a while, then seeing everything is ok, follow suit. The east turns red. The red you find in a blood orange. Deep, slightly purple, slightly orange. It wafts around like cotton actually.  	After Matthew wrote his little mental poem heâ€™d get into the shower and think some more. It usually took him at least seven minutes to get around to soaping. He liked the way the water bounced off the stunted muscle in his shoulders and ran down his legs. It made him feel just a little more superior. 	In the shower he had a little system. Heâ€™d first soap his legs, usually the outside first, just because it was easier. When he got to his waist heâ€™d stop to put some soap on his face to prevent acne. He had to wait to do this after the legs because if he bent down the water would run over his face and wash off all the soap. Then heâ€™d rub the bar over his arms. This took time. The feeling of the bar sliding over his muscle made him feel just a little more confident. He let it sit there. If you let a layer of water wash the soap off, youâ€™re left with a nice shine that displays your muscle a little better. If you apply too much water itâ€™ll start to collect into little beads and completely ruin the look. 	After soap came shampoo. Heâ€™d take the comb out of the medicine cabinet and comb it all back, then forward, then back again. The shampoo would wash off and heâ€™d stand there for another five minutes, water bouncing off his shoulders. Then heâ€™d turn off the water. But on cold days he has to wait for just the right moment. The moment in which he forgets itâ€™s cold. That is the perfect moment.  	Showers are proceeded by the morning meal. Matthew has no method for this other than to choose he perfect reading material for the day. Paperback novels are always hard to read at the table because one always has to use both hands to keep one cover or the other from flipping over. Magazines, comic books, and large anthologies ofâ€¦ whatever, are perfect. 	Walk out the door, walk down the stairs, walk out another door, walk down more stairs and Matthewâ€™s at the street. A few more steps and heâ€™s at the bus stop. For Matthew municipal transportation is meditation in motion. No one looks at each other or really interacts; get an early enough bus and youâ€™re all alone for your entire trip. He thinks about things. One time he tried to trace his thought cycle but it didnâ€™t work. He hasnâ€™t tried it since. 	Look, see the old man in blue windbreaker and navy polo. 	Look, see the bus driver to tired to do anything other than the scheduled task afforded to him. 	Coffee and Newspapers are the deities of the morning commuter. Entire lifetimes are spent attempting to attain the kind of peace gotten from a simple morningâ€™s walk. *	*	*  Chapter 2 Fast Times  	The school doors open at seven oâ€™clock everyday. Everyday the short Filipino man parks his van, runs across the courtyard up the stairs and opens the doors closest the office. There was always this old Asian man who stood there before the Filipino man came. He always looked so sad.  	Matthew got to school by seven everyday. With Matthewâ€™s determination to get to school early, he, over time, came earlier and earlier. He didnâ€™t do anything important with his time. He sat by his locker in another state of meditation. People would pass him in a moving mural of figures and colour but he didnâ€™t seem to notice. Sometimes people asked him why he sat there. He couldnâ€™t really answer them. He didnâ€™t know. 	â€œHeyâ€ It was this tall boy. He looked like a seventeen year old wanting to look twenty and independent. â€œWhy are you always sitting here?â€ 	He pulled off the look nicely. 	â€œionoâ€ 	He had short brown hair, tinged with blonde and wide cheeks but a narrow, strong chin. 	â€œYou know, getting up and talking to people is much more healthy.â€ 	He sat down next to Matthew.  	â€œi guess youâ€™re right.â€ 	â€œYou guess.â€ He had a military messenger bag and a pair of Adidas flip-flops. 	â€œyeah.â€ 	He holds out his hand, â€œMy name is Jude.â€ His and already looked older. 	â€œMatthew.â€ He wore a green track jacket with white and yellow stripes at the seams of each sleeve. He looked at Matthew with a smile. No teeth, just smile. Matthew looked from Judeâ€™s hand to his stubbly face. 	If you were to classify Matthewâ€™s face right now itâ€™d probably be perplexed, but its intent was not that at all. 	All of a sudden Jude starts laughing, â€œHasâ€ that bounce out of his chest. â€œYouâ€™re funny. I like you.â€ 	Matthew smiles, a cute smile, like a little boy who was just complimented by his pretty teacher. 	Matthew liked Jude. â€œi like you too.â€ 	â€œListen, whatâ€™re you doing for lunch?â€ 	â€œeating?â€  	â€œNo, like do you have plans.â€ 	â€œoh. um, no.â€ 	â€œYoouuuuu, need plans. Is this your locker?â€ 	Matthew looks up. â€œoh, yeah.â€ 	â€œOk, Iâ€™ll meet you here. Be here, ok?â€ 	â€œok.â€  	â€œOk?â€ 	Matthew squeezes out a few breaths, â€œok.â€ *	*	*  	â€œLadies and gentleman, meet-â€ he pauses and looks from the small cluster of people to Matthew, â€œMatthew.â€ 	He says Matthew the way a feather floats down on a light breeze.  	All of a sudden the mural starts talking. 	â€œHey man.â€ 	â€œHi Matthew.â€ 	â€œDo people ever call you Matty?â€  	He just holds up his hand and mouths â€œhiâ€.  	â€œYou two look the same.â€ Someone said. Jude looked down at his protÃ©gÃ©, â€œHeâ€™s my little brother.â€ And then in a softer voice, â€œMy own little brother.â€ Giving a short kiss on Matthewsâ€™s head then ruffling his hair. 	â€œWhatâ€™re we doing?â€ Jude says with his arm still around Matthewâ€™s shoulder, but his neck leaning out. 	A girl with short blonde hair contorted into various fountains: â€œWeâ€™re goinâ€™ up to get some soup.â€ She pokes the girl next to her in a Fargo hat complete with flaps over the ears. She laughs and curls up, lifting one leg and poking her back.  	He nods in approval, â€œAll right. Anyone else doing anything?â€ 	â€œZachâ€™s taking me to buy pizza.â€ 	â€œJoy. All right weâ€™re gonnaâ€™ go up and just sit in the sun.â€ 	And so Matthew and Jude made their way up to the little brick wall. They talked and talked. It was more like Jude was teaching the untaught, painting a masterpiece on a blank slate.  Jude spoke all of these sweeping statements about anything and everything. 	â€œNever listen to Rolling Stones after three in the morning unless it is â€˜satisfactionâ€™ and youâ€™re in a club or something.â€ 	He mainly talked about cultural sorts of things. Sometimes music. Sometimes fashion. Politics. Movies. Matthew told him his life story. That was really all he could talk about. Whenever Matthew spoke Jude would stop talking and listen. And whenever Jude talked Matthew would stop talking and listen. And they talked. This was the first time Matthew was ever late for a class. It was the first time he didnâ€™t mind. 	â€œWhereâ€™ve you been.â€ 	â€œIâ€™ve been,â€ he breathes through a smile, â€œtalking to an important person.â€ 	The teacher just looks at him thinking, â€dumbass.â€  Chapter 3 Teeth  And Jacob was left alone, and a man wrestled with him until the break of dawn.  And he sad the he had not won out against him and he touched his hip-socket and Jacobâ€™s hip-socket was wretched as he wrestled with him. And he said, â€œLet me go, for dawn is breaking.â€ And he said, â€œI will not let you go unless you bless me.â€ And he said to him, â€œWhat is your name?â€ And he said, â€œJacob.â€ And he said, â€œNot Jacob shall your name hence be said, but Israel, for you have striven with God and men, and won outâ€ 	 The next time Matthew walked with Jude they were rudely interrupted by a boy in a Celtics jersey and pants that didnâ€™t seem to agree with his waist. 	â€œWhat thâ€™ fuc yue doinâ€™, actinâ€™ all gedo. Yue think yue blac. Yue fuckinâ€™ aintâ€™. Goe bac to yoâ€™ mansion. Drink yoâ€™ lemoâ€™nade. Yue as white as mai teeth. Bich.â€ 	Matthew saw his brother, Jason, standing behind the Celtics boy. He could clearly hear the Celtics boy. But he didnâ€™t do anything. Jude did. 	â€œWhat are you doing?â€ 	â€œWuhs ah tahkinâ€™ tâ€™ yue?â€ 	â€œNo, but I heard you. Fuck off.â€ 	His teeth donâ€™t even move. His fist does. Matthew thought of how many miles an hour that mass of bone and muscle was traveling at. Jude gets hit in the eye. He stumbles back into the lockers. Matthew ducks down and runs into the Celtics boyâ€™s stomach, pushing into the opposite lockers. He pounds on Matthewâ€™s back. Only now did Matthew really realize how large this boy was, maybe six feet. The boy brings up a knee into Matthewâ€™s stomach and Matthew rolls onto the ground. From the ground he sees his own brother trying to take down Jude. Matthew shouts no but he canâ€™t hear it. He gets up and does the exact same thing to his brother that he had just done to the Celtics boy. Jude pulls Matthew off and to thank him Celtics boy punches him again. And itâ€™s over. Matthew and Jude are yet again sitting against the lockers. 	â€œDo you need a place to sleep tonight?â€ 	â€œyeah. if i go home heâ€™ll kill me.â€ 	â€œI doubt heâ€™d kill you.â€ 	â€œhe just might.â€ 	â€œReally now?â€™ 	â€œoh yeah. god honest truth.â€ 	â€œHuh, interesting.â€   Chapter 4 Romeo  	They sat in Judeâ€™s room, Matthew on the bed looking off the to the side on the walls, Jude on the floor sitting against the dresser looking at the wall behind Matthew. 	Matthew turned to look at Jude. 	â€œwhereâ€™s your bathroom?â€ 	He lifts his arms and points to the door. â€œWhen you get out the door, turn left. Itâ€™s the first door you see.â€ 	â€œthanks.â€ Matthew unfolds his leg from under him and walks into the bathroom. He comes back with a white washcloth steaming from warm water. He crouches down in front of Jude and starts patting around his face.  	You can look a thousand other places on a personâ€™s face other than their eyes. 	Matthew pats the cuts on Judeâ€™s lips. 	â€œyou know, chicks are into body damageâ€ Matthew says just above a whisper. 	â€œIâ€™m not into chicks.â€ Matthew stops mid pat for a slight second and continues. â€œGood Pilgrim, you do wrong your hand too much, which mannerly devotion shows in this.â€ 	Matthew smiles. He looks again off to the side and his cheeks flush. Jude chases him with his face leaning around to look him in the eye, smiling proudly. He gently grabs onto Matthewâ€™s hand and lowers it. Watching it the entire way.  	â€œO then, dear saint, let, lips do what hands do.â€ And Jude kisses him. â€œThen have my lips the sin that they have took.â€ 	â€œsin from my lips? O trespass sweetly urgâ€™d, give me my sin again.â€ And they kiss again, kissing until it is unclear where one begins and the other ends and who gives and who receives. It was not a wealth of passion or lust. It was a warm feeling.  	 *	*	*  	That night, Matthew lay on the bed and Jude lay on the floor. At one point Matthew peeked over the side of the bed down at Jude. Jude lay there, with his hands clasped at the base of his head. Neither were asleep so he crept down and lay his head on Judeâ€™s stomach.  Chapter 5  	Matthew and Jude. It is not carved in a tree. It is not scrawled on a stuffed heart. It is not sent along with a bouquet of roses. It is not Lifetime. It is not Hallmark. 	It is oneâ€™s affection for the other. It is laughs at stolen jokes. It is common disliking of dislikable characters. It is ones tardiness. It is ones love to another. *	*	*  Chapter 6 Times at Home  	When Matthew was about six he lived with a young couple, fresh out of college. They were idealistic types. They thought that maybe they could actually change the world with their votes. They didnâ€™t wear Gap or drink Coke. They were complainers, but they were happy. Matthew lived with them for a year. 	Every Saturday morning the man, Adam, would clean house while his partner was out at work. Matthew remembered sitting on the floor with crossed legs in the patch of sun that streamed through the windows, watching Adam clean everything, up and down, listening and singing along to R.E.M.â€™s Automatic for the People. Sometimes Matthew would get up and help. Mostly he liked to watch, heâ€™d take in more that way. He wanted to be like this man. He was kind and caring. He was calm and patient with Matthew, teaching him new things whenever he could. He was the only father Matthew would ever have. 	One Saturday his partner came home crying, sobbing into her hands. Adam dropped his cloth and ran to her. He put his hands on either shoulder and bent over to look into her face, asking whatâ€™s wrong. She just grabbed him, shoving her face into his chest.  	â€œWhatâ€™s wrong?â€ He asked, over and over again. â€œItâ€™ll be ok.â€ And he gently took her into their bedroom to lay her down. He didnâ€™t come out for another twenty minutes. And when he did, Matthew was able to see his blonde facial hair against his skin.  	Matthew ran up to him, â€œItâ€™s ok Adam. Itâ€™s ok.â€ And Adam melted onto the couch. Matthew crouched next to it, with his nose peeking over the side. 	The next month, Matthew was moved to an agency, and in another month or so heâ€™d moved to a different house. Adamâ€™s partner had lost her job. He never saw Adam again.  Chapter 7 Sweetness Follows  	â€œDid you know that Irish people used to be considered black?â€ Matthew boasts eagerly to show off his new knowledge. He skips ahead a few steps as he and Jude walk up to their usual spot during lunch. â€œYeah, when they first came to America everyone hated them because they took jobs.â€ 	â€œInteresting.â€ Jude breathed, looking behind him. 	â€œThere were so many. I wonder if my family came over in the first few waves.â€ 	â€œHow do you know youâ€™re Irish?â€ 	â€œI donâ€™t know. Someone told me one day. I guess I just accepted it. It was probably a doctor.â€ 	â€œYeah.â€ again, looking away. â€œMatthew, I canâ€™t eat with you today.â€ 	Matthew stops a few feet away, and turns around, and looks at Jude. Jude stands there skimming the area, then puts his hands in his pockets. â€œWhy not?â€ 	â€œIâ€™m supposed to meet someone.â€ 	â€œWho?â€ 	â€œAbel.â€ 	â€œAbel?â€ 	â€œYeah.â€ 	â€œIâ€™ve never met him.â€ 	Jude doesnâ€™t say anything for a moment. He turns away from Matthew and folds his arms. Matthew steps to his side. â€œWhatâ€™s wrong?â€ 	â€œNothing, nothing.â€ 	â€œWell then why do you look so glum?â€ 	He turns around, â€œHe and I are together now. I wonâ€™t be eating with you anymore. Iâ€™m sorry but Iâ€¦â€ and he trails off. He takes a few breaths in but thatâ€™s all he manages. Matthew is puzzled; less puzzled and more scared.  	â€œI love you Jude.â€ 	Jude looks away again and mumbles out a few laughs; nervous laughs; laughs that say sorry. Sorry I cannot return yourâ€¦  	â€œJude?â€ 	â€œno.â€ 	â€œJuude?â€ 	â€œNO MATTHEW! NO! no.â€  
    
</post>


<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The title is in Times New-Roman across the screen. Itâ€™s simple. A little squished on the top. Itâ€™s in white. All the words fade in unison except â€œrougeâ€ which fades into red as it fades out, slower than the rest.   (O.S.) Man: I apologize in advance for I canâ€™t tell you exactly what happened that night.  The camera pans in a crescent left slowly revealing a man hunched over a chair with his back facing us. His shoulder is revealed. Itâ€™s a low angle, looking up. Heâ€™s tight and well built, like an athlete. Across from him is a man in a suit. His jacket is slung over his chair. Heâ€™s walking behind it, dragging his fingers along the back of the chair. He owns the chair.  Man: (steady) I do not know what happened in detail, nor do I remember the night after. All I remember is the taste of my cigarette as I sat on a sink looking at nothing. What I tell you is a story pieced together by what Iâ€™ve been told and my knowledge of the characters.   When the camera passes behind the man in the chair and moves on the cop disappears. In his place a woman in a red dress walks out of the shadows. Her dress is simple. Spaghetti straps and the rest basically is a red covering of her figure, tall and thin. But not to tall and not to thin. Her hair is red. Her lips are red. Her nails are red. She is the woman in the red dress. She is Sylvie.  M:  Do you have a cigarette?   Cop: Sure  The cop pulls a pack out from his right pocket and pushes out a singular cigarette.   Cop: What happened?  M: (laughs nervously/ embarrassed) A phone call I suppose. Itâ€™s always a phone call.  Looks up and takes a draft.  M: (Half to himself) It always starts with a phone call.   Cut to: INT: Mans room (blue scheme). A telephone sits at the left side of the screen on a table. The camera is right next to the phone so it appears very large. On the right, out of focus is a man. He has his arm pinned against a window as he looks out. The man walks back to the phone and dials but all you see of him in focus is his hand, the rest is off screen.   Cop: (O.F.) Excuse me?  The man in his room stands back in the same position by the window except his unused hand now holds the phone while the other supports him.   M: [looks down again, ignoring the question] (O.F.) I live next door to this guy. Patch of bald on the top of his head and a white collar every morning. Heâ€™s maybe in his mid forties early fifties. I moved in there a few years back. Big house, one of those neighborhoods full of them. I figured heâ€™d been living there for some time. I mean a guy like him doesnâ€™t hop from house to house. Heâ€™s like a married man.   He walks off screen.  Cut to: shot of a cigarette as itâ€™s inhaled. The man takes a drag on his cigarette.  M: He called her one night.   Laughs to himself with his head down and a big grin.  M: She was so beautiful. Even over the phone you knew she was beautiful. Her voice was like something youâ€™d find in a homely chocolate shop.   The screen cuts to a diagonal shot looking down, from the upper right side of her head. All we see are her lips as she talks, muted.  The screen cuts back to a landscape shot of the man still sitting in his chair.  M: And thatâ€™s just her voice.   Cop: (O.S.) What was her name?  M: Sylvia but people called her Sylvie. People like Sylvie more.  Cut to: INT of another manâ€™s room. This is Johnâ€™s room. He is the first mans neighbor. Itâ€™s a white room. We see a landscape shot of it. In the center of the room (right half of camera) is his bed. It has deep red sheets. In the left corner of his room is a large light used for lighting photo shoots. On a tripod about eight feet away from it is a camcorder. On the wall at the head of the bed is a small collection of thumb tacked magazine pages. One of them is Marilyn Monroeâ€™s Playboy cover. They are all red based. In slow motion Sylvie pulls John onto the bed by his red tie. She is in lingerie and he is in a white, collar shirt, black slacks and red tie. He places his knee between her spread legs and leans forward, putting his hands on either side of her.   Cut to: INT of the Mans room. Heâ€™s pacing the room with his phone. (Throughout this shot the audience can never see his face.)   Sylvie: (O.F.) Hello, howâ€™re you?  Man: [nervous boyish voice] Hi.  Sylvie: (O.F.) Howâ€™re you?  Man: Oh  He laughs a nervous laugh.  Man: Iâ€™m fine. And you?  Sylvie: (O.F.) Iâ€™m bored. Entertain me.   Man: Iâ€¦  He stops pacing. No one speaks for a moment. Then Sylvie moans very quietly.  Sylvie: (O.F.) Never mind. Listen, I know why youâ€™re calling. I donâ€™t mind but Iâ€™d like to take you to a party first, to loosen you up. Would you like that?  Man: Oh, yeah sure. That sounds great.   Sylvie: (O.F.) Do you know the Cardinal hotel?  Man: Yeah.  Sylvie: (O.F.) Meet me there, Thursday at eight oâ€™clock.   Man: Ok.  Sylvie: (O.F.)  You better be there.  Man: I will.  Sylvie: (O.F.) Good.  A click is heard and the Man tosses the phone onto his bed.   Cut to: EXT. of the mans house. He walks out of his doorway. We still canâ€™t really see his face. He walks past the camera and down the street.  Cut to: Sylvie walks onto a staircase overlooking a ballroom setting and places both her hands on the banister. She wears a long, simple red dress. There is a cut in the dress on her right side that goes up to her knee and forms a diagonal to her left foot. She wears red high heels to match. Her hair is also red. It slides into a curl at her ear and works into a full loop around her shoulder. The camera goes up and over her locking onto her then moving on without doing a full 180 degrees. In front of the staircase is a sea of people, all in nice clothing; predominantly black (clothing). There is the noise of a hundred and some people chattering away; also vague music. She walks into the crowd making her way through, kissing here, hugging there, kissing everywhere else.  Person 1: It's nice to see you again.  Sylvie: And you too.  She spins around and grabs a glass of red wine off a platter carried by a waiter.  Matthew: Sylvia!  Sylvie: Matthew!  The two Kiss  Sylvie: Let me introduce my friend. Friend, Matthew. Matthew, friend.  He sticks out his hand.  Man: Hi.  Matthew Hello [sliding on the 'O's, then turns to Sylvie.] I'm so glad you're here, Will's telling old war stories again, the band's playing elevator music, and everyone's convinced their drinks can bring them back to life.  Sylvie throws her head back and laughs.  Sylvie:  Well then, I'll see what I can do. You. Stay here with Matthew.  Sylvie walks away into the crowd.  Matthew: Sheâ€™s really something.  Man: Yeah  They look to the stage.  Sylvie sings a song. It needs so have a quiet intro that showcases the womanâ€™s sultry voice. The camera turns to the stage. Sylvie is standing in front of an old style mic. Sheâ€™s smiling. The band behind her starts playing wildly. Everyone begins to applaud.  Matthew: [Leaning in and shouting] How old are you?  Man: Eighteen.  Matthew laughs, flashing his big teeth.  Matthew: Mighty young.  Man: Legal though, right?  Matthew: Legal.  They look around and continue clapping. Matthew leans in again.  Matthew: Is this your first?  Man: What?  Matthew: Will she be your first?  Man: Yes.  Matthew: You sure?  Man: No.  Matthew: Listen, since weâ€™re on the subject of sin, here.  He holds out his hand. In it lies a little white cube of acid.  Matthew: This too.   Hand pulls out a flask from his inside pocket with his free hand. He puts the cube on his tongue and flips up the cap and takes a quick swig throwing his head back.   Man: Sangks. [wait a moment] Fuck!  His eyes water and he falls to his knees clutching his stomach.  Matthew: How fucked up have you ever been?  Man: [out of breath] What was that?!  Matthew: Christian Brothers and Grey Goose. It's my special concoction just to fuck, you, up.  Man: Oooooh fuck.  Matthew laughs and slaps the manâ€™s back then leans on him with a straight arm and crossed legs.   Matthew: [proud] Does the job, eh?  The man stands up and puts his hands on his hips and leans back, breathes deeply, and then falls over.  Man; What was the, the, the...  Making circular movements with his hands.  Man: Cube.  Matthew: Sugar.  Man: Fuck you.  Matthew: I know, câ€™mon.  Matthew holds out his hand. The man grabs for Matthewâ€™s hand to help him get up, but misses. He tries again and gets it.  Matthew: Do you know where the bathroom is?  Man: No.  He is bent over because he canâ€™t stand up straight.  Matthew: Lemme show you then..  Person 1 (O.S.) You know life is not lived it is performed Person 2 (O.S.) No! Person 3 (O.S.) She looks and she goes, 'All that glitters is gold. Person 4 (O.S.) You see It is not as simple as it sounds Or seems Person 5 (O.S.) Yes to that and to this Person 6 (O.S.) Thou hast slain [pause] the bound of light  Man: (shouting) I Like your hand!  Matthew: (Laughing) Come on.  They push through a double door into this vast land of silver and tile. The Man walks to the urinal and takes a piss.  Matthew stands against the wall, arms folded and legs crossed. He has this purple tie on. The man pulls down that little tab for the paper towels. It's broken. He tries to walk out.  Matthew: Do you need to go out there? Stay with me.  The man thinks for a moment  Matthew: [pouting] Please?  The Man pushes by and Matthew looks past him longingly.   Sylvie waits for the Man where they were before.  Sylvie I told you not to leave. C'mon.  Sylvie drags him out of the shots immediate mesh of people.  Cut to: INT. of an elevator. Theyâ€™re both leaning against the walls of the elevator.  Man: I had fun.  Cut to: Close up of the stop button. Her finger presses it. Cut to black.   Open on the cop talking to the Man.  Cop: Whatâ€™d you do after that?  Man:  I went home.  Cop: And the next day?  Man: I stayed home. That night I went out to a bar. I drank and came home.  Cut to: Man walking down the street. He walks with a slight stumble. Heâ€™s drunk, but not too noticeably. One would need to know him to know he was drunk. He stops for a moment and tries to light a cigarette.  He tries with a book of matches, but after the first goes out he throws them to the ground and takes out a lighter instead. He walks on.   Cop: (O.S.) Would you say you were drunk?  Cut to: Man at his door. Heâ€™s fumbling his keys. He tries to insert one into the key hole, but drops them all.   Man: (muffled) Shit.  His cigarette falls from his mouth.   Man: (O.S.) No, not to bad.  He puts another cigarette in his mouth and tries to light it. His fingers wonâ€™t move right so he leaves it in his mouth and picks up his keys and goes inside.   Cut to: Him bending over at the range trying to light his cigarette. He ends up just taking it out of his mouth and lighting it in between his fingers. Off screen we hear a womanâ€™s laugh. The man spins up and looks at his wall.  Cop: (O.S.) How long had your next door neighbor lived in his apartment?  The man creeps towards the wall.  Man: (O.S.) Longer than I have.  Cop: (O.S.) Did he ever have any companions he lived with?  The man puts his ear to the wall. We hear the hollow noise of walls and the echo of a woman and manâ€™s pre-sex conversation.  Man: (O.S.) No. 
    
</post>


</Blog>