<Blog>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes it seems like I'm the only who has moved on....  Spending a week at your parent's house is often a humbling experience.  You come back to your roots, and really get in touch with yourself--especially when you're getting as much "Me Time" as I am.  I basically have no friends here any longer.  And sometimes I wonder what really happened.  It seems like over night I went from having a great time here--tons of friends, always out at bars and parties, never home to watch TV or play on the computer--to having no one.  And the weirdest part is...they're all still best friends, and I'm the one on the outside.  At times I can compare my friends here to a cult, at least my girlfriends.  There were five or six of us, and we did EVERYTHING together--worked, went to the beach, bars, movies, shopping, literally everything.  It seemed as if we never did anything without all of us there.  And I never realized it, but looking back, we were never very good at inviting other people into the circle.  Sure, we would meet other people when we went out, but the five of us would always arrive at places together, in the same car.  Parties in high school and after we graduated, it was the five of us.  But we never invited just one person to hang out with the group of us--we'd always meet up with everyone else.  We were very particular about who exactly we'd hang out with.  And usually there was never just one of us that went out on a given night--we always came as a group, or at least in twos or threes.  I never realized that we were probably alienating ourselves from a lot of people who would have really liked to have been friends with one of us.  But at the time, I thought it was the ideal situation.    Then, I think I grew up.  And they didn't.  Somewhere around the time I turned 21, just coming back from being abroad (which, by the way, I was accompanied by one of "the group") I started to think it was all bullshit.  I felt more foreign coming back to my hometown than I had living in an foriegn city for six months.  Suddenly, I didn't want to always hang out with the same group of people, and little quirks about each of them began to grate on my nerves.  Before I knew it, I was turning down the invites to go out every night with them because I felt, well, out of place.  I ran out of things to talk about with them, and got tired of the same things happening all the time.  Fights with the same ex boyfriend that happened when we were 17 were still happening at 22 and 23.  I guess I started to feel like I was moving on and changing, while everything else just stayed stagnant.  And whenever I was around them, I was on the outside, looking in at their friendly conversations and having nothing to offer to it.    And so now, after being in the real world for a year after college, the differences between me and them is all the more apparent.  I don't even talk to them anymore.  I'm home for a weekend and they all know I'm here, and no one calls me, not even just to say hello.  Sometimes I wonder what I did.  Is it really that I grew up and they didn't?  I don't know.  Sometimes I think that I alienated myself from them.  Maybe that's true.  I just stopped caring about the same old bullshit happening in their lives.  Because it was the same old bullshit.  It was like they were still living their high school lives here, and I was over it.  Sometimes, it really pisses me off.  The truth is, unless I stumble upon them in a bar, or randomly show up at the same party as them, I would never hear a word from any of them.  My best friends for so long, just toss me aside without a passing thought.  No calls, no emails, no invites to see them for a weekend.  Nothing.  I convince myself I'm better off without their bullshit.  That if they can drop me that easily, they were never that great to begin with.  But even that makes me feel awful--the people that I trusted and cared about for so long were never worth my efforts.  At some point I'm going to have to face the facts--the fact that it's time to bury these people in that graveyard of friends come and gone.  But the hardest part of letting go, is that on the surface, the only thing that has changed is that I'm not there anymore.  For them, everything is basically the same.    
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The house arrest is continuing, not by choice, obviously.  I had a bit of minor oral surgery which turned out to be not so minor.  What was supposed to be a 20 minute quick in-and-out appointment turned into an hour long hassle complete with six stitches to the bottom of my tongue.  I had gone in to this whole thing very mellow, just wanting to get it over with, not nervous at all.  However, ten minutes into the ordeal, my heart was racing, my knuckles white from gripping the arms of my chair, eyes watering, and jaw aching.  Both my Dad and the oral surgeon were suprised that the cyst being removed from the bottom of my tongue was so large and the surgeon appologized numerous times for the length of the proceedure.  So, since Tuesday afternoon, I've been eating only mushy foods, taking vicodin for my pain, and rotting in my house.  My Mom basically won't let me leave.  She seems to think that vicodin is much more potent than it really is.  I understand her not wanting me to drive a car--totally acceptable.  But she wouldn't let me ride a bike, Christ, I'm surprised she even let me walk from the couch to the bathroom.  Despite all her over-protecting, I have to be thankful--she did go out and buy me coffee ice cream, and made pudding and jello for me.  And I have managed to escape the house for a few hours here and there.    T minus 6 days and 1 hour.  "T" being my departure time for the airport.  It really hasn't hit me yet, that I'm leaving in less than a week to spend close to 2 months in Europe backpacking.  Maybe it's the vicodin that's not making me think clearly, not allowing me to grasp the concept of 24 hour days and 7 day weeks, and Wednesdays being closer than I believe.  Actually, maybe the vicodin is really helping in this situation--I feel like I should be more stressed out than I am, have more running lists of things to do and numbers to check and bags to pack than I do.  I feel like I should be freaking out, but I'm not.  In fact, I think I'm more concerned about finding time to get to the beach in between appointments and meals and errands than worrying about being out of the country for the next 2 months.  Maybe it's because my travel partner has been much more concerned about it all than me, and his worrying is making up for my lack of worrying.  It's like we've traded places recently.  I was always the stressed one--if I was going away for a weekend I'd be the one making lists of things to bring and things to do 5 days in advance and he'd be the one throwing shit together before work on Friday.  I like this mellow me--it's like back to the old days, when I was 18 or 19 and didn't give a shit and always left stuff to the last minute.  What happened when I turned 21 and 22 that made me such a nutcase?  This unemployed Mary is really fun to be.  I hope I can keep her around in September.    Back to my haze... 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's nothing worse than the Hamptons on a rainy day.  And even worse is a rainy end to a weekend.  For all their hype, this place can be suffocatingly boring--especially without the sunshine.  If you think about it, the only thing to do here during the day is to go to the beach, and when that options out, you're not left with much more.  Sure you could walk around any of the villages, or attempt to go shopping, but with the traffic, that's not even an option.  I would go to Bridgehampton or East Hampton and casually stroll through the villages, popping into all the stores where I couldn't afford a sock, let alone an entire outfit.  And driving the few miles east to get to them wouldn't be such a bad thing, but driving back would be an absolute NIGTHMARE.  Not to mention the fact that I'd just be torturing myself by seeing all these wonderful things that I could never afford.  So basically, I'm left with nothing.  I'm just sitting in my house, rotting.  Staring at the wall, flipping through the channels, playing minesweeper endlessly.  Stuck anyway you look at it--anywhere I go I'm going to have to drive west at some point, which is NOT an option today.  I can't even go to the movies--because that's what everyone else is probably doing, and I hate going to the movies when the theaters are PACKED.  I can't complain though, Saturday and Sunday were gorgeous.    You'd think I'd be used to this by now--having lived here all my life, and spent every summer here, you'd think I would have found a way to pass these long rainy days away.  Twenty three years in and I'm still hopelessly searching for something to bide the time.... But here I am, 1pm, trapped in my own house.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes my own insecurities amaze me.  I try to so hard to come off as settled, content, normal, when most of the time, the real me doesn't fit that bill.  I used to think that all my troubles would be gone if I were prettier, if guys hit on me more, if I had a boyfriend, if I lost 10 pounds, if I had a tan, blah blah blah.  I wanted to be vain.  I wanted to be beautiful.  But I wasn't.  The truth is, I was chunky.  Not fat, but... "slightly overweight".  And because of that, I was so insecure, so sensitive, so shy.  And I did what most overweight girls do--I tried to play the part of the funny one.  Isn't that what ususally happens to the "big girl"?  In most movies, she's never the one to get the guy, never the one to get the true happy ending.  And this was me--no happy endings, no perfect boyfriends, just sarcastic cracks at everyone that I am secrety jealous of.  And believe me, this is not an ideal way to live.  You make fun of all the girls walking through the mall with perfect bodies and golden tans and Abercrombie tank tops and all you want is to trade places with her for just a little while.  So I became one of them.   I lost the weight, bought a new wardrobe, got tan in the summer, highlights in my hair.  I cared what I looked like--I made sure my outfit was nice, my makeup looked right, that I didn't look FAT.  And you know what?  It wasn't any better.  Sure I got hit on more in bars, and sometimes I'll get whistled at walking down the street.  And it's kind of flattering....  But through all this change in appearance, something changed inside me too.  I had everything that I had wanted when I was a teenager--a good body, a cool wardrobe, tans in the summer and a great boyfriend.  But something was different.  I was more mature.  But I still had the same insecurities.  Take the last post as an example--even after all this self-realization and change, I still get stressed out when an old friend calls and asks me to go out.  I still get worked up into a frenzy because I don't feel like going out and getting wasted and doing the same old crap that I did in high school.  I'm inscure that this old friend will yell at me, or tell me I'm a loser, and this is rediculous, because what do I care?  I see her two, maybe 3 times a year.  And her opinion of me really shouldn't matter this much.   As my Mom told me this morning, I don't have to go and make up excuses if I don't want to go out, it shoudln't matter.  If I don't want to go, I don't want to go.  Yet every night, I end up in the same argument with myself.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's close to one month of unemployment for me.  And no, I'm not some drain on society sucking away at the government's unemployment program.  I don't think it's available to me anyway.    Being unemployed isn't that bad--as long as you find a way to keep yourself busy.  It wasn't hard at first.  I came home to spend time with my family, and I was constantly kept busy that week.  Then I went back to my apartment and began the search for a new apartment, started looking into the painful task of moving out of the current apartment, and working hard on my tan.  I went to a few concerts, an amusement park, out to a couple bars.  I was content.  But now... now the reality of unemployment will set in, if only for a few days.    I'm currently living at my parent's house.  I'm still young enough and poor enough to be able to consider this house my "home".  I'm told by my older siblings that there comes a point in time when you're established enough to be able to call some other town, state, country, whatever, your "home".  I haven't gotten there yet.  And at this rate, God only knows if I ever will.  Living here isn't so bad--provided that I don't wear out my welcome (which would take a lot.)  The only problem is, this town is just stinking of my old life--the person I used to be.  And even why I try to be the new me here--the confident, normal, happy me--something always brings me back.  I was doing fine.  I figured that since none of the people I knew in high school were around, it didn't really matter if I went out or stayed home.  It didn't matter if I went to the library instead of the hip bar.  I rode my bike around, I went to the beach, I went shopping with my mom.  It was great.  I relaxed, hell, it really felt like I was on vacation.    Then tonight happened.  It's a Friday, on a holiday weekend, and I guess you're "expected" to go out.  But in all honesty, I just didn't have it in me.  So I didn't even bother calling around to see if anyone was here or even remotely close to the area.  Until 10pm, when the call came to me....  One of the old friends--friends of a different time, a different era--called me up and asked me to go to a bar.  Now, for the normal person, this would be a no brainer, yes if you want to go, no if you don't.  Simple as that.  But for me, nothing is simple like that.  Truth be told, I don't want to go.  This particular friend has something of a reputation for being a terrific flirt, and if one ends up going out with her alone, chances are you'll be left fending for yourself after a while.  And tonight, I really wasn't in the mood to fend for myself--especially amongst a crowd of old high school buddies that I haven't talked to in at least a year, likely more than that.  I just couldn't bear to do the "catching up" conversation over and over again.  I just wasn't in the mood.  So I get tongue-tied on the phone, make up some lame excuses about being tired, not in the mood, blah blah blah.  She probably bought it.  Problem solved, right?  Well, not necessarily....  I end up spending half the night feeling like such a damn loser because I don't want to go out.  Even though there's no rational reason for me to feel that way.  I start wishing that I was back upstate in my apartment with the boys, getting high and watching the Family Guy or playing a game of darts.  I start hating being back here.  It's so strange for me too, because I used to LOVE this town.  I loved all my friends, the nightlife, the parties, everything.  Then something happened, I guess I changed, and nothing and nobody else did.  Because they're all still best friends, and still love this place, and I'm the one on the outside.    I try to tell myself that I'm the strong one in this situation--that I'm the one who is taking chances and moving on and growing up, instead of staying close by my home town and keeping all my high school friends and doing the same shit I did five years ago.  But most of the time I can't tell whether that's just me trying to make myself feel better or the truth.  It's this constant struggle when I'm here.  So my "vacations" end up being a big stressful event where I work myself into a tizzy wondering why I distanced myself from all these people instead of staying the same.  But change is something you can't stop. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>