<Blog>

<date>27,July,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well, Thank god it's Saturday, unforetunatly theres only, 1 and 1/2 hours till Sunday..... AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Okay, Okay, I'm good, I'm calm, I'm fine.... whew.... I'm dead...I guess I'll go practice now. *turns on a funeral dirge*
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I'ts Friday and I'm nearly a nervous wreck, I have to do a solo on sunday and my accompinaist hasn't called back about our last rehersal. Erk! I watched the first four episodes of Yu Yu Hakusho, Ghost Files. It is incredibly funny! I sniffled a bit in the first episode though. This is sooo wierd...I just noticed how I skip from topic to topic. Mucho Crazy. And Tsubasi No Baka Isn't answeriing his E-mails! I could strangle the twit! *Deep Breath* Okay, I'm calm now. Have  a Nice day!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2002</date>
<post>


       
      It's Friday, the 2nd of August, Tennis is over and I am Free!!! I'm getting my highlights done today! Costs major Moolah though :p Oh well. I'm going to the Arthur Murray Freestyles in september! Again...Major Moolah is required. :p We're gonna be eating Bolagna sandwiches for a month...And the costumes...Oh goodness...and the hotel room...Make that a year. It could be worse though. Could be Oatmeal. Ick. NEwayz, I hope my highlights look good...Wherever ya'll are wish me luck. :) I'm gonna need it. ^_^
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well....I screwed up at church, but they loved me anyway, so I guess s'all good. Tired beyond belief, I never knew someone could get so bone tired just from babysitting two kids for an hour at the pool...Dude, I'm gonna die tomorrow, Tennis is gonna kill me. thank god this is the last week of it. not to mention I got sunburned like nobodys business today. I'll be radioactive red tomoorow as I'm only lobster pink today. I failed my tennis evaluation so I'm still 1.0 Suckieness...But I tried! It would have been nice if my friend had stayed to watch though. Oh well. Tomorrow will be better!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well Well....It looks like I am sadly lacking in my updates...*winces* Sorry. Well lets see....I'm getting better at my dancing,(Yay!) But I'm a far cry from advancing a rank. (ooo.) I found most of the Mangas I've been looking for! (Yay!) And am now at least $60 in debt to my dad. (ooo) I've started highschool.( Um...Yay ooo?) I WRITE FANFICTION! VISIT Fanfitcion.net! (YAAAAAAY!) Now then lets see..not musch else except thatI'm now an inch taller! *does happy dance* =^_^=  (not that you'll want to read my fanfiction or anything...but Just In Case..My author name is Komikitty.)
     

    
</post>

<date>11,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well, Today is the one year anniversary of the fall of the Twin Towers and The crash at the pentagon...I was thinking and it came to me, that we should name the Towers the Fallen Angels and the Pentagon the Mended circle...But thats just me, I know there are people out there who lost friends and family...and I don't know what to say, I can't say I understand because I don't, I can only offer all the love i have in me to each and everyone one of you who is hurting. Please be safe, and stay strong. God Bless Us All. Kate
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Freestyles....Friday....AAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!! I'm so nervous it's not funny! What if I screw up? But I'll give it my best shot. Marmalade boy is a good Manga. So is Mars, Inu Yasha, Planet Ladder, Utena and Corrector Yui. WAAAAAAAAIIIIIIIII!!!!! I LUV Manga!!! And Anime!!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well, Freestyles went great! I got all Gold marks YAY!! NE Wayz, I had my first experiance with red Bull today...It was like...Duuuuuuuuuude.....I was talking that that old sniffles the mouse cartoon. Ya know where he talks like this: AnditwaslikethewierdestthingandIhadmydancelessonlikethisandIhadtodancewiththemanageranditwassooooooooembarassing!! ya Know? But it was Fuuuuuuuun! Red Bull doesn't give you wings, it gives you a major sugar rush!!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well it HAS been awhile...let me see.....I've gotten blue highlights, I've passed the first quarter. I've played almost all the way through Tenchu 2.There's about four weeks till my birthday and it's a great time to be alive. Yes theres more to it then that but its been awhile! I went to a birthday party today had toms of fun, "Big Trouble" Is the best movie ever! Working on getting more manga...and finishing Thanksgiving leftovers. And many thanks to Cosmos Sama who made me update.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've noticed a distinct contrast betwen my current mood and the happiness of my long ago post. It has distinctly worsened. (But if you ask some of the kids in my school they'll say that it's not possible.) My life has been pretty normal really, Nothing exciting about it at all. No one calls, and of the only two people who IM me on a regular basis, one lives in Louisiana and the other one is in another city. But to make this post a tad longer for those of you who actually take time out of your oh so busy schedules to read these things, I shall post a poem of my own devising. Please don't take it. It's not that good anyway.  Woe is I for in the darkness I have forgotten the light. And the only warmth is the dying ember of my hope. Yet I trudge on through life caring for my ember and making sure it never goes out completely. For the day it does is the day I cease to be as I am.  Ta-da.   Have a nice day. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, so long, and the first thing I'm going to do. . .is rant.     GODDAMNIT! The walls are still there! *sigh* Why should I be bothered, they're everywhere. Maybe it's me? Proabably. Gaah.  I hate being the one with the problem. But that's what I am. the "Antisocial" one.  the dog. To come when called. Or maybe the thug, to only appear when neeeded. invisible when it suits the Brain's purposes.  I hardly know them anymore, they're all so busy and hardworking, I feel like a bum. a mooch. Nothing worth befriending at all......   And there's my little rant. and . . .Sarah? IF and I mean IF you read this, don't. . say anything. Cause it's true. And I know it is.  . . .      Lets see, whats been going on. . . I'm 17 now. Neat huh? but I've already vowed I'd have no sex till 20. My word as a Knott. Hmm . . .I'm struggling in classes, but, *laugh* Nothing new there. Probably going to drop japanese next year. I'm not talented enough to deal with a language on top of all the other crap I'll have to do.  College? *shudders* Ugh! Don't even mention it. *sigh* And thats my life. Nothing much huh?   Go on, have fun! You deserve it! I probably won't post again for a long while. See ya'll later. =^_^=
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My, My, My. Time does fly doesn't it? I look at a few of my posts and I think, Goddess! I'm such a whiner, how do my friends put up with me? I'm glad they do though. Lots of stuffs been happening, I do have another motorcycle ride lined up...whenever I can apologize to the guy whos supposed to give me one for missing the first date we set. I'm not looking forward to THAT at all.  Oh well. C`est la vie....Such is life. But this one is good to...Postatem obscuri lateris nescitis. You don't know the power of the Dark Side. So true, so true. but this one is my favorite...     VAE VICTUS!!    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>