<Blog>


<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'd like to thank Val for this poem.  --  icy (pt. II)  eyes see what the ears can't hear but sometimes i think  I can almost hear your skin singing softly  whispering sweet somethings in wind gusts so only I can hear  so smooth a silky slippery slope there's no turning back  explosive radiance must be contained, trapped a cage of clothing - wrapped tight, like a second skin to bare the form from which my dreams are made, carefully crafted from every hint you've ever dropped along the way I gathered them like a sparrow in spring piecing it together, architecting a nest for my head to rest  Telling you every dirty thought I've ever had about you would take an eternity  And still we'd need a Time Machine  to span the lifetimes it would take  to recount every beautiful thought on the same subject.  And That Machine would certainly break down  before allowing us enough time to cover each reason that I write poems  like this one  Because every day i see something new in you (or perhaps it's just something I forgot - you know how my memory is) But it keeps me coming back -  as if coming back were an option...  As if I could stop thinking about you  As if I were on the open sea ebbing and flowing  As if I were a higher order function changing direction as I move closer to our origin  As if I were running a 5K on the track away with the wind before coming back to your voice  As if I were a boomerang and you had to throw me to get me to come back  But if you just hold me, I'll stay in your hand forever.  --  Fan P walking... 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Thanks to Blogger my dreams have come true and I now have I Gmail account!  And thanks to me, I now have a 51 page manuscript which I call "Magnetic Poetry." I'll be submitting it to the 2004  urlLink Steel Toe Books  poetry contest. I'm not entirely sure that link is going to work... Anyway, I'm very happy to have finished it, but plan on adding to it until I come up with an equally catchy title for a new book. When I decide it's finally finished, I'll make copies available at  urlLink the Fan P store .  Fan P walking... 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sketchbook drawing on funds that aren't really there The check is in the mail via TeleFile and direct deposit The first is in the air mail The Valentine is in the male Amtrak tooting my own horn like little boy blue in the face blistered and blustering like a windy frisbee player field playing, record rating, through the roof to the 4 stars above Two are my eyes, two twinkling in yours Both wishing on the same set through the snow &/or white skies  Any hauntingly silent city doesn't have enough streets let alone being paved with the gold of free public transit pushing the public towards Pike Place: Salmon & Starbucks. Seattle.  I can't stay... So I savor special situations. It's not the only place where the good times rock'n'roll, and truth be told I wouldn't want to stay... The only cities I can see myself in start with C And only one ends with you. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      eye c what's happening here  as if it were an out of body experience  like a neverending well dream i am falling  for you.  Like a Charybdal undertow your sweeping siren song - a carefully crafted cobweb ensares my essence like poems too deep to even be written they sit at the bottom of the ocean or the deepest wishing well  I wish you well Well, I just wish I was with you now...  So I could feel your pulse in the shape of a heartbeat beating out the shape of a drumline-chorus ever-rhythmically-steady and ready to create the form for which I'm looking  From the form from which I'm looking I can almost see the end of the Earth -  it's as long as a life itself (cause it gets closer -  or farther -  depending on where you are in the world)  Where in the world are you?  You left me a note that said to meet you here So I will wait 'cause I thought it would take an eternity to find you but it only took 19 years so I've got an eternity to spare and i'll spend it waiting for you 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It seems the only time I can think of cool titles for books or albums is when I already have one. But then I always forget to write them down and when I finish a book or an album it takes me forever to come up with the name for a new one. I use this time as an excuse, or a sort of hiatus period, for not actually working on my next masterpiece. I'm at that point right now... Eventually I'll start writing again even if I haven't thought of a title, because that's just what I do.  Fan P talking...  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The other night (Thursday, I guess), I wrote my first sonnet. I'm not about to post it here, cause it's pretty much terrible. I'm interested in the structure, though, so I'm willing to keep trying it. It'll be interesting to see if it gets easier as I get more experience - I'm so used to freeform writing.  Fan P talking...  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I got the first two copies ever of Magnetic Poetry from cafepress today! Unfortunately, they don't have page numbers (oops!), so I'll have to remedy that shortly. Luckily, all I have to do it update and upload a new PDF to their site.  I also got a new journal with the Magnetic Poetry cover on the cover. It's pretty nice. Sturdy and high quality. I haven't been too impressed with cafepress's clothing offerings, but the books and the journal are quite exceptional. If I were a stock broker, I'd rate them a "buy."  Fan P talking...  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Click Here to Order   Only available at  urlLink www.cafepress.com .
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If I had a star to wish on just one night I'd wish for an objective a mission statement 3 minutes of conversation to tell you who I am  If you hadn't asked I could have told you exactly who I am and where my life is going I have one destination but it's only a location - not a goal.  If I wasn't trapped in a headlight freezer with head spinning around my eyes; I can't look away to see the stars my wish falls by the wayside and I am speechless, a caveman searching.  If I could tell you exactly what I wanted My eyes would open and though it might still be dark around me I could see the path before me.  If I could spill my blood across these yellow bricks my wings would carry me back to the Midwest and maybe not end up on LSD, but still be happy.  If I could spread my wings instead of hold them I could take satellite photos and see where my path goes; I am good at turning pictures into words, cause I've got thousands.  If all those words quite dancing around my head perhaps confusion would clear like cloudbreak or fall by the wayside; I'd still be speechless trapped by your beauty.  If I looked long enough into your eyes I'd see words forming in my reflection: I may not be wearing shining armor but when the time comes I will be brave, I will be fearless.  --  Fan P walking...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ears earn their pay by sifting through sounds and telling the brain what to hear.  Without webcams eyes exercise extrasensory perceptions except when dissention among the stars leaves half the world in the dark.  And maybe it was the plan for "I don't see it" to mean I don't understand. Cause I don't see the money, honey, but I know they're putting a check for 5 grand in your hot little hand.  And it's no coincidence that the instant I switched this side of my brain on the strain on my eyes increased leading me towards sleep.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think the Oregon weather is trying to get back at me for making fun of it in this poem... Today I had to turn in my final project for a class and it was nice when I left, but when I was coming back a short time later the skies just opened up and started pouring. It was almost as ferocious as an Illinois rain. But not quite. Sorry, Oregon. You'll have to do better than that.   Wool Hat   That's twice now. Three times really, I think. I almost forgot my hat. Almost left it behind. Can't do that. I mean, I'm gonna need it. It's as cold as cold gets in Chicago, if you don't mind my saying so. Of course, I can't really believe that I've managed to hang onto this one for so long. That's not a metaphor for a girl or anything. I'm seriously talking about my wool hat. It's not as important as a girl - her name is Valerie - cause it only took five dollars and ninety-nine cents to leave TJ's with it; and we can say for certain that human life is irreplaceable. Love is inimitable. And tacit for that matter. I would argue that it is non-substitutable, but I'm sure you could make an argument either way on that one; but I'm not gonna touch that with a ten foot pole. Another topic that could invite argument is whether one can love a piece of clothing. If so, I damn sure love my wool hat. Perhaps it's because of the warm weather that it keeps trying to leave me. Or maybe I have just set my expectations too high - expecting it to jump up and back into my backpack. "It's old hat." So what about teaching an old hat new tricks? I think old Wooly is going to need some new tricks under his cap. Cause it really is as cold as cold gets in Chicago. You've got Alaska, and Siberia, and the Antarctic and all that, but for a boy who spent sixteen of the first seventeen years of his life in Portland, Oregon (where'd it go?), Chicago is cold. Portland doesn't have any "river" affect flurries. I could easily be convinced the City of Portland doesn't even _own_ a snow plow. They're like "Put on your wool hats and it'll be gone in a couple days." So I was going to write a Thank You letter to my wool hat, just to say thanks for sticking around so long, because my umbrellas never do. I guess at twelve ninety-nine, they're too upscale for me. I bet they'll be regretting it when I'm going business casual downtown with all the cool cats. But I'll be walking in there with my multi-crap bin wool hat and Circuit City grand opening giveaway umbrella. That's how I'll be rolling off the El. My red and white Circuit City spirit umbrella weighs a few stone more than the titanium alloy fashion understatement I got at Herrod's, but I'll bet dollars to doughnuts it holds up as well in the Illinois showers as well as anything. Cause it rains in Illinois. I mean, _rains_. Sure it rains in Oregon - yeah, all the time - but it's mostly just what we Oregonians call "spitting" or "drizzling." That precipitation that occurs in Illinois goes under the classification of "torrential downpour." It doesn't matter if it lasts only ten or twenty minutes; because if you're out there without protection you're soaked. Not like in Oregon where most of the time I could walk around with my black nineteen ninety-nine Old Navy jacket and be fine for days on end. To withstand the downpour of an Illinois showerstorm you need a jacket made out of material that will fight with the water. Like bio-engineered Goretex or something. Something that says "Water, if you fucking come near me, I'm going to kick your ass to the curb. Literally." You learn quick that "water resistant" means the fabric is all about being French when it's time to fight the Germans. "Waterproof" is closer to being British. I'm still looking for something that will come in like the United States and be like "Were you guys even trying to fight before I got here?" And if I can find that, I'll love it maybe almost as much as I love my wool hat, which is still not even on the same order of magnitude as the amount with which I love my girl. Her name is Valerie. Just in case you'd forgotten. Cause I almost forgot my hat.  --  Fan P walking...
     
    
</post>


<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Vlade Divac has left the Sacremento Kings. The Kings brought on Greg Ostertag to replace him. However, the Kings starting center would now have to be  urlLink Brad Miller . It would be sensisble for Rick Adelman - despite sometimes questionable substitions/rotations - to start Miller alongside Webber and Stojakovic.  What I want to know is how Miller went from .59 bpg in Indiana to 1.19 in Sacramento.   Fantasy Impact   With the departure of Vlade Divac, and despite the arrival of Greg Ostertag, Brad Miller should be posting bigger numbers than last season. I had him ranked as somewhat of a sleeper last season, but now everyone knows. He'll still be playing alongside a (probably) healthy Webber, as well as Stojakovic and Bibby, so don't overvalue him. That said, he is a good pick up at Center - especially now that Shaq is in the Eastern Conference. Certainly a good early round pick; I'd say as high as 2nd round in deep leagues as the roster stands now. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I realize they don't say wicked awesome in Miami, but I felt it was somewhat representative of the transition to the East.  urlLink This quote  from  urlLink End of the Bench  is great:    "We're gonna be straight," O'Neal said. "I was down here the other day working out with the kid from Vanderbilt we got (second-round pick Matt Freije), and I told him, 'I'm gonna come across the block, and if I get doubled, I'm gonna pass the ball to you and you're gonna have a wide-open jumper, or (forward) Udonis Haslem is gonna come down the lane and he's gonna get a dunk, and you're all gonna get big contracts.' He said, 'What do you mean?' I said, 'Just look at the history.  Travis Knight.  Horace Grant.  A.C. Green.  ' He said, 'Shaq, you're one of the coolest guys I've met.' "    And that's not even the best of Shaq... I'm so glad I can appreciate him once again.    Fantasy Impact        Shaq is clearly going to dominate. That's about the easiest call there is to be made this season. He's arguably the best player in the league and now he doesn't have to give up the ball to anyone unless he wants to. And since it sounds like he wants to, it seems that he could improve his assist numbers in addition to points and probably rebounds. It would not be difficult to make an argument for taking him first overall. He'll be gone by the end of the first round even in the smallest leagues.    
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Objective :  My objective is to fill a fantasy basketball void in the RSS arena by providing insight (via Blogger's XML feed) to those who are as addicted to fantasy sports and/or basketball as I am.       Fantasy Sports Experience :  I have coached fantasy basketball teams for 4 years, during which I have demonstrated a keen sense for players' hot and cold streaks and an ability to make key trades at opportune times.  During 2 of my 4 years I managed 2+ teams in several different leagues. I have drafted live as well as set up draft lists with top 3 finishes in both. I've been in leagues with anywhere from 8 to 18 teams, and have won championships in leagues of both sizes.      1 Basketball Championship - 10 teams, draft list, Head-to-Head  1 Basketball Championship - 18 teams, draft list, Roto  1 Football Championship - 10 teams, live draft, Head-to-Head  3rd place Basketball - 8 teams, live draft, Heat-to-Head     Best trade:  In 2003-04, I traded Kwame Brown and Caron Butler for Yao Ming.       Preferences:  I prefer Head-to-Head style leagues because they encourage the talking of smack. I also like leagues with lots of teams because they better simulate the importance of role players.      Writing Experience  :  For those who doubt my qualifications as a psuedo-intellectual-English-major-type-blogger, I self published a book of poems - some of which are available at:  urlLink Fanatical Pupil.com . In addition, my mother was in fact an English major, and I blame her for my extensive vocabulary.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Is it just me or does it seem like the Clippers are always on the verge of being awesome and then manage to fudge it up? With the acquisition of Kerry Kittles for a second round draft pick, they basically just traded Quentin Richardson and the pick for KK. I mean, that's great if you're a Villanova fan living in LA... but seriously, can all NBA teams be  that  cost-conscious that they let good players leave when they are on the edge of stardom?    I guess they must, 'cause... look where this trade leaves the Nets... They're basically putting the whole team on Richard Jefferson's shoulders.  I guess they're rebuilding while Kidd rests his knee... They've got 4 picks coming soon, so that must be the plan, right?     Fantasy Impact       If it weren't for everyone saying how they want to rest Kidd's knee, he would be a great pick. The Nets have one other player on their roster beyond Kidd that I would even consider drafting.  RJ looks like a great pick.  How could he not improve on 14.5, 5.3, and 2.7 with draft picks taking the place of K-Mart and Kerry Kittles???     Kittle maintains his value with this trade. He was about the 3rd or 4th option on the Nets and will be the starting SG for the Clips. I can see Elton Brand and Corey Maggette absorbing a lot of shots and points with the departure of Q-Rich. His rebounds may actually improve, and depending on how well Shaun Livingston distributes the ball, his assists may improve as well. He and Livingston will be feeding Brand and Maggette a lot.      RJ is the Money Ball. Count it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Anthony is with the Wizards now...       Fantasy Impact      Raise your hand if you had Peeler on your team last year.     No, I'm just kidding. Peeler can be valuable in deeper leagues that count 3 pt. percent and/or 3 pointers made. Of course, he'll be playing with Gilbert Arenas, Steve Blake, Larry Hughes, and Juan Dixon at the other guard positions. I can't see him raising his 18+ mpg, 5.8 ppg, and 2 apg. He might keep up with his nealy 1 3-pointer/game, though... And he does look like a thugged-out baller in his league photo.        Count it.    
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
           From the above title link:     In the space of three weeks,  urlLink Argentina's biggest basketball star  has been married and signed a six-year, $52 million contract to stay with the  urlLink San Antonio Spurs . He also started training hard amid hopes of leading his country to a medal at the Athens Olympics.    From me:    In somewhat related news, it appears the Spurs are trying to get as many foreign players as possible.  On the one hand, they've got Tony Parker. On the other, Rasho Nesterovic...  I guess if they hit 50% with their 4 foreign rookies they won't be too bad off.      Fantasy Impact     Manu had 10 ppg, 3.5 rpg, and 3 apg last season. He was listed after the departed Hedo Turkoglu on the depth chart, and showed progress last year. So, he'll probably be the starting SG for San Antionio. However, the Olympics will surely deplete him - being the star of the Argentine team, he'll be working hard. He'll certainly improve on last years numbers - everyone knows he's just waiting to blow up all over the court. He's still young enough that the Olympics might not take too much out of him. If you take him, don't count on him towards the end of the season.    Count it.         
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I haven't seen terms, but Ben Gordon and Luol Deng - the 3rd and 7th draft picks this year signed contracts with the Chicago Bulls. Am I happy about this? Of course. These guys are the "building blocks" of the team. I like that the organization learned it's lesson about drafting high schoolers after picking up Tyson Chandler and Eddy Curry.  I would have rather they taken Shaun Livingston and Luke Jackson, but that's cause Livingston is from Illinois, and I'm from Oregon.    I do like that Gordon is number 7 - my favorite basketball jersey number. I used to like 3, but 7 just looks better on a wider variety of teams, so I'm a fan of that one now. Sorry Tyson.     Fantasy Spin     If the trade involving Jamal Crawford ever goes down, Gordon looks to be a good candidate for a starting guard position. I'm thinking something along the lines of Dwayne Wade - but perhaps I'm being optimistic because I'm biased. Deng will be starting at small forward almost for sure.  Even with the deal (unless Harrington comes with it) he's the best small forward the Bulls will have. "They" say he's looking good in the summer league games, so he should be a solid mid-round pick.    From  urlLink Yahoo :    The 21-year-old Gordon, who left Connecticut a year early, is the school's all-time leader with 242 3-pointers and ranks sixth in points.     Deng left the Blue Devils after his freshman season when he averaged 15.1 points and nearly seven rebounds. He should give the team much-needed depth at the small forward position.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oh, it's real big. The NBA that is. Obviously. I'm not going to try to cover all the news that happens. Well, actually, I'm going to try. But I'm not going to be able to do it... So, I'm going to talk mostly about what interests me, and what I feel is the most relevant to fantasy basketball and the NBA in general.     As my profile indicates, I'm from Chicago. I used to live in Portland, Oregon. So there will likely be more analysis of the Bulls and Blazers than other teams. But I'm completely obsessed with basketball and the fantasy aspect thereof, so I assure you there will be all kinds of news and opinion.     I will beat the Blog Maverick.     Ha.    I am the Money Ball. Count it.     
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, evidently  urlLink Rick Fox has filed for divorce from Vanessa Williams . I guess he had enough of people calling him  urlLink Mr. Vanessa Williams , and he's decided to become his own man.  Of course, it says the two had been separated, so it wouldn't surprise me if she initiated the separation, and he was like "I'd better break up with her before she dumps me."  Okay, that's probably a really mean thing to say... but look at the man's hair!  Perhaps all the styling product affected his ability to reason.    Fantasy   Impact    Well, I'm sure a lot of men's fantasies will be impacted by this news.  As for the world of basketball, I can't believe that anyone is really going to care if Fox is depressed and can't manage more than 3-4 points a game next season.  I read in some article about it that he was considering retirement as  an option to continuing sucking.  Seems like a poor time to file for divorce when you're finally going to stop travelling around the country for 8 months out of the year.  But I've never been married, so what do I know?  If he does retire, look for Ricky Davis, Jumaine Jones, and maybe even rookie Justin Reed to pick up Fox's 20 minutes, 5 points, and 4 rebounds per game.  In related news: Thanks to Yahoo for taking Mr. Vanessa Williams picture down from his profile page! I was able to fully scour the depth of his career without being reviled by his hideous mug. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Read this . Then  urlLink read this.   Tell me I'm not all over fantasy basketball. ESPN should just hire me. I bet I could do it for less than they're paying Graham Hays.   And I won't even ask who's analysis was more entertaining.  Count it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Click the title. He knows what he's talking about.  I forgot about Payton making the Vengeance Scale. And I'm not privy to all this insider information... To be a real columnist...   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, so I just made up the title of this post. It's not necessarily true or anything. But it sounded clever cause it rhymes.  So... where the hell are we? (Is it just me or are there a ridiculous amount of trades going on this off-season? All the more reason to get some good fantasy analysis!)  According to Yahoo (and others):   The  urlLink Los Angeles Lakers  resumed their makeover Friday by trading  urlLink Gary "The Glove?"Payton  and  urlLink Mr. Vanessa Williams (Rick Fox)  to the  urlLink Boston Celtics  for  urlLink Chucky "Not the Diet Guy" Atkins ,    urlLink Marcus "Could Be Money" Banks  and  urlLink Chris "Wishes He Made More Money" Mihm .     The Celtics also received a conditional first-round draft pick and cash in the deal and sent a second-round pick to the Western Conference champions.            So... I'm glad the Lakers got rid of Rick Fox. Actually, not true. I would have rather they kept him, so I could focus my disgust more easily instead of having to split it between two coasts (see also: Kobe Bryant is an Ass Clown). At least being located in Chicago will make it easier for me to heckle Mr. Williams' used-drug-dealer-John-Travolta-Greaseball-wannabe-pimp-and/or-player hairdo. Seriously, worst hair ever.   This is almost sort of one of the fairer trades I've seen this off season. At least it's got that going for it. And it will make these teams fun to watch. They should both be running their asses off to create offense, since the don't have any legitimate post players (well, okay, the Lakers do. I just hate to admit it... but any team could run their half court set through Vlade Divac and be sweet).    Fantasy   Impact     (Gotta Love the Glove)  Even with Shaq and Kobe on the team, Gary managed 14 ppg on 47% shooting last year. In Boston, there won't be any triangle "holding him back." His points should increase back to around the 19 or 20 he had with Milwaukee and Seattle in 2002, even though he is older. Being able to run with Paul Pierce and Ricky Davis should give him some good assist opportunities, and I would expect him to surpass the 5.5 he had with the Lakers.  This clearly makes him a good early round selection for this year's fantasy drafts.   As for Rick Fox? I couldn't bear looking at his stats with his ugly mug staring at me.    Fantasy   Impact     (Chucky Atkins?)  Atkins will obviously be the starting point for the Lakers now (since Derek Fisher is gone and Payton went with this trade). He'll be less of an option than he was on the Celtics, however, since the Lakers still have more talent than the Celtics (and don't expect Kobe to give Chucky, let alone anyone else, his shots). Marcus Banks could be a sleeper, but I'm not ready to commit to that (maybe next year). He busted out a couple 20 point games last season, but he might get a little lost in the Lakers rotation. Both of them should be able to increase their assist totals since they'll have more reliable targets to get the ball to (as opposed to the 1 they had in Boston). Atkins has 5 apg and Banks 2 last year. If Chucky knows what's good for him, he'll be more selective with his shots, and work on getting the rock to his teammates. I wouldn't bother taking Banks unless your league is really deep.  Atkins is a decent pick  for mid-sized leagues or later rounds in 8 team leagues. Also he'd be fun to have on a team with someone like Eddy Curry, so you post the following in your league forum: "I'm gonna get Atkins on Eddy Curry so he can break his fat ass down and make him get some damn rebounds." Keep in mind that the  urlLink recent signing of Damon Jones by the Heat  makes him a better pick for a PG than either of the guys I just talked about. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       To quote  urlLink this Yahoo article :      The Chicago Sun-Times is reporting that guard   Jamal Crawford   has verbally agreed to a seven-year deal worth at least $56 million that will eventually land him in New York. The Bulls are planning on sending Crawford and forward   Jerome Williams   to the Knicks for forward   Othella Harrington  , guard   Frank Williams  , center Dikembe Motombo, and center   Cezary Trybanski  .      Crawford was the Bulls' leading scorer last season, but he never jelled with coach Scott Skiles, so his future was cloudy at best in Chicago. Even though the Knicks are paying him close to $60 million, he'll still have to fight for shots with   Stephon Marbury   and   Allan Houston  . Unless another deal is made (or until Houston gets hurt again), Crawford will see fewer opportunities in New York than he did in Chicago. As for the Bulls, Jamal's departure leaves minutes open for rookie   Ben Gordon  , if he is ready to handle them.           I'm not sure what made Chicago feel compelled to go through with this trade. It's almost like a bad fantasy league where people feel like just because someone proposes a trade they're compelled to somehow make it work out. For what the Bulls are getting, I would have rather kept an unhappy Crawford. I think the Bulls look more promising than the Knicks right now anyway, so I don't know why Crawford couldn't wait a little while. Sure, it'll be a couple years before they fully mature (if they don't ship off all the pieces they have in place now), and maybe it's just because I'm biased, but - even without Crawford - this Bulls team will be good. This trade, however, reminds me of one involving Elton Brand a few years ago...      Fantasy    Impact    As mentioned above, Crawford won't get as many shots in NY as he did in Chicago. This might actually help his percentage, though, since he may actually be forced to take good shots.    Of course, if Stephon is tired out from the Olympics (at least somewhat), Crawford may become the Knicks best option, leading him to once again hoist the ball at will (see also:  urlLink Antoine Walker ).     Jerome Williams will probably fill up the hole that Othella Harrington is leaving, so you can expect those kind of numbers from him (they're pretty close to what he was doing already anyway).    Fantasy  Impact     Frank Williams will be the backup point to Kirk Hinrich, and perhaps Jannero Pargo. This might be his chance to make a run at the shooting guard position, since he's fairly well suited for that (except for being undersized for a SG, but then, so is Ben Gordon). Othella Harrington (a la Vice Versa) will take over the role played by Jerome Williams, so you can probably expect those kind of numbers from him (6,6).     Frankly (haha! oops...) - no seriously - I'd like to see Hinrich, Gordon, Deng, Chandler, and Curry starting. Sure it would be probably the youngest starting line ever (except for maybe the one the Clippers use to have), but it would show promise of a brighter tomorrow. I realize Bulls fans have been blessed, so I shouldn't be complaining about having to wait for another championship caliber team, but I was in Portland when Jordan was in Chicago, so I didn't get to enjoy any of it!  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I not quite sure what to say about this trade. I mean, Philly wanted to get rid of  urlLink Coleman , so that's cool, but does Detroit really need another big man? And why do the 76ers need Williamson? They've got  urlLink Glenn Robinson  (listed as SF), they've got  urlLink Kedrick Brown ,  urlLink Kyle Korver , and they just drafted  urlLink Andre Iguodala . I'm looking at their roster and I can't really figure it out.   Fantasy  Impact   (Corliss)   urlLink Corliss  will probably be getting about the same playing time in Philadelphia as he did with the Pistons. He should be playing behind Glenn Robinson at the SF spot.  He'll probably be good for 8-12 points and 3-4 rebounds. His 50% field-goal shooting is attractive.  In fact, "We like that he has a high field-goal percentage," Sixers general manager Billy King said at yesterday's press conference in the Lexus room of the Wachovia Center. He did go on to support my doubts by saying "Nothing is going to be easy in training camp this season. Guys are going to be fighting and competing for starting spots, which is a good thing. With a young player like Andre [Iguodala] and other athletic guys like Brian [Skinner], Samuel [Dalembert] and Kedrick [Brown], I think we have a great mix of talent." I think by "athletic guys" he meant "small forwards." And by "fighting for starting spots" he meant "we have too many of them."   Fantasy   Impact  (Coleman)   urlLink Samuel Dalembert  is going to see a lot of time at center now that Coleman is gone. He had 8, 8, and 2 blocks a game last year. He's a sleeping giant about to awaken.  Count it.   As for Coleman, he'll be backing up the Wallaces in Detroit, along with Elden Campell and Antionio McDyess. I can't see him getting much more time than he had in Philadelphia, and as unimpressive as his numbers were there, I can't recommend him as anything more than a 6 and 6 if you're lucky. Combine that with his FG and Ft percentages and it's not looking good. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Rodney Rogers  has jumped off the Nets ship for the Hornets. Good move Rodney. Someone on the Nets needs to warn the captain about the iceberg, 'cause right now Bruce Ratner is sitting in the hold of the ship guarding the treasure chests and can't see outside.   Fantasy  Impact    Rogers is expected to start for the Hornets and should be able to post about 8 and 5. Not a sentence I'm going to end an exclamation mark with, but it might be enough for the deeper leagues out there. Ratner, on the other hand, is going for leagues about 20,000 times deeper than those Rogers will be valuable in.  Count it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink This article from ESPN.com  doesn't even require an Insider subscription!  He says pretty much everything pretty much everyone is thinking. I won't elaborate further (though I probably could)... since it doesn't really have a fantasy impact. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So it appears that Antoine Walker is going to be with Atlanta Hawks next season, and Jason Terry and Alan Henderson are going to be with the Mavericks (I just looked at the Mav's roster, by the way, and it's HUGE! - They have 19 people now that Toine has been cashed in for 2 more players).    Fantasy   Impact  (Antoine)   Antoine should be huge. He and Al Harrington are all the Hawks have going for them... Which may or may not be better than last season... When Walker was with Paul Pierce in Boston he put up about 20, 8, and 5 for about 4 seasons straight. I expect more of the same from him in Atlanta. "Put it up, Antoine! It'll go in eventually!" will certainly be what he thinks the crowd is chanting.    Fantasy   Impact   ( Jason Terry)   The fantasy outlook is not so promising for Jason Terry. As I mentioned, he's going to the overloaded Mavericks. They have been clearning some space by getting rid of Fortson and Walker, but they still have players who are going to get more time with the rock than Terry. As the starting point guard (according to ESPN), Terry should be able to keep decent assist and rebound numbers. But with Dirk, Stackhouse, and Finley ahead of him in terms of options, his points are almost surely going down. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      According to  urlLink this article , Kwame (Brown, not Jackson) will be ready for training camp after having foot surgery today. I'm sure if something goes wrong, the press will be alerted.   Fantasy   Impact   It's too bad, because, as the article says, he was looking really good. He has been steadily (if slowly) improving since he joined the league. If he recovers as anticipated, he should maintain a draft position around where he was last year. With no real history of injury (not that he's been around long enough to have a history of anything), he should be a relatively low risk pick. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       So we all know   Shareef   (I think we're on a first name basis), has been demanding to be traded from the Blazers so he can have a starting role somewhere else. To be honest, I don't blame him. I hate that players can demand trades and get them, but I think that in situation's like Shaq's and Shareef's it may be somewhat warranted. (Shaq deserved the trade just for putting up with Kobe so long) Shareef is going to be sitting on the bench behind   Darius Miles   and   Zach "Zebo" Randolph.   This much makes sense, especially after his play last season. But here's why I sympathize: The Blazers are not going to be good enough to come close to winning a championship for at least 3-4 years (sorry, but adding   NVE   is not going to do it), and by that time Shareef is going to be getting a little old. As someone interested in the fantasy aspect as well as the basketball of it all, I say, "get him to another team and let him put up the numbers he is capable of while he's still in his prime." It's too bad New Jersey shipped Kittles off to the Clips because with KK, NVE, Miles, Randolph, and   Ratliff   (healthy) the Blazers would have actually looked pretty good.    Fantasy  Impact     If Shareef can't be traded, he'll be stuck on the bench as I mentioned above. He'll likely produce numbers equivalent to those from the second half of last season (after he was traded to Portland). If he remains in Portland, it may just upset him enough that he'll want to show other teams what they missed by not trading for him. Just as a big deal has been made about Shaq wanting to prove that he was the true money player in LA, Shareef will have a chip (granted, a much smaller chip) on his shoulder as well.     If Shareef does get traded to a team where he can be in the starting line up, we can expect numbers more a long the lines of those he has put up for most of his career (19, 9, 3).   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The title-linked article talks about  urlLink Danny Fortson . While he was a fantasy bust last year, that wasn't so much his fault as the Mav's overloading their roster. Mark Cuban likes forwards, can you tell? Anyway,  urlLink the article  got me thinking about whether Fortson can get back to the 16 and 16 he had in 2000 (granted, he only played 6 games), or even the 11 and 11 he had in 2001 (playing in 77 games). That sure would make him a good pick-up. I'm not sure if it qualifies him as a sleeper...  If he can get back to a double-double average, the Sonics have pulled off one of the better trades I've seen in a while.   Fantasy Impact   The article mentions that he'll be competing for the PF spot with  urlLink Vladimir Radmonovic ,  urlLink Reggie Evans , and  urlLink Nick Collison . They also say the Radman will spend some time at SF, and that Collison may play the 5 against smaller centers. Both of those statements make sense. Collison hasn't played in the NBA yet, so his minutes will likely be limited as he gains more experience. Evans has been given minutes, but hasn't been able to produce like Fortson has in the past (at least not yet). Yahoo has Evans listed before Radmanovic on the Depth Chart, but I find that hard to believe.  Don't bother with Booth (who was traded for Fortson) unless your league is approaching 18 teams deep. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>