<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me and my iTunes “Play Count” feature are homies.  Being a recent convert to the iNiverse (‘round last New Years’), this is about the greatest thing to happen to me in a long, long time for a couple of reasons—mostly, tracking how often I truly listen to each song/album appeals to the deepest darkest recesses of my OCD brain.  Here’s my top 10 (11, really) most-played songs since the beginning of 2004:   Artist	"Song"	(Play Count)  Fatlip	"What’s Up Fatlip"	(25) Kanye West	"My Way"	(22) Kanye West f/ Lauryn Hill	"Self-Conscious"	(19) TV on the Radio	"Blind"	(18) Modest Mouse	"The View"	(17) OutKast	"The Way You Move"	(17) The Black Keys	"I Cry Alone"	(16) TV on the Radio	"Satellite"	(16) Modest Mouse	"Float On"	(15) TV on the Radio	"Dreams"	(15) TV on the Radio	"Ambulance"	(15)  Looking at this, you get a reasonably fair estimation of the music I’ve been most interested in for the past six months.  I’d say that Kanye, Modest Mouse and TV on the Radio have been the three artists I’ve been most intrigued by.  You notice that I like “The Way You Move” much more than “Hey Ya!” just in terms of sheer listenability (although I, like everybody else, think “Hey Ya!” is about as genius of a single as it gets, “The Way You Move” has been stuck in my head more.  Who knew.)  As a comparison, here are the most-played songs in each genre* I have on my iPod:   Artist	    "Song"	(Genre)	   Play Count  The Walker Brothers	"The Sun Ain’t Gonna Shine Any More"	(50’s/60’s)	5 Blue Oyster Cult	"Burnin’ For You"	(60’s/70’s Rock)	9 Tom Waits	"Telephone Call From Istanbul"	(80’s Rock/Alt. Rock)	7 The Black Keys	"I Cry Alone"	(90’s/00’s Alt. Rock)	16 !!!	"Me and Giuliani Down By the Schoolyard (A True Story)"	(Alternative)	12 Iron & Wine	"Naked As We Came"	(Americana)	11 Felix Da Housecat	"What She Wants"	(Electronica)	12 Electric Six	"I’m the Bomb"	(Hard Rock/Heavy Metal)	11 Fatlip	"What’s Up Fatlip"	(Hip-Hop)	25 TV on the Radio	"Blind"	(Indie Rock)	18 El-P	"When the Moon Was Blue"	(Jazz)	5 Soft Cell	"Say Hello, Wave Goodbye"	(New Wave)	2 Lumidee f/ Busta Rhymes & Fabolus	"Never Leave You"	(Pop)	5 Pharell f/ Jay-Z	"Frontin’"	(Pop)	5 Blondie	"Hanging On the Telephone"	(Punk/Post-Punk)	14 Lloyd Price	"Just Because"	(R&B/Soul)	13 Wayne Wonder	"No Letting Go"	(Reggae/Dancehall)	6  What I think intrigues me most about the whole play-count thing (beyond how much I’ve actually listened to something compared to how much I think I’ve listened to it) is this: seeing my own—true—musical taste reflected back at me.  It’s inescapable.  The numbers don’t lie.  So to one-up my own nerdiness and celebrate the midway point of 2004, I put together my top 10 albums of the year so far ranked by the actual number of times I’ve listened to them based on my iPod Play Count.  And it’s pretty accurate.  A couple of really solid albums get left out (Musicology, Madvillainy and The Hold Steady Almost Killed Me), one anomaly sneaks in (High Water: Mark), and a couple of albums that most likely won’t be there at the end of the year show up, but, all in all, things make perfect sense.   The Top 10 Albums of 2004 (So Far):   10.  	Ghostface -  The Pretty Toney Album  9.	El-P –  High Water: Mark  8.	The Von Bondies –  Pawn Shoppe Heart  7.	The Streets –  A Grand Don’t Come For Free  6.	Murs & 9th Wonder –  3:16 the 9th Edition  5.	Cee-Lo –  Cee-Lo Green is the Soul Machine  4.	Iron & Wine –  Our Endless Numbered Days  3.	Rjd2 –  Since Last We Spoke  2.	TV on the Radio –  Desperate Youth, Bloodthirsty Babes  1.	Modest Mouse –  Good News For People Who Like Bad News       *I’ve been fucking around with the genres on my iPod for a couple of months, and these are the ones I’ve settled on for now.  They’re pretty blatant. 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a dream the other night that MTV was running a bunch of old Van Halen videos in order to celebrate the release of Best of Both Worlds.&nbsp; The (faceless) VJ announced that the current video was one of the shortest in the Van Halen pantheon, clocking in at just over a minute.&nbsp; It was an instrumental, and sounded very much like the David Lee Roth version of Van Halen had done an extended version of “Right Now”—possibly inspired by the latest  urlLink Chuck Klosterman article .&nbsp; The amazing was that, in the dream, I watched the video totally coherently from beginning to end.&nbsp; The video was an early one, but was shot on digital video, reality-TV style.&nbsp; It starts with David Lee Roth hitchhiking on a busy street at the bottom of a hill.&nbsp; He catches a ride, but ditches the camera.&nbsp; The cameraman somehow manages to find a ride as well and finally catches up with Roth at the top of the hill, where Roth hang glides off the top of the hill.  Here’s some of the stuff I got from the  urlLink dream dictionary  to help me decipher it:  Camera:&nbsp; Image of experience. Record. Sometimes a means of distancing.  Car:&nbsp; Personal power. Ego.  Jump:&nbsp; Inconsistent in love affairs. Escape from danger. Adventures.  Mountain:&nbsp; Natural elevation of yourself. Aspiration. Success through effort.  Music:&nbsp; Big pleasure in life. Rhythm. Harmony. Need to express yourself.  Television:&nbsp; Movement. Images. Virtual reality. There is something that you wish to observe.  Valley:&nbsp; Life. Protection. Growth. Feeling conformable with the present situation.  Voyeurism:&nbsp; Safe distance from desires. Fear of being discovered.  …so, basically, it looks like I subconsciously envy David Lee Roth for leaving Van Halen to pursue his own creative ambitions.&nbsp; But I also fear him. &nbsp;I think I need to listen to  Crazy From the Heat  and sort this all out. 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There’s something totally hip-hop about Fiona Apple’s new song, “Extraordinary Machine.”  The groove—as it were—is basically just a reworking of “Happy Trails” played with, like, a string section.  Big Dre move circa  Chronic 2001 , right?  Then, she lays down the lyrics and gets away with worse internal rhyming than  To the 5 Boroughs .  (“He’ll let you ride with any guide” and such.)  She adds orchestral flourishes all over the place; accents the end of every line with some sort of percussive bell—I’d like to believe it’s a triangle, but I’m worried that may be asking too much—and if that’s not Wu-Tang, I don’t know what is.  The RZA is somewhere wishing he had used more bassoon.  In a flawlessly composed song (or at least the kind of flawlessly composed song I’m interested in right now), each individual part swoops and flitters in and out of every other individual part, pops up every time you need to hear it—even if it’s only for an accent—but retains its own iconoclastic-ness within the song itself, so that if you saw that individual part all Pro Toolsed out next to all the other parts, you might not even be able to tell it belongs to the same song.  Yet it so obviously does.  I’m talking about some serious mind-melding voodoo shit.  I’m talking about Ghostface Killah’s “One.”  I’m talking about Daft Punk on “Around the World.”  I’m talking about “Tangled Up in Blue.”  And I’m saying that Fiona Apple comes  thisclose  to achieving that.  And by this close, I mean that I have some serious reservations about her lyrics and her belabored delivery, but that’s about it.  Fiona just straight up lacks the vocal freedom that Ghostface and Bobby D possess.  Maybe what I mean to say is that there’s something totally Bob Dylan about hip-hop.  Whatever. “Extraordinary Machine” might still end up as the song of the year.  It wouldn’t sound out of place in, say, 1954. (That is, if it weren’t for the batshit personal revelations Fiona always thinks she’s having in her lyrics.  Those are total new millennium.)  But it feels so vital to  now .  And when your song takes its cues even more from Spike Jones than even from Dylan or Dre—which “Extraordinary Machine” does—if you want to be vital, you’ve gotta be at the top of your game—which Fiona Apple is—and that may require being more than a little insane.  And there you go.  To sum up:  Daffy Duck is good.  Daffy Duck is great.  If you don’t love Daffy Duck, you don’t love America.   Ten Other Songs That Could Underscore Looney Tunes   Madvillain f/ M.E.D. aka Medaphor – “Raid” Tom Waits – “I’ll Be Gone” The Magnetic Fields – “Fido, Your Leash is Too Long” Brother Ali f/ Slug – “Blah Blah Blah” Mouse On Mars – “Diskdusk” Nobody – “This Will Be Our Year” Common – “I Am Music” Rjd2 – “Ghostwriter” Soul Coughing – “Screenwriter’s Blues” Eminem – “Kill You” 
    
</post>


</Blog>