<Blog>


<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Note to self:   Stop reading pretentious hipster bullshit like  urlLink Pitchfork . Oh don't look at me like that. It passes the time. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Yay Christmas!   And Yay For My Bitchy And Totally Untraditional Family!  We have no tree, we're going to see Return of the King tomorrow, we get to open our presents tonight, and we're having yummy chicken curry for dinner tomorrow!  Yeah, Bitches.    Addendum:  Yay for  urlLink HD  and his awesome mix tapes!  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Brother: You can be kind of a bitch sometimes. Mother: Well, you  do  get on people's nerves sometimes.  Wow.  Happy Fucking Holidays.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Thank you for the comics,  urlLink Paul!  Way to be  totally awesome .
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Totally saw the Return of the King yesterday (which might also be called THE BEST DAY EVER). It rocks harder than your mom, but you already knew that.   Some other things of note: - Showers are fun.  Very  fun. - I scored in the ninety-seventh percentile in the verbal section of the PSATs. My math score?  We don't talk about that.   - All I want for christmas is a  urlLink Trogdor  hoodie. - Sometimes I'm so california it hurts. I went to see The Revolution Will Not Be Televised, which I thought was very interesting and entertaining, in Berkeley. Also? I find it hilarious that Eddie Izzard: Dressed to Kill is recommended for those that enjoyed The Revolution on IMDB because I LOVE IT SO MUCH.  It is  Christmas  Winter break and you may be sitting at home wondering "Whatever will Shanti be doing to occupy her valuable time over this joyous holiday?" Then again, you might not. I will, however, answer my own slightly megalomaniacal question: ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.  Chances are there will be a couple more awkward family fights that result in my brother not talking to me for four days. (I'm sorry I didn't know it's not cool to joke about the lubricant you leave out in plain sight I will avoid doing so at the dinner table next time ok thanks bye.)   I wanna be your wife, you can beat me every night. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Hott  - Rolling out of bed and heading to a Starbucks in a posh part of town wearing no make-up and your pajamas. Why? Because I wanted a gingerbread latte, natch. - Making out with cute boys in cars. - Correct spelling and proper punctuation. - Riding the trikes around Toys R Us on a saturday night. We rock 1526% harder than you do. - The Decemberists. I will totally have your babies if you take me to see them at Bottom of the Hill on Jan. 15th. No, seriously.   Nott  - Um. You. - Getting the facts of life speech from your father. Boys are only after one thing you say? Well gee, thanks for the heads-up. Ass. - This insane super flu. I don't want to alarm anyone but I might be dying a little bit. - That little wrinkle you get between your boobs from wearing a cardigan too long.  - Missing the  urlLink Frontalot  show in SF because you didn't check your email earlier.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       An open letter.   It hit me with the force equivilent to a drop kick in the face. You're a total asshole. You've been one all along. How could I not see that? Maybe I had some rare form of brain cancer. I don't know.  You grate on my nerves. Every little thing I overlooked for the sake of it just irritates the sweet ba-jesus out of me. From one manipulative bitch to another  See you in hell.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Be honest now...   Is it completely nerdy of me to want  urlLink this  for Christmas? Ok I can deal with that.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So as you can see I've got a whole new look. Different address and everything.  I didn't think it was possible, but events in my life have left me 5,482 times more bitter than when I first started out. Bring it on, you bitches. The more you beat me down the angstier I become.  I am a fucking  emo machine .  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Mordant.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Note to self:    BEST.WEEKEND.EVER. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Things I did not do today:   Fight the Power. Trust Whitey. Go to school. See Coheed and Cambria at Bottom of the Hill. Anything productive.   Things I did do today:  Lock myself out of my goddamn house, dammit. Polish off an entire package of Milk Chocolate Milano cookies. Don't look at me. Watch The Creek. That's pretty much it, actually. My life is sad. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My hometown is totally name-checked in that new  urlLink The Network  song. Yeah, the context is pretty accurate. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *Sad Face*  I have the sniffles.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today's Public Service Announcement   Friends don't let friends drink and dial.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink These  are the best panties EVER. I want to buy every pair on the face of the planet and live in a giant pile of them. Is that weird?
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink        urlLink Which Takeshi's Castle Character are you?   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Did I ever tell you guys about the sexy dream I had about  urlLink Corin Tucker ?  Hm. Nevermind then...
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What is new in my life. In bullet points.   - I have a new boyfriend. (Yeah yeah...) He definitely doesn't suck. In fact, he kind of rocks my face off. And also, he has Tech TV. - I'm completely obsessed with Lingo, this shitty show on the Game Show Network (Whose website blows, by the way.) I tried to find a fansite but I can't. And maybe that is for the best. - I've been procrastinating like hell and Finals are a mere two weeks away. Fuck me. - SheeplovR2: nothgins better then post messiah birth sex - Quick survey: What is your favorite flavor of jelly bean? 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My beautiful, shiny red Honda, she is totalled. Thanks to a drunken asshole in a truck slamming on his brakes for no apparent reason. The next thing I know I'm slamming on my brakes, staring at his god damn trailer hitch, and colliding. My glasses flew off and with my fuzzy gimpy vision I watched him take off as fast as he could. I put the car in park and got out, surveying the damage. I'm not quite sure but at some point I think I actually fell to my knees on the pavement and yelled "KHAN!!!" I can't make sense of why my life is in such a bad way right now. My mom's last day of work was fucking YESTERDAY. What am I going to do?  Frankly I think this is Jesus punishing me for hating his movie, which I saw earlier in the evening. At least no one was hurt.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I currently can't stand:    Condescending nerds My grades The fact that I actually started  trying  to do well and I'm repaid with a big old kick in the balls. The balls that I do not possess.  Worrying Weekdays This god damn rain when I am forced by the public school system to stand outside for thirty minutes DAMMIT. Sad daffodils dying on my desk ... Oh fuck it. No one cares. Not even I care for chrissakes.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two people I have crushes on because I am weird:  The new mayor of San Francisco,  urlLink Gavin Newsom . Oh you know power is sexy.  And also?   urlLink MIKE PATTON TURNS ME ON.  Yeah, I've been listening to A Small Victory (Faith No More) nonstop for about three days now.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Boy, I sure do love failing. I tell you there's nothing better than straight up  SUCKING  at everything I attempt. No pressure there, no sir. But of course I'm not bitter. No wait scratch that because  I TOTALLY AM .   I'm going to go weep in the corner about how my life is awful like the pathetic emo kid I secretly am inside.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And also?  HAPPY BIRTHDAY  urlLink SHEEPY , YOU OLD SALT.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My life? Sucking. Actually, what comes after sucking? Because it's totally that. I don't feel like getting into the particulars because I'm a vague bastard. I'm just generally sucking at life. Isn't that what being a teenager is all about? Hey world? I'm flipping you off right now.  By the way, I hate  urlLink Melos. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I choo-choo-choose you.   So that Valentine's Day thing is just around the corner, and for some reason people keep asking me what I'll be doing.  A) Why do you care? B) I will probably be watching Lingo with Mr. Tech TV (TM  urlLink Jacob ), hugging a hippo, and drinking toffee nut lattes from Starbucks.  C) The thing about V-Day (I hate that abbreviation but for expedience's sake) is that yes, it's a Hallmark holiday. Created to make money and sell poorly-made stuffed bears from Taiwan. But the other thing that irritates me is that it gives people without "Valentines" (Jesus what a dumb concept.) the excuse to feel sorry for themselves. I'm sure I've fallen victim to this as well, because I'm a lame ass. I would find proof in the archives but I'm also lazy. Sue me. With that said... D)  urlLink Muffin , will you be my internet Valentine?  This just in, I am officially the lamest woman alive.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Because I'm secretly a fourty-six year old gay man from San Francisco, and because I rock so god damn mother fucking hard, I went to a Bette Midler concert this evening with my mother. Hey... Shut up.  Eh I'm just talkin' some jive. I'm going to go pass out now. Goodbye for now, my delicious creampuffs.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back. Hooray for internet.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No, I'm not dead. As good as, in my horrific unconnected existence. Do you realize that I have to actually, like,  go outside  to amuse myself? I mean what the fuck. And there is a significant lack of pornography in my life right now. I'm kidding. Or am I? No, I'm totally not. My mommy bought me a new computer, but I have no idea when the internet will be hooked up. Hopefully when I return to chez moi. Good Christ am I tired of mooching off my boyfriend's internet. And Tech TV. And Gameshow Network. Did I mention he's the best? Ever? Well my bebes, Lingo is on, so it's time for me to depart. I shan't be gone long.   XoXoXo  Shanti
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Prom is stupid.  Like that's going to stop me from going. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I may hate Melo and have no soul, but  urlLink he  makes me laugh.   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pinch me.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am many things -- teenage cynic, obsessive-compulsive punctuation corrector, unlicensed surgeon -- and now I am the driver of a manual car. It was tough learning, and yes I'm still popping it in first gear but you know what I am just learning so I'll see you in hell Guy Behind Me At The Stop Light Honking At Me In Your Piece Of Shit Van.  Mmmm... Catharsis.  Also, my mother is going out of town on Thursday.  Party over here...
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The comments are the best part.   What a bunch of bullshit. A protest will do nothing. Kids are just looking for attention and an excuse to get out of class, and hey, I respect that. But seriously if that's what you're about own up to it. Otherwise get over your naivete and face the fact that your attempt at activism will accomplish nothing.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              I don't know what to write about anymore. If I write about my problems I'm emo, if I talk about relationships... I guess I'm still emo. My problems seem trivial.  It's not that I care about the feedback, it just goes a long way in discouraging me to write. I mean.. Eh fuck it I don't even know what I'm trying to say.        (Girlfriend) Let me break it down for you again. Christ I can't believed I just referenced a Lauryn Hill song. I'm so nineties right now. But I digress... Basically my life -- life in the grand scheme of things being a series of peaks and valleys -- is in the valley-est valley that was ever a valley. Let me work that word in  one more time . Quite frankly, I don't see the need to display my "emoness" for all to see. (I'm going to go off a tangent right now. I am so sick of that god damn label. Buzz words in general irritate me, but it's becoming a plague of our generation. Actually, this could just send me into a rant about existentialism and the definition of one's self, and trust me nobody wants to be privy to that.)      In conclusion, this is what my paper journal is for. I don't know what this means for old Bessie, but I know one thing, I'm going to get a new template.   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Someone shoot me, please?
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - Prom was a lot of fun. You tell me there's something better than shaking your ass to stupid songs or singing Don Henley as you're coming home in a limo, and I'll tell you to suck on my junk.  - In unrelated news, to the jackass in the 1987 Honda hatchback in front of of me on 680 just outside of Fremont: It's called the fast lane for a reason, motherfucker. Don't get in it unless you are prepared to BRING IT. I cannot stress that enough.  - I'd slice a man in the face to be able to go to Coachella.   - For the life of me I cannot get  urlLink Black Betty  out of my head. Side note: The link was originally to the Nick Cave version of the song, and when I erased the link the sentence said "For the life of me I cannot get head." I laughed and laughed and laughed, because I'm actually eight years old.  -  urlLink Here you go, bastards. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink I love this word.    urlLink Greg, is that you?   Last night I had a dream that my boyfriend's mom came and redecorated my room against my will. Yeah. I don't know either.     
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Stupid Prom Update:  I bought my dress, (strapless, burgundy, Jessica McClintock).  Next up?  Shoes , bag,  accessories .  Following that, picking a place for dinner. And then the excrutiatingly awkward photo session with everyone's parents.  I can't wait.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holiday what? Resurrection who?  Happy Easter, or something.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How to make me laugh:  - Tell me about the time you had a bee in your pants and were subsequently stung several times in the groin area.  - Put on MC Chris when I'm in a bad mood. How can I resist "Her cunt tasted like skeletons"? - Silly pop culture references always get my proverbial goat. - Show me a picture of when you at halloween when you were four and dressed up as a ninja turtle. (!!!) - Call me "madame". - (Not exactly part of the list but relevent because I laughed quite a bit at this movie) Holy shit have you guys seen  urlLink The Substitute?   I knew it would be awesome when Ernie Hudson broke a board the Woodshop class made him and then giving a lecture about harnessing your chi. And then there was the fight in the school library! And the most awkwardly acted sex scene ever! And it was awesome!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lists are the last resort of the uncreative. Check it out!  Things that are lame: - Boys who break their edge - Boys who have edge - Quirky teachers - My irrational love of The Newlywed Game. Yeah I know I'm like thirty years late on that one. - Me not having my dress yet - Me not owning one damn pair of pointy toed flats - The mutha fuckin TIME CHANGE. DAMN YOU,  urlLink UNIFORM TIME ACT OF 1966!  - Me still not grasping the concept of  urlLink Schroedinger's Cat. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On a completely different note, big ups to  urlLink Paul  for being my Mr. Bungle hook-up. It rocks my motherfucking face off in six point three different ways.   No foolin'. Good Christ that was lame. I'm sorry.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow I can't wait till I'm older and I get to tell stories like "The Time I Accidentally Had Anal Sex."  April Fools. The anal was intentional.  Just kidding. Or am I?   No, I totally am.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My uncle died today.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I  might  have a bit of a problem with socializing. After all I'm writing this shit instead of being "out there", uh, looking at drunk people. I guess. Is that how parties work?  Mmm Internet, you are my social safety net.  Anyways, I don't see what the big deal is about the "party". What if you don't know anyone? Then it's all about finding someone to talk to who won't throw up on your shoes. Fuck that. It's like the High School Theory. Find someone who will let you stand next to them.   Ugh.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A new post, in which I whine.   Waahhh... 1)My uncle is really sick. Doctors are saying it doesn't look good. 2)My mom is out of town for a week. Doesn't seem like such a bad thing but I have the flu and now there is no one to take care of me. 3)I kind of just want to curl up in a ball and die.   That is all. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You, stop being such a fucking drama queen. You, ENOUGH of your pity-me bullshit. You, stop telling me about your dumbass problems. I don't give a shit.   Now naturally I'm being a coward and making these announcements anonymous, but I've got some aggression I need to get out of my system. In conclusion, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD SHUT THE FUCK UP.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The  urlLink Song Fight  show last night was awesome. Despite being held in  urlLink Vagina Central . The only band I really enjoyed was  urlLink The John Benjamin Band , for their delightful renditions of "My Sister" and "Red Robot". And then, of course, there was  urlLink Front , who rocked the mike ten ways from Sunday. That's all I need to say about that.  P.S. DEAR MC FRONTALOT I DID NOT KNOW YOU HAD SUCH A CUTE ASS. KTHXBYE.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things that make me sad:  - When I rant to my mom about how much I hate Rupert and the fact that he won the additional million and then I get back upstairs and realize that she TOTALLY WAS NOT LISTENING AND DID NOT CARE. AT ALL.  - When I dream that I had a tiny little grey kitten that I held all day and I wake up and there is, in fact, no kitten. Hell, I don't even LIKE kittens.  - The fact that I can best my boyfriend at EVERY ARGUMENT WE HAVE EVER HAD. * Related, the fact that we barely ever have anything to argue, much less fight, about. Sometimes I need an itty bitty fight to spice things up. Does this make me a horrendous bitch? Ok, I can deal with that.  - The fact that my english teacher had to look up the word "argument" in class today to see if there was an 'e' in it. What is UP, California public school system?  - When I dream that I have these wicked hott tattoos on my hips and I look stunning in low rise jeans and I wake up to find that neither are true.  - Blogger comments.   NOT PART OF THE LIST BUT BEAR WITH ME BECAUSE IT NEEDS TO BE SAID. Gentlemen, and Ok I guess Ladies too: When you respond to a compliment with arrogance, it does not come off as cute or cheeky, it comes off as "asshole".  There's your goddamn PSA for the day.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      JKLSDFJKLSFDJKAASJFD  SATURDAY. TO SEE FRONTALOT. IN BERKELEY.  WILL IT BE RAD? I SUBMIT THAT IT WILL.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that when you buy  urlLink these , you should also receive a sticker that says "Hi, I'm an alcoholic."
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dear Blogger,  You know I'm uncomfortable with change. What up? P.S. Beige is SO over.   In other news I took the AP Psychology test today.  urlLink Jacob , I saw you there but I did not approach you. Instead, I merely observed you like the creepy stalker that I am.  I'm not sure how I did. Multiple choice was aces, free-response? Not so much. Ooh, maybe I'll get in trouble with the authoritarian AP nerds for discussing the test. Wouldn't that be exciting.  Yeah you're right. It totally wouldn't.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well she's sexy and seventeen  My little rock-roll queen  Acts a little bit obscene  Gotta let off a little steam  Dig that sound shake it around your mind , mind , mind   Hooray for being seventeen, the age no one cares about! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      GO TIME MACHINE, GO!  Can it just be my birthday now, please?
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink I have to beat off now. Excuse me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       AWKWARD:  Hearing that my dad's  wedding vows  included the story of how he met his bride, but the universe conspired against them to keep them apart, and that seeing her again two and a half years ago made him  realize how unhappy he was . With his children. And his wife of twenty years. And he said this in front of my brothers.  This is classic My Dad behavior. Jackass.   FUN:  Underwater karate.   ALSO AWKWARD:  Running into the ex and  his entire crew  at Starbucks. I seriously felt like committing seppuku right then and there. Ugh.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm glad I caught you on my view screen, Sailor   I don't know what it is about  urlLink that song , but it totally  makes me want to do it .   Continuing in that vein, here are some other songs that just rev me the fuck up. (Alternate title, Mix To Play When You Are Getting All Kinds Of Intimate.) 1) The Jon Spencer Blues Explosion - She Said 2) Velvet Underground - Venus in Furs  3) PJ Harvey - The Letter (Jesus that is a sexy-ass song.) 4) The Killers - Kill Me Now  5) The Clash - The Guns of Brixton 6) Cat Power - Sea of Love (Other versions also acceptable.) 7) The Cure - Pictures of You 8) Jesus and Mary Chain - Just Like Honey 9) H.I.M - Endless Dark (Sentimental.) 10) Johnny Cash - The Man Comes Around (Drives me crazy.) 11) Tom Waits - Cold, Cold Ground 12) Malcolm Mclaren - About Her 13) The Faint - Sex is Personal 14) Sparklehorse - King of Nails 15/16) Pixies - No. 13 Baby / Hey (Double the pleasure, double the fun.) 17) The Smiths - Wonderful Woman 18) Faith No More - A Small Victory  19) Arab Strap - I Still Miss You 20) Shudder to Think - Hot Ones (Naturally.)  21) Leonard Cohen - Hallelujah (The coup de gras.)
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My dad is getting re-married this weekend.Still feel weird about it.   I don't think I'm gonna go.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was tidying up my room a bit today and I came across an old bag of mine (Mm..Loop NYC) and I noticed there was a great deal of  stuff  at the bottom. I peered into the bag and said what the fuck? Inside that tote bag was all the lip balm/stick/gloss that this world has ever produced. And also, two packs of Juicy Fruit and an unopened pack of peach Smints (which, by the way, are the greatest things ever.) It was like my birthday came twice in one year. I've only used this bag once, so where the hell was I going and why did I need that much stuff?   I am puzzled, to say the least.  ETA: I'm finding the strangest things in my closet. Two plaid miniskirts. Because one was not enough? When and why did I buy those? Also found: - Purple corset (I think I wore that to a wedding a couple of years ago. God I sound like such a goth faggot.) - Knee high pointy toed boots (Wore to homecoming sophomore year. Shut up, it went with my suit.) - Ugly but comfy floor length green skirt.   Wow. If I had a time machine, I would go back and shoot myself for making such horrid fashion choices. That would mean that I wouldn't exist, but thinking too much about the complexity of the space time continuum makes my head hurt. I'll just look out the window and think about birds for awhile.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am loving summer at this point. So far I have: - Swam at night in a stranger's pool. - I cannot fully disclose but there was a shower involved. - Played Life for the first time ever and won. Yay Business! - Played Parcheesi (The Royal Game of India!) with my mom and boyfriend and totally kicked their asses. - Also played Win Lose or Draw. (Wasn't Jim J. Bullock in that?) Kind of fun with two people but I've been into the board games recently. - Gotten new glasses that I look really hott in.  Sure it sounds trivial but considering dance camp starts soon and from that point on I will not have a moment's rest until my big solo recital in August, I'm trying to savor it while I can.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Like, oh my god. I'm so totally a senior now.  Sign my virtual yearbook, assholes.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friend One: [Makes pun about the Breakfast Club] Friend Two: We should be the Brunch Club. Me: Oh, totally. We'll come with a slice of cantalope on the side.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's three in the a.m and I am writing my god damn Psych final.  Fuck off.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If I ever had a band I would name them "You haven't heard of them".
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's get frivolous!  Here are some clothes I want: -  urlLink I'm into birds on clothing recently.  -  urlLink They have whales on them, people. WHALES.  -  urlLink It's the most popular design for a reason.  -  urlLink Shit yeah.  -  urlLink ADSJSKNDSI   And also, it's the end of the year crunch and I'm full on freaking out. This weekend I have to write my psychology final and a research paper as well cram for finals.  Fun stuff.  P.S. Because this post sucked.  urlLink Heh. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rabbit rabbit.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A) My arm looks gigantic. B) I'm hiding. I'll be back in a few days. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    SUCK MY BACK.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Xangas are so terrible that I think they give me cancer.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am glad that Kerry selected Edwards as his running mate because I think that Edwards is a hottie.   What, my opinion is relevent too.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You do not know as much as you think you do.  You are not as clever as you imagine yourself to be.  Your writing sucks.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back. I did my arangetram. You don't care.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>