<Blog>

<date>30,August,2002</date>
<post>


           
      I just got back from a performance at the Children's Museum. It was so embarassing what we had to do, we all had to sing in front of all these two and three year olds.  On the plus side though, Lucy looked pretty good in her peacock dress...
     

        
</post>

<date>29,August,2002</date>
<post>


           
      As usual I'm not doing anything interesting.  My dad came back from China yesterday and that's good because he brought back a lot of cool -- but bootlegged-- DVD's including Rush Hour 2 and Training Day, what sux though is that the quality isn't that good.  He also brought me back a cool RPG for the computer that's all in chinese.  It's pretty good, it's based on the ancient chinese myth, "The Battle of the Gods", you're a god and you go around killing other gods.  I got past the first world easy, but the second world's mad hard.  Once you appear like 12 swordmen and 4 bowmen ambush you.  It's easy to kill the swordmen cuz like two slashes of ur sword will kill them, but its so hard to get past them without getting killed by the bowmen who are far away and you cant kill with your sword.  Oh well, I'll find a way 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,August,2002</date>
<post>


           
      ahhh...i get it now it's a stationary background, don't mind me, I'm just testing out the new blog
     

        
</post>

<date>28,August,2002</date>
<post>


           
      aaah, that's scary the frames move too if you scroll sideways, i guess for best viewing you should maximize the screen so you can see all that you need to w/o scrolling
     

        
</post>

<date>28,August,2002</date>
<post>


           
      whoa I just realized this, but if you scroll up and down, the cubes move with the screen...
     

        
</post>

<date>28,August,2002</date>
<post>


           
      This is my first entry in the blog, I'm not going to write much because not much has happened lately, other than recently getting over a stint of conjunctivitis, during which my vision was seriously impaired and I was found walking into walls and trying to read books upside-down.  Oh well, I'm better now
     

        
</post>

<date>30,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Ok I've decided to keep everybody posted on the situation of our soccer team. From now on whenever we have a game, I will display the results as follows:   Tigers Score --- 1 Walpole Score - 3   Overall Record-- 0 - 6
     

        
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      I feel like quitting Chinese Chorus.  Everybody else in the chorus is quittng.  I'm not joking, there's only four people left who are over eight years old.  Even Lucy left, so I don't see any point in staying.
     

        
</post>

<date>12,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      No one's gonna under understand this except Dietz and Me but I'll say it anyways.  Alex: Who did the Nazi's make an alliance with?  Loren: Presumably someone much shorter!  That wasn't as funny as I expected...
     

        
</post>

<date>12,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Ok, I haven't said anything in a while so here goes.  School has been alright, a lot like Day, except much bigger and with more passing time.  I'm gonna be on the North Soccer team come wednesday, but I'm gonna be like fourth string.  One interesting thing that happened to me so far was once when I was walking to lunch, someone i didnt know, presumably an upperclassman, picked me up, put me on his shoulder, walked to the end of the hall then put me down again.  It was pretty weird.  I see to be losing quite a bit of sleep lately, going to bed at 12 and waking at 6.  but there's always the weekend to make up for that.  My procrastination is catching up with me, and I have to change my ways soon.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      With school starting up in a couple days, I had to find a way to exercise my brain, and what better way to do that than to pick out the flaws in the plots of TV shows and movies.  First I was thinking about "Small Soldiers" for some reason.  Then it hit me.  You know how they inserted those military chips into the toys.  Where would they get millions of military chips.  And those chips cost a lot of money, wouldn't they go bankrupt selling $20 toys with million-dollar chips in them?  Then I started watching "Malcolm in the Middle", the one on Sunday, You know when all the different groups started fighting because of the Krelborns? Well, I thought "There's got to be sth wrong with this" Then I thought about it and looked at the diff groups, there were the jocks, goths, skaters, and the posers, and then I was like, "Wtf, there's no group of posers, that's why they're called posers, cuz they act like people in other groups."  That's all for now, I'll probably add to this later...
     

        
</post>

<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Happy birthday Amy... yesterday... I would have said that earlier, but I was up until two in the morning yesterday doing my stupid flipbook for Math and character sketch for English.  That flipbook took me f***ing five and a half hours to finish, it's so time-comsuming, drawing almost the same thing over and over again, and i did it by hand.  I started it right when I got home from Soccer parctice at 5:30ish and worked until 11:15.  Then I started my Character sketch at 11:30, and finished at 1:20.  It took me so long to search through the whole book and find quotes because I wanted to go to sleep so badly....
     

        
</post>

<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Other recent events in my life:  In Model U.N. I'm representing the Lao People's Democratic Republic, more commonly known as Laos.  My efforts on the Math Team have gotten their reward, I have been upgraded to "A" Team, with a sophomore moving down.  That sophomore is actually my Chinese school teacher, I hope she doesn't like fail me because I took her spot.  Now there's two freshman on the five-person total "A" Team, Brian and me.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      The season's over, we have been doing remarkably well lately, and I came so close to scoring today, the ball was rolling away from me right in front of the goal and all I had to do was slide and I would have had it. Instead I tried to run it down and the defender beat me to it.  Oh well. Our record for the season was 1-13  I'm going to compare the first ten games of the season with the last four now:  Record:  1st ten: 0-10 Last four: 1-3  Points scored:Points allowed  1st ten- 5:55 Last four- 7:9  See an improvement?  Today we played Needham, the team we lost 9-0 to, they beat us 3-0... it would have been 3-1 but I hesitated on my slide, jeez.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      We Won!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Tigers-- 3 Natick- 1  They were a team with a winning record too...  Overall record: 1-10
     

        
</post>

<date>12,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      We Won!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Tigers-- 3 Natick- 1  They were a team with a winning record too...  Overall record: 1-10
     

        
</post>

<date>12,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      We had our first math meet on Wednesday, it wasn't as hard as I expected, but it was still pretty hard. We had two split up into A-team, and B-team, because we had too many people, so I got put on B-team with Ian and Kevin. North B-team came in dead last with 13 points [9 of which were mine, 3 Ian's, and 1 Kevin's]. North A-team got 41 points total.  Brian Liu was on A-team and he scored 14 points argh he beats me at everything.  I'm happy because I got more points than my Chinese School teacher and one of the juniors.  North A-team beat South A-team, so I guess thats all that matters.
     

        
</post>

<date>04,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Results of Thursday's game  Tigers------ 1 Brookline - 6  Overall Record-- 0-9  Goals scored to goals allowed ratio- 5 : 52  Coach got pissed at us so he cancelled practice on Friday
     

        
</post>

<date>04,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Results of today's game  Tigers ----- 0 Weymouth - 7  Overall Record-- 0-8  Goals scored to goals allowed ratio:  4 - 46
     

        
</post>

<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      We've sunk to a new and far worse low...  Tigers Score ---- 0 Needham Score - 9  Overall Record-- 0-7
     

        
</post>

<date>27,November,2002</date>
<post>


           
      In Model U.N. monday, they had a speech contest.  We had to give an effective 30 second speech about Global Warming using only words that began with "I" or "T"...and they all have to be real words and make sense.  I think that this industrial toxin, that illuminates the troposphere, is insufficient to invent treaties.  The temperature takes time to increase, therefore I think that immeadiate involvement isn't tenable.  The task is tremendous, to tell industrial territories to trim their industrialism.  The imperious territories that insist that the treaty is imperative, impede the tiny territories' trails to increase their thrift.  This treaty therefore then increases the tiny territories's instability.  
     

        
</post>

<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>


           
      A coupla days ago in English, while explaining the Fall of Troy Ms. Craig-Olins said:  "Those who did not die were killed"  I forget where I heard this, so I won't cite it, don't sue:  "Some day, a New Yorker is gonna go to Africa or Latin America and say, 'Boy, there are a lot of minorites here.'"  Another funny thing that was said by Al:  1) We go to Africa, and I say, "Boy, look at all those black people." Then Al says, "Not black people, Loren, African-Americans" 2) We go to India, and I say, "Boy, look at all those Indians."  Then Al says, "Not Indians, Loren, Native-Americans."  Bush:  Rarely is the question asked, "Is our children learning?" 
     

        
</post>

<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>


           
      I did so much better than I thought I would this meet.  I expected pretty much 2 points and I got 8, pretty good.  I actually beat Brian, who got 6 points. Last meet I got 9 and he got 14.  I could have potentially have gotten a 16, but I was so stupid.  I forget that parallel lines had equal angles at intersecting points, and that screwed me.  Then I completely left off two really ez questions.  North-A came in fifth place overall, I think North-B came in 7th or 8th.  Still not quite sure, but I think Me and Brian still lead the pack with 17 and 20 respectively. 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,November,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Not sure, but I think with Yin Zhao gone, Me and Brian are the highest contributors to the Math team, two freshman wow, well, it won't last past this meet.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,November,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Math Meet tomorrow, I think I'm gonna do horrible.  On the practice round I literally got 4 out of 18 points.  I sucked so badly.  Like everybody on B-team cept maybe Kevin is gonna do better than me and then they're gonna put me back on B-team.  I know Anne, probably Kanwei, and probably Ian are gonna do better than me.  I cannot multiply matrices for crap, even though we learned how in liked 7th grade, and Geometry is so ez once you get it, but it takes so long for me to find the way.  
     

        
</post>

<date>08,November,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Oh yeah I got a 120 on my Chinese midterm and Anne's really proud of me.  Yay...  Yesterday I got my Latin test back, and i got a 105, i was like Holy crap thats a good grade.  I find ironic that I'm far more enthusiatic about a 105 in Latin than a 120 in Chinese, in which lately I've been struggling.  Maybe its because Anne's been so mortherlike to me. it's so weird, she's only a sophomore, but she talks to me in such a condescending manner.  At Yin Zhao's farewell party, she even poured my drinks for me... without me asking her to, she just took the cup out of my hand and poured a drink, I got really confused, I was like "Wtf..." except i didnt really say that.  And then when I accidently got some chalkdust on my back, she started like helping me sweep it off, and being like, "Here, I'll do that for you." Idk maybe its just goodwill, but how often do you see that in a highschooler, and even so, an underclasswomen.  Oh well, I guess I have a second mom, not to say that she has any involvement with my dad...i hope.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,November,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Contrary to comments made in Alex's speech in Model U.N. in which he stated that everybody had nuclear weapons, and the US should not pick on Iraq, I am going to state that not everybody has nuclear weapons.  The country I'm representing, for example, Laos, does not possess any nuclear weapons.  Lao's navy also consist of only one merchant ship but that besides the point.  In addition, Laos has a miniscule GDP of only 9.2 billion dollars compared to that of the US ($10.082 trillion).  Lao's per capita is $1,630, while the US's is $36,300.  And yet Laos is the third largest illicit opium producer, producing an estimated 200 metric tons in 2001 with 22,000 hectares of cultivation.  According to the CIA, Laos is also a "potential heroin producer; transshipment point for heroin and methamphetamine produced in Burma; illicit producer of cannabis; growing methamphetamine abuse problem".  The exports of Laos include sweet potatoes, vegetables, coffee, sugarcane, tobacco, cotton; tea, peanuts, rice; water buffalo, pigs, cattle, poultry, and corn, or as the Indians called it, maize.  Another famous Indian was Crazy Horse.  In conclusion, Laos is a land of contrast.  
     

        
</post>

<date>30,December,2002</date>
<post>


           
      I have so much homework over the weekend: Latin stupid stuff, two pages of questions in French, a page of math and a math project, a paper about Hermes, a paper about the crusades, stufy for a unit test in WH, stupid chinese hw.  Oh yeah I went to Kevin's house and we played DDRMAX workout mode.  After awhile we realized that the more times you stepped, the more calories you burn so me and Kevin were like, "FOOT FIRE!!!", and we burned like 80 calories per song by going crazy.  Then we were making a lot of noise so the downstairs ppl got pissed off.  In English, Alex wrote a summary of one of the books of "The Odyssey" and it had an appositive in almost every sentence (If you dont know what that means you're stupid and shouldn't being looking in my blog).  After hearing him I said: "Odysseus, being a man, walked over there. Athena, seeing him walk over there, also walked over there." Later, Ms. Craig-Olins said that Athena made Odysseus look like a god, so I wrote in my notes, "Odysseus = god).  I was trying to simplify.  In history we watched a video, here's a quote:  "To the Europeans, the world looked like this, with Europe to the lower left. To the Muslims, the world looked like this, with Europe dwarfed by Asia. To the Chinese, the world was China."   Idk, what they mean by "the world was China", it still is...
     

        
</post>

<date>13,December,2002</date>
<post>


           
      We had a math meet this Wednesday at Newton South.  I, myself, didn't do very well, but it was really fun.  A-team came in 4th and B-team came in 7th of 12.  I only got one measly point on B-team.  Brian got F&*%ing 13. North A beat South A, and North B beat South B, so thats all that matters.  There were a lot of laughs at the meet.  First, I didn't realize it, but for some reason I had brought my ping-pong paddle with me to school that day.  Next, because there were no upperclassmen on B-team, all of us had to do really hard rounds.  My rounds were fractions and related word problems, Polygons and Areas involving them, and advanced trigonometry.  Then, on the team round it was really funny.  The team round is three questions that are harder than the ones on the regular rounds, and you can work as a team.  I forgot to put down my paddle, and accidently brought it into the testing room.  Then we got started.  When we got our tests, we really didn't have any idea what to do with the problems so we started like yelling at each other because they weren't doing it right.  Note that we were in the same room as three other teams, including North A.  They just kind of stared at us then went back to their tests.  We finally managed to scrape out an answer for one of the problems with about 30 seconds left. At the 15-second call, we panicked because we didn't have anything worked out for the next two problems.  So we were like, "OMG, just put a random number! Put 6! put 6!". The groups around us were all whispering to each other, "don't believe them, it's not 6".  We wrote it down right when our tests were collected.  We went outside and waited for the answers to be posted.  Guess what the answer was. 6! We got 6 points for team round and had the second highest score for that round, higher than North A, and higher than Boston Latin, Newton South. Praise the Paddle!  Ahhh... Good times
     

        
</post>

<date>28,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Convo between me and Alex:  Alex: "You take three languages?" Loren: "Yeah, French, Latin, and English." Alex: "English isn't a language!"
     

        
</post>

<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Do the weird lyrics contest in my subprofile!
     

        
</post>

<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Johnny get Zkart back on your calculator, I have to beat "Ian's" high score.  It was so annoying, i was playing Zkart on Jonny's Calc in our free, and i got this amazingly high score, like ten times higher than any I got before.  It easily won the honors of being the high score on the calculator.  But then when I went to type in my name, Ian snatched the calculator out of my hand and wrote his name.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I was in Physics doing my WH homework with jacob Levenfeld and then he says, "Oh thats why China is another name for porcelain." Except he pronounced, [or as Alex says, pronunced] it wrong.  He said (Porky-layn) and then I started cracking up.  Jacob's stupid.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      As George and Kevin would say, Al is a "Say Bak Gwai", or at least a "Say Yo Tay Gwai
     

        
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Ok Al, i guess if "convo" isn't a word then "mockamatation" is? And also, wtf is a "rikou" anyways?
     

        
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Convo with Hiro on AIM:  Hiro: You should add this to your sayings section Hiro: Why do doctors call what they do practice?  later in the convo:  Loren: Why did you need a tarpaulin from George? Hiro: Wow, I'm impressed that you spelled that right. Loren: yeah, well Hiro: Anyways, I didn't, I just took it to spite George. Hiro: You should try it sometime, its really fun.  Later in a chatroom: Amy: Who's gothedistance66? Loren: Hiro, ummm he was in science club. Amy: Oh yeah, was he the guy who was swearing a lot?
     

        
</post>

<date>20,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      So bored... so bored that I'm actually updating this thing... I dislike vacation as Amy would say... 
     

        
</post>

<date>13,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I just noticed that yesterday for some reason I wore shorts, even though I missed gym and didn't go to the club 
     

        
</post>

<date>13,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      After the meet bri, ian and I were walking to Ian's car.  Suddenly bri said "Hey guys ima walk into this fence" At the time i wasnt quite sure why he said that.  So then i jumped up to touch the top of the gate thigny that we were going under, and as I came down, I smacked right into a fence.  It really hurt, but bri and ian were laughing their [butts] off.  Then Brian said, "why do you think said that" and i said "oww..." and i ended up with big scrapes on my hand, elbow and back, and i got ian's car all bloody.
     

        
</post>

<date>13,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Hey math meet yesterday, so now for my traditional mass blog posting  So we didn't start off the meet too badly, we were first after the first round with 17 out of a possible 18 points.  Yin got 6, Bri got 6, and i got 5.  Then the second round we only got 10 points, putting us in third.  Brian got another freaking 6 and I got a 4.  The senoir, Greg Yu, frikken 0'd out on us.  We were like wtf!  The third round we got 4 points, and we stayed in third.  I got 1 and Bri got 3.  Anne had to go 0 out on us too that round.  As a matter of fact, Anne 0'd the whole meet.  So then after 4 rounds, we were in 4th, after 5 we were in 5th.  And thats how it ended.  I ended with 10 points, a record for me in highschool, bri got a 15, also a record for him, and Yin got 11.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I just realized how freaky the next couple weeks is going to be... Parents not being here May 1-4, then going to NYC May 8-9, then my birthday May 10....
     

        
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Also my birthday is coming up soon (May 10), don't get me anything though, I hate feeling indebted to ppl cuz of birthday presents, unless I invite you to my birthday party, in which case, get me something, money probably, a new soccer ball would be nice also, (the New Adidas Geo looks really nice, the metallic blue one, i think its only like 20-25 dollars too). I'm not sure what I'm going to do for my party... Probably see some movie or just hang out at my place... I was asking my parents if they'd take us to see "Better Luck Tomorrow", they were ok with it, but idk how your guy's parents would feel about a rated "r" birthday party.  Also I don't even know who I'm going to invite yet... 8 people including myself... who to invite... PJ, Bradley, Alex, John Garabedian, Brian Prince, Brian Liu, Craig, Kevin, Jason, Jacob, Josh, Ian, George (yeah right), Derek, other ppl.... or maybe if i made ppl drive themselves i wouldnt have the problem of fitting everyone in our cars, why'd my mom have to go total the caravan... not that I don't like the new Altima, its really nice... or if we just hang out at my house we wouldnt have to worry about that either... but my house theres nothing to do at all... IDK! Birthday's are a lot less fun than b4... especially planning for them...
     

        
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      My parents are going to be away for a couple days, May 1-4 or 5 i think, thas gonna be fun... PARTY AT LOREN'S! Yeah right, you come to my house I'll shoot you
     

        
</post>

<date>20,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Hey Happy Easter everyone... What's the deal with easter egg hunting?  I never understood why a little kid would want to look around for a bunch of colored eggs that don't even have anything to do with easter.  And how did the bunny get involved?  So confusing... "Look Mommy i found a colored egg!"  When are you going to hear that on any other day?  Maybe I'm biased cuz when i was little my mom made me eat the eggs i found, so the fewer the better... But seriously, an egg isn't like candy, like sweet, you can't play with it much, you cant buy anything with it, what do the little kids wanna get out of finding them?
     

        
</post>

<date>13,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      We were watching a video on reformation in the church during conformation class, and the lady said, "Though many people liked the Avignon Pope, in general the Italians didn't, so they elected a new pope who ruled from Rome.  The Cardinals saw this as a problem.  To fix it, they tried electing another pope..."  Now where is that going to get them?
     

        
</post>

<date>07,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      ok so today, craig and I went over Alex Dietz's hizouse after school, but we basically just hung out downstairs, im'd random ppl on his brother's s/n, and played Super Smash Bros.  But it was so funny when we were leaving.  Alex's father was giving us a ride home and Craig was still getting into the car and all the sudden Alex's father started backing up.  Meanwhile, Craig has like one leg stuck in the car, and he is trying to like hop along with it, and his dad kept backing up until he was out of the driveway and Alex told him that Craig wasn't completely in yet.  Then, Craig got in the car, and he was like "Alex's dad almost broke my leg...And the poor people were laughing at me!" And by that time, Alex and I were cracking up so badly, and apparently so were the movers next door.  Then Craig gave the "poor people" the middle finger.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Titles are weird
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Welcome to the New Blogger!  Your blogs have been migrated to the new, completely redesigned Blogger. Most of the functionality will be familiar as we've built this version to be a more reliable, easier way to manage your blog.   Whoa that's interesting...
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Still can't believe Beckham left Manchester United to play for Real Madrid...  Come on Beck, you're English, you can't play for a Spanish team...  41 million Euros isn't that much...
     

        
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Done with Finals, w000t, yeah you heard me, 3 0's...  Amy is disgusting, even if I'm too shy...  I getting this strange new liking for Emo music, until like a few months ago i didnt even know what it was, commonly mistaking it for other genres...  I need to find the actual almost definition for Emo, google should do the trick.  That strange new icon is really weird  Ah this should do the trick, a site titled "What the heck is Emo anyways"  "This site is intended to be a basic FAQ and primer on emo - short for "emotional." Emo is a broad title that covers a lot of different styles of emotionally-charged punk rock."  That's interesting... Let's read on...  "Lyrics tend toward somewhat abstract poetry, and are usually low in the mix and hard to decipher. Record inserts have lyrics, but often so disorganized and haphazard that they're very difficult to read [unless the record was released on Ebullition Records, in which case there are many inserts on small, brightly-colored papers containing poetic writing from the label owner and all his friends about disillusionment, anger, and things that happened when the writer was four. Such writing is known as emo writing, and there are many, many zines just like that]. Said inserts are almost always done with antique typewriters or miniscule hand-lettering, containing no punctuation or capitalization. Often the only information about the band listed is the band members' first names. Another trait of really emo records is to have no information whatsoever about song titles."  Some emo bands that are actually good: Taking Back Sunday, New Found Glory, Jimmy Eat World, etc...  Commonly mistaken for punk rock, alt rock, stuff like that, actually a branch of those, xcept with more emotion, compare a Taking Back Sunday song to a Blink 182 song, there is a difference, noticeably....  AAAH what am i talking about  Now i see again why no one ever visits this thing
     

        
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      What's with my mass updating this thing, I wait like 2 months between posts and when I do post, its like 20 at a time...
     

        
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I listened to my entire media library today... that's 304 songs... ugh... hold on i strongly doubt that... right now im on song 200... if the average song is 4 minutes long, then that's 15 songs an hour, 300 songs would take 20 hours... hmmm... oh I see, this makes more sense... I started on song 170... 30 songs so far...  thats 2 hours of music... lot less than 20
     

        
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Apparently the Adidas Geo Chrome was actually a Nike Geo Chrome... Nike is such a superior brand... just cuz of the sweatshops... If you get enough Chinese five-year-olds, you can make anything...
     

        
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Finals w00t, yeah right, finals are definitely not w00t material.  So far they havent been that bad.  Math was really easy, english and french wasn't bad, history he gave the entire test to us.   Phys and Latin left...   "Where the hell is Spain?!" ~ Jacob Fleming
     

        
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      720 790  750 780
     

        
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Roger Federer beats both Roddick and Philippoussis in straight sets, that's not cool...  At least Philippoussis made it to finals... I'm happy...
     

        
</post>

<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Roddick and Philippoussis, the two awesomest tennis players, my favorite at least, both adavnce to quarter-finals, w00t.  If they face off in the finals that would be awesome
     

        
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      OK so today was Brian's birthday party.  It was pretty fun, I'm actually still at Brian's house.  We played Melee and Soul Caliber II, the Link one.  The we watched Head of State, which was pretty funny.  The basically I played Darts with Alex for like ten million hours, that was fun.  Today is Andy Roddick's 21st birthday, Happy Birthday A-rod! 
     

        
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Ok I haven't updated this in a long time... mostly because I haven't been doing anything at all during the summer...  I go to MIT every week, don't do anything interesting there...  I stole Jay's entire new cd off Kazaa, but now i think I'm going to uninstall it (Kazaa), because people are going crazy about the subpoenas and stuff...  Andy Roddick is on top of the ATP Champions Race Rankings, good good, Federer is in second, Scud is in ninth, did he have to miss the Masters Tourney at Montreal because of a fever?   umm.. what else to say  I went to Rockport with Alex on his birthday, that was pretty funzo  Got a new desk and chair for my room...  Hung out with random people... (Sam, Jason, Alex, Craig, Kevin, Ian, Brain, JK, Brian Prince, PJ....other people...)  umm...yeah so that is my boring life 
     

        
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I had third lunch Thursday and Friday this week, it was so like eh...  Thursday like no one was there, and I ended up sitting with Anne the whole time while she was doing her like Bio hw.  It wouldn't be that bad but like, sitting with Anne feels like sitting with my mom...  Friday some more people were there but I still didn't like sit anywhere.  I moved like from the Azn Senior table to like sitting with Jason and Josh, to like talking to Anne and Hiro.  Oh oh oh, I just remembered, apparently Hiro wrote about me in his application for Stanford, it was really quite strange.  He talked about after Olympiad when he was still trying to do a problem, and he was trying to use like integrals and stuff, but then I told him that he could just unroll the cylinder and it becomes a rectangle... Good Stuff...  The question was something like, well I am substituting different numbers in: "A right cylinder has a diameter of [4/pi] and a height of [15]. A spiral is drawn from the bottom to the top of the cylinder, making exactly two complete revolutions around the cylinder.  What is the length of the spiral?"  So if you follow, Hiro was trying to use like unnecessarily hard things to solve the problem like calculus and stuff. But really you juat have to unroll the cylinder and then it becomes a rectangle with the spiral being the diagonal of the rectangle, and then you just Pythagorize it.  So that was pretty cool, and then Anne was like, "Now, Loren, when you apply for Stanford, you can be like 'I am the notorious Loren that Hiroaki Tanaka wrote about in his application.'"  Haha good stuff.  Zahntorgsama (5:40:36 PM): i love you MandarinYellow31 (5:40:44 PM): thank you ian Zahntorgsama (5:40:54 PM): welcome  This is getting out of hand...  Oh yeah today in Chem:  Belmarsh: "What does the Silver take from the electrode?" Thomas Foote: "Its lunch money..."
     

        
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      This updating because I'm bored thing doesn't work very well.  I like don't have anything to say at all.  Oh yeah Yilun was reading John's comment, and in response to it she said:  "I would love Loren if I were crazy..."  That's not very nice.  Jason, make your girlfriend be nicer to me...  Oh yeah, and then Ian read what Diane said and all he had to say was:  "My girlfriend loves you, that's not cool"  Yin spinning me around on his head was pretty cool, he has to be like really strong to do that.  I got a ride home from Nong the other day.  He doesn't have that bad of a car, like a Solara.  Anyways, he was listening to like very old school CPop, and I was like "Nong this is terrible"  and so I made him a CD of cooler chinese music.  79:35, that's the closest I've ever gotten.  Ram cleared on my calc, that's not fun... It's also almost out of batteries... I need to find something better to do with my time.  Possibly like my homework.  454, 500 would be so cool.  Quote  Steve: But how is it possible that I weigh three pounds more after running than before? Nong: You were running so fast that you converted energy into mass.  Nong is so great.  edit: Oh yeah I forgot, I made up another word today in my frustration over something, it was like "stab-eeb" or something, it was really weird.  I think what my problem is that when I can't figure out the word to use in time, I will just yell incoherently. *shrug*
     

        
</post>

<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      First of all, did everyone hear that Jason Sullivan and Yilun are going out, wow, how long have we waited for that?  Anyways, so much like amorous emotion is being directed my way, from like improbable sources; it makes me feel uncomfortable.  Me: Everybody loves Loren... John G.: I would love Loren if i were a girl/homosexual.  Diane: ily! Diane: so berry much Me: um ok Me: I feel loved. Diane: u should be loved Diane: i love u b/c i'm a lesbian.. Diane: YUP!! Me: But im not a girl...  Yesterday was the PLAN test, that was pretty easy.  Alex overslept, it was so funny.  Afterwards, we (Alex, John, Jonnykalow(whose name is now shortened to one word) and I) went for lunch and then saw "Runaway Jury."  It was a pretty good movie, but Alex and I agree, that although there was a substantial twist at the end, it didn't deserve to be deemed, "The Biggest Twist of the Year!"  And then, we all went back to John's house where we basically just played Melee, IM'd people and played on our calculators.  Good quote, mine though:  So I was like engrossed in the calculator game, and like in my frustration after dying, I think I like combined several words into one.  "That's so  sore-al !  Whoa, did I just say soral?"  I'm not quite sure what I was trying to say, but looking back, I think it was a combination of "stupid" and "horrible" with like miscellaneous things on the end.  Blogger should really have like a comments section so I know how many people actually visit...  From what I hear, my visitors include: Alex, Jason, John, Julia, Ian, and Me.  This doesn't even have a hit-counter, it's so annoying... especially for a person who lives by getting hits... 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      PLAN test on Saturday, and then I think I am watching "Runaway Jury" with like Alex, Jonny, John, etc.  Sunday I have my Chinese mid-term, I hope I'm still like a teacher's pet, even though I didn't do my hw those times so she gives me a good grade on the test.  Um...  The Table Tennis Bake Sale is on Wednesday, October 29.  Be there and buy like 20 dollars worth of baked goods... It's on the half-day, I wonder if that will help or hurt our business.  Speaking of the half-day, between Tuesday and Wednesday, I only have 6 classes, but they are like the worst to have.  I miss my best classes both days.  Tuesday my schedule would go: English, Math, French.  Wednesday it would be: History, Math, French.  Exciting...  I miss BL twice, 1 Chem, 1 Gym, 1 Comp, and 1 History[which is the only good thing coming from this]  Math sux, if I get a B+ I'm going to blow myself, in a less suggestive way... I'm not a contortionist, though that would be pretty disgusting if I were. 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Blogity blogity blog... I don't really have anything to write...But I am mega bored... It is really hard to buy clothes for me... Oh yeah side-note, today I went out to buy myself I new Ping Pong paddle, but I couldn't find any, so instead I bought I think 3 new sweaters, new shoes, a new frisbee, a ski hat, and like winter glove-y type things... I need to cut down on my implusive spending... Anyways back to it being hard to buy clothes for me... No sweaters like fit me right it so weird, either like the shoulders are way too broad or the sleeves are mega long, or something... I need a new ping pong paddle...  But now I'm short on the cash... Today I must have spent what like at least 150 dollars... Oh well...  Anyways... I think it's gonna be our half coming up this friday, pretty exciting... Too bad I blew all my money... Actually I still have 50 dollars to spend... This is how much money you get if you ask for lunch money every week and don't actually use it...  New idea:  Let's calculate how much money you can save by not buying lunch... Let's say the average person spends 20 dollars a week on school food stuffs, that's like a meal and a drink every day.  4 dollars a day for 180 days... that is... 720 dollars per school year...  Ok. so for a person like me, I might spend 5 dollars a week, or like 1 dollar per day on average. So I save 3 dollars per day [disregarding the fact that I starve].  So that comes out to like 3 dollars a day for 180 days, so like 540 dollars saved... Loren is loaded...  I doubt this plan will actually work though with my huge spending sprees...  Anyways, yesterday at John's house, the following conversation took place:  Me: "Kevin, you do realize that those were down my pants..." Kevin: "W/e I'm eating them anyways"
     

        
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I was bored so I began scanning Yin's xanga, and I decided to do his like about me thing...  [my name is]: Loren. [in the morning i am]: Dead. [all i need is]:  Food and Sleep, possibly not even food and/or sleep. [love is]: Very Confusing... [if i could see one person right now]: Oh definitely it would be... idk... probably [im afraid of]: A bunch of things...  have u ever..  [pictured ur crush naked?]: I plead the fifth... [actually seen ur crush naked]: Haha, I laugh at the thought. [been in love]: real love fake love, who knows... [fallen for ur best friend]: Um... my best friend eh...  [been rejected]: Probably, I don't remember these things... [rejected someone]: I don't think. [used someone]: Me? No... [been cheated on]: Probably. [done something u regret]: Who hasn't. [cried when someone died]: Oh yeah that and a bunch more. [cried because of someone saying something to u]: Sure, real and fake. [drank alcohol]: Probably. [lied]: Sure.  do u ever...  [sit on the internet all day waiting for someone special to im u]: Who doesn't...normal people... [save aol/aim conversations]: Sometimes. [save e-mails]: For a while. [smoke]: Nah. [drink alcohol?]: Not really. [like watching sunrises or sunsets]: Of course, assuming I can get up early enough [trust others way too easily?]: I probably do Idk. [wish u were a member of the opposite sex]: I don't think.  who...  [makes u laugh the most]: Dietzy, haha, or Shep idk. [makes u smile]: A bunch of ppl. [gives u a funny feeling when u see them]: Funny feeling? [has a crush on u?]: hmm...if I knew, would it really be a crush? [can make u feel better no matter what]: um, at times, idk [are easier to talk to: boys or girls]: Guys are stupid, Girls can get annoying, but generally if you have anyone to talk to, it's all good  who was the last person..  [u talked to]: Online, Jason, in person, idk, probably Sam [u hugged]: Anne, i think...she seems like a very huggable person... [u slow danced with]: Hmm, I have to go way back for this one... Melody? [u instant messaged]: Jason [u laughed with]: Dietzy  
     

        
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I've have just learned that my blog actually has like regular visitors, so I will try to update more often I guess...  And even people who I don't even talk to look at by blog, e.g. Julia Kalow.  Anyways, I don't really have anything to say, except that I'm really tired, haven't gone to sleep b4 2 in a while... Also I'm annoyed that the Sox and the Cubs are both out, when they both should have won....  I'll leave you with this Alex quote I guess, this updating business is hard...  "Life expectancy wasn't very high for minors [miners]" ~ Alex Dietz  And of course, we are the coolest mutha-fonkers on the planet.... heh
     

        
</post>

<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      So Saturday I slept over Josh's at Philip's Academy.  I got there at 7 or so and then josh, Lynette, and I debated about what to do for aout an hour.  Josh wanted to get a pizza and Lynette wanted to go to the cemetery, oo spooky...  Anyways, we ended up buying a pizza and eating it in the cemetery, which wasn't a very good idea.  Josh was sitting on someone's tombstone while holding the pizza box, and then dropped the pizza, on some dead body.  Harriet Beecher Stowe is buried in that cemetery... She might wake up and go all "Uncle Tom's Cabin" on us...  So then we walked around for another 3 hours going back and forth between Lynette's dorm, Josh's dorm, and other places, and then finally at like 11:30 me and Josh went back to his dorm.  I met Brian again, and his roommate, Andrew, who is outrageously smart, and other ppl like Vincent, Owen, Aaron, Geoff, etc.  In the morning I had to go to NH, so I had to leave at like early morning, but it was really fun.  Oh yeah today I see the Red Sox play oooooo, what now....  Lynette/Josh I will visit again someday...
     

        
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      刮风这天 我试过握着手  但偏偏 雨渐渐  大到我看不见  还要多久 我才能在身边  等待放晴的那天  也许我会比较好一点   从前从前 有个人爱很久  但偏偏 风渐渐  把距离吹得好远  好不容易 又能再多爱一天  但故事的最后 好像说了拜拜  Quite the Dilemma...  edit: Oh shoot stupid encoding, to read that you have to be in like GB encoding (simplified chinese), i know no one likes simplified but it's so annoying to write in traditional.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      We did pretty well, placing 3rd out of 12.  We actually beat Brookline B team and BLS B team that's a first.  Ok, I'm not going to bore you anymore, but anyways I got a 13, which really should have been at least a 15, and B team got 8 points total and got owned by South B team, who got 54 points.  Ms. Heidlage: "The grading is harder, the bar is harder..." Alex and I found that pretty funny.  Also:  Ms. Heidlage: You don't have to cite things that are generally known. Emily Price: Like those things on that CIA website? Ms. Heidlage: Exactly.  You know she's referring to the world factbook but still...
     

        
</post>

<date>05,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      On saturday me, sam, Josh magid, Noah Jampol, Jake G-A, Andrew habermehl, and Phil keefe all played football at Day it was so much fun.  They insisted on playing tackle, which if you think of Me, sam, G-A, and Noah tackling each other, was pretty amusing.  The first play of the game I had the hugest hit on sam it was soo funny and we were both like on the ground for a while. So basically sam, knowing it was me that was charging him, thought he could just like bowl me over, but apparently he couldn't and and so we like smacked into each other and sam like flew backwards, and everybody else started cracking up so badly.  I had some more unexpected hits on G-A and Jampol, but none as exciting as the first one.  Also G-A kept running out-of-bounds so he wouldn't get tackled, which was pretty funny also, but kind of annoying.  On Sunday I had chinese school which was quite boring, and no one really cares...  I would put funnier stuff in here, but all the semi-funny stuff goes in my sub Profile so look there...  But I will leave you with these things Joe said, as he was trying to recruit people for science team:  "Join Science team because we're not as nerdy as we look!" "Join Science team to show off how much you know... or don't know..." "Join Science team so you can get into pretty much any college you want... not really though..."  And finally my quote to Calvin:  "Women, can't live with them, can't go 2 milli-seconds without thinking of your sister..."
     

        
</post>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Well that cow was pretty uneventful... Let's recap:  Wednesday:  Jason, Yilun, Jean, and Melody came over.  Between my window pointing and dying-ness it was pretty fun.  I won't elaborate because I am lazy.  So basically unless you are Jason, Yilun, Jean, and/or Melody, yes a combination works too, you probably won't get what I mean.  Thursday:  NH, met up with the Wheelers, they are pretty cool people.  Half and Half. Weird. Of course none of you know who they are.  Austin and Charles Wheeler.  Oh yeah that girl Juliana was there too.  They are all Ivy-League ppl, aah.  Jason: So how was Gaymont? Me: You mean Gay Hampshire?  Friday:  Went to one of my parents crazy drinking parties.  The 18 year old 8th grader was there.  My mom was complaining that the drinks were too light.  Guo Hanbing came with us.  Her family is a bit too uptight for their parties.  Saturday:  Chinese School Thanksgiving party.  Ehh... Boring-ness.  I need to find some like real parties to go to.   Sunday: Sat around, watched the Pats game, football is stupid.  I am kind of tired from staying out past midnight for three days straight...  But I am going to elaborate on my wednesday experience anyway.  Anyway, Jason and I went to Starbucks for lunch, Jean and Melody apparently were hungry for the pizza-type food, ugh.  Somehow, although we got the same thing at the same time, my order came in 15 minutes after Jason's.  And then I saw Melody and Jean in the reflection in the window and pointed at them, not realizing that Jason wouldn't be able to see them.  So he was wondering what I was pointing at, and I was like "Look look they're coming." And he was confused, untl they got close enough that we could see them without looking in the reflection.  And then we went to my house, played some PtR and Tekken 3, two of the best games ever made, and then decided to go to Franklin.    We played that slappy game, and I broke the blood vessels in my hand.  That was the first time I've gotten broken blood vessels by anything other than... umm yeah. Anyway... We then played this stupid game that Jean wanted to play called, "Two ppl swing while two other people run under them trying not to get kicked in the face"  and then we played "See who can launch themselves off the swings the farthest"  I neglected to acknowledge that I had never tried jumping out of a swing before and therefore did not know how, so I killed myself on the landing, or lack thereof.  I won though.  So then we went back to my house and... did...stuff... Jean looked kind of left out, though one could argue that he was just as involved as I was, :P.  Jean was acting pretty gay though. Not that there's anything wrong with that of course...  I just don't enjoy having my balls groped by Jean as much as it might seem.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Lily is such a beach.  Thanxgiving is almost here... woohoo... Let's all give thanks for stuff.  We have to have those stilt wars Sam.
     

        
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Holy Crap Margaret this is long... Oh well i am bored so I have stolen it off your blog and I am putting it into mine...  [BASIC]  Name: Loren Nicknames: Well, let's see... there aren't that many... crazy people call me like L-Ren, and Lorne.  Josh Shephard calls me Manny D-lite, and before that C-Lo, and somehow, T-Unit.  Umm... A long time ago there was Chenboy.  And then there was Ratface, I think that's all. Age: 15 Single Or Taken:  Taken  Grade: 10 Current location: Jewton Date of Birth: May 10 Astrological Sign: Taurus Place of Birth: NH Parents' Names: Luying/Hudong Siblings' Name: Pamela What Elementary School Did You Go: Franklin What Middle School Did You Go: Day What High School Do You Go: Newton North  [SKIN DEEP] Ethnicity: Chinese Eye Color: dark brown Hair Color: black Height: 5'7", 5'8" I'm not exactly sure Glasses Or Contacts: glasses Piercings (if none, would you?): errr... I don't think so Tattoos (if none, would you?): same Shoe Size: an 8, I think  [LAST...] Thing You've Eaten: Rice Person You've Called: not sure... I haven't in a while Person That's Called You: Kevin Person You've IM-ed: Jason Movie You Saw In the Theater: Runaway Jury Movie You Rented: who knows TV Show You've Watched: SNL probably, oh wait no, what's that show after SNL, no one knows. Thing You Did With Your Family: Eat Dinner Thing You Did With Your Friends: Chinese School? does that count? well Monday we're all crashed at John's house, Tuesday we all hung out after MT, Wednesday we all hung out after Sci Team.  Oh yeah and Friday working out with Jason and Jean and Doug, and getting abducted by Sally. Thing You've Bought: Me Myself? I don't know... Food. Time You Cried: **shrug** Time You Laughed: Chinese School.  "Loren, you watch Chinese *pause*  soap operas?!  Time You Fell: Playing some sport, oh wait no, in computers class I fell asleep while leaning back in my chair and I fell over. Time You Showered: This morning Person You've Shared A Drink With: Share a drink as in physically or like in a bar... in any case I don't no. Time You've Seen Snow: It snowed a bit in NH. Time You've Seen Hail: Seventh Grade Song You've Listened: Mortal Kombat Theme Song You've Had Stuck In Your Head: Mortal Kombat Theme Song You've Downloaded: Hey Ya ~ Outkast CD You've Wanted But Haven't Bought: I generally don't buy cd's Time You've Fought With Someone: I avoid fights if possible. Person You've Hugged: Um... Still not sure... I think it would be Anne. Like a week or so ago.  [OPPOSITE SEX] What Do You Notice First: idk... Turn Ons: eh.... Turn Offs: If they are all like "out-there" if you know what i mean, cough Anne Chan. Ideal Eye Color: Asian Style Ideal Hair Color: Black, or like Black dyed some funny color idk. Ideal Height: Not like scarily tall like Sally. Ideal daily basics For Them To Have: A nice...aaaa...personality Ideal Sports For Them To Play: who cares. Ideal Personality Traits: ehhh....  [HAVE YOU EVER...?] Fallen In Love: With Melo Gone on A Date: iffy Made Out With Someone: Made out like hooked up? I plead the fifth. Gotten Drunk: No Done Drugs: No. Smoked: No. Gone To A Party: Birthday Party Been Completely Intoxicated: Intoxication doesn't usually happen to me Woken Up With A Hangover: No. Wanted Someone You Couldn't Have: Not Really Wished on A Shooting Star: No. Taken A Vow Of Silence: No. Cheated On A Test: I plead the fifth. Cried After Watching A Commercial: A Commercial? ehhh... Purposely Set Something On Fire: Oh yeah Had Your Heart Broken: Not too badly Broke Someone Else's Heart: I don't think... Had A Job: Volunteering at the Club with Little Kids. Cooked A Full Meal For Guests: Yeah, Curry rice with stir fried chicken and vegetables, so simple. Laughed, And Couldn't Stop: Idk, I don't see myself as a can't stop laughing type of guy. Pulled An All-Nighter: Yeah, a couple times. Watched The Sunrise: Yes. Watched The Sunset: Yes. Been To An Exotic Place: Er... Define Exotic. Philippines Been Swept Away By A Current: Once, it was pretty....frightening.  Especially since I was like 3. Been On A Freefall Ride: You mean like Scream? Yeah. Made The Wrong Decision On Purpose: I regret it. Stolen Something: ...Fifth Amendment Right not to incriminate myself! Broken Something Out Of Anger Or Sadness: Oh yeah funny story.  Throwing my calculator. Hurt Yourself Out Of Anger Or Sadness: Physically? No I don't think. Pinched Yourself To See If You Were Dreaming?: Yeah, and I was. Cussed Someone Out: No. Bungee-Jumped: No. Broken the Law: Eh... there are many things one could do to break the law. Made Yourself Throw Up: ...There was a stage in my life... Kept A Secret From Everyone: Well,  almost everyone  Had an Imaginary Friend: Like 50.  They never seemed to like me very much. Had a Crush on A Teacher: With my teachers? Oh yeah Charlie's Mom... Pictured Your Crush Naked: My crush? Fallen For Your Best Friend: Kevin is so hot. Used Someone: Umm... not maliciously... Been Cheated On: I... hope not... Regretted Doing Something: Yes. Regretted Not Doing Something: All the time.  [DO...] You Have a BF or GF: Yes. You Have a Crush on Someone: Why would I? You Wish You Could Live Somewhere Else: Not especially. You Think About Suicide: No. Well, not seriously, sometimes in my like "I wonder what would happen if I..." things, but like the endings to those are so horrible, that it's not very encouraging. You Believe in Online Dating: No. You Find Yourself Attractive: Oh yeah, they can't keep their hands off me. You Drink: Not...in that sense. You Do Drugs: No. You Smoke: No. You Like House-Cleaning: No. Sometimes. Well, if people are coming by, I do. You Wait Online All Day For One Person: Yes. Save AIM/MSN Conversations: Yes. Wish You Were A Member Of The Opposite Sex: No. Ever Cry Because of What Someone Said: Well, when I was little. You Color Your Hair: No. Habla Espanol: Not very well. Parlez Francais: A tad bit better.  [WHAT / WHERE / WHO] Kind of Shampoo Do You Use: Store Brand! No not actually. Kind of Soap Do You Use: S-ss-suave Are You Most Scared of: The dark? Car You Would Like to Have: TT Do You Want To Get Married: Well, as in like what kind of a reception place?  I'll leave that up to the girl? Do You Want To Live: Here is fine. Do You Want To Have Your Honeymoon: Rio! No not really. Makes You Laugh the Most: Jason, maybe Lex. Makes You Smile: People Gives You A Funny (good or bad) Feeling When You See Them: Sally, like I'm about to get raped or something. Easiest to Talk to: Kevin.  [WHICH OF YOU'RE FRIENDS...] Is Most Likely To Become An Athlete: None of them. Is Most Likely To Become A Model: None of them. Oh oh oh, Brett, if he counts as my friend. Is Most Likely To Become An Actor/Actress: Eh...  Is Most Likely To Become A Millionaire: Brian Liu. Is Most Likely To Marry A Millionaire: dk Is Most Likely To Get Married Many Times: Who's that whore we all love? Is Most Likely To Never Get Married: Alex seems to having trouble in that area. Is Most Likely To Become Famous: Jason. Is Most Likely To Become Infamous: Kevin Have You Known The Longest: PJ Is The Shyest: Me? Is The Weirdest: dk, none of them.  [EVERYONE] Who You Go To For Advice: Depends. Who You Call When You're Crying: Umm...Who has gotten a call from me crying?   [THIS OR THAT] Me or You: Me. Cold or Hot: Cold Pool or Hot Tub: Well, my swimming skills aren't that spectacular. Shower or Bath: shower On or Off: Off.  As in your clothes. Open or Closed: Closed. Water or Tea: Neither? Fruit or Vegetables: Fruit TV or Movie: Neither, unless it is Late night Radio or CD: CD say more or IM: IM Phone or IM: IM Cookies or Cake: Neither Food or Drink: Drink. Baseball or Soccer: Soccer. Football or Basketball: Football with jewish Kids Tennis or Badminton: uh.. I'd say Badminton, however gay that might be. School or Work: School.  Actually... with my job, who wouldn't like it. Cash or Check: Cash. Blonde or Brunette: Don't Care. Hug or Kiss: Don't know... Ocean or Lake or Pool: None of them? Florida or san jose: San jose Old or Young: Young, ooo child molestor, actually no old. Summer or Winter: Winter Spring or Fall: Fall Day or Night: Night. Sunrise or Sunset: Rise. Math or Science: Science. English or History: History, were it not for Heidlage. Music or Art: idk, either. Coke or Pepsi: Pepsi, bradley's gonna kill me for saying that.  Actually at our school, Coke just to watch the awesome machines, but then Pepsi has that machine where it just drops which is also great... Dr. Pepper or Root Beer: Dr. Pepper. 7UP or Sprite: Sierra Mist. Smoothie or Juice: Juice. Cursive or Print: Print. Lace or Satin: Um.... Flowers or Candy: Both. Scruff or Clean Shaven: For me?  Well there isn't much there... Tall or Short: Average?  [FOR OR AGAINST] Long Distance Relationships: Whatever works... Using Someone: Eh... Suicide: Against Killing People: Against Smoking: Against Doing Drugs: Against Premarital Sex: hmm... Driving Drunk: Against Gay/Lesbian Relationships: Er... No op.  [NUMBER...] Of Times You've Had Your Heart Broken: 0 Of Hearts You've Broken: 0? Of Continents You've Lived In: 2, unless you count stints of like 1 month. Of CD's That You Own: Possibly like 1, unless you count my aunt's like 50 cd's Of Scars On Your Body: Let's count...  [YOU...] Want: You. No, not really. Wish: What? what kind of a question is that. Love: Melody ;) and my family I suppose, and everybody loves Kevin! No not really. Miss: Childhood innocence. Fear: A lot of things Hate: Fei Zhu Hear: What I want to hear. Wonder: about the beginnings of time, and if I will ever get some...food.  [RIGHT NOW...] Wearing: My SWOOSH sweater, my new blingin watch, Jeans, socks, glasses Eating: As usual... Drinking: Sierra Mist. Thinking About: What I am going to write about in my autobiography.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      There are a bunch of things I could be talking about...  Topic #1: Re:Sally   Sally has become increasingly forward, it is frightening, and also pretty annoying.  Jason, Jean, and I were in the weight room, and Sally popped in and insisted that I watch the football game with her.  When I refused, she like grabbed me by the shirt and dragged my out of the weight room.  In response to my many escape attempts she said the following memorable quote:  "Come or I will rip your shirt off!"  She did actually rip my shirt a little.  Melody said, "You should have ripped her shirt back, then she would have to walk around half naked." I didn't know how to respond.  And then I escaped when she asked me to go into the locker room to see who was in there, and then I just went back to the weight room from there.  But when I got back to the weight room, Jason had apparently gone looking for me.  So I had to go back upstairs and get recaptured.  But then she let me go again to go talk to Pat Pierce, who she had tried to run with earlier that day.  Haha, Sally running with Pat Pierce...   Topic #2: Re: The Locker Room Incident  So Jason and I went into the locker room on friday and Polgar was there, and he started telling us how Eric Dooley and this other kid turned off the lights, started singing the Mortal Kombat theme, and then "exposed themselves" and started running around the locker room terrorizing people.  And then maybe like a minute after Polgar finishes his story, Dooley and that other kid walk in, and Jason says, "We heard what you did" and Dooley just laughs.  Then the other kid turns off the lights and they start singing the Mortal Kombat theme and running around.  Except this time, Polgar took out a flashlight and shined it on a certain part of Dooley's body.  Now Jason and I are scarred for life.  We did get a couple laughs out of it however, later on.  Jason: "Eric Dooley's 'member' is a Nazi." And by that I mean a skinhead. Me: Haha, he seems to be quite deficient in some areas. Jason: Hahaha, hairless half-incher.  Topic #3: I guess there weren't that many topics after all...  The End.  [edit] Oh yeah now I remember one more ok.  Topic #3: Business Law  On Friday I was so bored during Business Law that I was falling asleep, and we took a test midway through the period.  And so, I was taking the test and I fell asleep while taking it, and apparently I fell asleep while writing something because I was in the middle of the word, and then after that there were like scribbles on my paper.  That was pretty weird.    Topic #4: Computers  Matt Woolf and I are so ahead of our Computers class, that our teacher asked us to make up our own project and then do it, and then have it be the next assignment for the class.  So we decided to make a square root reducer, which is pretty simple, if you know what you are doing.  That was fun.  Extra credit.  Ok really the end now.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I am going to attempt to translate that song I put on my blog a couple days ago cuz I'm bored.  This is gonna be hard.  I'm going to transliterate and translate how bout that.  Ok here goes:  Hei Se Liu Ding Black Tangerine  Jin tian wo xin qing you yi dian guai guai.  Ke shi shou bu chu dao di wei she me. Hao xiang you yi dian bei shang le zhen chang. Ke shi bing ying bu zhi dao. Tou shang you ju se de jia zhou yang guang Wo de kou dai zhi you hei se de liu ding. Wo zhi you yi ge lan se de gan jue. Bu wen wo wei she me. *** Today I'm feeling kind of weird and I can't exactly say why. It's like something is harming what it normal. But you don't know what the problem is. On your head there is the orange california sun In my pocket there's only a black tangerine. I only have one blue colored emotion. Don't ask me why...  Hen xiang shuo... dan you gan jue mei you hua hou shou Wo zhi hen wo zi ji, tao bu chu zhe jian yu ho xu wo... shi ge mei you chu xi de xiao chong bu gai yi zhi zuo meng, ni bu shi ge ying xiong. *** You really want to speak... but then you feel like you don't have anything worth saying I just hate myself, can't escape this prison. But I... am just a little bug that doesn't matter You shouldn't be constantly dreaming, you're not the hero.  Ye zi yong zhui luo zheng ming huan ji Ke wo hun hun chen chen mei you ban fa xing Ni yuan yi zuo ge ying xiong, hai shi ni hui yao fang qi Tian shi liang di que bu man wu yun Suo yuo jiao ju bei shan guang pan le si xing Ni xiang zuo she me ying xiong, wo kan ni bu guo shi yong bing Wo zhi xiang ku, zhi xiang ku zhi xiang ku *** Leaves fall to signify a changing of seasons But I'm so dazed that I have no way of waking up Do you want to be a hero? Or are you going to give up? The sky is clear, then it's taken over by dark clouds. All focal points are given the death penalty by a flash of lightning. Why are you even trying to be a hero? I don't see you as more than a slave. I just want to cry.  Jin tian yi qi chuang wo jiu tou tong Bu guan chi le ji ping yong dou mei you yong xi qing you yi dian mo ming de jiao cao Ni li wo yue yuan yue hao Wai mian you ju se de jia zhou yang guang Wo que duo zi ji gu du de hei dong Wo zhi you yi ge xiao xiao de yao qiu Jiu shi qing ni leave me alone.... *** Today once I woke up my head hurt No matter how much medicine I took, it didn't help The emotions are confusingly burnt(???) The farther you are from me the better Outside there is the orange california sun But I hide in the dark hole I dug for myself I only have one little request I just want you to leave me alone  Then a bunch of crazy repeaty-ness  I'm such a bad translator.  You're not a hero...jeez stop trying to be heroic.  Here's the babelfish-ized version of my griping yesterday:  Today that fat pig changed stupidly. Xu is peaceful, she gave me her scientific schoolwork to have a look, but he took away it. The at that time I really want beat the crap out of him. But I do not have, Xu is peaceful, she snatched her schoolwork. -odd German, I, with Xu An all thought that fat pig is very stupid. Melody is very attractive, I love her very much. But that fat pig fat also is stupid. I want to kill him.  Well... today I hung out with Yin and Nong a lot between lunch and Math Team and the back seat of Nong's car, cough cough, yeah right.  Surprisingly I didn't see Anne at all today, it was disheartening if that is a word.  After math team we played makeshift baseball kind of like we do in Homeroom, except instead of that tube we used a two-liter Pepsi bottle that made an awesome sound when you hit it.  Nong pwn'd cuz he plays tennis.  And then after that we played catch with a football in the parking lot, Nong Yin and I.  And then Nong drove us home.  I wonder where Anne was today, Anne is never sick it's just not Anne-like to be sick.  Speaking of Anne, Anne Chan is such a "get-arounder."  We were talking about that girl who wears so much mascara that her like eyelashes take over her face the other day.  We don't actually know her name though.  She hangs out with Sally a lot and she went to Franklin.  I remember when I was in like third grade or something and she was a grade below.  Ken Zhao is the best freshman in the world.  "Well they are both white chinese girls..."  The german should get with the star with my numbers in my opinion, but it isn't for me to decide, if there isn't like a bond.  I could definitely see it happening though.  Or the star with my numbers' cantonese friend, if Kevin dosn't want to go all mandy on us. 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I have realized that, for you to see my chinese blogging, you would not only need to change the encoding, you also need to allow your computer to view East Asian Languages.  To do so:  1. Go to the Control Panel 2. Click on the Languages Tab 3. Check the box that says "Allow for East Asian Languages" or what not.  It has been said that this requires the Windows CD to do, but I don't think that that is true. But if you do whatever.  So anyways today we raided John Garabedian's house, I was still a bit pained from my workout, but the others basically ate everything single ounce of food in his house, including all his english muffins and all his cough drops.  And all his single serving Tylenol packets.  Not really though.  It has been said that my blog is lacking substance.  I don't really know how to fix that seeing that nothing interesting ever happens to me.  Maybe I should take my mom's advice "and then I see some action."  My mom definitely does not have a heavy accent, at least she isn't as bad as like other Chinese people.  Jason, you're just racist against everybody.  Including yourself.  Self-Racist.  Stop polluting our race. Jeez...  "Get out of my daughter!"  Sally took a picture of me on her phone on my way to the weight room, I was like "What the hell..."  Why would anyone take a picture of  me?   My skinny-ness doesn't even show on the screen, and my body turns out to be about 1 pixel wide.  Haha.  This is why I am bulking up.   I played Nong in ping pong today, I did surprisingly well, I wasn't sailing shots like I normally do.  I lost 12-10, one deuce, which is amazingly good against Nong.  I was winng 7-4, and then I gave up 4 straight points.  And he completely owned me on the last point it wasn't even like worthy of existing.  And I know he was putting in like 10% effort, but it's still good.
     

        
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      今天那肥猪变更笨了。 徐安，她给了我她的科学功课看看，但是他把它拿走了。那时我真的要beat the crap out of him。但是我没有，徐安， 她 抢回来了她的功课。余德文，我，和徐安都觉得那肥猪很笨。Melody 还是很漂亮， 我很爱她。但那肥猪又肥又笨。 我想打死他。  My Chinese skills have seriously declined.  I had to resort to using chinglish in that one part.  Maybe if I did my chinese homework, Anne's mom would like me again, and then by default my chinese would be better.  That actually babelfish's quite nicely, except that it continuously screws up names, and it calls Kevin " Odd The German" because that is basically what his name means in chinese.  And it calls Anne, "Xu is peaceful", because that's what "An" is in chinese.   I need to blog more often in chinese and see how bad it turns out in babelfish, because that was a very amusing experience.  Switch to GB encoding, now. That's Chinese (Simplified).
     

        
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      黑色柳丁  今天我心情有一点怪怪 可是说不出到底为什麽  好像有一点悲哀的徵兆 可是病因不知道  头上有橘色的加州阳光 我的口袋只有黑色的柳丁  我只有一个蓝色的感觉 不要问我为什麽   很想说 但又感觉没有话好说 我只恨我自己 逃不出这监狱  或许我 是个没有出息的小虫 不该一直作梦 你不是个英雄  叶子用坠落证明换季 可我昏昏沉沉没有办法醒  你愿意做个英雄 还是你会要放弃  天是亮的却布满乌云 所有焦距被闪光判了死刑  你想做什麽英雄 我看你不过是佣兵  我只想哭 只想哭 只想哭 我只想哭 只想哭 只想哭   今天一起床我就头痛 不管吃了几瓶药都没有用  心情有一点莫名的焦躁 你离我越远越好  外面有橘色的加州阳光 我却躲在自己孤独的黑洞  我只有一个小小的要求 就是请你 leave me alone  很想说 但又感觉没有话好说 我只恨我自己 逃不出这监狱  或许我 是个没有出息的小虫 不该一直作梦 你不是个英雄  叶子用坠落证明换季 可我昏昏沉沉没有办法醒  你愿意做个英雄 还是你会要放弃  天是亮的却布满乌云 所有焦距被闪光判了死刑  你想做什麽英雄 我看你不过是佣兵  我只想哭 只想哭 只想哭 我只想哭 只想哭 只想哭   今天我心情有一点烂烂 可是说不出到底为什麽  好像有一点悲哀的徵兆 可是病因不知道  我只想哭 只想哭 只想哭 我只想哭 只想哭 只想哭  Simplified Chinese is so great because obviously white people won't understand, and Canto people will only be able to read traditional, soo... Loren Wins.  And it means I can cough without other people knowing what I'm coughing about.  Sometimes it is better if I keep what I blog to myself.  [edit] Simplified is even harder to read if the encoding is off, switch to GB if you want.  On a lighter note, I have a couple of quotes, the first of which happened during third lunch when I was sitting with Yin, Nong, George, Calvin, Mike, Jason, etc.  George: "Calvin, I hear Loren is sleeping with your sister." Yin (almost immediately after George finishes): "George, I hear Loren is sleeping with your brother."  I had never before simultaneously wanted to laugh at George and punch Yin.  There was that John quote that I could put in here, but for multiple reasons I won't, mainly cuz Sally scares me.  oh yeah that reminds me, Sally has a study across from our History class and we were talking the other day.  Sally: "I'm from Great Britain." Me: "Really? He's from Great Britain." (pointing at Matt Woolf) Sally: "Oh, actually I'm from Australia."  That day I also found out that Jessica Li is both Mandy and from New Hamshire, pretty interesting.  She lived in Durham, what a weird place to live.  Jing is a weird girl.  Kevin's and my rules for being Asian:  1.    Be Smart 2.    Be an Overachiever 3.    Have only Asian friends 4.    Sell drugs 5.    Listen to Techno/Asian music 6.    Be cheap 7.    Eat weird stuff at home, e.g. chicken feet 8.    Have spiky hair 9.    Have a sweet car, e.g. Lancer Evolution, or Vandergosh's TT 10.  Drag Race 24/7 11.  Play video/computer games, esp. DDR and CS 12.  Wear unexpesive yet stylin clothes 13.  Know some form of Martial Art, preferably Kung Fu 14.  Take off shoes when going into house 15.  Start sentences with "Confucius says" 16.  Use Chopsticks 17.  Scatter chinese phrases into normal conversation 18.  Like to eat chow fan, and ho jo yu wonton 19.  Wish today was sunday so you could get a cheeseburger for 39 cents at McDonald's, baby 20.  Wish today was Wednesday so you could get a hamburger for 29 cents at McDonald's
     

        
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Ok so there was a Math Meet today, which was so incredibly hard, oh my god.  I only got 7 points. Me. Only 7 points.  Terrible.  Shows how hard the thing was.  Anyways, I got 7, Yin 11, Nong 12 crap he is good, Anne 7, other ppl etc.  So disappointing.  Jew Unit sucked face.  I'm so tired... I got a ride home from Nong today, that was fun.  Sometime soon I need to steal my bike back from Melody's house.  I left it there yesterday. eh....
     

        
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Uh huh it is Veteran's Day, and I have nothing to do.  I'm supposed to stay home but that's no fun... Let's see the things I could be doing...  1. Watching the Matrix with Alex, John, Jon, Rich, and such. 2. Playing football with Yin, Nong, Hoi, etc. 3. Probably doing something interesting with Jason. 4. Going over Melody's and having wild monkey...s over to play.  But instead, I have to stay home while my mom is out, boohoo...  Diao, diao, diao, diao, diao... is what you are. And is what my mom is not for making me stay at home...
     

        
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I chipped a nail... and it hurts :'(.  And it looks ugly now.  Boohoo.  I have like 0 A's if you don't count Computers and French, it's so annoying, and possibly Business Law.  Chem sux, Math sux, English sux, History sux.  I hate it.  I've been listening to this Melody song for a long time now on repeat.  It's like this guy who's singing about his girlfriend.  Who's name is Melody.  I like it.  It's like I can alomst identify with him.  Good song, I can send it to ppl if they want to listen.  David Tao.  He doesn't sound like a 34-year-old.  Or look like one for that matter.  He's so diao.  Not as diao as Jay though.  And neither of them as even nearly as diao as Melody =).  My mom told me that I can't watch the Matrix on Tuesday cuz I have to study.... bleh.  "Melody oh Melody, wo yong yuan bu hui wang ji, ni shi duo mo de mei li, rang zhe ying yue yi zhi bu ting xiang qi."  Baically: "Melody oh Melody, I will never forget how beautiful you are, don't let this music stop playing..."
     

        
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      If there are two things that I hate most in this world here they are.  I hate it when people have low self-esteem and are like constantly putting themselves down.  Especially when there is absolutely no reason for it.  I mean, why would you do that, it's so annoying.  You are only making yourself worse.  I don't know people's reasons behind it, but when they start like saying, "I'm so bad, I'm so bad" it's not like we're going to make fun of them, so they might as well just try their best and then if they truly are bad, they can get better.  Second thing I hate the most.  People who are completely full of themselves.  I mean I'm not going to name names, but most likely the person I have in mind thinks he too cool to even look at Loren's blog.  I was discussing this with Kevin earlier today:  MandarinYellow31 (10:20:38 PM): and he thinks hes so cool seihakgui (10:20:40 PM): his pride and pop is getting to his head seihakgui (10:21:01 PM): he lies 2 girls MandarinYellow31 (10:21:10 PM): loser seihakgui (10:21:22 PM): like he says hes always pimping it out seihakgui (10:21:27 PM): n hookin up seihakgui (10:21:44 PM): and other "stuff" like that MandarinYellow31 (10:21:50 PM): he hasn't hooked up with a girl ever seihakgui (10:21:54 PM): he said hes been 2 3rd base MandarinYellow31 (10:22:00 PM): fuckin liar seihakgui (10:22:02 PM): i know seihakgui (10:22:09 PM): i told heather everything MandarinYellow31 (10:22:12 PM): I don't even think he's gone to first MandarinYellow31 (10:22:25 PM): has he? seihakgui (10:22:29 PM): i told heather i havent been anywhere seihakgui (10:22:34 PM): well seihakgui (10:22:37 PM): he hasnt seihakgui (10:22:42 PM): not even a kiss MandarinYellow31 (10:22:46 PM): i know seihakgui (10:22:49 PM): i shouldnt be talking seihakgui (10:22:50 PM): .... MandarinYellow31 (10:22:59 PM): no but you're at least honest about it seihakgui (10:23:03 PM): yea MandarinYellow31 (10:23:09 PM): Brian is just full of crap  Whoops I said his name, oh well, who cares, what's he gonna do, get Keith to beat me up.  When he is like showing off his not really great phone and like bragging about how good he is at everything, I just want to be like, "STFU, you fat white drew carey clone"  Ok, enough venting for one day.
     

        
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I'm doing so bad in school... argh... B+ in Chem, B+ in Math, B in English, god... who knows what I have in history...  So today I worked out with G-A, Merlet, Jason, it was actually quite fun.  The only annoying thing was that G-A has like zero self-esteem.  He finished his 2 miles like 3 minutes after the rest of us, cuz he didn't think he could keep up.  We weren't even going fast at all.  And he like basically walked the warm-up lap, as he would say "That's such a dick thing to do" with numerous voice cracks mixed in.  And then in the weight room, he wouldn't even try to do the bench press, I mean he can't be much worse than me...  If G-A actually tried, I'm sure he could have kept up with us, and it's just annoying how he puts himself down.  Tomorrow I'm going to go watch Melody do her thang... and by that I mean play the piano.  Tuesday I think I'm gonig to go watch the Matrix Revolutions with like the nerd crew.  Sometime before then I have to watch the Matrix Reloaded...
     

        
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      This new skin is weird, The links don't actually work, and currently it doesn't like my comment system.  I will work this out soon enough.  It's Jay Chou though.  So that makes it better.  [edit:] Ok so I got the comments back working. But the links are still down, and Idk how to fix them, because I am not like fluent in CSS like these people apparently are.  They're are like "option value=  urlLink " argh. I need to figure this out  haha the tag I put in doesn't show up when you look at the blog  [double edit:] Apparently the comment thingy isn't working, oh well you guys can live without commenting right, the window like wants to pop up but it doesn't...
     

        
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      After math team I got a ride home from Nong, and he was playing that CD that I gave him, and I don't think he likes Jay Chou's mumbly-ness very much.  Basically he was just like, "How much of this do you actually comprehend?"  Oh yeah we were listening to "Niang Zi" which is terribly difficult to understand if you listen to it, he like slurs every word with like 3 other words.  And like Nong was wearing Anne's big green jacket, which was interesting.  Well then, I have a chem test tomorrow that I should probably study for, and I have like history to do I have a free B-Block tomorrow which is good, more study time...  Ken Zhao pwn'd today in math team, he's like the new age Brian Liu.  It was so great.  Yin: "I have a wide ass," after I asked him to move over so I could buckle myself.  Ppl have been abusing the comment feature, eh I guess that's what it's there for.  [edit]- Oh yeah I forgot, thanx Julia for reminding me.  Today I fell asleep in English, then I fell asleep in Computers, and then I fell semi-asleep in Math.  The Computers one was actually pretty amusing, because I could still hear what she was saying, but I was like so dazed, that I couldn't think, and i didn't know that I had actually fallen asleep.  So I'm like dreaming and I hear her say "Could you nudge him a little?" and I'm like, "that's a weird thing to say in class, oh wait am I asleep?" and then I woke up, and it was pretty funny.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      sweetness, I figured out how to work them out, this is so awesome, I'm still not quite sure how to have ppl post comments, just I know were ppl to post them, you could click on that little thing on the bottom that says "comments = 0" to look at them
     

        
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      "Ok so I was dreaming, and then all the sudden Ken Zhao walks in and I'm like 'Ken, why are you here? Get out of my fantasy!' But he wouldn't leave so I tried to ignore him, but he kept bothering me while I was doing the things that I do during fantasies.  So then after a while I gave up and decided to just stop with the fantasy.  Stupid Ken Zhao..."  hahaha... That didn't actually happen, and no one actually said that, I just like to say random things about Ken Zhao.  So... I got new batteries for my calculator, exciting... 462 ooo pwnd  I've started to write in red and yellow again for AIM, back to my roots... Black and white was getting boring...  Generic Guy-handwriting. haha. "I'm sleeping with you" good stuff... We should sleep with each other more often.  Have you noticed how excruciatingly random I am? Excruciating might not be the right word, not exactly as painful as being crucified, is it? It might be.  Blogger really needs to get a place where people can comment, so like I know who actually looks and w/e. Or some people can just beach in general about the overall bad-ness of my blog.  "I need to go / Just as bad as you / What I had this morning I don't even want to say to you"  PTR rox. 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I never understood what they meant when on the commercials they said that the stuff like reduces the size of your pores... until I saw Andrew Habermehl.  Speaking of which, a little kid to Andrew at the Christmas Pageant:  "Do you have the chicken pox?"  I was laughing for sooo long.  I have nothing else to add... except for possibly some comments about some people's candy posteriors.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I just realized that i screwed something up by adding that thing to my blog template, I'm going to try to fix it now.  meanwhile: New Song, "Liu Xia" by David Tao
     

        
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I need to change this song... It's so terrible. Especially in midi form.  So my Christmas.  Rocelyn came over, she's my Filipina aunt. She's pretty cool.  Wait did I spell her name right? Uhh... I think so... w/e. Anyway, we opened presents and my mom got me like a DDR set thingy, except she won't let me open it cuz Kevin got me the same thing and she wants me to get the receipt from him.  So now I have 2 DDR things, and I can't play either.  Ros mentioned how I looked so anxious and that I just wanted to like rip the box open.  She compared me to "A starving man who can see food right in front of him but can't eat it."  She's pretty cool.  I already said that.  Well then I opened other presents. And I got a bunch of CD's by HK people.  Which is so weird, cuz I only listen to Taiwanese singers, but because of recent events I have realized that they would never buy me a Taiwanese CD.  So they got me a Andy Lau CD.  weird.  I am never going to listen to it.    Sorry but i have to say that Taiwanese people are annoying.  Not because of class differentials or anything. But like, they're part of China, and then they are all like "Screw you guys, we're becoming independent" and then we're like "Hey, we're all Chinese, can't we all be friends?" and then they're like, "No, screw you guys."  And so now they're independent, and they try to make us look like the bad guys, by saying that we want to bomb them, which is completely untrue.  And now the President of Taiwan is like "Just to make our relationship with Mainland China worse, I'm going to say that Taiwan never should have been part of China, but really should be included in the Japanese archipelago."  I mean shuuutttt uuupppp.  Just cuz you are half Japanese yourself doesn't mean you have to take your whole "independent state" with you.  I mean you all speak Mandarin, however bad your accent might be, and you are mostly all Chinese by blood, other than the aboriginals, because most of you migrated from Mainland China.  So while I don't have  that  much of a problem with Taiwan being independent, I hate how they are like "Nananana, we're not part of China, screw you guys."  Ok, enough ranting, back to Christmas.  Hmm...what else happened, oh yeah on Christmas Eve, we had our Christmas Pageant.  Andrew Habermehl was Joseph and Willa K-H was Mary.  Anne: "Won't you guys have a pretty chubby Mary?" Me: "Well she  is  supposed to be 9 months pregnant in the beginning."  Anywho, the lady running it was retarded, for lack of a more pc term.  Stephanie Kaplan: "I hate it when people get mad when you say retarded.  I mean it's obviously a bad thing so shut up already"  But she really didn't know what she was doing.  She sent people up at the wrong times, told them to do the wrong things, and overall made it quite disatrous.  Andrew (to Eric): "Who are you supposed to be?" Eric Beam: "I'm the Shepherd's Joy.  Well, I'm a shepherd, but specifically I'm his joy." Andrew: "Hahaha" Eric: "I AM JOY"  For anyone who didn't understand that, there was this part of the pageant called "The Shepherd's Joy" where one shepherd (Eric Beam) goes up and reads a monologue about how he is so happy about like being able to see Jesus and all.  I saw "The Last Samurai" the other day, it was a pretty good movie.  I have to watch LOTR:ROTK soon.  I still want to just rip that DDR box thing open, but I can't...  Am I going to make this longer and even more excruciatingly painful to read?  I could but I don't think I'm going to.  I still need to get new musak.
     

        
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Newer Song: "Wei Lan Gu Bao (William's Castle) ~Jay Chou
     

        
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      So I was staring at this like picture-thingy cuz it is my new found hobby, and I am constantly so utterly bored.  And so, I was looking at us.  And of course Melody looks absolutely perfect as always.  She's holding a water bottle, and the top of it like just sticks into the picture.  Because of the perspective, I can't tell if she's leaning forward or leaning towards me, or a combination of the two.  So then I switched to looking at me, because apparently I am vain.  In the picture, my teeth seem like 4 shades whiter.  And my eyebrows are actually normal... I remember those days.  My hair is screwed up in that picture, or possibly, it justs seems that way cuz I am standing in front of like this strange thing.  My arm is bent funnily.  It looks weird.  Anywho, if it were yesterday, I would start griping again about how amazing of a present this is, and how I felt bad cuz my present sucked.  But today is not yesterday, so I won't go into that.  Song: "Runaway" ~ David Tao
     

        
</post>

<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Doo doo doo.  It's vacation. Wooohooo...  If you couldn't tell, that was supposed to be sarcastic.  I'm never very enthuiastic about these things.  Eh.... I am inordinately grumpy today, and then I'm mean to people.  And I know I'm being mean to them too, but I don't care.  This is weird and like un-me.  I'm supposed to be like Loren, perfectly complacent and like Lorenesque, for lack of a better term.  Melody gave me a picture of us in like a luvvy-duvvy picture frame.  I keep looking at it.  It's so nice.  It was such a thoughtful present.  The frame is glass, and my desk is glass so it is cool in that way too.  My presents for people were so terrible.  I am such a bad Christmas shopper.  ughhhhhhhhh...    I hate it when people complain like this on their xangas/blogs/livejournals.  I swore that I would never ever do it.  I don't even know why I am.  Talking to Anne just generally makes me angry.  I mean, she's great to be with in person but online she just won't stop complaining... Ugh, and it's always like "my mom this, my mom that."  I like Anne's mom.  She gave me a Christmas present, and Anne didn't.  I also gave Anne's mom a Christmas present but not Anne.  Conflict of Interests.  Anywho, apparently since she doesn't have AIM anymore, again I'm the only one she can bitch to.  And while I won't say anything to her, I just want to be like "Shut up..."  I also realized that for some reason if the picture falls down/gets pushed down, not only will the frame break, but my desk will break also.  Oh well, let's hope that doesn't happen.  I can't how like nice this is.  And it's all like "Love is magical and eternal, Love is selfless, Joy, Passion, etc."  Why can't I get people presents like this?   Get over it, Loren.  Nobody wants to hear you complain, especially not about your completely lame presents.  Ok.
     

        
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      So today in French, we were watching "Au Revoir Les Enfants" and Jean Bonnet/Kippelstein was reading 1001 Arabian Nights with Julian.  And so they start reading this story in which there is this naked girl.  And so the narrator describes her in terms of different races/nationalities, I can't remember them because frankly I wasn't paying much attention to the erotic-ness.  But then the last line in the description caught my eye; it was "She had the narrow passage of a Chinese girl" and I started cracking up.  Other people didn't find it quite as funny.  Then I stopped laughing because I realized that it would be a long, long, long time before I got to enter any narrow Chinese passages.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I wanted to issue a correction.  Alex made up that +8 armor comment, and not some unknown person.  Also today in Business Law, Michelle Sellke said, "They're totally going to lawsuited"
     

        
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Stolen from Jing/Melody  name : L-ren birthday: May 10 siblings:1 hair color: black eye color: brown height: 5'8ish I think been in love: It seems like that is the case eaten an entire box of oreos: I agree with jing, Oreos are not very appetizing. been on stage: 8th Grade Asian Night! been dumped: ...Does it count as being dumped if I say that I never went out with her in the first place? gotten in a car accident: Nope dyed your hair: Yellow hair and yellow skin don't mix, according to my mom gone to school in your pajammas: never gotten a detention: a few times loved someone so much that it made you cry: Jing has never been in love, and yet has loved someone so much that it has made her cry, I will possibly never understand girls. last talked to : Kevin  x THiS/THAT x  cold / hot: Cold blue / red: Red rain / snow: As I said before, rain is the best form of any precipitation. give / receive: Give wool / cotton: cotton private school / public school: Private school, mos def chocolate milk / plain milk: Plain celsius / fahrenheit: Fahrenheit, cuz metric system is for euro losers spring / fall: Fall history / science: Chem, my 98 average pwns all of yours, unless you have Srikanth, in which case you're cheating math / english: uh...neither... like at all... Chem! country / rock: Rock coke / pepsi: Pepsi cherry coke / vanilla coke: Vanilla Coke is  terrible  sprite / 7up: Sierra Mist sleep / eat: Usually neither  x OPPOSiTE SEX x  do you like someone right now: It seems like it do they know: Hopefully Wat do you look for in the opposite sex: If I say the same thing as last time then it's just going to be annoying do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend: Sure  x FRiENDS x  who is your most annoying friend: People are going to kill me for this but I wuold have to say that in person it is either Lily or like Kevin, and online it is Anne. which one do you wish you saw more often: I can think of friends I would want to see less often, but more often idk. whos the loudest: My friends... aren't loud... G-A possibly, constantly yelling. whos the shyest: idk. who are you jealous of: A bunch of people who has the best room: ME who do you trust the most: the most? I don't trust people, generally.  Jason I would have to say. who knows the most about you: Jason u usually miss: Andover friends... why didn't I go to Andover...  x WiTHiN THE LAST 24 HOURS x  had a serious talk: not like  serious  hugged someone: I believe, not quite sure, actually maybe not missed someone: all the time gotten along with your parents: Always fought with a friend: Well Jason got pretty mad when I poked him in the stomach with a pin, I don't even know what I was doing cried: No felt empty: No  x DO YOU LiKE TO x  give hugs: Give/receive I can't even tell anymore take walks in the rain: The best feeling ever go to the beach: I don't watch tv: Only late night do homework: Sometimes play in the snow: No stay up all night talking to friends: Sometimes talk on the phone: Kind of go online: Sure do freaky things: I'm not a freaky kind of guy  x WHiCH ONE OF YOUR FRiENDS x  is most likely to grow up to be a model: I told you I don't know... have known you the longest: PJ do you know most about: People don't see me as their confidant for some reason, understandably.  x HAVE YOU EVER x  been out of state: We don't live in like Kansas broken a bone: Nope met a famous person: Bill Cosby! and Bret Boone I suppose, but no one likes him. bought something and then sold it: Yes, many many times stole from someone or somewhere: ...I plead the fifth, I have at least once per survey. stalked someone: Well, stalking as in like  stalking ? idk  x LOVE x  single or taken:  occupied   if you were gonna go out with anyone, who would it be: Hmmmm? had an online relationship: A short, fast-moving one  x EXTRAS x  what really makes you mad: I dislike...as Yin would say "Laziness, Arrogance, and Grade-Whoring"  Laziness and arrogance I can stand, but I hate it when people like push for points, it's so annoying.  This is why I don't do bonuses usually, though people take that as being arrogant. what is your earliest memory: I talk so much about wanting to be a kid again, but I can't remember like any of my childhood...I remember my first day of first grade, I remember my frist day in Newton, I remember some parts of living in New Hampshire, but before that not much.  x NOW x  where are you:in In the study are you wearing any jewlery: Uh, my chain possibly constitutes when was the last time you showered: Last night/this morning I'm not sure what color pants do you have on right now: jean-y what song are you listening to right now: This weird mix of "Jian Dan Ai" and "Truly Madly Deeply" what is the last thing you said: yeah what is your computer desk made of: Wood what was the last thing you ate: ummm... not sure what would you really want to be doing right now: Melody, I mean, umm... yeah... if you were a crayon, what color would you be:  who cares... They need to make a crayon color called Mandarin Yellow, and have it be the asian flesh tone.  That was the stupidest survey ever. 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      HA! It works! Now I just need to find a better song...
     

        
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Dan Jung ruins everything, I won't go into details.  Eh... it is mostly my fault, but I like to pin the blame on other ppl... W/e you all know that I am a failure when it comes to these things.  Or at least I pretend to be, ooo hidden dark side... no not really though.
     

        
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Speaking of sappy chinese love songs...  爱很简单  　　　    忘了是怎麽开始  也许就是对你一种感觉  忽然间发现自己  以深深爱上你 真的很简单    爱的地暗天黑都已无所谓  是是非非无法决择  没有後悔  为爱日也去跟随  那个疯狂的人是我 喔~      I LOVE YOU 无法不爱你 BABY 说你也爱我  I LOVE YOU 永远不愿意 BABY 失去你    不可能更快乐  只要能在一起  做什麽都可以  虽然世界变个不停 用最真诚的心 让爱变得简单    I LOVE YOU 我一直在这里 一直在爱你  I LOVE YOU    ( YES I DO )  永远都不放弃 这爱的权利  如果你还有一些困惑 OH NO 请贴 我的心倾听  听我说 爱你 ( YES I DO) 我爱你    Ai hen jian dan ~ David Tao Love Is Simple   Wang le shi zen me kai shi ye xu jiu dui ni, you yi zhong gan jue wu ran jian fa xian zhi ji yi shen shen ai shang le ni zhen de hen jian dan *** I forgot how this all started Maybe I just have a sort of feeling towards you All of the sudden I find myself so deeply in love with you, it really very simple.  Ai de di an tian hei dou yi tian suo wei Shi shi fei fei wu fa jue ze mei you hou hei wei ai ri ye qu gen sui na ge feng huang de ren shi wo. oooo~ *** Holy crap this is so annoying to translate and so I am just going to stop here sorry, I'm pretty sure you didn't want to hear much more of it anyway.  Well I guess I will do the chorus.  I LOVE YOU, wu fa bu ai ni, BABY, shuo ni ye ai wo I LOVE YOU, yong yuan bu yuan yi, BABY, shi qu ni Bu ke neng geng kuai le, zhi yao neng zai yi qi, zuo she me duo ke yi sui ran shi jie bian ge bu ting yong zui zhen cheng ge xin, rang ai bian de geng jian dan. *** I love you, there's no way for me not to, baby, say you love me too. I love you, I never want to, baby, let you go. I can't be more happy, I just want to be with you, we can do anything you want Even though this world is always changing, in the most honest hearts (???),  let love be more simple.  I LOVE YOU wo yi zhi zai zhe li, yi zhi zai ai ni I LOVE YOU (YES I DO) Yong yuan dou bu fang qi, zhe ai ni de quan li ru guo ni hai you yi xie kun huo, OH NO, qing zhan wo de xin zhan ting Ting wo shuo ai ni ( YES I DO ) wo ai ni *** I love you, I'll always be here, always loving you I love you (yes I do) I will never lose the ability to love you If you still have some confusion about this, OH NO, please stop, my heart will stop Listen to me say that I love you (YES I DO) I love you  Man this guy is whipped, oh crap I just realized that I finished the song.  I hope I'm not as whipped as him.  I probably though :\.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Back to my survey-stealing antics....  This one is from Melody's livejournal.  *What do you most like about your body? Hmm... I would have to say these like sexy bones. *And least? There's not a bad spot on me. *How many fillings do you have? 1 *Do you think you're good looking? Oh yeah, I mean look at me. *Do other people often tell you that you're good looking? Sure *Do you look like any celebrities?  My Mommy says that I do...   FASHION:  *Do you wear a watch? "The watch makes the man" in the words of my mom. *How many coats and jackets do you own? Um. One? That I never wear. *Favorite pants/skirt color? Khaki *Most expensive item of clothing? My... Shoes? I really don't know. *What kind of shoes do you wear? Asics  YOUR FRIENDS:  *Do your friends 'know' you? Not many people do. *What do they tend to be like? Like friends *Are there traits in you that are universally liked? I don't think. *How many people do you tell everything to?: None.  GENERAL QUESTIONS:  *Who is the smartest man alive at the moment? Oh oh oh me. *What do you prefer, a sunny or rainy day?: Rain is the best kind of any precipitation *Do you consider yourself lucky? I don't see how that cookie anecdote has anything to do with being lucky, but I can be quite lucky at times. *Do you feel pity for people who commit suicide? Their choice. Feel happy for them. *Choose one word to describe how you feel most often: Hungry. *Do you own any plaid clothing? Yes, never wear it though. *Do you own converse shoes?: No. *Do you own saucony shoes?: No. *Do you own old school nikes? No. *Do you wear tight pants? No. *Is there more than one zipper in your pants? If you count like pocket opening zippers yes. *Crush: Hmm... *Virgin: What do  you  think? *Natural hair color: black *Current hair color: Umm... black, I hope. *Eye color: Brownish I guess.  I don't gaze into my own eyes very often. *Height: 5'...8? *Weight: Too little.  I believe I  *Birthplace: Hicksville, Gay Hampshire *Shoe size: 8  FAMILY:  *Parents: 2 of them *Siblings: Pamela is so cool. *Live with: My parents and my sister, and myself presumably. *Favorite relatives: I would have to say my Filipino side, my aunts and uncles.  Or my uncle who has a beachside mansion in Rio.  THE PAST:  *What is the one thing you would change about your past? I would... probably do some stuff differently in elementary school. *What is the biggest mistake you've made in your life? Well... there was something I did which I probably shouldn't have in 5th grade... and again in 6th grade... *Last thing you heard: The song on my xanga. *Last thing you saw: Snow *Last thing you said: "not very equal standards" *What is the last TV show you saw?: Seinfeld, last night at 11. *What is the last song you heard?: The one on my xanga.  WHO IS THE LAST PERSON YOU...  *Saw? Mom *Kissed? Um... I'm not sure *Who is the last person you hugged? Don't...know... I still think Anne is the big hugger. *Fought with? I generally...avoid any confrontation at all. *Were on the phone with? Kevin.  FUTURE:  *What day is it tomorrow?: Sunday *What are you going to do after this? I don't know. *Who are you going to talk to? Whoever. *Where are you going to go? Outside I guess, no it's too cold, I am going to go be indecisive. *How old will you be when you graduate? 18? 17, if I feel annoying... *What do you wanna be? A bum on the streets *What is one of your dreams? Well there was that one where I went crazy. *Where will you be in 25 years? Living on the streets as the most successful bum on the block.  OTHER:  *Do you write in cursive or print? Print. *Are you a lefty or a a righty? Righty. *What is your sexual preference? I'm not gay,  not that there's anything wrong with that  *What piercings do you have? None. *First Crush: Umm... yeah... *What do you first notice about the opposite sex? If... they are hot? *What's your idea of the perfect date? I don't know. *Biggest turn on: A nice a....... personality *Ideal girl/guy: Hmm... well the  ideal  girl would be one that is intelligent, easy to talk to, has a great personality, amazingly good looking, and somehow is not at all conceited.  Or in other words, Melody. ;) *Sweetest thing that's happened to you: Sweet things... don't happen to me.  THE PAST:  *Memory [thing] you miss the most: Here we go again with my Holdenesque Childhood Innocence. *If you could go back in time, where would you go?: Well I would go back to 4th grade, and like not do some stuff that I did, and not hang around with people I did.  4th grade was like the turning point in my life.  Grades go way up, and social life goes way down, because certain best friends of mine were beginning to engage in some questionable activities, namely Eddie Han, Dan McLaughlin, and James Shirley. *Thing that you regretted doing after you had done it: That thing I did in 5th grade. *Memory you would like to forget: The memory of ever liking Amy, I mean omg what was I thinking. *What'd you do yesterday: pseudo-school, then I went to Newtonville with melody to like the bookstore, came back, ran with her, went to the weightroom, went home, did SAT stuff, eat, More Sat's, Watch TV, sleep. *Last song you listened to: Didn't they just ask this? Well since then I have also listened to "Black Tangerine" ~David Tao. *TV shows you wish they would re-air again: I'm not a big TV fan, unless it is at 11 or later.  THE FUTURE:  *Occupation: They just asked this too.  I still don't know. *Kids: LIke how many? um. 2 seems like a good number *Future son's name: Every cool chinese guy who isn't also a humongous nerd I know is named Vincent.  Or at least the majority. *Future daughter's name: I have to change my last name for these to work.  My daughter's name will be... idk I will let the mother decide. *Honeymoon: Rio *What are you doing tomorrow: Chinese school assuming it's not cancelled, nothing else.  FAVORITES:  *Food: Air seems good. *TV show: Seinfeld at 11. *Movie: Fight Club *CD: I don't see why anyone would buy cd's anymore. *Color: Red  HAVE YOU EVER:  *Been on a date: Not recently, and even then, not like an actual date. *Cried in public: I think I have. *Climbed a tree: Yes, every one I find. *Fell asleep in a movie theatre: Yes, the movie was so long and so boring. *Met a celebrity: Bill Cosby! And Bret Boone, but no one likes him. *Met the president: No. *Been scared to get a shot: Not the shot, but things coming after the shot. *Shopped at Abercrombie & Fitch: I wasn't actually shopping there... just accompanying some of my preppy friends from Philips... *Loved somebody so much it made you cry: I'm not sure...  RANDOM *Are you named after anyone? I don't believe so.  Jackie Chan, my chinese name at least. *Do you wish on stars? No. *Which finger is your favorite? I like the ring finger on my right hand. *When did you last cry? Some time ago. *Do you like your handwriting? It's not too small, it's just smushed.  My handwriting is too like tall and thin and smashed together they say. *Who do you admire? Taking a page out of the Melo book, it would be myself.  That's Car-melo Anthony, btw. *What is the #1 goal in your life? You said the same thing like 5 times.  My #1 goal in life would be like to... do...something... *Your favorite lunch meat? Umm... what is this "lunch" you speak of? *Any bad habits? Profuse finger-giving. *What store would you never be caught dead in? Oh god, Sephora. *If you were another person, would you be friends with you? If I was another person, would I still have the same like preference in friends as me?  Umm... well I would be inclined to say no. *Are you a daredevil? Haha no. *Have you ever told a secret you swore you wouldn't tell? Yes, and I did.  Tell, that is. *Do looks matter? Looks are half the battle..  *When was the last time you wanted to punch someone? Like, yesterday, when Doug was being an asshole. *Are you trendy? I'm such a trendsetter. *What do you do to prevent anger? Not... have much of it... *Who is your idol? Idol? iono. *Do you trust others easily? Not very. *What did you play with as a child? The good old days of genesis. *What class in school do you think is totally useless? I would have to say...Math completely, so stupid. *Do you like sappy love songs? Only if sung in chinese. *Have you ever been on radio or television? I have. *Have you ever intentionally hurt someone? Of course, I don't thin it hurt very much though. *Have you ever been in a mosh pit? No. *Do you feel understood most of the time? Haha no. *Would you rather have a sore throat or an upset stomach? Upset Stomach.  Sore throats hurt.  If you are going to throw up anyway, who cares about an upset stomach. Um, don't read that last part. *What is/are your nickname(s)? Umm... I have been called... Lo, L-ren, Chenboy, Mandarin, and then going back to the Philips days, C-Lo, Manny D-Lite, and uh... Ratface. *Could you be a vegetarian? Possibly. *Would you ever bungee jump? No. *Do you untie your shoes every time you take them off? Yes. *What are you worried about right now? No worrys. *Ever wear overalls? No, oh god, never. *Do you think you are strong? Hahahaha. *Do you have a driver's license? No. *Last person you called? Wasn't this question... somewhere earlier?  it was Kevin. *Last person 2 c u cry? Me? *You last went to the mall with? I don't know...
     

        
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Today was amazingly awesome.  It like doesn't even deserve to be counted as a day.  Let's Recap:  A-Block: We had a sub for English.  Supposedly we were doing our homework in class, but around my area, very few people were actually doing it.  Ian's brought in some very good brownies, and basically the whole period we played with my frozen Sierra Mist.  B-Block:  I had a free block because my teacher was out.  That was fun.  I just sat outside that Latin room doing my homework the whole period.  C-Block:  Another free because Belmarsh was out.  Ian' tried to drag me into his History class, but in the end I just hung out in the cafeteria with Jonk and Kevin.  E-Block:  Our history class was in the library, "researching".  It was pretty unproductive I thought, since we weren't allowed to take out the books we found on our topics.  G-Block:  All we did in math was this weird graphing exercise the whole class, it was pretty boring. And stupid and pointless.  As is everything we do in Math.  F-Block:  Mlle. Mazor is back from her malade.  We spent most of the class going over the hw and playing this fun game where Sam and I made great sentences together.  Overall, very fun.
     

        
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Well my life lately has been very unenlightening.  Let's see what has happened since my last post...  I have learned more about certain double 0 agents and their guns, plus an interesting sidekick named Jake.  Fun fact: James Bond's supervisors all have those stupid letter names, e.g. Q  or maybe... yes I agree.  Yesterday in History, Ms. Heidlage was telling us this "Little Black Sambo" story, which I now realize wasn't that great so i am not going to waste my time blogging about it.  Speaking of that, I have noticed that an increasing number of people are using nouns as verbs, namely those crazy WarIII people.  Like they will say, "He totally suicided on me." or like "I +8 armored the whole time." haha "And then I said ' plus eight armor! '" I've said that so many times it's just dead now.  And it wasn't mine to begin with.  What else...  Apparently Calvin does  not  engage in such activities.  Uber-Christian.  Anne was enlightening me about the socialist side of Helen Keller, as that is a possibility she is considering for her Junior Thesis.  It got me wondering what topic I am going to do for that.  Nong suggested I do, "The Economic Impact of Dorito's Advertising" when I pointed out how Dorito's always name their stuff like "Spic ier  Nacho", "Cool er  Ranch", and "Nacho Chees ier " and I was wondering what they were spicer, cooler, and cheesier than.  Kevin's philosophy is that it is completely acceptable for a girl to be overly insecure, but utterly unacceptable for a guy to be at all.  I think it has some value.  I don't think I'm  that  insecure...  Hmmm...  I don't believe that Yin can be drill instructer like, it's just so un-Yin, I mean I know he's driven, but he's always seemed like the apathetic type of guy. 
     

        
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Who do you think you ahhh?  I haven't blogged for a while, so I am, but I don't really have anything to say.  What has happened since the last time I did this... hmmm... let's back track.  On Tuesday, I watched the gymnastics meet.  The best part was when Jason broke the ring in half it was so funny. Let me see if I logged my conversation with Justin on this topic...dammit a day too late, I will give you the reader's digest version, not exact quotes  Me: That was so awesome when the ring broke Justin: I know Me: All of the sudden you hear this crack Justin: And then you hear him go "Aaaahh" Justin: And I'm like "Oh shit he fell" Justin: And he he gets up and he's like Justin: Dum dee dum I have a ring in my hand... Me: Hahaha  Well put.  What else happened... I've been talking to Julia Kalow online lately, it's pretty amusing, from her bathroom elf stories to her discussions of who is good looking.  Ah I did log this one.  MandarinYellow31 (9:45:54 PM): Sarah Blanks sits next to me in Chem pestface (9:45:58 PM): oh right pestface (9:46:04 PM): you must be the person who always sleeps pestface (9:46:06 PM): that she mentioned MandarinYellow31 (9:46:12 PM): whaat pestface (9:46:17 PM): or plays calc games/ MandarinYellow31 (9:46:18 PM): I do not always sleep pestface (9:46:19 PM): i can't remember pestface (9:46:22 PM): do to pestface (9:46:23 PM): o MandarinYellow31 (9:46:28 PM): that was only like MandarinYellow31 (9:46:30 PM): 3 times pestface (9:46:32 PM): hahaha MandarinYellow31 (9:46:34 PM): or like 5 pestface (9:46:35 PM): that's a lot MandarinYellow31 (9:46:38 PM): I don't know I don't count pestface (9:46:41 PM): clearly MandarinYellow31 (9:46:43 PM): I was really tired! ... pestface (9:52:40 PM): i think anyone with the last name dietz shoudl be neutered pestface (9:52:42 PM): just in case pestface (9:52:49 PM): preemptive strike MandarinYellow31 (9:52:55 PM): they are like, "I was planning to move in for the sneak attack at 1000 hours but that manuever was aborted" ... pestface (9:59:02 PM): she has a rotating roster of pseudoboyfriends MandarinYellow31 (9:59:10 PM): I have heard pestface (9:59:12 PM): and i've never understood what they find so attractive MandarinYellow31 (9:59:13 PM): who is it now? pestface (9:59:19 PM): some guy from waltham pestface (9:59:21 PM): named kwong MandarinYellow31 (9:59:22 PM): ok pestface (9:59:38 PM): she cant' ahve nong pestface (9:59:42 PM): so she goes for the next best thing pestface (9:59:48 PM): someone with a name that rhymes  Good stuff...  Yes. It's been fun.  People are going psycho, and I like playing along with psycho people so I'm going to stop blogging there. Or here. Whichever.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's been pretty uneventful lately, but I'm bored so I blog.  Because of New Year's, 4 of the last five days, not including today, have been spent at my parents' drunken parties.  They actually been pretty fun, even though I was like the only sober one there.  Chinese people show that they are drunk in their faces, but they don't act like they're drunk very much.  Then again, I don't really know how people act when they are drunk.  Jay Chou performed this song in the New Year's Festival, if anyone watched that, I don't know why you would.  He's such a bad live performer.  Oh well.  Oh oh revelation.  Oliver can be like Young Lu, that loser.  I actually think I might be able to beat him up, despite my lack of the ability to throw a punch.  I think you need like your arms to be able to function to do that.  I can actually bench more than my weight now on the Nautilus, I'm proud of myself.  Then again, being able to bench more than  I  weigh isn't really saying much.  Yup.  My father is watching that New Year's Festival thingy over and over again, he taped it.  It's pretty exciting. 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This song is fun, if you can stand the horrible screeching in the beginning.  "In the Name of the Father" ~ Jay Chou
     

        
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Oh yeah I just remembered another Kalow-ism.  OK yesterday in Chem, we were doing the Periodicity Lab, and Mr. Belmarsh gave a a relatively large piece of sodium to react.  And so we were supposed to take the submerged test tube out of the water without letting the gas escape, except Jonny couldn't get his finger over the hole, so he ended up with his hand in the Sodium hydroxide solution for like 30 seconds while not realizing what it was, and he was like:  "Why is this burning my hand so much?!"  Today he complained that a layer of his skin had ben taken off.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jonny Kalow is the funniest kid I have ever met.  I should just fill this post with Jonny quotes.  And that's what I'm going to do.  So here goes.  You'd probably have to be there though.  "Nothing can hurt me, I'm on weed!"  Me: "So you should really call it bust-a-move instead of Snood." Jonny: "More like Bust-A-Stupid!"  "To me, he's just an ordinary father, but to other people, he's something more..."  Greg Bemis: "Are you gonna smack some balls?" Jonny: "I'll smack your balls"  Actually that's all I remember... Jonny say more funny stuff. 
     

        
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Haha, I just had one of those times when I think of random things and then I crack up.  This time I thought back to that time after Model U.N. when I was talking to Joey Backer and Ben Fong and they were telling me this story about Ben and John Garabedian.  So apparently in the winter Ben Fong sees John Garabedian while walking to school and he likes to push him in the snow.  So one day Ben sees John Garabedian walking to school and he decides to push him as usual.  But then John like falls into the street, and so Ben feels bad and decides to help him up.  But then, here's the best part, when Ben helps him up, he sees that it isn't John at all, but some like old man.  Haha, I was laughing my face off.  And now Ben Fong is scared to go near anyone for fear of injuring senior citizens.  I thought it was pretty funny.  You'd probably have to be there though.  Or have Ben Fong tell the story.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I just realized this, look how many times I say "That was fun" in my last last post.  It's like every other line.  I must have had a lot of fun that day.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I was "master of ceremonies" emcee-ing for the Chinese New Year Festival thing at that Chink School of mine.  I think it went wonderfully well.  Afterwards, I went to the "dance" with Kevin, Brian, Larry, and the Jing gang.  It wasn't as much of a dance as a "sit-around-and-talk-while-older-people-dance-to-ballroom-music."  But it was pretty fun.    So... them Patriots are going to the Superbowl, eh?  Great excuse to watch those awesome commercials they have.   "An Jing" ~Jay Chou.  I like it.  Except that it's like the ultimate "take me back" song, and I don't know who I would be asking to take me back.  Actually it's less of a "take me back" song than a "She left me and I'm going to have to get over it" song.  Cuz he realizes that she won't.  Take him back, that is.  Oh yeah, one more thing, I am funny and cool in Stephanie Kaplan's book.  This excites me. I probably shouldn't keep saying that or else as I said to Alex, "I will cease to be funny or cool."
     

        
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So Wednesday was a half-day.  Woohoo.  I did so many stupid things that day and I am back to my losing ways.  I was playing volleyball, and apparently I got hit in the face, although I don't remember it happening, and it knocked the lens out of my glasses and I didn't realize it until like I was changing back into my normal clothes and when I took my glasses off, my finger went through the hole where the lens goes.  I was pretty surprised.  And then I had French.  Jacob Fleming made me transfer my calculator games to him and afterward I put the calculator in my desk. But after french I forgot to take it back, and the next period I had a math test, and one of the questions was like, "Use the calc function on your calculator..." and I was like "Uh oh." That was fun.  Math sux.  And then after math I went out in search of some people, and then I saw Emily Price, and she was like "If you're waiting for Melody, she already left."   And so, I was so disappointed because my entire purpose in life for that day was finding her, and I didn't so I was like, "Why do these things keep happening to me?"  So then I found George, and we were both looking for ways to get home, and so we decided to combine our efforts.  He started asking all his Russian friends and they all refused to give him a ride.  Somehow Nichole Seto knows who I am, that's so weird.  George asked her for a ride and she was like "Why don't you ask Loren?"  And I was surprised.  Kevin, Nichole Seto is the short one that likes Nong.  Then George and I decided to go to KFC.  We found the gang there, and I ditched George for them.    Then we went to John's house and we well funned ourselves.  I left my backpack at KFC, which was annoying.  Ok so yesterday, it was pretty exciting.  It was supposed to be D-day, so just to make Alex happy, I said that I had rushed back from Computers to see how it went when really I just went to see Melody in all her splendor.  Ahhh...  Good Splendor.  Then I went to lunch. I paid 50 cents for Hiro to say stuff to Julia Kalow, but it didn't really work. He was supposed to to say:  "Hey, Julia, do you know if Jonny likes anyone?  ...Do you know if he's free this Saturday?"  But then it backfired when after the first question, Julia said, "JONNY DOESN'T HAVE HORMONES!"  That was fun.  So then after school, I went to chess club with "who-else" and then i went to the club to pseudo-work.  It was pretty fun because I had to staff over Bradley and Nick Lombardi and I could like tell them what to do.  **Control freak**  W/e  that was fun.  Oh yeah one more thing.  Alex was listening to "Hey Ya" and he got annoyed when they said "fo sho" instead of "for sure" and then in History, they were talking about this place called "Fashoda" and I wanted to say to him, "Shouldn't it be 'For-sure-da?'"  And we both said that at like the same time.  I think he has made it "For-Sure-The" now, but it was pretty funny.  Yeah...  That was fun.  
     

        
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      That's the bad thing about mp3's, since they are so much bigger than midi's, if you don't have a good connection, they'll just like stop in the middle of the song and then you get annoyed.  Well, maybe it is a good thing that it is stopping idk, w/e you want. 
     

        
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The other day I went to Boston with Alex, John, and Jon.  It was moderately fun.  We watched Paycheck, and then I ate a Mandarino Gelatto.  It tasted pretty good, but I only bought it because it was "mandarino" flavored.  Oh I also ate a "wonder pop" which was less than wondermenting.  Possibly wonderful.  That basically all I wanted to say about that.  Hm.  I feel like... I've done something horribly wrong... I just have that feeling, but I don't know what is causing it.  I'm sorry for being so apologetic.  I did it again, gah.  Recently, I've been apologizing for every little thing I do, and I don't know why.  This might have something to do with the thinking I did something wrong, but I don't know.  On a lighter note (I went from a light note, to a somewhat heavier one, back to a light one) um... I don't actually have anything to say.   Jumping to conclusions Made me fall away from you. I'm so glad that the truth,  has brought back together me and you We're sitting on the ground (sitting on the ground)  And we whisper, (and we whisper)  "Say what you're thinking out loud."   "Best of Me" ~ The Starting Line  
     

        
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Taking Back Sunday is a good band.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I was pretty bored so I decided to take part in everyone's favorite pasttime, surfing around on the College Board Website! No, not actually.  Well, actually I did do that for like half an hour :\.  But what i really meant was putting these stupid surveys on blogs/xangas/livejournals. Oh yeah and changing the song to a far more annoying one. "Mi Lan de Xiao Tie Jiang" ~ Jay Chou.  I translated the chorus in the last post.  I think that's the only song from which I took the chorus. Ok survey-time.  Am I going to cite my source? Maybe. You can figure it out.   I see: Right now? My computer? I need: Nothing really. I find: ?? I don't understand. Random pieces of crap of the ground I want: Hmm... Some people's candy posteriors... Not really.  I want... I don't know. I have: If I was slightly more whipped than I am, I would say something like "The best girl in the whooole world." But I'm not that whipped, so i won't say that, even though I think it. I wish: Wishing is for losers. I love: a lot of stuff.  Not really actually.  A few select things.  Not things, but you know what I mean. I hate: A lot of things. Not that many actually.  I am not a very hateful person, if that is a word. Person... I miss: Here we go again... "Childhood Innocence." I fear: That I will do something royally stupid one of these days and screw up my life. I feel: Bored, whihc is why i'm doing this in the first place. I hear: The Chinese TV channel in the background. I smell: ... I don't smell. I crave: Your mother.  Sorry I had to put one of those somewhere. I search: For answers to my many questions. I wonder: Why I am doing this at all. I regret: Doing stuff, saying stuff, doing a certain some...thing (1?)  When was the last time you ...  Smiled: Some time ago. Laughed: Probably at/with my sister today. Cried: Kevin, you can't cry because you lose things, I'm sorry, but there are more important things in life than like your wallet and its contents and like your other stuff that went with it. Bought something: Kevin, you bought your best friends for Christmas, ha.  I bought like something sometime, i dono. Danced: Meh. On the cruise I suppose. Kissed someone: A while... Talked to an ex: I try to refrain from such activities. Watched your favorite movie: Like maybe a month ago. Had a nightmare: I don't have nightmares.  Sometimes scary dreams, but not nightmares.  Scary dreams as in like something bad happens, but they aren't like wake-me-up-in-the-middle-of-the-night scary.  A Last time for everything ...  Last book you read: Hmm... I think one of those books I read over break, like "The Kitchen God's Wife" or something.  That was a girly book. Last movie you saw: LOTR or The Italian Job. Last song you heard: This one that is playing now, assuming you didn't mute it. Last thing you had to drink: Milk. Last time you showered: This morning. Last thing you ate: Lunch.  Do You ...  Smoke: Nope. Do drugs: Uh uh. Have sex: Not anymore... That implies that I used to. ooOOoohh. Not that good. Sleep with stuffed animals: Sometimes. Live in the moment: I am so not spontaneous. Have a boyfriend/girlfriend: The best. Have a dream that keeps coming back: That one with the car. Play an instrument: Nope. Believe there is life on other planets: I believe that with the universe so large and the possibility of millions of other Earth-like planets, that on one of them there has to be life... somewhere. Remember your first love: I do Still love him/her: I do not. Read the newspaper: Sometimes Have any gay or lesbian friends: Hmm... Does Hoi count as my friend? Just kidding... Believe in miracles: Not really.  Just do it. Believe it's possible to remain faithful forever: Faithful like to a girl or like to a religion? Consider yourself tolerant of others: Ehh... There are more tolerant people than me. Consider love a mistake: Do I? I don't understand how that would be possible. Like the taste of alcohol: Not especially but it's not horribly terrible. Have a favorite candy: Candy... I don't know.  I don't eat the stuff much. Believe in astrology: Not really, I read my horoscope from time to time though. :Believe in God: I believe with the world how it is, there must be a higher power guiding it.   Pray: Not like every day, but from time to time I do. Go to church: I do. Have any secrets: Kevin, the point in keeping something a secret is that it doesn't get in the wrong hands.  That's why you don't tell people...  I have a few secrets that only like not that many people know about... What Melody calls my "secret Mafia life."   Have any pets: I used to.  My caty was soo cool Do well in school: TERRIBLE, I hate it. Go to or plan to go to college: Hopefully. Have a major: I am terribly indecisive. Talk to strangers who instant message you: Kevin that is so obviously an automated message, seeing that I have gotten the exact same thing like 10 times.  Or maybe they just like me more, because I am cooler than you.  I talk to strangers when they message me yes. Wear hats: Not often.  My Oakley hat, that's so funny. Have any piercings: No. Have any tattoos: Ew, no. Hate yourself: At times. Have an obsession: Isn't it obvious? Have a secret crush: Shh, don't tell... Not really. Do they know yet: If I had said yes to the previous question, I would say "Well then it wouldn't be very secret would it?" but since I said no, this is pretty irrelevant. Collect anything: Girls, not really though. Have a best friend: I'm not the kind of person to rank one friend over another.  But I have to say that some friends are better than others. Wish on stars: Don't wish, just make it happen yourself. Like your handwriting: It's exciting. Have any bad habits: I don't think that is considered a bad habit Kevin.  That is considered being a guy. Care about looks: Hm.  I want to say no, but you know that's a lie. Boy/girlfriend's looks: Wait, was the previous question like the looks of like random people? I don't get it. Friends and other people: Yeah all my friends have to be so hot.  XP. Believe in witches: No Believe in Satan: Hmm... maybe... Believe in ghosts: Well in all my dying dreams, I can still see what happens to me after, so I would say yes.  No one comes to my funeral... It's so empty.  It's like no one likes me.
     

        
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Fraternizing with the enemy Triplets lying withing the Beast It claims to be Silent but crys out "Take out the Charlatanical Leaders!"   Wow that was weird.  Anyway, there are many ways that I could start this post. I could be like "What a ripoff" or like "So close yet so far away" or like "It's implied" or something like that but I'm not going to. I tend to fill my life with "if only"s but in retrospect, while some things would be nice, I really can't complain about how it is now.  So... new year's, woohoo.  First Night was really fun, Kevin and I lioned pretty well.  That was exciting.  I think I'm going to do it again next year.  I have to learn to head though, so I'm not constantly in the Lion's ass.  Ehh... I have nothing more to say. So I'm going to barrage you guys with Chinese songs/Translations, there's really no point in reading on, and this whole post was pointless anyway, you shouldn't have wasted your time reading it at all.  I'm going to take excerpts of songs this time, cuz entire songs don't seem fun enough. And I'm going to number them woohoo. And I'm not going to put the actual chinese cuz it is annoying to write and nobody can read it anyway.  And if you do read the songs, don't take some of them the wrong way, I just like the song, I'm not identifying with it in any way.  1. "Wei Lian Gu Bao (William's Castle)" ~ Jay Chou  ni shuo ni shuo fen shu zen me ting liu  yi zhi zai ting liu shui rang ta ting liu de  wei shen me wo nu peng you chang wai jia you  ni que hai rang wo chu qiu  *** You say, you say why the points stop coming in, They keep on stopping, but who makes them stop. My girlfriend is in the stands Why do you still make me look foolish?  2. "Yi Si Lan Bao (Istanbul)" ~ Jay Chou  chu zai yi si tan bao que zhi  xiang ni he han bao  wo xiang yao ni de wei xiao mei tian dou neng kan dao  wo zhi dao zhe li hen mei dan jia xiang de ni geng mei  *** I'm in Istanbul, But all I can think about is you and the burgers(???) I want to be able to see your smiles everyday I know it's beautiful here, but you, at home, are more breathtaking.  3. "Nuo Fu (Coward)" ~ Jay Chou  shuo bu bu dai biao nuo fu ni ying gai hen jiao ao  *** Saying no doesn't mean you're a coward, you should be very proud.  4. "Pu Tong Peng You (Just Friends)" ~ David Tao  deng dai wo sui shi sui di zai deng dai zuo ni gan qing shang de yi lai wo mei you ren he de yi wen jiu shi ai *** I'll wait, However long or far, I'll wait I'll make it depend on how you feel I don't have any objections Only love.  5. "Ta De Jie Mao (Her eyelashes)" ~ Jay Chou  qin ai de zong xie shi shi mei ban fa jiao  biao cuo qing de gan jue you yi dian zao  lai zhe bu zou hui rang ren hen gan mao  yi shang zhe dao li wo quan dou liao  *** My dear, some things can never be taught.  Coming on to the wrong person is pretty bad Insisting on staying can make you get sick. I understand all of the above.   6. "An Jing (Silence)" ~ Jay Chou  Ni yi jin yuan yuan li kai  Wo ye hui man man zou kai  Wei she me wo lian fen kai dou qian jiu zhe ni  Wo zhen de mei you tian fen  An jing de mei zhe me kuai  Wo hui xue zhe fang qi ni  Shi ying wei wo tai ai ni  *** I was going to be annoying and put a fake traslation, but then I realized how stupid and pointless that would be, anyway, here it is.  You are already so far away I'll slowly leave too Why is it that even as we break up, you still have power over me? I really can't do it Staying quiet is too hard I'll learn to let you go Because I love you too much  Ok here is the fake translation I was going to put, I don't even know why:  So All My Codes Only Have Evil Numbers If Someone Thinks Hard, Even Evil Numbers Express Many Yearns  That was exciting, now on with the songs.  7. "Gong Bao Ji Ding (Kung Pao Chicken)" ~ David Tao   Wo zhi xi wang mei tian gen ni zai yi qi Bu yong zuo she me, zai jia li jiu ke yi Oh..baby I dont know wei she me kan shang wo Mei you qian qu song ni "Hello Kitty" Ke yi, wo suo you de yi qie tong tong dou gei ni Ying wei wo ai ni *** I just want to be able to be with you every day We don't have to do anything, staying at home is fine Oh Baby, I don't know why you see me I don't have enough money to give you "Hello Kitty" Ok, I would easily give you everything that I have Because I love you  8. "Mi Lan De Xiao Tie Jiang (Milan's Little Blacksmith)" ~ Jay Chou  Ta zhen de zhen de xiang zhi dao  (Na shou lai zi dong ou de min yao he xian dao di shen me tiao)  Mi lan de tian kong gang po xiao  (Na ma di tie hai yao qiao duo shao ji ta cai neng mai de dao)   Ta zhen de zhen de xiang zhi dao  (Ta bu zhi dao, zen me ban cai hao, shui bu zhao) Ta jiang na pu man da po liao (Xiao xiao yuan wang jiu kuai shi xian le ta zai xiao) *** He really really wants to know (That folk song from Eastern Europe, in what key is that tune?) Milan's Sky has just awoken (How long does he have to work on those horseshoes before he can buy the guitar?)  He really really wants to know (He doesn't know, what is he going to do? He can't sleep) He takes the coin box and smashes it (His little wish has almost come true, he's laughing)  Ok, I think that's enough.  8 songs should do it.  Well, I still "zhen de zhen de xiang zhi dao" a couple things, I'm sure you do too. Like what was with that little italicized part in the beginning, and why I would bother to make that fake translation.  Oh well.  Figure it out. 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I just realized that a fun way to make people actually listen to you is to add "not that anyone cares" to the end of your ramblings as long as you aren't talking about like poop-shoveling or something.  Yeah so I was talking to Ken Zhao the other night, and he made me realize a lot of things about things.  Being really vague is also helpful.  Houston is 10 games over .500, awesome pwnage!  Something that makes people drone you out is when you are overly excited about something that is pretty unimportant.  Another thing that does that is when you talk about what people listen to and what they don't.  I often find myself asking the question, "When was the last time I actually listened, not physically, but like through any form of communication, to something important that [a person] had to say?"  And then I try to think of what they were talking about and what not, and sometimes it is difficult.  And then I ask the opposite, "When was the last time I have told [this person] something important?"  I would have to say never for most people.  I don't say because you don't care.  See I did it again.   For them I do call But my tears, they do not come. When will it return?   Yeah so apparently, I can't fake cry anymore.  I don't know whether that is a good thing or a bad thing.
     

        
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I just realized how screwed up Wednesday, March 10 is going to be for me.  The National French Exam and our last math meet are on the same day, which means that I'm going to end up getting to math 10 minutes late because of French, stay for 15 minutes, and then leave half an hour early for math team.  What's more, that day I get to miss French for French F Block, and then I miss Math for Math G block. Screwed up.  And then Thusday, March 4 and Thursday, March 25 I miss the entire day for various engineering related reasons.    Ni shuo wo xiang yi ge xiao hai, zhong ai rang ni cai Wo shuo ni cai xiang ge xiao hai, zhong yao wo shuo cai ming bai   You say I'm like a little kid because I always want to make you guess I say you're the one who's like a little kid because you always need me to tell you
     

        
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Soo... my sleek, aerodynamic do... Reactions:  Jonk: "Now Loren looks like some little asian kid..." Brian Wang/Kevin/Doug: "Um... ok."  Jason: "I just realized that you look like a Shaolin monk when I looked at your shadow and it was so smooth..."  Kevin: "Now we can rub your head for good luck."  Me: "I think the main reason I did this was so people could rub my head" Ian: "You mean so you can rub your head?" Me: "..." Ian: "Oh fine so you and Anne can rub your head?" Me: "..." Ian: "You know it's true."  [Doug starts rubbing my head vigorously] Me: "Doug, this head has been in exotic places." Kevin: "Yeah, I wouldn't touch it if I were you."  Jake GA: "Hey Loren, way to have no hair..." [Shut up, you are GA]  Jason: "Your head is so much better shaped than mine...[Goes into long story about how his head is flat because his parents wouldn't let him sleep on his side because it made his ears stick out]"  Stuff about going with/against the grain  Jeff: "Hey now you can wear this viking hat!" [I put the viking hat on] Jeff (to Nong): "Wow, do I look that stupid when I wear it?" Nong: "Pretty much."  Brett: "Take off your hat" Me: "Take off  your  hat" [referring to his bleached hair] [Both look at each other and then walk away]  Ha... Then we went to John's house and it was like complete maulage time.  Except really not.  You guys make such a big deal and we didn't even do anything...  Or at least we didn't do much...  Ahh, cuddle bitches... Haha Jason, the ladder theory.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wow, cutting your own hair is harder than it looks...  My head is cold.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Audio conversations with people on MSN messenger are fun.  Especially when said person has two little brothers who think that said person is emamored with me just because I went over said person's house once or twice, or possibly three times, and keep making like kissy sounds in the background.    And also because one of said person's little brothers is amazing at the piano and I have never seen anything quite like it.  Watching him play is quite the experience, especially when he gets to the loud part and things start falling off the wall, and then in the soft parts his hands dancing across the keys so delicately and with such intricate detail.  And then when I was over said person's house and my phone rang, he runs downstairs and starts playing the song on my ringtone, that crazy Turkish one.  That was so funny.  It was pretty good.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Yesterday was the most fun I've had in a while.  I won't go into details though, because some parts of it were kind of sketchified.  Actually, if you look at the individual parts of my day alone, it looks just like a really fun day.  But then if you like take the whole day as a whole, the duality of it is like weirding.  Lots of fun though.
     

        
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I have to actually watch this movie sometime.  Kevin, can I borrow it sometime during vacation?  Parry Shen reminds me of Kenny.  And then his name reminds me of Jason.  Mmhm.
     

        
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I need to write down these quotes like Alex does so i don't forget them...  And I think that I forgot all of them actually.  I remember there were a bunch from my English class, and they seemed so memorable that I didn't write them down.  Aparently they weren't that memorable.  Some stuff about Macbeth.  Of course there is Chun Fun's little thing  Chun Lau: "Why don't you get that girl that Jason used to like. What's her name again? Beijiar?" [And then he writes it down on something as "Bayjar"]  And of course you can't forget "Wei-Weian".  Good stuff.  I'm still trying to remember that Macbeth quote, and failing...  W/e it is a lost cause.  As I said to Stephanie Kaplan, now I get to do more, harder math, woohoo, it's my life dream.  Such a nerd.  I think I'm going to spare you the random anecdotes about my life this time.  It's a combination of my being lazy and realizing that you don't care.  Ok.  All-star game tonight.  Who's psyched for some uncompetitive action with a complete disregard for defense?  I know I am.  Just a note, I'm wearing this extremely gay shirt right now, and I don't know why, I've never worn it before in my life because it is so amazingly homosexual.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Awesomeness...
     

        
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ok more quoting...  From English class:  Jamie Axelrod: "Wow look at the snowflakes! They're as big as my nose!"  [When the witch says that she took the pilot's thumb in Macbeth] Beth SomeLastName: "Wait, they had planes back then?"  Ms. Zolli on Macbeth's dilemma: "Well it's like inviting one of your friends over for dinner and a sleepover, and then killing him.  It's not a very nice thing to do."  In French:  Sam: "I got chalk all over my pants, but they're kind of yellow anyway, so I guess it doesn't really matter." Me: "I got chalk all over my hands, but they're kind of yellow anyway, so I guess it doesn't really matter."  I really shouldn't quote myself, it just isn't right.  Oh yeah then in chemistry today, Jonny Kalow was doing his Rubik's cube thing again, and I started timing him to see how fast he could do it.  This was before class started, so like everyone in the class was watching Jonny do his Rubik's thing.  So then he had like two left to switch around, and only like almost 2 minutes had gone by, and I was commentating since I am that much of a loser.  And it went something like this:  "Come on, Jonny, you're almost there, one minute and 45 seconds, [and then the rubik's cube breaks apart cuz he was going too fast] Oh My God! You loser! You broke it! You fail miserably, DNF!"  And I was like yelling this in front of the whole class, and when I realized it I was pretty embarrassed. Yeah.  Ok.  We're playing Grand Strategy in History.  It seems like it would be more fun if I wasn't Serbia, possibly the worst country ever.  She going through the list of countries, and she is like "US, UK, Italy, Austria-Hungary, France, Russia, and... Serbia."  So I was talking to like Matt Woolf and Josh Magid, and they were like:  Josh: "Matt, how many troops does Austria-Hungary have?" Matt: "150" Josh: "Really, France does too! I think UK has like 120 and Russia about that number too.  Loren, how many troops does Serbia have?" Me: "Uh... 5" [Everybody laughs at me]  That conversation never actually took place.  I lied.  But parts of it happened, but not with all participants involved at the same time.  Uh huh.  Yup. That was fun.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Boo not the whole song.  [edit:] Even more boo, no song at all.  I was trying to get PPK on here, but the link is so slow.  So I was left with this obnoxiously loud song.  Yeah, my Durango Number ninety-five Take me to the home Kick boots And ultra live  See heaven flash A horror show Knock it nice and smooth Step back And watch it flow, yeah  (chorus) Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop (stop, stop, stop)  Yeah, the devil Ride a dinosaur He paint the monster red So the blood Don't stain the floor  In and out Real savage show Sorry as a shot Came sickness Watch it flow, yeah  Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop  (hook) Scream if you want it 'Cause I want it more Scream if you want it 'Cause I want it more  Yeah, my Durango Number ninety-five Take me to the home Kick boots And ultra live  See heaven flash A horror show Knock it nice and smooth Step back And watch it flow, yeah  Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop Never gonna stop me Never gonna stop  Scream if you want it 'Cause I want it more Scream if you want it 'Cause I want it more
     

        
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I feel the need to make up for the loss of Alex, so here is a quote from history:  "You will be doing it with your partner during class time" -Ms. Heidlage  Yeah, I know it isn't as good as his, but I am not perpetually in striking position to write down quotes like he is.  I can see from the look on your face, you're a long way off.  Jonny Kalow.  Just saying his name is good enough.  What did he do now?  He is so good at Rubik's cube solving; it is so amazing.  I was marveling at his abilities the other day in gym when Brian Wang brought one in.  It was like mind-bogglingly cool.  Oh so cool.  On a somewhat related note, I'm in Anne's gym class, I'm not sure if that's a good thing or a bad thing.  What am I saying, of course it's good, it's Anne... I'm not sure if that was meant to be sarcastic or not.  I'm me. This is who I am. And if anybody's getting kicked, it's gonna be you.   Speaking of which, or not really, actually... Yeah... I got lost there.  "I'm so unbelieveably annoyingly pissed that I lost something that really was of neglible importance that I am going to annoy everybody by complaining my face off and if they say anything about I will make personal attacks on their family"  I should stop doing that.  I alienate myself too much.  My Valentine's day poem is coming along nicely.  Except that it's not and it's the worst poem I've written in my whole life.  I have the first two quatrains done and the couplet.  One more quatrain to go.  I sent my second to Kevin.  He said it sucked.  I agreed.  I would write it here if it didn't suck so much.  But since it does, I won't.  Sun medallions, whoa.  Speaking of which, Superbowl commercials were sub-par this year, but there were some good ones.  The best ones I think were the Bud Lite horse one, the Pepsi bear one, and the Staples godfather-esque one.  And of course you can't forget the most quotable one, that Cialis commercial:  "If erections last for more than 4 hours, SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP."  Ren ci de fu, wo yi zhui ru kan bu jian zui de guo du. Qing yuan liang  wo de zi fu.  Too religious for Jay. Then again he  is  from Taiwan.  I don't know what that was supposed to mean, so don't beach.  I really should get that song back up here, but Alex would beach, and Ms. Jackson is not bad.  Your mom is not bad... IN BED.  One more time you will laugh about it and he'll never try to give you more. And I don't care he is such a dick. He treats you like you are a stupid whore.  Yeah, I agree.  Wow, what a waste of time. I wonder how many times I broke into song, I do that so often now...
     

        
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So Jason and I went to Starbucks today and we started talking about stuff that we probably should have been and this happened, in a crowded coffee shop:  Jason: [whispers something to me] Me:  QUADRUPLE PENETRATION?!?!  Jason: [Looks at me really surprised and then hides under the table] Me: [Realizes that I said that really really loud, and then tries to sheild my face]  Hmm... what else happened... Oh yeah while walking with Jason to Starbucks, we walked past like Chris Leavitt and them, and it reminded me of the first day that the close-up kids came back.  Me: Do you remember when the close-up kids came back and they discussed stuff in our History class? Jason: Yeah. Me: Did you find it weird that Somers complained that other kids were smoking in the rooms? Jason: [Laughs]  Ahh...  -Who did the Nazis sign a non-aggression pact with? -Presumably someone much shorter!  This week sucks.  Make it better.  I think I'm going to get my teacher recommendation from Belmarsh.  I think he is the only teacher I have who doesn't like despise me.  Except for Mme DeRobert of course because that would be biologically impossible for her. 
     

        
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Britney apparently likes this song.  "I schtill shee people schtarving on the schtreets of St. Peterschburg."
     

        
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So many birthdays, so little time...  Happy birthday to:  Felix 2.25 Bradley 2.26 Lily 3.5 Josh 3.10 Kevin 3.18 Jung  3.23 Melody 3.28 Jing 3.31 Hannah 4.1 Margaret 4.5 Lynette 4.7 Anthony 4.12 Debbie 4.21 Zach PC 4.22 Sherwin 4.22 Hayley 4.22 Kenny 4.25 Nong 4.28 Eric C 4.28 Andrew 5.4 Tommy 5.7 Loren 5.10 Grandma 5.13 Anguel 5.17 Anna 5.17 Anne 5.19 Shannon 5.19 Matt 5.22  That looks like a lot.  Oh yeah Jason fits somewhere in April I can't exactly remember where... If I happened to forget you, it is either because I don't know you, I don't care, or I don't know your birthday.  Or that I just forgot.  Ok bye.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
              But, soft! What light through yonder window breaks?          It  is the east, and Juliet is the sun!          Arise fair sun and kill the envious moon,          Who is already sick and pale with grief          That thou her maid are more fair than she.          Be not her maid, since she is envious.          Her vestal livery is but sick and green,          And none but fools do wear it. Cast it off.          It is my lady, oh, it is my love!          Oh, that she knew she were!          She speaks, yet she says nothing. What of that?          Her eye discourses, I will answer it.          I am too bold, 'tis not to me she speaks.          Two of the fairest stars in all the heaven,          Having some business do entreat her eyes          To twinkle in their spheres till they return.          What if her eyes were there, they in her head?          The brightness of her cheek would shame those stars          As daylight doth a lamp; her eyes in heaven          Would through the airy region stream so bright          That birds would sing and think it were not night.          See how she leans her cheek upon her hand!          Oh that I might be a glove upon that hand,          That I might touch that cheek! 
     

        
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hahaha, Anne Chan, that was sooo funny, I don't think I've laughed like that in a while...  Let's recap:  Side-to-side walking Walking like she has something... I won't go on Buck Teeth Midriff showing Asscrack showing  Impersonations were the funniest part, hahaha, Brett and Justin are the best.  This is the reason not to become a Guidance Aide w/e thing.
     

        
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jay Chou has a huge range...  But then again his falsetto sounds like stuff.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So nothing has happened at all lately, but I am going to post anyway because Alex wants me to, and apparently I will do anything he says, especially when it's something like updating my blog, and also apparently I like writing in really long run-on sentences that seem to have no end and just keep going on and on and on...  OK enough of that.  [Trying to think of stuff to write]  The other day in English, Jamie Axelrod was telling this story about her dad's kittens and it went something like this:  "Oh oh oh, I have this really funny story that is kind of like that.  So when my dad was little, he used to hide things in his sock drawer because no one would find them there.  So one day, his cat had kittens, but the family couldn't keep them and were going to give them away.  But my dad wanted to keep the kittens so he hid them in his sock drawer.  But then he forgot about them for like 3 weeks, and  THEY ALL DIED"  And then Ian and I were like, "That's not very funny..."  "When the time is right, will you be ready?"  That is a funny commercial.  Let's all laugh a lot. Hahaha.  Yup...  Anyway...  [Still trying to think of things to write]  Oh yeah Thursday in computers, Jonny was writing a quote in his notebook like Alex does that was like Matt saying something to Gail and then it ended with *SMACKDOWN* and I thought that was kind of funny.  And so I laughed and then Jonny said something inaudibly.  And then I was like:   "What Jonny, you think Gail's face is funny?"  And then he was like, "Huh? What?"  And then it was like *SMACKDOWN*.  Ok I think that is enough.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ha, I just remembered the funniest experience of my life, I'm going to be laughing for days on end...  This was like in 8th grade or something, I was walking past Franklin, and I was bored so I decided to say to Aaron, "I'm going to walk up to some little kid and magically know his name" and he goes "ok" And so we're walking and I see this kid named Dmitry who was in like 4th or 5th grade or something and I go "Hi Dmitry" and then he turns around and looks at me with like a look of sheer disbelief on his face and says, "HOW DID YOU KNOW MY NAME?!"  And then Aaron and I started cracking up so badly because I called that.  And what made it more funny was that Dmitry had like a Russian mixed with English accent so his voice was really comical.  Yeah. Good Story.  I agree.
     

        
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hmm...  JETS Competition today.  We pwnd.  1st place.  It was pretty fun.  Hiro hit this big kid in the face with a paper airplane and the kid flipped him off.  And then while we were eating, they were discussing their AP Lit class, and I felt like saying something, so I said "Wow, snowpeas are crunchy"  And then Hiro said, "Wow, Loren that was so deep! You should write a haiku"  And then he wrote a haiku for me.  It went like this:  My name is Loren I write a haiku like this My name is Loren  But that sense of satisfaction after winning JETS was quickly erased after I got the ARML results and found out that I didn't qualify.  Oh boo.  I'm so annoyed, I so should have made it.  Yin and Hiro pwnd me.  I was so psyched about it too.  I mean, yet another chance to do more, harder math while socializing with the nerdiest seniors in the state?  What more could I ask for?  I'm not sure if that was sarcastic or not, but I am disappointed.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Josh: "Vincent, yes or no, do you have a *****?" Vincent: "I SAID I DON'T HAVE PENIS YOU F***ING RE-RETARD!"  Haha, Vince is funny.  In an annoying way.  We got that one on tape.  Hahaha.
     

        
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      That blue/black design got old, this is possibly more homosexual.  And suddenly I'm so much more homophobic.
     

        
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Alex stole my history quote, so I will give you one from Engineering.  You'd probably have to be there though.  So we were talking about cooking hot dogs in our solar ovens, and stuff.  Brian Prince: "Can we cook cheeseburgers instead?" Mr. Rosenhahn: "No..." John Dyer: "What about prime ribs?" Mr. Rosenhahn: "Do you realize how long that would take?" Evan Schein: "Fine, Mr. Rosenhahn, will you at least let us have some potato salad to go witht eh hot dogs?" Alison Fletcher: "Pasta Salad!" Evan Schein: "No, potato salad is definitely much better than pasta salad." Mr. Rosenhahn: "We're building solar ovens not having a picnic!"  Hehehe...  Alex was asleep today in history.  But who wasn't?  A lot of people.  Mr. Barry started throwing stuff at Noah, and then when he woke up he was like, "Why is everyone laughing?"  And then he claimed that he wasn't really asleep.  Suure.  Yeah so yeah.  That was fun.  Overnight Celebrity is a fun song to sing along to.  More like, have your tongue commit suicide/have a seizure and your lips fall off.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's that time of the year again...  I'm never too excited about this.  Boo.  It's just another day like all of the rest.  But anyway the countdown is down to 13.  Am I going to have a party?  Most sources point to no.  I might have a little one though.  So basically for like 90% of you that means no anyway.  Those of you who read my blog anyway.  Or maybe more like 75% yes, depending on the people I invite.  I have no idea.  I don't even know who looks at this anymore.  I probably won't have one.  But maybe I'm just saying that so people I don't invite won't feel left out.  Maybe.  Hehe, Jacob still thinks that Sam is a senior.  That's so funny.  Yeah so that was fun.  This sucks.
     

        
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wooo....  The Heifer Project beckons.  Things left to do this vacation:  1. Animal Farm Project.  I haven't started drawing yet.  2. Chinese homework.  Haha... ha...  3. That's basically it.  I should work on those sometime.  4.  Oh yeah I almost forgot, buy a present sometime soon.  For the yeah.  Which is in like... two days...  wow.  What do people buy as presents, hmmm.... I'm bad at this.  5.  You know what's in 17 days?  I don't.  Well, I might.  17 days is bleh time.  Those are annoying.  6.  Usher looks really weird in the "Yeah" video.  He reminds me of Farnsworth Bentley.  Who, ironically, also is in that video.  7.  So much for this being a "things to do list."  Well off I go.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      These take a long time to load, at least on my computer.  Alex doesn't seem to be having much trouble with them.  W/e.  Anyway, I thought it would be pretty cool to do that.  Now you can like choose a song, or like combination of songs, or like *gasp* not listen to chinese music at all!  Wooohooo.  So anyway, yesterday was another fun-filled adventure.  Possibly not fun-filled in the way I would have preferred, but still it was OK. Uh huh.  Yeah.  Fun.  Soccer is a fun sport to play.  Less so when you only have three people though.  Tennis is OK'ly fun if like people know how to play, and none of us did.  Or at least I didn't know how, and les autres just weren't good.  Ohhh...  Sorry.  How 'bout that Bagdamin?  Ehh...   Yeah so I know you'd like to thank that your... [crap] don't stank, but lean a little bit closer, see that roses smell like poo poo poo.  Today was like funly stupid.  Without the fun part.  I did absolutely nothing.  Other than like eat stuff, watch stuff, read stuff, play stuff.  Drums don't sound as good when all you have left is a snare and 1 stick.  Especially when you can't play the drums in the first place.  My bike is flat.  Certain other things are too, but we won't go into that.  Like tables and stuff.  Oh yeah that reminds me.  Today I was obsessing over how clean my room is again, and so my sister comes in and I'm like "Don't mess up my room." So she looks at me for two seconds, and then she like runs to my dresser and like dumps all the clothes on the ground just to spite me.  That was pretty annoying.  But in retrospect it's actually pretty funny.  Yeah so yeah, did you hear how my salsa makes all the pretty girls want to dance and take off their underpants?
     

        
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      See now I'm just bored.  And somewhat annoyed.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I watched "Searching for Bobby Fischer"  today on OnDemand.  That's a good movie.  That little kid is good at chess.  Meanwhile... yeah.  I cleaned my room again yesterday.  And then I messed it again.  We got a new vacuum.  Exciting.  Cuz I blew up the old one.  I turned it on and the back blew off.  It was pretty shocking.  Like it broke off and flew across the room.  And then I said "oops".  So that was fun.  I smashed my CD player today.  Not fun.  [M] Ban ye shui bu zhao jiao  Ba xin qing hng cheng ge  Zhi hao dao wu ding zhao ling yi ge meng jing   [F]: Shui meng zhong bei chao xing  Wo hai shi bu que ding  Zen hui you dong ren xuan lu zai dui mian de wu ding   [F]: Wo qiao qiao guan shang men  Dai zhe xi wang shang qu  Yuan lai shi wo meng li chang chu xian de na ge ren   [M]: Na ge ren bu jiu shi wo meng li na mo hu de ren  Wo men you tong yang de mo qi.  [M]: Yong tian xian  [F]: Yong tian xian, pai cheng ai ni de xing zhuang  [M]: Yong tian xian, pai cheng ai ni de xing zhuang   [F]: Zai wu ding chang zhe ni de ge  [M]: Zai wu ding he wo ai de ren  [F]: Rang xing xing hen cui [T]: Cheng zui lang man de ye wen   [T]: Yong bao zhe shi ke,  Zhe yi fen, yi miao Quan dou ting zhi  [M]: Ai kai shi jiao jie   [F]: Zai wu ding chang zhe ni de ge  [M]: Zai wu ding he wo ai de ren  [F]: Jiang feng huang he yi sheng gei  [T]: Zui gu du de yue   [T]: Yong pao she shi ke,  Zhe yi fen yi miao,  Quan dou ting zhi  [M]: Ai kai shi jiao jie  [T]: Meng you ni er mei   [F]: Rang wo ai ni shi shei [M]: Shi wo [F]: Rang ni ai wo shi shei [M]: Shi ni [F]: Zen hui you [T]: Dong ren xuan lu huai rao zai wo lia de shen bian   [F]: Rang wo ai ni shi shei [M]: Shi wo  [F]: Rang ni ai wo shi shei  [M]: Shi ni  [F]: Yuan lai shi [T]: Zhe wu ding you mei li de xie hou  [M]: Zai wu ding chang zhe ni de ge  Zai wu ding he wo ai de ren 
     

        
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I sort of want to sing this song for next year.  The only problem would be that I would need to find a female counterpart.  Hmm.  W/e.  So much for that idea.
     

        
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Looking forward to:  1. Soundproof. Somehow I need to get my hands on the Logs' new album.  Songs I am anxious to hear them cover are: "The Scientist" -Coldplay, "Stacy's Mom" - Fountains of Wayne, and... those are basically the only ones.  "Time After Time" seems like it would be good.  Anything sung by the Logs is musical heaven.  Who knew engineer nerds could sing?  2.  April Vacation.  Sort of not really.  I hate vacations.  I'm going to spend this one doing history hw 24/7.  3.  Flourescence.  Ken Zhao is like Ken Zhao.  He's a pretty chill guy.  He's giving me this like 50 million page textbook so we can do a research project together during the summer.  4.  One year in one week.  That should be exciting.  We should do something or something.  I'm completely broke though.  How did this happen?  Didn't I have like 150 dollars in my wallet like 2 weeks ago?  My wallet is lonely with only like 15 dollars in it.  5.  NBA Playoffs.  Rockets v. Lakers in the first round.  After the Rockets get their derri??res kicked, I won't care anymore.  Phil Jackson is 13-0 in the first round of playoffs.  6. Heifer Project.  I'm not sure exactly what this is, but I'm going with my church so that should be good fun.  Friday April 23 - Sunday April 25.  It's so sad...  Sad actually meaning like unhappy and not like lame.  Anyway, I've spent my first real day of vacation at MIT and then talking to Stephanie Kaplan about being a math nerd so far.  Bleh.    In that conversation, we also concluded that in comparison to me, she and Alex Dietz are short and fat.  But who isn't.  At least the short part.  Listening to people sing is so soothingly refreshing.  Mb cuz I used to be a singer.  Only guys singing though for me.  Because girls sing too high for me to sing along to.  But that was back in the prepubescent days when everyone was a singer.  Prepubescence lasting until freshman year.  Yeah.  That was exciting.  I'm not sure if my voice changed or not.  I can't hit the notes I used to though.  High or low.  My range just all of the sudden spontaneously shrunk.  That was fun.  You like so can't survive being a 2-octave tenor.  And they aren't even the right 2-octaves.  Yeah so yeah.  Ok.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ni bu guai you shi hui zuo guai Dan ni bu huai zhi shi bu zhuang ke ai  Leng xia lai qi fen dou bei po huai Suan ni li hai re dai dou bian han dai  Ni jiu shi tian shi bie huai yi Huai pi qi zhi shi mei ren dong ni  Hao yun qi neng he ni yi qi Cuz I can't help falling in love with you  Everytime I look u straight into your eyes I can't explain this feeling it's blowing up my mind The touch of your hands and the touch of your lips Make the temperature so I know that this is it  Ni bu guai you shi hai hui shua lai Dan ni bu huai qi shi ni hen ke ai  Bei dai bai ni po huai tian cai Ju jue fan mai xu wei zuo zuo dui bai  Hao yun qi neng he ni yi qi Coz I can't help falling in love with you  I just can't stop it, I just can't help it Falling in love with you, no matter what I do You taking me to heaven with everything you do So I'm falling in love with you and baby that's the truth  Ni jiu shi tian shi bie huai yi Huai pi qi zhi shi mei ren dong ni  Hao yun qi neng he ni yi qi Coz I can't help falling in love with you  Jason and Yin are so god.  *good.  Or not.  Omg their voices.  I was like *melting*.  JK.  But they were very good.  
     

        
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    I got a new phone today. It is like coolio.   urlLink    Here's another picture of it, taken deftly with my webcam.  Cheapness to the max.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today in History Ms. Heidlage said, "Every newspaper article you read will have a bias on this."  about the Israeli-Palestinian conflict.  That led me to think of the following headline:   The Lord of the Rings grosses a record high $300 billion.  Palestine still evil."   That was pretty exciting and made Alex laugh for a bit.  That and "Is the bum old."  Because I had misheard Alex and thought he had said "bum" when he actually said "pope" and blah blah blah, ramble.  Oh yeah and then we were talking, but we had to be quiet, which is why I didn't hear his pope thingy right either, but I figured out that he was talking about Jessica Li and nice looking stuff, so then like... I don't know how to transition into blockquotes...  So here.   -Are you saying that you think Jessica Li is good looking? -She's a girl!  ---Me and Alex respectively   Interpret that how you want.  But it turned out that he was talking abuot her handwriting.  I've lost 5 pounds since going on my fat diet.  I haven't been this weightless since the summer.  It's annoying.  I mean you'd think you'd get fat from eating KFC everyday, but no...  It turns out that the KFC diet is more effective than the Subway diet.  Psh Jared with his 60 pounds in a year.  I just lost 10 pounds in 3 weeks(5 of which weren't on the KFC diet though). And I'm not even fat.  It leads me to believe that I have like a tapeworm or something, except not.  I think my meatbolism works in reverse.  I should starve myself and see what happens.  And hope I don't like implode.  So we played basketball after school.  We being Me, Calvin, Hoi, Steve, Craig, Lenny, and White kid, and Melody for half a game.  Playing with big black kids every week makes playing with medium-sized asian kids somewhat easier.  I still get schooled though.  Calvin beat me one-on-one 10-5.  It was pretty bad.  I wasn't trying...  But I can't play one-on-one anyway.  Well first I lost 7-5, and then he was like do you want to play to 10, and I was like ok, and then I didn't score, and I was like damn.  Then we decided to play three-on-three, which was funner, because I could beast on everyone.  I blocked white kid so many times.  I think we lost.  Most of the games.  Then I went to the club where I played my sister in ping pong. I beat her 21-12.  It was exciting.  I think she like gave up at the end though. Cuz she like wasn't even trying anymore.  It's depressing to beat someone when they don't even compete. Like the score was 15-10, which is still relatively close, but then I took my entire serve, and then she just blehed.  Yeah so ok.  I'm pissed at Sam (Richards) for not finishing our math project.  If I get a B this term it's his fault.  A B this term would mean like a B+ for the year.  Which would not be fun at all.  OK, so that was pretty annoying.  Even if it was from 3rd to 5th grade it's not like I was constantly like, "skdjfsjkhahskjghsdkljghsdgjkldg" all the time.  By that I meant like basically the way Alex feels about Jessica Li.  Or possibly the way Alex thinks I feel about Jessica Li except I don't.  Except not, because Alex probably thinks I like want Jessica Li to like have my children and such.  I say like a lot.  It's annoying.  I'm in fourth in fantasy baseball.  Take that Sam Richards, Sam Cohen, Schindler, Geoff Kellman, Ben Goldstein, Ben Rome, Zack Held, Andrew Habermehl.  And you better watch out Phil, Josh, and Ben Gurvis.  I'm only 5 points behind Gurvis, and we get like 40 points per night, and tonight I actually got about 70 cuz I am cool like that.  OK enough about fantasy baseball.  Hiro was posting about his freshman year in his journal today.  It was entertaining.  Oh yeah this was in Yin's profile:   Dan: Hey Yin. How's it going? Yin: Not feeling as good as I should be, but that's ok. Dan: What happened? Yin: Oh no, nothing happened. Just missing Yiyi. Dan: Yiyi...? Is that some Japanese catfish food? Yin: Girlfriend.   Yin caught himself a Harvard girl.  Exciting.  Oh man I need to do these commentaries.  Meg Burkly came to our History class today to inspect the portfolios, and it was pretty annoying.   Meg: They really aren't as long as they seem, it's just that they have like 10 90-page essays in them. Ms. Heidlage: What did Mr. Stark have you do for the essays? Meg: Well sometimes we had short essays, but then also sometimes he would just have us do like a timeline or something. Eric Messinger: Why would you ever tell us that...   We had to write 3 5-7 page papers, 2 4-page papers, and a 3-page paper for that portfolio.  It's come to the point when Ms. Heidlage calls a 3.5-page write-up a "short essay".  I didn't litter this post with random lines from random, usually Logarhymthical songs like I did the last post.  Probably cuz I wasn't listening to them while writing it.  I think I'm done.  Ma fan ni le.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    Man look what Jay is wearing...  If you can, read the words on his shirt.
     

        
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Yeah so today I hung out with Kevin and that bunch of Asian girls after school.  You know like, Vicky, Andrea, Lauren, and Angelique.  We went to Starbucks.  I got a tall Caramel Machiatto and a Lemon Crumb bar.  It cost $4.99.  Everyone else got frappacinos but you know what I always say, "Fraps are crap."  Actually I've never said that in my life.  But I did tell Andrea after she ordered her tall Java Chip Frappacino with whip that Java Chip Frappacinos look and taste like shizznaz.  She was somewhat offended.  Maybe I shouldn't have said that.  Idk they seemed to like it.  Vicky looks like a panda, if you know what I mean.  And you  dooooo (take me to hell and back that is, but you know that I would give you this once, twice, forever just as long as we're together)... I don't want your freedom, I don't want to play around, I don't want nobody baby, part-time love just brings me down, I don't want your freeeeeeeeedom.  I have to stop randomly breaking into song.  Yeah so then we went to Star Market and Andrea bought Rice Krispies and Marshmallows probably so that she could make Rice Krispie treats.  I didn't expect Vicky's voice to sound the way it does, today was the first time I've heard her speak.  She has a big voice for a little girl.  Sry.  After that I made my way to the club, where I played basketball with a bunch of big black kids like I do every Tuesday.  I don't like being on Darius's team.  He's the only one I can D-up.  Even though he also blocks every single shot I take like into the bleachers, assuming there are bleachers, which there usually isn't.  I was just kidding, I didn't like obsess over her.  Too much.  You like disappeared today when I was talking to Sam about the French.  You see while I have a way of mysteriously showing up, you have a way of mysteriously leaving.  Because everywhere I go, you know, I'd take you with me sweet darling.  And, baby, I, always tried looking at life through open eyes, and, baby, my dream came true with this treasure I found inside of you.   Sorry.  I had to correct my english teacher today.  That doesn't happen very often at all.  Some stupid thing about sentence structure and the nomenclature thereof.  The whole class including the teacher was so convinced it was one way, but relative clauses are subordinate clauses too... I mean, yeah.  I have like 150 pages to read.  But it's alright, it's alright, it's all right, she moves in mysterious ways.   Speaking of which, a line from that song is "If you wanna kiss the sky, better learn how to kneel."  And I don't mean to be vulgar or anything but...  "I can make you W and N if you want..."  That reminds me, quote from History a couple days ago:   "Lots of things went on there at various times." "[As if beginning a list of things] Massacres..." ---Ms. Heidlage and Eric Messinger respectively on Tiananmen Square.   If you would just stay with me I'd write you dirty love songs.  Talking to Brett about Gym has to be the highlight of my day every time we have Homeroom. [insert random line from a song that doesn't have anything to do with what I was talking about except for possibly a bridge until you realize that the end of the paragraph and the beginning of the song are talking about similar but pretty different things.]  What song did I put on this thing?  I remember I was going to put Istanbul because Jay sings outrageously high in that song, but I think I put that Ban Dao Tie He song.  Jessica Li is not Taiwanese.  My respect for her has grown without bounds.  I'm not pseudo-country-ist, what are you talking about?  First I thought she was from Hong Kong, but I realized that that couldn't be right because she's "Li L-i."  That doesn't work as well in writing.  But I meant as opposed to Cantonese Lee.  So I guess I assumed because of her, uh, lack of intellect, that she was Taiwanese.  Also she knows who Jay Chou is.    Yeah so yeah.  That's all.
     

        
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This weekend was pretty awesomely awesome.  Friday afternoon was the volleyball game against Millis.  It was pretty exciting.  Hooorah.  Club people went to that game, but it was just the Fannings (Ryan and Mouse) and a bunch of whores.  Libero tracking was... fun.  Stuff about stuff you, yeah, sry, idk, I stumble over words.  Watching Matt Murphy go after things was exciting too.  Saturday night PJ, Bradley, and Kevin came over.  We were going to watch Troy but it turned out that PJ and Bradley had just come from watching Troy, so we decided to watch Shrek 2.  So we got to the theatre at 8:10, hoping to watch the 9:00 show, but tickets were all sold out, so we were like shit.  So then we bought tickets for the 9:30 show, before they all sold out too at 8:30.  In the hour we had before the show started, PJ, Bradley, Kevin, and I, went to the Natick Mall (the movie was in Framingham).  But we got to the mall at like 8:40 and had to leave in like 15 minutes.   So we went through Spencer's Gifts and Kevin and I played one game of DDR (we failed, but it was on heavy so w/e, and the pads were shit) and then we left.  We got back to the theatre at 9:10 and went in, and it was completely packed.  There should not have been that many people watching a 9:30 show of Shrek 2 seriously.  But the movie was really funny.  Being with PJ and Bradley brought back a lot of memories.  I need to hang out with them more.  That Jason Cohen story was so funny.  I hate that kid so much.  Bobby Broderick stories too.  Club girls are whores.  Krenare is in like 7th grade.  Stupid whore.  Idk if Drilon knows either.  He would kill her if he knew.  Her father would kill both of them if he found out...  K... what are you doing?  You bring shame to your family.  Presents:  CD from Kevin, $20 from PJ, $15 from Bradley(cheap).  They were supposed to have slept over, but we decided not to, since it was like 12:30 already when we got home, and we were all really tired, and Bradley had to fly the next day, PJ had to go to his trailer, and Kevin had stuff to do too.  Maybe I shouldn't be talking about my birthday party when people I didn't invite are going to read this and be like what.  W/e.  Now people like people are going to comment and be like annoying and ish.  Oh yeah and don't think I'm kidding when I tell you not to talk about my sister.  Sunday:  I watched Troy today, 8:05 show at the Embassy.  It was a good movie.  It's cold and I'm tired. The Embassy is like right down the street from my house.  It was like completely empty when we watched.  We had a fire drill in Chinese School today.  Fire Drills in Chinese School mean that some stupid kid pulled the alarm.  Stupid chinese boy.  Brad Pitt hasn't looked so good since Fight Club, in a completely straight way...  I haven't weighed myself in a while.  I think I'm developing a gut which disconcerts me.  Idk, I don't mind the skinny, weak, inch-away-from-death look, but if it's what you want...  I need to stop referring to people in the second person in my posts.  but I know those are the only people who are going to read this so whatever.  Yin's little brother is funny, I'll give you that.  "Let's go Yellow J..."  I was talking to Meng about you in Chinese School today.  She's moving.  It's so sad.  No more Meng on 40 Fordham Road...  She's moving to Oak Hill.  I don't remember how I know Meng's address but I do.  I remember a lot of people's addresses/phone numbers from elementary school.  Let's see... who are 964-1140 and 332-8818, I know, but should I?  Probably not.  I used to stalk people apparently.  Actually no, it's because I had that watch, and all the girls thought it was so cool, and they decided to enter their phone numbers into it.  Player from day 1.  But it's not like I ever called those phone numbers other than for homework.  I called Meng more for homework in 4th and 5th grade than I called PJ I think.  And I  hated  Meng back then.  Like omg, so badly I hated her.  But I guess you can't call it hate.  You don't hate those whom you were indifferent towards.  I'm getting too tired to do this.  Blog I mean.  I start to say things I don't mean and shouldn't say.  Yeah so do stuff and have fun doing it.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's pretty late, but I don't feel like sleeping.  I'll give the MCAS a handicap.  It just isn't fair with me at full strength.  The club is going on a field trip tomorrow (today technically).  To North.  To watch the Vball game.  Ugh.  The was this poster and it was like this clip art picture of a goofy looking cartoony guy and the caption said "This is Mike Lichten, go cheer for him at Newton North on May 21 when they play State Champions Millis High!  See Louie for a permission slip."  I wonder how many people from the club are going to go.  I guess I'm going.  I've never seen Varsity lose, or go to a third game for that matter.  Let's see if that streak holds.  Alex thinks I'm sexist.  I probably am.  Jiazhen was being pretty passive aggressive when Youqing died.  It was a sad part of the film, but I wanted to start laughing so badly.  She was like "Youqing, it's all my fault, I should have stopped your dad from sending you to school.  I should have tried harder to make your dad let you stay home.  I should have done anything to keep your dad from doing that.  Oh man, I screwed up so badly.  I can't believe I didn't make your dad not send you to school."  And then I expected Fugui to come in and be like, "ALRIGHT, I GET IT" I wanted to start laughing so badly because that was all I was thinking about.  And then Jiazhen goes psycho on Chunsheng.  All he did was kill her son... And it was more her fault anyway.  I mean, those dumplings are deadly.  I like "To Live."  It's a good movie.  Especially because I actually can survive without reading subtitles.  And today when Ms. Heidlage was saying how we can't look away for long, and she was like "except maybe you and you," she pointed to Eric Messinger and Jessica Li, and I'm like "Hello... I'm the one who speaks Mandarin, Jessica Li is a Taiwanese counter-revolutionary."  Well, she is.  She might as well be Jiang Jieshi.  Reincarnated.  In like full bloody form, with the like deadness transformed into somewhat good looks.  Uh, I didn't say that.  Anyway...we're so mean to that girl...It's so terrible.  I wonder what happens in the 60s.  That's like when my parents were little kids.  I'll look for them.    Oh yeah Ms. Heidlage was talking about the democratic movement in Tiananmen Square, and I told Alex that I was there and he didn't believe me, so I was like "I have a t-shirt!"  But I really do have a t-shirt from there.  It says "Democratic Movement, Tiananmen Square, December 1989" on it, not necessarily in that order.  I should find it and wear it one day.  Just to prove you all wrong.
     

        
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I ehhed on that paper.  10 like X, and 50 like L.  Yeah.  Fun.   Wow I didn't know Loren was magical.  ---Alex, when he saw me "hovering in the air"    Oh, 'n I missed such a gravy opportunity today when I wuz asking Melody how her weekend had been 'n brizzle wuz like, "annoying" "that shiznit's hot," 'n I should has been like, "yeah, I has that problem izzall da time n' shit.  ---After www.asksnoop.com'ing Alex's Blog 
     

        
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Yeah so, currently I have one comment from someone who isn't me.  And that's only because we're    If you browse by my [blog], leave a comment. I know at least [idk] other people who keep tabs on my [blog] to find out about my incredibly amazing life, yet don't do anything. LEAVE ONE SO I CAN FEEL E-SPECIAL OR ELSE I WILL COMmiTTtTt suICIDe. :-(   ---Kenny, on his xanga, slightly modified to fit my purposes.   Yeah so leave one so I can feel e-special or else I will committttttt suicide, except that I won't, cuz that is stupid, and suicide is for loser wimps who can't deal with things normally.
     

        
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      OK so firstly... A-block... English.  Funny discussion, if you disregard how tubborn everybody in our class is.  So if you haven't read Jane Eyre, which is like everybody who reads this with the possible exception of Julia, assuming she still reads my blog, during Jane's wedding with Mr. Rochester, it is reveiled that he is already married to some crazy beach who tries to kill them all and everything.  So stuff that was said:   -She's not a murderer... -I think when you light someone's bed on fire, that counts as trying to kill them... -Yeah, and she stabbed that guy in the heart. -OK, she's a bit violent...      ---Ms. Zolli, Erin Hannah, Dani K., and Ms. Zolli again, on Mr. Rochester's "wife"     WHY DOESN'T HE JUST KILL HER?   ---Jamie Axelrod, on how to solve Mr. Rochester's problem    B-Block: Engineering.  We spray-painted our oven today.  On the bottom of the box, we wrote "ZIM SUCKS"  That was pretty thrilling.  But then when we brought it back inside, Rose didn't let us bring it back into the room because it smelled so bad.  So we had to leave it outside.  Yeah so yeah. Hopefully it didn't get smashed.  C-Block: Chem.  *sleepytime*  E-Block: History.  Test wasn't bad, except that I had no idea what the NSC-68 was.  G-Block: Math.  Test wasn't bad, but like only two people, me included, in our class finished.  It wasn't even hard.  I shouldn't talk because I currently have an 86 in math.  Stupid hw quizzes.  F-Block: French. We had another great discussion about L'tranger.  I can't understand how you possibly find them boring.  Like talking about character traits and plot happenings is so interesting, like getting people's viewpoints and such.  Especially when you have Kohse in your class.  That "you" was directed at me, sry.  Ian was saying how our English class would be so much more interesting if Kohse was in our class, as a male chauvanist to go against all the annoying feminist people in our class.  After School: I like ran to the library to get my SAT scores.  I did alright, math could have been better, but I can't complain.  Next was the volleyball game.  It was about as exciting as a volleyball game could get, the varsity game at least.  During the JV game I totally got hit in the face.  That was not funny.  Like it was one of those ones that go really high and it was going to land right in front of me, but the kid tried to hit it even though he obviously couldn't reach it, and he hit it right into my face.  And then I was like "Ow, my nose hurts."  Varsity won, JV lost.  Yeah so today in general was pretty fun.  It made me "wanna run through the halls of my high school."  Except not really.
     

        
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Let's see...  Today was Nichole's Birthday.  Happy Birthday to her.  Nichole has the same brithday as my grandmother.  She had a cake.  Conversation:  Nichole: "Loren, why aren't you eating the cake?" Loren: "Idk, I don't really like cake." Nichole: "Come on, there aren't any laxatives in it..."  Speaking of which, I completely suck.  Oh yeah that reminds me.  Over the last like 3 weeks I've lost 8 pounds.  And this is while eating 2 lunches and 2 dinners.  I'm serious.  Everyday now I eat lunch at school, then I eat lunch at KFC, then I get a sub from Pete's, and then I eat dinner at home.  Why am I not like 5000 pounds.... I mean like what the hell.  That also explain where all of my money went to.  Other than like the street.  Ugh.  [edit] Homer (in a car): "THIS IS NED FLANDERS, MY FRIEND!" Lenny: "What did he say?" Carl: "I don't know, something about being gay."  I need to stop saying "fuck you, fuckhole."  But that implies that I started saying it.  Which I haven't.  Is that really Steve singing?  Wow.  I so don't hear that voice coming out of him.  George is going to prom with some Western Mass. chick whom nobody knows.  Good for him.  Lately things have been bleh. "I wanna scream at the top of my lungs."  John Mayer has a high voice sometimes.  Like when he says that.  Me screaming at the top of my lungs is like "umm... ahh... yeah..."  "um... could you... uh... i need..." "OH, DO YOU WANT ME TO GET OUT OF THE WAY?"  Hehehe.  How many people will understand that quote?  Alex, and possibly Jonkathonk.  Everyone will be just like ok.  I don't remember saying that I wanted to launch myself.  What a weird thing to say. Almost as weird as "I'll smack  your  balls."  Haha.  Sorry.  Chem test wasn't bad.  I better have gotten at least a 55.  If not I'm going to be pissed.  But when I get pissed it's mainly because I am tired and don't want to put up with things anymore and that usually goes away within like an hour or so.  But when you're like really tired and cranky and have a headache and are hungry even though you already ate dinner twice and simultaneously you also want to throw up but you don't because then you're bulimic, you begin to stop putting up with the crap you would take in more normal situtations.  Sorry if I was being annoying/piss-off-ish during those few hours of self-control-less-ness.  [super edit:]  So now I've switched from JCSS to PotO.  OMG listen to the title song and tell me that girl, usually Sarah Brightman I think, doesn't have at least 5-octave voice.  Antonio Banderas is a pretty sizzling singer.   Sing my angel of music   That accent is meltifying.
     

        
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Everything I am and everything in me Wants to be the one you wanted me to be. I'll never let you down even if I could. I'd give up everything if only for your good.  I posted bunch of crap on my X.  You can go see what I've been up to lately over there.  The link is on the sidebar.
     

        
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Blogger Reloaded is so much cooler than new blogger. It's like so streamlined and everything.  And like yeah.  It's like whoa.  Coool...
     

        
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Holy wow, what happened to Blogger?  Anyway, if you disregard all the shit stuff that happened, I'd have to say that this was an awesome birthday.  Oh yeah that reminds me.  After dinner yesterday, my mom got out a cake, and then this conversation took place:  Dad: "Why are we having cake?" Mom: "Because it's his birthday..." Dad: "Oh... Really?"  Wow thanks.  W/e.  My father is a funny guy.  Today in English they were saying how Phineas can't be Gene's best friend because they are so competitive.  Yeah.   I'm not competitive at all with my friends...   Yeah so yeah.  The club was pretty fun today.  For once.  Teen Open Gym, I got to play basketball with a bunch of big black kids.  That was pretty fun.  Especially cuz I suck.  I kept blocking Darius though.  He was like "Jeez, Loren, how come you only play defense on me?"  I couldn't buy a basket though.  Like I missed every single lay-up I took.  Then I played my sister in ping-pong.  She's getting really good.  She beat me one game.  I was playing left-handed though.  And I let her win.  Psh.  I'm even competitive with my 9-year-old little sister in ping-pong...  Wow.  But she is getting good.  I need to teach her to use the spin and then she'll be better.  And she needs to learn to aim a bit better.  Anywho...This new blogger thingy is amazing.  It's so streamlined and such.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Dum dee dum... Sophomore Sleepover was fun I guess.  It's fun to be awake 47/53 hours and then be asleep the next 12/13 hours. Yeah...  The best part was getting Kevin to be my manservant.  "You can be the Farnsworth Bentley to my P-Diddy!"  I was so tired...  I got Kevin to go across the cafeteria to get me a drink and pizza though because I couldn't move.  Dum dee dum, why couldn't I moove?  Stuff left to do:  1. Chinese hw:  haha...ha... Good one. 2. French Paper: Boooo. 3. History Paper: Not coool. 4. History Country Project:  Ewwww. 5. Find my calculator: Without which it is really annoying to do chem/math hw.  So I don't. 6. Big end of year Comp project: I'm not allowed to work with Matt on this one.  Uh oh. 7. Other random assignments: They're not difficult, just a pain. 8. Get some: Not happening. 9. Have a happy birthday: Let's see.  Which reminds me, that anthology of Blog quotations was amazingly funny.  
     

        
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I made my first successful ATRAC3PLUS CD today.  It's not like nearly full.  It is every single chinese song I have I have though.  Which is like 43.  About 35 of those are Jay Chou though.  And then 3 of the others Jay Chou either wrote or has a minor part in (SARS Song).  Basically everything except the 4 David Tao songs and the 1 Wang Lee Hom song is somehow related to Jay Chou.  I separated them into albums:  1. JAY Album (8 Songs) 2. Fantasy Album (8 Songs) 3. 8 Dimensions (8 Songs) 4. Ye Hui Mei (11 Songs) 5.  Other Random Chinese Stuff (8 songs)  I'm very tempted to put a complete track list, but I won't make you suffer that much.  Mme Putzeys is scary.  My mom thinks I'm anorexic.  She was like "30 dollars?!"  And then I said, "You could just not give me dinner and make me eat 30 dollars."  And then she said, "Yeah right, I bet you go there and say you'd already eaten and just not eat anything."  I probably would do that.  Peer pressure though, you never know.
     

        
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      SATs today.  They were pretty fun.  Let's see if I'm still saying that in 3 weeks...  I got a new CD player today.  Or rather I used the 2-year replacement plan on my old one to... replace it.  They make you buy a new replacement plan when you replace it.  So I was like "ok..."  I don't see what the store gets out of this.  I can just like break my CD player every 2 years and get a new one for 10 dollars. W/e I'm not complaining.  This is actually an "MP3/ATRAC3PLUS/CD Player.  Fun stuff.  Yeah so yeah.
     

        
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Shanghai is pretty cool so far.  I demonstrated my immense logic skills before and during the plane ride there.  OK so since my plane was leaving at 7:30 in the morning and I would have had to get before 5 anyway, I seriously contemplated not sleeping that night, but then I did for maybe like 2 hours which just made me groggy.  Then I couldn't really sleep on the plane so I just watched the movies/in-flight entertainment, thinking that I would just sleep when I get to China.  But then I realized with about like an hour left in the flight that the plane was landing at about 3 o'clock in the afternoon and it would be like at least 6 hours until sleepytime.  By that time my eyes hurt because I hadn't been sleeping, and I couldn't sleep because my eyes hurt.  It was a vicious cycle.  Except that that didn't really happen.  On the plane I watched four movies.  I forget what the first one was because I didn't really watch it, but the other three were "Welcome to Mooseport", "Star Runner", and "Big Fish".  "Big Fish" was ok.  "Star Runner" was really good though.  I never thought I would like an action movie this much.  Especially a chinese action movie which is about kickboxing and whose main character is named "Bond" and is played by Vanness Wu.  But anyway, Bond is a kickboxer who's entering the "Star Runner" competition, which is a fighting competition where the fighters can use any style they want.  He realizes after being kicked out of his kickboxing school after mouthing off then losing to a guy named Chris that he needs to work hard if he is going to stand a chance against a Thai guy from New Zealand named Tank.  Bond decides to learn Kung Fu to help beat Tank.  It gets exciting after that.  A side plot is woven in that involves Bond's Korean teacher who is this guy named Simon's mistress.  She and Bond fall in love, but she goes back to Korea with Simon when he divorces his wife.  Bond also has a grandfather who is dying.  Go  urlLink Here   In China I have been watching the equivalents of MTV and ESPN on TV.  The Sports channel is like only covering the European Championship and Wimbledon.  The music channel is like completely taken over by Jay Chou it's amazing.  I was watching the top ten countdown thingy and 3 of them were sung by Jay and 4 others were written by him.  I went to the store to try to find the Star Runner DVD but I couldn't.  I was in there for possibly half an hour and I heard them play 5 Jay songs.  "Ye Ye Pao de Cha", "Fan Fang Xiang de Zhong", "Wan Mei Zhu Yi", "Hui Dao Guo Qu", and "Yi Di An de Lao Bao Jiu".  While I was in the store I realized something.  Shanghai girls that look like they might be my age are actually like 30.  Also chinese guys are really short.  Except for the mutant ones that are humongous.  There isn't any middle ground.  For fun I went on this scale in the store that told you how tall you were, how much you weighed and your build.  I'm 176.5 cm tall, and weigh 50 kg and am underweight by 21 kg. Jeez that like me and a half.  But that's to be expected.  I was also wearing shoes.  Chinese scales always have that build thingy, even home ones.  At my grandparents' house I was weighing myself, and there are levels for the build that are basically like "Super Skinny", "Very Skinny", "Skinny", "Normal", "Fat", Very Fat", "Super Fat" with an arrow that you set to your height.  When I went on, the arrow didn't even go into "Super Skinny" I found that kind of funny.  It's raining.  Dvds here cost less than 20 RMB.  That's about 2 dollars. If I go through customs with like 20 DVDs, do I need to declare them, since I only would hypothetically have paid like 40 dollars total for them.  Hmm...  They also put their adult section right next their kid's section.  If you know what I mean by adult section.  Food is good.  Going to get fat here.  Grammar worsening.  That's too bad.  k thx.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm still dreading that 7:30 flight...  [edit] Yes I am adding onto an already obesely long email.  So we had dinner with my aunts today.  I hadn't seen them in 2 years.  It's ridiculous.  Not that I haven't seen them in 2 years... that they're my aunts...  I think they're like 24, 25, and 28 but other than the oldest one, whom I've seen more often because she goes to MIT, they don't look older than like 17 or 18.  I was like holey moley those are my aunts. Ahhhh....  And they are good looking too.  So I have aunts in their mid-20s who look like extremely hot asian teenagers.  Whoopie go me.  Except not because I'm pretty sure that would be considered incest.  So stuff that's happened recently:  Paradorn Srichaphan gets upset in the the first round at Wimbledon to Ivo Karlovic, the giant killer.  Ahh...  Karlovic upset Lleyton Hewitt last year in the first round.  He's so annoying.  Paradorn Srichaphan is my second favorite tennis player after Mark Philippoussis.  Of course, all I ever watch of tennis is the grass court season.  Martina Navratilova comes out of retirement at the age of 47.5 to defeat Catalina Castano 6-0, 6-1.  Wow.  Lakers are reportedly going to offer Rudy Tomjanovich the head coaching job that's open now that Phil Jackson is out.  Rudy T. took the Rockets to the champsionship in '91 and '92.  Tracy McGrady is on the trading block and currently it seems like the Rockets are the highest bidder.  Repots say that the Rockets would send Steve Francis, Cuttino Mobley, and Kelvin Cato for the reigning scoring champion.  Steve Francis is the fourth player in NBA history to average over 15 points, 5 assists, and 5 rebounds in each of his first 6 NBA seasons.  Other places for T-Mac to go include Dallas, where he wishes to reunite with "big brother" Shaq, who is his part-time neighbor in southern Orlando.  Dum dee dum...  Lebron is the rookie of the year and Carmelo made the playoffs, but who's an NBA champion? DARKO!  Hmm... what else...  Look for China to medal in the 2008 Olympics (to be held in Beijing) when 14-year-old Chen Jianghua matures into a world-class point guard, Yi Jianlian becomes a Chinese version of KG (7'1" with a 30" standing vertical, *gasp*, and he's only 16...) and Yao... is just Yao...  OK enough about sports.  Or actually one more thing.  The Devil Rays have won 11 straight.  The Devil Rays...  They haven't lost since the Lightning won the Stanley Cup.  Wow.  OK so enough about sports for real this time.  School is over that's pretty cool.  My grades were bleh but that's alright.  My TV's keep randomly turning themselves on.  This is getting scary.  And I'm not even in the same room as them.  So I'll be in Shanghai in a couple days.  Seeing that I'm going to spend almost the equivalent of one day on the plane, ugh...  Three reasons I should be able to pick up some girl in Shanghai:  1. C'mon, have you looked at me lately? JK. 2. 50 dollars American should be enough in China...  That's like... 420 RMB... 3. I'm American.  That should speak for itself in Shanghai.  Three Reasons I will have trouble picking up some girl in Shanghai:  1. Chinese girls will think I am retarded because     a. I will sound stupid because I can't speak chinese.     b. I will sound stupid because I can't do multi-variable calculus in my head. 2. Chinese girls sit at home and do homework all day.  Yes, even during the summer. 3. I probably won't get out very much, unless I buy myself a bicycle.  Which might cost me about like 20 RMB, or like 2 dollars and 50 cents.  My aunts arrive today from the Philippines.  Oohwee.  Shut up that is disgusting.  They're my aunts.  Yeah ok.  I can't understand how my whole family got to be so good looking...  We need to like share the wealth with the rest of the world...  Hehe, JK.  I find it funny how some of my cousins are older than some of my aunts and uncles.  I think I remember that film, and as I recall, I think, we both kind of liked it.  Well, that's the one thing we've got...  Those might be the worst lyrics ever, except then Mr. Durst had to come out with his new version of the hokey pokey...  With some high school math mixed in.  1, 2, 3 times 2 to the sixth, jolts in for your fix with the Limp Bizkit Mix.  Yes, I agree.  I am somewhat ashamed to say that one of the highest grades that I got during exam week was on Alex's Friend test.  Josh finds it funny that the only people that I talk to are Asian.  He made this remark before we went to French today, when Britney, Billy, Jing, Theeda, and Derek all said hi to me coming out of their class (E-block people).  I made two copies of "Holy Wow." just because I liked it so much.  It turned out surprisingly well.  At least I think so.  You might not with your like weird taste in music.  If I were to rank my final exam grades, it would go:  1. Math 2. English 3. French 4. History 5. Chemistry  And then final grades...  1. Math 2. Chemistry 3. French 4. History 5. English  So it's not as screwed up as I originally thought.  Blah that was a waste of time then.  But there was on point in the day where the grades I got back were:  1. English 2. History 3. Chemistry  That was surprising.  Especially since I sucked so badly in English this year.  And didn't even read the book that our final was on.  I expected to get a higher appearance grade on my country portfolio.  Like that it would be the grade that pulled me up.  But it actually brought me down and it was annoying.  Whatever.  I did better than Matt Woolf, I'm happy.  This is a long post.  The best day of my life is all thanks to you.  Few scenes from my life or moments mean more to me. Than our fine night. I remember like yesterday the time of my life.  Most of it consists of random lyrics that I've been picking out of "Holy Wow."  So if I were to pick any point to finish it would be this one.  OK.  Finished.
     

        
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Sega Genesis is the best system ever created.  I was in the car with my father going somewhere and my mom was following us in her car because we were going to get guests and all, and my dad kept taking crazy turns and stuff, and it was like:  Me: "What are you doing?!" Dad: "I like to tease your mom." Me: "Why?" Dad: "Because she is soo cute..." Me: [throws up]  That was pretty distressing.  Super Sonic is so scary.  He like goes so fast and jumps so ridiculously high and you can't even control him.  I learned today that my flight to Shanghai departs at 7:30 AM.  That's soo early...  I might as well like not go to sleep...  Like ahhh...  Yeah so yeah.  I'm almost done packing.  Only 3 more days until I say goodbye to Jewface.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       First Term:   A- Math B- Engineering C- AP US D- French E1- Personal Fitness E2- Robotics F- English G- AP Bio   Second Term   A- Math B1- Lifetime Activities B2- Free C- AP US D- French E1- Advanced Robotics E2- Free F- English G- AP Bio  So that's exciting.  [edit] My Blog was jealous of my xanga so there.  Oh yeah and here is a random quote that my father said after I gave my valedictory speech at chinese school and decided that it was too hot to keep my button-down shirt tucked in.   "Loren! You look like the president of the Philippines! 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So I slept over Jason's house yesterday, which you probably figured out from my title or rather, most likely already knew.  We watched "Saved!" and a bunch of annoying girls were there.  It was pretty awkward.  When we were buying tickets, Maggi Lloyd and Katie Kondub were in front of us in line and when we heard that they were seeing "Saved!" Jason was like "shit" and then I started laughing uncontrollably for some reason.  Katie Potere found it amusing that Jason and I would watch that movie without there being some girls involved.  Or at least that's what I gathered from her unenthusiatic "ha..."  The movie itself wsn't too bad.  During this kissing scene, we could hear the group of girls behind us going "Aww..." and then Jason yelled "SO CUTE!!!" and then we all started laughing.  So when the movie finished, Jason went to the bathroom, so I ws like all alone.  And so as I walked past the group of girls, I heard Michaela Yule say something to Danielle Jakob and so I think I glanced at her for a second out of surprise that she would say that, and she said "Hi" except that it wasn't as much of a "It's nice to see you" hi as a "Why are you staring at me?" hi.  So I said "Hi" back, except my voice cracked.  And then a bit later Danielle Jakob asked me which movie I saw, and I was like "Uh... 'Saved!'..."  And then she was like "OMG! US TOO! Did you like it?!" and then I was like "khsdfuhwe" and said something inaudibly.  And then Ruru came out with some guy and she said "HI" to me.  And I was like, "I don't even talk to you..."  except I didn't actually say that.  And then to save the day, Jason came out of the bathroom.  And then Charlotte Brill was like, "JASON SULLIVAN!" and he was like "CHARLOTTE BRILL!" and everything was better.  After we left the theatre, we were somewhat hungry I guess so we went to get pizza.  But when we got to Papa Gino's, they ere just closing, so they were like "OK, we have 4 slices left, is that OK?" and then we said that it was fine.  But then the guy said that he was already giving one slice to another guy so he was only giving us three but that it ws on the house, so we were like "Alright."  And then we got into Jason's car and opened the box and there were only 2 slices inside and it was depressing.  Jason and I watched "Rashomon" at his house.  It was a pretty good movie.  And then we discussed how it would be Ms. heidlage's worst nightmare.  We fell asleep pretty early, but that's ok.  It was fun.  I left jason house at about 1.  And then I went home.  And did nothing for the rest of the day.
     

        
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm done with finals.  I'm estatic.  Except not really.  Today was pretty fun.  I got to school at about 7:40 for no reason at all.  Then I wandered around for like half an hour realizing that there were only freshman there.  Then I found Bao and stayed with him for a while.  At like 8:30, I got bored of Bao and just randomly up and left him and started wandering around the school again.  After like 2 minutes I found Melody and we were like   So then after that we had our history final.  For my essay I wrote about five pages, but I think that's because my handwriting is bigger than everyone else's because I really didn't say anything remotely significant.  After the final, a group of us went to Cabot's.  Group of us being like, Melody, Sam, Melanie, Julia, and Jessica Cobb.  And me.  So then we ate there and were like ok.  After that I went to Sam's house.  it was so incredibly hot.  I couldn't believe it, it was so incredible.  At Sam's house we played Madden for like an hour maybe, and then we went outside to play basketball.  By accident I managed to like throw the ball off Sam's face when he was standing right in front of me.  That looked painful.  I don't even know what I was trying to do.  Except that I knew it went wrong when I heard the ball like smash into his face.  Yeah sorry about that.  It was soo hot today...  You're so hot always   Just kidding.  Sam, I know I'm irresistible, but you going to have to control your emotions.  "These things should be kept behind closed doors."
     

        
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I told you this would happen.  An hour of fantasy baseball was fun.  I really have nothing to say.  I can't find my memorandum assignment.  I was looking for it, and I found like so many grades that I didn't see before.  Apparently I got a 50/55 on my WWII/Cold War Quest. The only points I got off like on the whole thing was the NSC-68 thing which I had like no idea what what what.  Alex doesn't understand stuff about stuff.  It's heehee-ifying.  Heehee...  Yeah no.  Analyze.  Conundrum.  Tout  fait confusant.  Barter.  The Link.  Mike P. Michaelson.   "You want some chocolate?" ---KFC Associate    "All of the carbs, none of the taste! =D" ---Bad Diet Coke Commercial   "Oh-ma-ho" 
     

        
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      In a drastic effort to waste time, I stupidly started listening to the Super Mario Theme Song on my computer, knowing that whenever I listen to it I never get any work done at all...  Ahhh... And now I can't stop...  But I realized that if I only listen with my left ear, I only hear the left hand playing part for the piano.  It's amusing.  Your barbecue stole four hours from my life when I could have been doing my history project.  So if I finish at 3, which I won't at this rate, it's like I could have finished at 11...  And like actually slept.  At all.  But whatever it was fun.  I figured out that the "S" stands for "Sinic" by the way.  You know like Chinese.  Sino- stuff.  Yeah so that was exciting.  What a bad name for a group.  "The Sinic Eight."  It's so random.  And it doesn't even like alliterate, even though it is like an obviously knock-off of the dirty dozen.  But there aren't even a dozen people in D12...  Ahhh...  See how much I waste time... It's like 1 and I haven't even finished commentaries...  It's terrible.  I need like focus pills... or like Speed...  Yeah that would be nice...  I also need to like unplug my internet completely so I don't keep getting distracted...  Tonight I had the worst urge to... do that stuff that I don't do that you think I do do but like I obviously don't because you'd be able to tell if I did.  How's that for circumlocution...You know what I'm talking about though.  Or you should.  But it remains to be seen whether other people will or not.  What other people... Nobody reads my blog except for you and Alex... and possibly Jason from time to time.   Yeah so it was pretty bad.  I got over it by drinking two cans of pepsi and eating an entire fried dace.  If you can't go cold turkey, go fried dace...  Canned fish tastes disgusting.  And yet I eat it without any moderation.  One-third of what I just ate has 35% of my daily value of fat.  That's horrible.  It's also 260 calories.  My hair is coming out.  Maybe I should stop pulling it.  So then Rhonda said to Damian, "Did you hear what happened to Emmaneul?"  Damn, why can't I just like do this... AHHHH....  Cry.  I'm going to fail history.  Oh yeah I think I'm going to get an N in Engineering, idk how that happened.  Like when did I ever miss class...   Your dad attacked me.  It was scary.  I was like totally freaked out by him.  Oh yeah and then your mom walked into the room while we were (more like I was) doing sketchy stuff, and that was pretty weird.  And she was like "whoaa...."  "Cal, you're gonna get tapped like your sister does every night.  By me."  I am such a bad trash talker.  And whenever I trash talk Calvin, I always have to like involve you.  I'm sorry.  The marshmallow incident was pretty funny.  Jason like staring and being like "DO IT! DO IT!"  Oh yeah and after I made that horrible remark that made everyone start laughing/clapping, I wanted to say, "I think of you..." but it didn't seem appropriate.  That whole party was in appropriate.  I'm sorry but your baby cousins are like the ugliest creatures I ahve even seen in my whole life.  Just kidding.  I'm sure like Gila Monsters are worse.  I spent like 20 minutes writing this.  It's so long.  That's what your sister said last night Calvin...  I'm SORRY...  How about we just kiss and make up...Just kidding... OK jeez, calm yourself.  I was just joking...  Chun Lau scares me.  I am perpetually scared that he is going to eat me.  Did you see how he was staring at me... I actually think he was staring at you because you were behind me and I think you were like bending down or something, and so I punched Chun Lau.  In my mind.  We freak people out.  Namely like... everybody.  You need to like cool down your sexual urges... I mean I know you want me so bad, but that kind of thing needs to like stay restricted to like restricted places.  Where there aren't like 8 perverted guys watching...  Or Berlinda.  Who might count as a perverted guy.  But I don't know her that well so I wouldn't know.  It was funny when that lady came and she looked at me and she was like "Lei ge pung yao?" and you were like "NO!"  And I was like uh... ok.  w/e.  I probably would have done the same if I was in your position.  Except probably not.  I would have shrugged.  Haha, marshmallows. "DO IT! DO IT!"  Jason cracks me up.  Especially because he like has a crush on Emma Watson.  Yeah what happened to like stuff we/you said after new year's...  I forgot what I sent back.  But I remember it was like a bunch of crap.  I suck at writing stuff.  I go on like random tangents.  People outside my chem class watch us...  People being like Philippe.  Thomas Foote is like the perfect kid.  It's amazing.  I want to be him.  Like white and everything.  Just kidding.  And he's so modest too... If I were him I'd be like, haha, i'm better than you in every way possible... But he's not like that.  I like have a crush on him.  Haha, I should stop making bad jokes.  Yeah... I think I'm going to get back to work... Before I make myself seem more like:  1. A stoner 2. A rapist 3. A homosexual  Imagine someone who was all three of those things.  A homosexual sexual predator on drugs...  AHHH... That reminds me of my conversation with Jason yesterday about "Farm Sluts"  Hold on lemme find it...  Aww man I don't have the log of it.  But it went something like this:  Me: Eww, what is that doctor doing... OMG, that's like gay post mortem intercourse, could anything be more disgusting? Jason: Lol, homosexual necrophilia.  OK enough time wasted...
     

        
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm up to 10 for commentaries.  I keeping taking like "10-minute breaks" which end up being like 2 hours long, it's annoying.  This project does not want to be completed.  On a different note, Jay Chou has a music video for almost every one of his songs, I found that kind of weird.  Some of them are good others are just like weird.  Ahhhhh.... I think I'm going to do maybe like 11 more... If that is possible...  Does it matter that much if I don't go to your barbeque... W/e I'll come anyway.  Chinese Final tomorrow.  Fun fun.  I asked Joie what she thought of Derek and she responded that she thinks I am a lot cooler.  I'm flattered.  I actually had a dream yesterday, it was weird.  My dreams don't make sense.  I think it was my birthday, except not really, and I didn't have a party.  But then for some reason like Melody and Josh Nathan came to my house, and I was just like why are you here.  But that was like the morning after my birthday and they had come in the middle of the night but I didn't notice because they stayed downstairs in the guest bedroom for the night.  And then I woke up and Melody and Josh Nathan are there and I'm like what the, how'd you guys get there.  So then I was somewhat annoyed that they like came over and didn't tell me, but then I was like w/e.  And I thought it was kind of sketchy that they slept downstairs in the guest bedroom, where there is only one bed too.  Then Josh somehow disappeared or went away or something, and Melody stayed and I forget what happened after that.  But I do remember that it was like really incoherent and like the background kept changing, and oh yeah I tried to turn on the lights once and I was like "Damn why won't the lights go on."  Today in history:  Ronald Reagan dies. Smarty Jones loses Triple crown bid at the Belmont Stakes. Loren realizes that he is going to fail history.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Titles are worthless.   "Loren! Why do you smell good?!" ---Joie   I didn't realize that normally I am so horribly odorous.  Yeah nothing else happened.  Commentary count: 0.  Left to do: I don't know yet.  Woohooo....
     

        
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I think it sounds a lot better without that horrible horrible noise in the background.  I mean ahhh... play the guitar don't strangle it.  Or better yet, don't play the guitar at all and just sing. Like the Logs.  You see/hear what I mean about the "Look how they shiiiiiine" really nice part?  Probably not because you'd have to go pretty far into it to hear it.  Like right before the end.  And it isn't even like spectatamizing.  Ok... this is taking a long time to rip...  Ce n'est pas chouette/rad/whatever they say.  So the part that I was talking about comes in at about 3:55.  I was sort of wanting to do "An Jing" at asian night, but that would be so hard and nobody likes it when you sing depressing songs.  And I'd have to do it alone, because you cna't break that into 2 parts.  Unless one of them is the piano.  Dammit rip faster... It worked splendidly the first time, until I realized that I set the quailty as 320kbps and got like humongous files.  And was like damn.  But now it won't go at all.  Cheap ripping software...  Actually... free ripping software.  Ok so I downloaded a new one, thank gosh for Cnet.  This one seems to be working.  This is exciting. Go go go.  Woohoo. Look at it go...  I might as well put a track list as I am waiting.    urlLink Freedom ~ Wham!     urlLink Mysterious Ways ~ U2     urlLink Black Balloon ~ Goo Goo Dolls     urlLink Everywhere I Go ~ Shawn Mullins     urlLink U Remind Me ~ Usher     urlLink If I Ever Fall In Love ~ Shai     urlLink Hungry Like the Wolf ~ Duran Duran     urlLink Heavenly ~ ...I don't know...     urlLink All the Small Things ~ Blink 182     urlLink Yellow ~ Coldplay     urlLink Man in the Mirror ~ Michael Jackson     urlLink Superlogs ~ REM, only sort of    That was fun.  If you didn't notice, those are links to clips of the songs.  So idk.
     

        
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Cashed that $100 Chinese school check and my birthday money (cheap people giving me checks).  This is the most cash I've had in a while.  And only like... 30 dollars of it is from starving, wow.  Impressive.  Not really though.  Cash is useless if you don't have anything to spend it on.  Or... anyone...  Haha, no.  Anyone want $250...  We watched "The Manchurian Candidate" for Alex's birthday party.  I guess it was not a bad movie.  Too many sudden loud noises.  I have like a permanent cocaine hangover.  Aah bright lights and loud noises...  Except that I don't do cocaine.  I sat in the back on the ride home.  It was pretty uncomfortable.  Like being thrown forward whenever Alex's dad accelerated and sideways whenever he turned.  I changed my comforter finally.  I remember that conversation I had with Brett during HR once about how we sleep with two comforters and it's so comfortable and warm.  Back in second only 50 points behind Josh.  What now.  Hmm...  not a lot to do lately. 
     

        
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Not much to say...    Other than that Ma Qi Di Di is still amazing.    "Pi Li Pa La" - Andrew Chou.  Wait until the end, assuming it loads fast enough.    Very cool 12-year-old kid.    It's so cold...  
     

        
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      There's a comment on my blog that doesn't consist of Alex berating me.&nbsp; Intriguing. 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I think I'm beginning to hallucinate...  So you know how a little menu comes down sometimes when you type something into the input boxes?  I started to write in the "Title" box, or rather, I clicked inside of it, and a little menu came down, and there was like "Damn" and "China-ing" and stuff like that.  And then all of the sudden the menu grew longer and three more lines came up that said:  "i can teach you english" "we seem to have the same interests" "would you still love me tomorrow..."  And they showed up exactly like that.  It was really weird.  And this was like right after I read that part of the "Duan Le De Xian" lyrics that go:  Ni lei shui wang xia de diao Shuo hui ji zhu wo de hao Wo ye wan qi le zui jiao xiao  Which means:  Your teardrops stream down You say that you'll remember me I then curled up the corners of my mouth and smiled.  I'll be taking about maybe a one-week break from the internet now.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I had this good long post, but then I realized that dial-up internet sucks, so I will give you the general idea.  1. Stuff about how I can't tell how old Chinese girls are.  2. Stuff about Wimbledon and how Federer sucks but Maria Sharapova is good-looking.  3. Stuff about how I watched Yi Jianlian play and how he is very good.  4. Stuff about Chinese music.  Lin Jun Jie is cool.  Especially in his MV when he's like, "Hey, I'm... JJ."  I think that's all.  [edit]  I almost forget, I made up a new signature for myself.  I'm still working on it though.  And also, a post wouldn't be complete without some lyrics in Chinese for you not to read.  I'll blockquote them for you.   wo chen mo ni de hua ye bu duo   wo men zhi jian shao le shen me  bu shuo  ai yo... wei xiao hou biao qing zhong yu you dian nan guo  (wo zhe ni de shou)  wen ni jue ding le zai zou   wo tu ran shi huai de xiao  xiao sheng pan xuan ban shan yao  sui feng zai piao yao a yao  lai dao ni de mian qian rao   ni lei shui wang xia de diao  shuo hui ji zhu wo de hao  wo ye wan qi le zui jiao xiao   ---"Duan Le De Xian" ~ Jay Chou 
     

        
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Changing my medal predictions after seeing that debaucle in SCG.  Gold: Lithuania Silver: Argentina Bronze: USA  I still think that the USA won't medal, but you really can't bet against them.  Spain is pretty strong, unbeaten in pre-Olympic play, including wins against Lithuania and Argentina, but I still don't think their team is deep enough to medal.  When China played SCG in the Diamond Ball tournament, Yi Jianlian had 5 blocks and 7 boards in 24 minutes.  That's like awesomexors.  Yao won MVP honors in that tournament after averaging 26+ points and bunches of rebounds.  China came in fifth.  In other news, Loren is cool.   "Wai? I'm recording.  Uh... Chicken w/ rice.  Hey, add an egg OK?" 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I was listening to the new Jay again today, and on track 6, he hits that high D flat and it is like wow how did he do that?  I mean I can hit that note but it doesn't sound nearly as good.  I found out yesterday that I live a lot closer to Waltham than I thought.  What happens to the kids on that part of Derby St. who live like 500 yards from Franklin but are districted to some Waltham school?  Rockport tomorrow.  Should be a nice clean match.  I mean, fun.  USA plays Serbia and Montenegro tonight in Belgrade.  Haha... ha...  I still don't know how you sing a D flat that well.  At least I think it is a D flat, I might be offpitch, since it's been so long.  I'm bored.  I finished my math and now I have nothing to do.  Other than possibly burn down the house.  Yes, that would be fun...
     

        
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Is it just me or does "Jiang Jun" (Track 5) sound a lot like "Pirate" minus Jolin and with different words?   Ru guo yao zou, qing ni ji de wo.   Ru guo nan guo, qing ni wang le wo.       --"Jie Kou" ~ Track 3          I feel like pissing Alex off and saying that if I could vote in this coming election it would be for Bush. I feel like being an instigator. Like Serbia.  Alex is going to comment and be like "You feel like being stupid, stupid." Or something like that.  I went to work with my dad yesterday. It was really fun. Nerdily fun. All I did was distract his co-workers by asking them to teach me math. So I learned a bunch about Fermat, Goldbach, other number theory things.  I must have just discussed this stuff with them for about 2 hours.  It was... fascinating.  I didn't get a chance to see what Todd did, although my dad said that it was very good.  Who is that little girl?  My dad has a co-worker named Rick Shock.  What a cool name.  Well I guess it isn't that cool. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I feel stupid now after asking Eddie how he found my blog and not realizing that it was in my profile.  Pamela went over her friend's house today, which left me home alone. Woohoo fun.  Except not.  Technically if I was ever going to have people over/go over people's houses during the summer, today would be the day.  But that didn't happen. Oh well.  Note to self: Refrain from cooking with gel in your hair unless you want to be eating gel again. Either that or don't lean over a pot of boiling water so much.
     

        
</post>


</Blog>