<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Random jottings has moved to  urlLink www.planethopkins.com/blog    Please update your bookmarks!  neil h.
    
</post>


<date>07,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the sun has just started to shine after a particularly heavy shower. I can see it glinting through drops of rain on the garden chairs outside the window. Frankie the kitten is sat with his nose pressed up against the glass, and Jess the dog is standing over him like a protective older brother. Biddy the top cat is rootling in the flower bed. Jan is pooting on her laptop and I can hear Jamie playing upstairs with his friend Sophie from up the road. Alicia has just been told to brush her hair so she is stomping upstairs.  A typical, lazy Saturday afternoon in Burncross. I think I shall save this, and maybe fire up Baldur's Gate II for a bit of hack and slay.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      A flipping miserable day in Sheffield. It's chucking it down with rain, it's foggy, cold and gloomy. I'm working at home today, so I'm taking the chance to catch up with some bits and pieces of admin and then have a think about the next phase in my asset register project. I've just been for a haircut and got some shopping from Asda, and I think I need to have a cup of java and put the heating on (in September!) before I start my next bit of work.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday afternoon, and we've just been out to see Spiderman which has just been reclassified to allow children under 12 to see it. An excellent film, but the cinema was packed with fidgeting kids, rustling sweet wrappers and talking during the quiet bits. Very annoying! It was more violent than I was expecting - hopefully some of the brats will have been traumatised and have nightmares tonight ... :-)  Kitten news - Frankie has widdled in the corner by the TV again. I thought that we'd cured him of that by putting a little bowl of food there - ah, well he's only small and thankfully we have a wooden floor that is easily cleaned.  Right, must go and get the washing in off the line and make sure that Alicia has some school clothes ironed for tommorrow morning.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The weather has turned from being able to sit with the patio doors open at the weekend to a hail storm today. The sun came out around tea time with a spectacular rainbow across the sky as Barney and me set off for our evening walk.  Work was fairly busy today, testing a routine to split some spreadsheets three ways for different market sectors. It's clumsy, unwieldy and takes ages to run. It's a really bad way to run a business, and my next job is to write a report for the group accountant to explain why using spreadsheets to store data is not a viable way to manage our systems.  Rant of the day. Before opening my account with First Direct I had a Halifax account with a platinum visa card. I cancelled it a couple of months ago, cut up the cards, and got a refund of the outstanding credit balance. Today I had a statement through with a transaction for £40.00 for an AA subscription. How on earth can they carry on charging things to a cancelled card? Haven't rung them yet, but I am going to be cross with them when I do. Grrrr.  No time for writing today, but I'm going to mull things over when I drive down to Birmingham tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello blog, my old friend - I've come to talk to you again ...  Well, it's been a while - I signed up for this thing ages ago and never got started on it properly, but reading a couple of regular blogs has inspired me to start it up again. Writing is one of the things that I would like to do more of (along with exercise) and writing a few words every day seems like a good place to start. I have been meaning to write some game reviews for ugvm magazine, but haven't found the necessary circular tuit to actually do them yet. Perhaps if I have to give an account of my progress here I will be shamed into getting them done? On the other hand, it could be like my timesheets for work which are largely, errm, fictional - a frightening portion of my working day is spent staring into space before I actually knuckle down and do what I am supposed to at the last possible minute.   Anyhoo, there are two things to recount today.   This morning, I fell off the wagon of vegetarianism after nearly twenty years and succumbed to a bacon sarnie. Jan cooks bacon on a Sunday morning for the kids and after resisting for several years I gave in and ate one. It was flipping gorgeous. I felt slightly guilty afterwoods, and wondered why. I'm not really an ethical vegetarian or a particularly health conscious one - it's more of a habit, and a matter of taste I suppose. I'll have to find a source of free range happy bacon and eat that.  At teatime we all went for a walk in the woods with Barney the dog. It's fabulous in Foxfield Spring woods at the moment - the bluebells form a shimmering purple carpet with lime green tree shoots poking through. The bird song is a surround sound treat, particularly first thing in the morning. There is a woodpecker in residence at the top end of the woods and it's knocking sounds exactly like the noise that the Predator makes in the eponymous films and video games.  Anyhoo, Barney is a nervous dog, and not particularly well trained. He stays on the lead when we are out and I reel him in to keep him under control when other dogs are around. He came from the RSPCA and we don't really know what sort of experiences he has had. Just as we were at the entrance to the woods a medium sized brown whippet ran up and started nipping at Barney. It didn't have a collar on and there was no sign of the owner, until a fifty something woman came round the corner shortly after.  "Is this your dog?" I asked "Only, it should have a collar on and be under control"  "It's a whippet - it has a harness, not a collar and anyway it's your dog that's not under control"  She then proceeded to have a go at me for being a newcomer to the area "I've lived here 38 years and I've never seen you before" (when I've walked twice a day in those woods for the last three and a half years), and how ridiculous it was that I should have my dog on a lead and that it was somehow my fault for her dog being out of control.  The icing on the cake, as it were, was the shit on the path.  The dog settled down for a nice leisurely dump in the middle of the path, as it's rude and obnoxious owner walked away.  I couldn't help myself - "Excuse me, your dog has just defecated on the path!" I shouted in my best, plummy, outraged middle class voice. Cue much hilarity from my family, as Jan escorted me away and got me to calm down a little.     
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday afternoon, and a five mile walk from Reeth along the banks of the Swale and back via the village of Grinton. My dad drove us all into Reeth in the farm landrover - a slightly hair raising journey with six people and two dogs in a 30 year old landrover down lanes that are barely wide enough for one car at a time.  We kicked off with an ice cream from the shop - I could have happily eaten the whole menu, but I eventually went for the pineapple flavour - yum! The walk was comparitively easy compared to the hike yesterday - mostly flat and through shady woods. The river was a mere trickle compared to it's potential - the swing bridge was built in 2002 to replace the original that had been destroyed in a flood. The plaque said that the river is capable of rising 3 meters in 20 minutes and looking at the high water marks and flood plain it is easy to believe it.  Coming back to Reeth we met the strangest dog that I have seen in ages - a collie crossed with a corgi - corgi shaped, but with the face, colours and markings of a black and white collie.   Finally, a well deserved pint of beer outside the pub in Reeth before returning to Hunt House. I ended up listening to a retrospective feature about acid house on Radio 2 of all stations - it made me all nostalgic although I did feel old when I realised that the second summer of love was 16 years ago ... gulp. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Swing bridge over the river Swale&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Off to Swaledale for a weekend break! One of my dad's friends is seriously wealthy and has bought a 300 year old farmhouse in North Yorkshire as a holiday home, and my dad has done some of the restoration work on it so he gets to stay there for free once or twice a year. It's in a stunning location about halfway up the side of U shaped valley overlooking the river Swale, five miles from the nearest village and fifteen from the nearest town of any significance. Looking out of the windows gives an uninterrupted view as far as the eye can see, with only occasional farms, fields and barns on the far side of the valley to indicate the presence of civilisation.   There is no TV, no mobile coverage (maybe one bar if the wind is in the right direction, but as good an excuse as any to switch the bloody thing off), no noise apart from the calls of curlew and skylarks wheeling overhead and a sheep or two. Wild rabbits are everywhere (including a few squashed ones at the side of the road ... :-( ) and Barney the wonder dog was in paroxysms of joy sticking his snout into every rabbit hole he could see.  We arrived at two o clock, and after a late lunch set off to walk down to the bottom of the valley to the river. It's at least a thirty degree slope for most of the way (with even steeper bits in parts) and the day was quite warm, so I was soon puffing. ollowing the path through the woods revealed a fantastic waterfall that I had no idea was there with a double drop of at least 3 or 4 meters. From there to the river was somewhat easier and we were all glad of a sit down on the river bank at the bottom. Barney headed straight for the water and surprised me by swimming up and down in mid stream, and surprised me even more when he shook himself dry standing right next to me.  The walk up the hill was sheer, bloody murder though with some sections taken one step at a time with a breather at each wall and stile. It was worth it to get in and have a cold beer at the top though - bliss!  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hunt House in Swaledale&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Barney the wonderdog&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hidden waterfall in Swaledale&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A day off today, hurrah! Walk the dog, fling open the patio doors (am I the only person in the world who sees the word 'patio' and has an irresistible urge to pronounce it to rhyme with 'ratio'?), fire up the x-box and settle down for a day on Knights of the Old Republic.  Thirty hours or so into the game I finally get ambushed by the villain of the piece Darth Malak. Hang on, I thought there were supposed to be at least 40 hours of play on this and there are planets I haven't been to yet - have I missed a bit, or cocked something up somewhere? However, there is a plot twist to rival anything in Empire Strikes Back and my planet hopping resumes. I am really enjoying some of the character interactions as I succumb to the power of the dark side - as is my wont, my character is female but that doesn't seem to have stopped my snooty Jedi mentor Bastilla from trying to chat me up by going on about the bond that we share. Hmmm - is the Star Wars universe ready for hot girl on girl action?  I read something on geek.com recently about gamers who were outraged that The Temple of Elemental Evil had an ending where your male character could be gay and settle down to live happily ever after with another man. It wasn't compulsory, and you could also rescue the princess if that was your preferred choice, but they didn't even like the possibility that their alter ego might be anything other than staunchly heterosexual.   My most satisfying game experience ever was being romanced by a paladin knight whilst playing Baldur's Gate II. When I finally succumbed to a night of passion he buggered off and left me, the bastard ... men, eh?   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Driving in a car without a radio is a strangely cathartic experience. I do the drive from Sheffield to Dudley at least once a week and I pace out each landmark on the way on the trip meter. On the way down 30 miles puts me just past Chesterfield, 42 miles at the services, 54 miles on the M42, 80 miles for the M6, 100 miles just coming off the M5 and then a couple more miles to the office. Coming home is slightly different, with 48 miles marking the end of the M42, 90 miles being the junction with the M18 that means that home is only 20 minutes away and 100 miles being the slip road for Chapeltown.  I also like to try and match the digits on the trip meter to the time on the clock (so that at 16:35 I've driven 35 miles for example) and then try to maintain a 60mph average (or 80 if the road is clear and I'm being naughty) so that I can estimate how much time there is till I get home on the one mile is a minute principle (plus 10 minutes at the end to get through Chapeltown). Since I am usually traveling faster than 60mph when the road is clear it usually balances up the times when I hit a queue of traffic (not literally though).  I find myself taking strange trains of thought that meander through work to be done (or procrastinated), stories I want to write, blog entries that I probably won't make and odd childhood memories that still seem vivid after 30 years or more. The bright patches that I do remember (holidays, Christmases, birthdays, the time I nearly strangled to death when my hood got caught on a branch) throw into relief the times that are hazy or completely forgotten. Perhaps by reliving these memories they will be reinforced and stay with me into my future senility?  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                     A four hour session on this game this afternoon  finally polished it off.       &nbsp;    Wow.      &nbsp;    This knocks the last two Star Wars films into a  cocked stormtroopers helmet. Epic in scope, with fantastic characters, twists  and turns, spectacular environments from space stations to underwater bases to  the dune sea of Tatooine and the forests of Kashyyk. Space battles, light sabres  that you can customise (I went for a blue blade), betrayals and a hint of  romance. It is difficult to talk about it in detail without spoilers but my  character's gradual descent to the dark side and her final triumph&nbsp;is one  of my most supremely satisying gaming experiences ever. Worth buying an xbox  just for this game alone, particularly if you can pick it up  cheaply.      &nbsp;   &nbsp; The question now is which game I'm going to  go back to next. I have Harvest Moon on gamecube to get stuck into although I  think I fancy continuing the two player co-op game on Baldur's Gate:Dark  Alliance II that I have on the go with Jamie. Grand Theft Auto , Crimson Skies,  Beyond Good and Evil and Prince of Persia are all crying for attention as  well.      &nbsp;    Decisions, decisions ...      &nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Big brother has turned into 'People on the Toilet'.  I could leave it there, but I'm not going to. Michelle is seriously scary. The moment when she said of Stuart "He'd better shed a tear for me" before reaching up to the screen with a plaintive "Chicken" sent shivers up my spine.   Emma is just plain thick though. She has the reading age of a junior school child, which is why she is always given the laminates from Big Brother to read. It is toe curlingly embarrassing to watch but even that doesn't compare to watching her jumping on the bed and screaming like an over exited toddler, or even falling out of her top several times.  To quote one example :  Michelle: "If Big Brother deems your work satisfactory and you abide by the rules you will re-enter the house at Big Brother's discretion."  Emma: "What does that mean?"  Michelle: "It means if we abide by the rules we'll go in there at their discretion."  Emma: "Right."  More interesting though is the game playing in the main house. There are two main factions : Marco's harem and Jason's league of heterosexual gentlemen. Dan is the wild card playing both sides against each other. They've come as close as they can to discussing nominations without actually naming names, but I think this is a good thing. After all, the nominations themselves are secret (unless they let Emma and Michelle see them) so people can make all sorts of promises to build up alliances and then break them when the time is right.  I've not played Diplomacy for a while, but one of my best games saw me as Turkey allied with Austria - an unlikely partnership at best. I encouraged him to move north whilst I moved fleets through the med to attack France. I kept assuring him that I was only interested in a draw to prove that a Austro-Turk alliance could work, and so he left his southern border undefended. At the critical moment I had enough armies on hand to smash through the Balkans and win the game outright.  Who in BB5 has the right killer instinct? What will happen when Emma and Michelle return? How will the next set of nominations go?  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Working at home today, like most Fridays. Mum and Dad and their dog Penny are stopping for the weekend on their way back from Swaledale and Dad is putting up a pergola in the back garden for us. Hence there is much banging and hammering through the window whilst I am banging my head against a brick wall trying to get one of the divisional directors to use a sales order spreadsheet properly. Apparently having a button to press marked 'Authorize' with a tooltip popup message of 'Click here to authorize this order' is not obvious enough and he's been trying to type directly into a protected field. I've even sent him a screen dump with a big red circle around the button that he has to click but he hasn't replied yet.  I had another nice compliment today from Eileen when I turned round an amendment to a report that she needed in 15 minutes. "What would we do without you?" - I refrained from replying "You might like to imagine that scenario and offer to pay me accordingly" ... :-)  Right, time to go and get a can of coke from the fridge, make up some figures for my time sheet. It's usually pretty accurate unless I have  been bitting and batting between lots of little things like today. I mean, I can't really put "Dealing with complete numpties - 23 minutes" can I? I usually keep a log file where I can timestamp what I am doing and then dump that into an excel pivot table to get a summary by activity, but I forgot all about it yesterday. Oh well, I don't think my boss even looks at them anyway ...  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      'Walk on water man :)'  'Man who knows everything'  'Neil.  You are wonderful.'  Blush. I deserve a crunchie bar from the machine downstairs.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two random examples of sales droid behaviour :  The droid I was sat next to just started to ask me a question when I got a call on my mobile. When I came back to him two or three minutes later he said "Oh, I think I managed to work it out for myself, but I thought I'd ask you seeing as you were sat there".  We've changed the four digit security codes on the doors today and I've just seen a senior sales droid walking around with the new code biroed on the back of his hand.  Heh.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in the Leeds office today, so I've had the usual faff trying to find a hotdesk to use. The designated ones seem to have been claimed by various project managers who fill them up with their files, notes, phone chargers and gonks, and the one I picked was reclaimed when the owner sauntered in at 11 o'clock. She made a half hearted offer to move her stuff, but I ended up moving to the wilderness of the soul that is the sales and marketing department, scrabbling under the desk trying to find a network point.   I wandered into Leeds at lunchtime to have a nonch (that's 'mooch' in nokia predictive text) around the Corn Exchange, which with it's magnificent vaulted cast iron domed ceiling is easily one of my favourite buildings. Inside there are three levels of little hippy shops, with craft stalls on the middle level, and the Travelling Man games and comics shop on the top. I thought about getting some of the Sandman graphic novels but maybe I'll hold out till my birthday, so I just bought a Heroclix booster pack instead. Why do I buy figures for a game I rarely play? I don't know, but they are just so dinky and maybe I will get a full set of x-men circa the 1980s Claremont era if I keep buying them long enough.   On to Habitat to buy some side plates for my Mum and Dad to replace some that got chipped at Hunt House in the dish washer. I had a flashback to Saturday afternoons as a child when family entertainment meant a trip to Habitat or John Lewis' in Watford or Welwyn. The plates were just inside the door, but as the main till wasn't working I had to go upstairs to pay for them. Coming back down I got disorientated and nearly walked through a plate glass window on the way out.  Finally, a pack of sushi and a strawberry smoothie for lunch and back to the office to eat it. Before I could sit down I got collared for help on the sales spreadsheet by some of the sales droids before I had even seen the email from Eileen the contracts manager at Dudley asking me to sort them out. At least I was able to email back with a smug 'Done!' and get a reply of 'walks on water man!' which seems to be my official job title now.   Doesn't seem to come with any more money though ...   Open the Heroclix .... Rookie Daredevil and Kingpin ... Rats! Anyone got any swapsies?   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Off to Brum again for my usual weekly visit, made slightly more enjoyable by a relative lack of traffic on the roads due to half term and the reappearance of my errant cd player. This allowed me to listen to the final two chapters of an audio book and my copy of The Streets 'A Grand Don't Come For Free' - an excellent little concept album dealing with the problems of getting a signal on your mobile and debating the relative merits of going out to the pub or chilling out on the sofa watching Eastenders or The Bill.  Work was the usual mixture of 'we need this report today - can you write it now, please' and 'I've forgotten how to do this procedure that you showed me last week and gave me some documentation for - can you explain it to me again in words of one syllable?' The report wasn't too bad to write (even if Wallchart, our scheduling system, has the most cack handed and awkward report writing tool ever although I made the mistake of assuming that because the sales director had asked for 'days chargeable' to be shown on the report he actually wanted the chargeable days rather than the days delivered ... Cue a heavy sigh and a quick re-write.  The journey home was about as good as it ever gets - two hours from leaving the office to getting home, and the last bit with the sunroof open and Goldfrapp on full blast coming through Chapeltown. 'Train' and 'Strict Machine' are just so deliciously sleazy ... ;-)  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hospital appointment this morning. I have a dodgy varicose vein in my left leg which has a nasty tendency to throb in bad weather. I saw a consultant a couple of months ago who poked and prodded me for a while and stuck some sort of microphone into my groin so I could hear blood swooshing where it didn't ought to be swooshing and recommended an operation to whip it out.  This was my first visit to the Day Surgery unit and in the end they just gave me loads of leaflets, weighed me, measured me (not quite tall enough for my weight apparently) and told me I'm going to be having my operation on the 20th of July.  Bum.  That's four days before my birthday and I had planned to take a week off the following week to go for a ride in Emma Kennedy's new car and see Richard Herring's new show but I don't know if I'm going to be capable of driving anywhere by then. On the plus side, Alicia will be on holiday with her mother that week so I don't have to worry about driving her to school or whatever.  I've never had an operation before, so I'm mildly anxious. I've seen enough episodes of Holby City to know that going in for a routine minor operation means I'm a certain to be diagnosed with some rare tropical disease of the leg and end up with blood squirting all over the grumpy surgeons gown before I end up having a pneumothorax or a subdural haematoma or worst of all in vf which is invariably fatal regardless of how many volts they pump through me.  Like I said, bum.  I had a call from the garage who had a replacement cd player in stock. The service guy assured me that it would take a mere 20 minutes to install but when I actually got to the garage that turned out to be all day before they could get the requisite circular tuit. I decided to get a bus home, and managed to just miss one that would have taken me all the way to Burncross so cue a twenty minute wait and a journey of nearly an hour to get home.  I did a bit of work in the afternoon in between trying to catch up with email and usenet, and then got another bus back at ten to five. To quote a text from Alicia, 'this has got 2 b the hottest summer eva!' Stuck in a rattling bus full of sweaty people in 30 degree temperatures was not my idea of fun, but it was worth it to get my car back, stick the air con on full blast and crank up the new stereo for the drive home. Bliss.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was my dad's birthday today and he was very happy with the Phil Drabble books that my mum asked me to track down on the net for him. The 'Badgers at my Window' had a scary looking badger on the front - blimey, those things have got sharp teeth. I had to explain why we all started singing "Badger Badger Badger" though ... http://www.badgerbadgerbadger.com/  We managed to get away by 10:30 which wasn't bad going, even though I had to clean tree sap off the car windows. I also found an enormous weird green insect crawling up my face as I was driving down the lane - it's a good job that I not too squeamish.  As soon as I got back into mobile signal range I had two calls from work - one for something that should have been installed when the internal support guys rebuilt one of the accounts pcs on Friday and a bit of handholding for a new procedure that I set up last week. However much I document these things (even including pretty pictures and simple bullet points for the hard of thinking) it is never enough for some of them. Grrr.  We got home in two hours exactly, and found two cats waiting expectantly for food. Barney scootled around the garden for five minutes and then settled down on his dog settee with a big sigh ... home again.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's up to the top of Swaledale today, past rabbit warrens along a path between two ridges and up to the shooting butts at the top. Strict signs warn against disturbing ground nesting birds - presumably so they can be blown to smithereens with lead shot in a couple of months time. There were piles of discarded cartridges lying around the butts showing that some heavy duty fire power has been unleashed at some point.  The main purpose of the trip was to try out Jamie's new kite - just a cheap jobbie from Marks and Spencer of all places - but it flew like a dream. The wind was just right, and the butts provided an excellent vantage point.  Back to Hunt House for a cold beer, and a look at Jan's sketches of the house - she's an excellent artist, even if small scale detail sketches are not her usual thing. We sat on the bench at the front of the house watching Barney running round like a loon and leaping off the wall until the aphids crawling up and down my arms became unbearable.  In the evening we played Cluedo (Alicia had been pestering for this for the last two days) and the Simpsons board game which is excellent fun even if I did come last. The Moe's Tavern Kareoke challenges were the most fun but I ended up trapped in the nuclear power plant for half the game.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Kite flying at the top of Swaledale&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, she's gone.  Big Brother has just told the housemates that Emma won't be returning to the house " to ensure the welfare and safety of all the housemates, including Emma." In retrospect, Emma was a poor choice for the show - easily the most volatile of the lot of them, she clearly lacks the self control and awareness to play the game. They were obviously looking for another Jade Goody (or Goodier as Emma kept referring to her), and perhaps Emma will make some money from the tabloids in the coming weeks.  So, where does this leave the state of play now? The league has three strong players with Stuart and either Dan or Vanessa as possible allies. Marco's harem is now just him and Nadia with Michelle a weak supporter and likely to follow Stuart. Shell is a floater and likely to be isolated when Vanessa goes.  My predictions? Vanessa to be evicted this week, with Nadia and Victor as nominations. Victor is the more likely to survive one public vote but if he is nominated again he will go.   Apparently beer sales in the uk have doubled in recent weeks - watching young men running round in shorts must be thirsty work. I've done my bit by buying a mini keg of Boddingtons which is very drinkable indeed, and I've just ordered a pair of Bombadier kegs to go in the garage.  I may never leave the house again ...  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Flowers in the rain&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Another green world&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the recent run of fine weather has ended and it's been chucking it down for most of the day. The sun peeked out briefly at about half past five so I took Barney out for a quick walk and took a couple of pictures.  I keep Barney on the lead pretty much all of the time - it's an extending one, and I can reel him in like a fish when I spot another dog coming. Most other people seem to let their dogs roam free without worrying about the consequences. Milo, the crossbreed that lives in the house opposite the playground escaped from his garden twice yesterday and followed us most of the way home. Today we met a little beagle puppy in the woods that came sniffing round and then chased us across the field all the way to our gate, blithely ignoring its owner's plaintive calls. Very cute, but certainly not most excellent.  When I left the office last night the security guard had rigged up a little portable tv and had changed out of his crypto-fascist uniform into an England shirt to watch the game. The house next door has more banners and flags than a BNP rally and wearing flags as ponchos seems to be de regeur for the denizens of the pub down the road.  This weird flag fetish seems to be perfectly socially acceptable and yet if somebody puts on a pair of elf ears or a klingon costume to go to a sf convention it's all "Har! Har! Look at the sad geeks that need to dress up to have fun!". 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in Leeds today and I've had enough of fiddling with subtotals on spreadsheets. I can add auto subtotals to a 1000 line sheet in a matter of seconds but trying to remove them would take hours if I let it run through. Also, it bloats a 100kb spreadsheet to something approaching 5Mb. Hmmmm.  Well, the big news has to be the bust up in the Big Brother house. I was going to write a blog analysing the different voting blocs and how the alliances would have shifted (in a nutshell, the league of heterosexual gentlemen would have stuffed unless they could get Dan or Vanessa on side and pick off Nadia or maybe Marco), but it all looks to have ended up in a massive ruck at two o'clock in the morning. I can't see how Emma and Victor can possibly stay in the same house and my betting is that one or both of them will leave with replacements coming in next week.   Of course, I could be entirely wrong - the net admins here have the internet locked down tighter than a gnat's chuff, unless it's them that want to download Spongebob Squarepants screensavers or Euro 2004 results - so I won't get to see the BB news page or live feed until I get home in an hour or so.  Isn't there some kickabout in a park in Portugal going on as well?  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The musical accompaniment to my trip to Dudley today is the soundtrack to Interstate 76. Forget all of those Jeremy Clarkson "Now That's What I Call The Best Driving Album in the Entire History of the World Ever!! Volume 47" cds that you find in motorway service station bargain bins alongside the string backed leather driving gloves and travel sweets in a little tin with icing sugar. This is the business.  Interstate 76 was a vastly underrated car combat game set in an alternate reality Texas of the mid 70s where the oil crisis was just a little bit worse and tipped the US into near anarchy. Auto vigilantes took to the back roads of the badlands in souped up muscle cars armed to the teeth with 50 cal machine guns, missile launchers and flame throwers to protect the dwindling oil supply. The hero of the piece is the ultimate 70s medallion man Groove Champion who inherits his sister Jade's car when she is murdered by a sharp suited assassin. The world weary Groove falls in with Jade's partner smooth talking partner Taurus (clearly modelled on Shaft) and a psychotic hillbilly mechanic Skeeter to track down the killers.   It is a fantastically compelling game, but the best thing about it is the music, with every wah-wah peddle, bass riff and horn blast of the best 70s funk. The soundtrack takes the music and adds cb radio chatter, tyres squealing, engines revving and bullets flying to the mix.   So, today I've been hunting creepers on the radar and calling in a code six-pack .... remember - *never* get out of the car ...   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "It was sposed to be so easy"  Just update the pricelist database, insert an extra column in that spreadsheet and get a glass of orange from the fridge.  Step one, the pricelist. What did I do with the print outs of the things she wanted changing? They're not in my briefcase, not in my folder. Perhaps I can find them in my email? Where are the buggery bollocks are they?  They're tucked inside my notepad.  Ok, lets start on this, but first I'm just going to check my email and maybe I'll get a snack to eat.  Ok, I'm definitely going to do it now, and I need to look at how I'm going to restructure it. What did I do with my notes on that? Ah, in my task list.  Here we go.  Oh, bugger - a phone call - better answer it.   It's Eileen.  "Can you just put an extra column in the order book spreadsheet so we can break it down by products and services?"  "Yep, no problem"  Except it is. There's a whole lot of macro code that's using absolute column references rather than named ranges. Is there an easy way to do a global update? No, and I've just changed every 'J' in the code to a 'K'. Get the original version back and try again.  Call Eileen and tell her it's more complicated than I first thought.  "That's ok" she says, "We don't use those macros anyway. We just use the ones on the other sheets to extract the new and amended lines"  "That should be straight forward then"  Except it isn't. I put the extra column in on the front sheet and the two extract sheets, click the button and it only copies half of what I was expecting.  Open up the visual basic editor and try and follow what is happening. It makes no sense whatsoever. What are all these references to absolute rows and why is it copying it one cell at a time rather than in chunks?  Time for a drink of orange from the fridge. I reach for the jug of squash on the top shelf and catch the light switch, spilling a significant amount.  Squash now starts dripping down every shelf in the fridge.  Unpack the whole fridge, take the shelves out, drip orange on the floor, wash the shelves in the sink, wipe the floor, it's still sticky so spray some floor spray on and wipe it again, wipe the bottom of every jar, bottle, yoghurt pot, margarine tub and milk carton and put them back.  Pour a glass of squash. Drink.  Look at the code again and set some breakpoints to step through it. Oh, I get it - he's looking at some hidden rows to check the format that each cell should be and when I've inserted a column I've missed a marker that it was expecting hence breaking the control loop. Well, that's all very clever but without comments it is impossible to follow without a great deal of effort.  Unhide the rows, decode the markers the code is expecting, rehide the rows and test.   Success on a plate!  Email to Eileen for testing and wait for a reply. Perhaps I can blog this while I'm waiting, and then I can have a look at the pricelist database again.  "Today I have achieved absolutely nowt ..."  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In the late 80s I worked for a small company in Sheffield writing production control software. It wasn't a bad job - mainly office based with occasional site visits. However, on one of those site visits I went with a salesman called Joe and I came as close to dying as I ever have in my life.  To call Joe unreconstructed would be an understatement. He had stepped through a time warp from the Sheffield of the 70s with his greasy, straggly hair and brown suits. Needless to say he chain-smoked, drank like a fish and went to the pub for his lunch just about every single day. He had an unshakeable conviction that his life experiences had given him a unique insight into the human condition that bordered on arrogance. His way of doing things was the only way and woe betide anybody that tried to tell him different.   Driving down the motorway he stayed permanently in the outside lane, hunched over the wheel daring anybody to get in his way. Somebody did. A woman driver, a subhuman species in Joe's opinion, pulled out to overtake a string of lorries and had the effrontery to be in front of him doing a totally unreasonable 70 miles per hour. He gripped the steering wheel harder and hit the accelerator until he was on her tail. He flashed his lights, sounded his horn and came within inches of ramming into her. The woman found a gap between two lorries to move across but that wasn't good enough for Joe. He drove alongside her, swearing, spitting and swerving from side to side in the outside lane.   I jammed my foot on an imaginary brake pedal and closed my eyes and prepared for impact. Fortunately the woman escaped into the slow lane and slowed down dramatically, disappearing into the traffic behind. The absolute icing on the cake was still to come. He pulled in at the next services, found a traffic cop and reported her for dangerous driving, saying that he had been cut up and was driving defensively. "People like that shouldn't be on the road - absolute menace".  I spent the rest of the journey gripping the edges of my seat in fear and I never went in a car with him again.  Fast-forward 14 years or so and I'm watching Traffic Cops - one of my favourite programmes on TV. The current series is set in South Yorkshire and it is great fun watching high speed chases round the estates, back roads and motorways of my area. There are licence dodgers, twoccers, speeders and all manner of automotive lowlife that get their respective collars felt by the boys in blue.  On last night's show, the police had received a tip off about a man drinking heavily in a pub at lunchtime who was about to get in his car to drive away. The traffic cop waited at the side of the road and stopped him before he got to the end of the road.  "Bloody hell - I used to work with him!"  He was still arrogant enough to take a five minute call on his mobile in the back of the police car, try to claim that he had some sort of liver disorder that stopped him metabolising alcohol ("I think you should know that before you take me to court"), argue with the booking sergeant about procedure and finally express surprise that he was more than three times over the limit when he had only had a couple of pints at lunchtime.  I think he got a fine and a thirty month driving ban.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the pergola is up and has been decorated with  hanging baskets and various other bits and pieces - isn't it fab? It's been like  something off Ground Force except my dad looks nothing like Tommy Walsh. It  completely transforms the back of the house and frames the view of the flower  bed as I sit on the settee looking out of the patio doors.   We even found some canvas to put on top of it to  give a bit of shade this afternoon and it was just like the episode of Robinson  Crusoe where he builds the bit at the front of his cave and puts a bit of sail  up to shelter it. I loved that series, and that  episode in particular, and always harboured a secret desire to live in a cave  like that. It really upset me when the cave got attacked later in the series and  the shelter destroyed by the cannibals.  Right, I'd better go and water those plants  ...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Our new pergola&nbsp;
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Biddy checks out the view&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shopping in Leeds today, and as we drove up the motorway large drops of rain started to spatter the windshield. Oh well. Park in the Royal Armories car park and get the umbrella out of the back of the car.  First stop is the Corn Exchange to swap a necklace for Jan - the staff in Hippypottermouse are extremely helpful and friendly, and I could sing their praises. If you are ever in search of anything vaguely hippy in Leeds - Celtic jewellery, joss sticks and the like - it's worth a detour.  Next is upstairs to traveling Man, so Alicia can buy Buffy magazines, and Jamie and me can have a look at the games. The live action role playing swords are excellent, but expensive so I divert Jamie to have a look at the D&D stuff. That's when I meet the Rolf.   If you've ever been to a games convention, you'll know the type - dressed like a diplomat on an overseas posting with a panama hat, linen suit and goatee beard, and with a voice projected so that everybody in the shop can get the benefit of his vast experience. Everything I looked at, he either owns, has played or has an opinion on. I refrain from pointing out that I was playing D&D when he was in nappies ...  In the end I couldn't resist buying Munchkin, if only because Jamie will appreciate the humour of a game where the objective is to "Kill the monsters, steal the treasure and stab your buddy". Great stuff.  Sushi for lunch, and then while Jan went looking for bags we browsed for a while in Game and then made our way to Borders to look at books and have a coffee (white chocolate mocha for Alicia, iced mochachino for Jan and a Raspberry frappachino for me).  Home for a snooze, at least until Frank jumped on me and a woman called at the door doing a survey on "Micras less than 12 months old" when ours is clearly older than that. Weird ... 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jamie : "Alicia, don't you even know what armour class is yet?"
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Alicia - tidy up your tarot cards from the server room."
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I would have got the sales spreadsheet done if people hadn't kept ringing me up this morning to update prices on the existing database. We haven't had a purchasing manager for a couple of months now and the new chap doesn't start till next week, so it will be a while before he gets up to speed. When people ask me what the cost of maintenance on an ImageRAID is, or whether it counts as a server or a scanner all I can do is make whale noises at them.  This afternoon I got a request for a report out of our scheduling system. One of the divisional managers isn't just interested in what his team have been doing, he wants to see every single bit of activity for April and May for all booking types and contracts. It's easy enough to set up the report but Wallchart's notoriously inefficient client-server architecture makes the whole thing run like a dog over my VPN connection and it takes an hour and a half to run, pulling back over six thousand transactions.  Fun fun fun.  In other news, my two casks of Bombadier bitter have arrived and the first glass was sampled on the patio in the last half hour and I can exclusively reveal that it is spanking gorgeous.  Excuse me while I go and get drunk ...
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alicia : "Typical! I'm being attacked by a pack of wolves and my mother rings!" 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The skies are dark - rain is lashing the house, cold winds are howling and still the dog demands to be taken for a walk. Typical weather for Wimbledon fortnight I suppose - there was even some hail mixed in with the rain in Leeds yesterday.  Most of this morning I sat staring at some modifications that the sales director wants for her order spreadsheet. I have been procrastinating on this one for ages, but now I come to look at it, the actual coding should be fairly straightforward. I've been telling everybody how tricky it's going to be, because it involves database changes but the only complicated bit is checking the usernames against different authorization levels and requiring two directors to authorize for orders over £500,000. If I can lay my hands on the necessary circular tuit I might get this finished tommorrow, always assuming I don't get interrupted by anything else.  Biddy the cat is going mental. I'd put the chairs upside down on the dining room table earlier to hoover up some crumbs and left them there. Sitting in the lounge reading email, I heard two almighty crashes as she chased Frank round the house knocking the kitchen bin over and one of the chairs off the table. Frank now has a little scab on his head where Biddy has swiped him, and she's just had a go at Barney as well. She's obviously asserting her status as top cat even though she is the smallest of all of the animals in the house.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was going to walk into town today, but it was chucking it down so I walked to the Boots in the retail park round the corner instead. I'd forgotten about the gas works round the back of the office building where I work - there are all sorts of weird pipes of different colours and sizes jutting out at strange angles like something out of an old Monty Python animation or Brazil. Terry Gilliam obviously had a strange pipe fixation.  I wondered why terrorists don't try to blow up gas works. This one would be a doddle with handy on street parking right by the front gate, although the car would probably be broken into and the bomb stolen judging by the number of little piles of broken glass that dotted the pavements not to mention the used condoms. Ewww - glad I don't work here after dark.  The retail park doesn't compare with the Corn Exchange for nonching purposes - a Currys, Comet and two other electrical type retailers, a Staples, an Argos, Bathroom and Flooring showrooms and a Boots that seems to make most of its money selling sandwiches at lunchtime. Not a huge amount of choice, and they seem to have stopped doing the sushi that they used to have. No, I do not have a Boots card.  Back to the office, and I see in the signing in tick sheet that a guy I used to work with in the old Sheffield office is in today so I went looking for him. He used to have the strange Asperger's habit of standing by your desk rabbiting on about his various obsessions while you were busy working and obviously ignoring him. Today, I was the Asperger's case as he was on a customer site stepping through live code to find a bug. "I have to keep typing otherwise the connection times out". Oh. I know when I'm not wanted.  I'm sat on my own in the upstairs office as all of the project managers have disappeared into meetings and none of them have made me a coffee since I made a round this morning. Hmmmm. Seeing as the manager I wanted a word with isn't in and there is no clue in her outlook diary as to her whereabouts I might as well have worked at home today and I would have had nicer coffee as well.  I'm tired as well, the air con isn't working leaving the office hot and stuffy and the rubbishy catering pack of instant coffee here just isn't cutting the mustard today. I was woken up at three in the morning by my own farts - the most vile, noxious, burningly hot sensation that propelled me to the loo for twenty minutes or so. Is this still the after effects of the weekend chilli or something else that I am incapable of digesting?  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A cup of java, a square of Green and Blacks organic chocolate, feet up, patio doors open and the windchime clonking in the breeze like a demented Gamelan orchestra.  Ahhhhh. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If your clapped out old lorry is going to break down and catch fire, where is the very worst place that it can happen? Yep, the junction of the M5 and the M6 - the busiest bit of motorway in Europe - would be the ideal spot to cause maximum chaos.  Fun fun fun.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'd like to get away from Birmingham by four o'clock at the latest, so 3:55 is not the best time to start a planning meeting for redesigning the gross margin delivery system.  Apparently having automatic subtotals in the sheet will be confusing because the end users are used to seeing the totals with a blank line separating each contract. Never mind that you can re-sort the whole list or auto filter for a particular contract or customer - if it isn't the way it has always been it won't do.  Repeat after me. Designing order processing systems to run on spreadsheets is a bad idea. A very bad idea.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "A load of records have gone missing from the asset register database!"  "Ok, let's have a look. Remember when you started putting the new aquisitions in before running the year end rollover and asked me to delete them? Those are the records that aren't there because they've been re-added with different sequence numbers."  "Oh. I see"
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Headless mice : 1 Piles of dog poo : 3  V.V. Bad  No, not a particularly disgusting chapter of Bridget Jones' Diary, it's stuff that I picked up in my garden this morning. My garden is a bit like the Hundred Acre Wood in that they both have a Pooh corner. Barney has a prodigious output for a medium sized dog but at least he is consistent about where he outputs it to. He is pretty good in the woods too - he will scootle off the path and go behind a bush, but he usually saves it until we get home.   Dudley today, a nice sunny day, not so much traffic as usual and - uh, oh - what's this approaching the M6? 'Major Roadworks from June to November - long delays expected'. Oh, fan-bloody-tastic. They had nearly a years worth of roadworks two years ago with road widening and bridge repairs that turned the stretch of the M6 from junction 4 to junction 9 into a living nightmare.  Guess which bit I drive on every week? Just to make my happiness complete there are bridge repairs on the M42 just by the junction for the A5 and I expect that they will find somewhere on the M1 to dig up for the summer as well.  Thank goodness for air conditioning and cd players.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Davina : "What has the Big Brother experience taught you?" Emma :   "Nothing - nowt"  So, violent confrontations, cake bras and 24 hour CCTV surveillance are normal features of Emma's life? Mind you, she does live in Oldham ...  Two bits of good news for geeks -    urlLink SpaceShipOne  has successfully flown 100km into space. I'd always thought that re-usable rocket planes were a far more elegant solution to getting into orbit than the big dumb rockets pointing straight up. Chuck Yaeger and the other X pilots of the 50s were the true pioneers of the space race.  Secondly, the various legal problems that have dogged the new radio production of the last three Hitchhiker novels appear to have been resolved and it's been scheduled for broadcast on Radio 4 starting on the 21st of September - you can hear a clip from it  urlLink here . I'm really looking forward to this, as I've enjoyed Dirk Maggs' other 'audio movies', particularly his adaptation of Stephen Baxter's Voyage about an alternate history where NASA put it's efforts into a manned flight to Mars.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like hot food. Hot food does not like me.  Well, it's my own fault. I had jalapeños on my pizza on Friday night and some of my special chilli (lotsa garlic and half a pack of birds eye chilli peppers) last night, and boy did I regret it this morning. Several times.   I like curries too, but rather than tucking into a nice vindaloo or madras I find myself thinking of the consequences and opting for a mild one instead. Is this incipient irritable bowel syndrome, or some other dread disorder of the nether regions that I will regret googling for? Perhaps I should grit my teeth, clench my buttocks and put the loo roll in the fridge ...  What else, today? I had a nice card from the kids for father's day - it had a dad telling a kid to tidy their room with the caption on the front saying "In this house what Dad says goes .... in one ear and out the other". Very appropriate.  I've worked out how to add links to my template but there are only a couple down there at the moment. If you would like to be added then all you have to do is ask nicely ... :-)  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just practice dragging and dropping monsters and treasure and I'll show you how to do a merchant later. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Frank the fat cat
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The coolest happy meal toy EVER!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Biddy and Millennium Falcon
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My heart says Michelle, my head says Nadia, the bookies say Marco.    Who goes, you decide ... 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Get their hair caught in a mini personal fan blade.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I *thought* I'd finished it. Wrong. Think again, boyo. A meeting with Eileen, and  well, I'll let my task list for this project speak for itself :  - version number history - unprotect purchase invoice and order no areas - protect supplier column - if supplier present highlight total cost in red to indicate 3rd party purchase required - add permission to add/amend after authorization to user table for ES,JS,EA,NC - show invoices raised in a box on the main tab within the print area - add payment type on order summary screen, validated to IUF/SP,IOC,IOM,IAT - if payment type is IUF/SP force entry to the payment profile - pro-rata the total cost in client payment profile section - add expenses chargeable yes/no  - if yes force entry to the expenses description box - warning message if client address not entered - password protect the database - add amended date to the component table in the database  ... and I've got to drive to our head office in Bourne End in Bucks for a meeting on Tuesday (that's 4-5 hours each way).  *sob*
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, that was a surprise.  I think that my predictions for nominations this week were mostly correct, but the real surprise was Shell siding with the Jungle Cats and going for Nadia and Marco. Her votes tipped the balance and gave a clean sweep against the harem.   The best twist was still to come though. Becki, having thought that she was exempt from the nomination process this week, was called into the diary room and asked to make one nomination. She had fifteen minutes to pick one housemate by kissing them on both cheeks making automatically up for eviction.  Michelle did not like it, to put it mildly. She had no reason to expect nomination this week and it was a real bolt from the blue. If she survives this week, and doesn't realise that Becki was responsible, then she will be feeling completely paranoid and isolated particularly as the harem is certain to lose one of it's core members.  I think that Jason may well do the maths and work out that Michelle must have been nominated by Becki - he noticed that she came out of the diary room looking troubled and behaving oddly - but if he stays true to form he will keep his gob shut and try to get Becki on his side.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Today I have been mostly wondering why I blog.      I think it goes back to my days running a fanzine in the early  80s. I started co-editing a role-playing games fanzine called Quasits and  Quasars with a school friend called Dave Hulks, and then struck out on my own  into the world of postal games with what was known at the time as a personal  zine. These zines were often intensely personal affairs with editors discussing  matters close to their hearts, reviewing films, comics, books and games,  exchanging letters of comment with readers and running a few games of postal  diplomacy to give the thing an excuse to run to reasonable deadlines. The  physical effort in producing one of these zines was considerable though - typing  the pages on a manual typewriter, cutting and pasting artwork (with real  scissors and glue), letrasetting headlines, duplicating the required number of  copies, posting to the subscribers and maintaining accounts that would in no way  pay for the time, effort and materiel involved. There was no real reason to do  it, other than for the resultant ego boost and the contact with like minded  individuals around the country and occasionally the world.     My zine folded when I came to university and ran out of time and  money.     Fast forward ten years or so, and something else triggered a  need to write.     My wife at the time and myself were expecting a baby, but  something went wrong and Ethan was still born. It was a terrible time and the  only way I found to express the way I was feeling was to write it down.  Eventually, I wrote an account of the experience and posted it to a support  newsgroup on the internet. I received dozens of replies and continued  correspondences with people who had had similar experiences for years  afterwards. The story is still archived in a couple of places, and I still get  occasional emails every two or three months from people and I offer what support  and encouragement I can in response.     The newsgroup uk.media.radio.archers was the next area that I  explored. It has been described as 'a newsgroup for the sort of people who might  listen to the Archers' and I have been reading and posting there for six years  or so now. I've laughed at the jokes and fish puns, discussed serious issues and  seen people fall out and make-up, been to several real-life barbeques and wept  bitter tears for the three umrats I have known who have passed away over the  years.     People who I have only known as phosphor dots on a screen have  become a real community to me. The blogsphere is a similar community, in some  ways more diffuse than a newsgroup and in other ways much more personal and  intense. People carve out their own little corners of cyberspace and invite  others to join them.     There are real people on the other side of the screen  ...     
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I finally knuckled down and finished the work on the new version  of the sales spreadsheet. It now filters by market sector (when I figured out  how to do radio buttons in visual basic properly), checks the authorization  identity against the database and is generally tidied up and lovely. All that  remains is to punt it to the sales director and her flunky for testing an  approval. Woo hoo!  Why did I procrastinate on it for so long? I don't  know really - a lot of the time when I am staring at the screen thinking of ways  to do things I get distracted, either by genuine work (usually inane questions  from users) or by something else that I persuade myself is a higher priority  (blogging, hem, hem) and the train of thought is derailed.     I wonder how much work I could achieve if I worked to a hurry-up  drill all of the time? I don't know - I think that I need the adrenaline rush of  leaving things to the last minute and storming through them. If I have a lot of  projects on the go, then I can set myself overlapping deadlines for them to up  the panic factor a notch.      Anyway, if I made things look too easy then people wouldn't  appreciate all of the hard work I actually do ...     
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My leg hurts today.  It's my own fault. I was fencing with Jamie in the back garden yesterday with the wooden swords that we got from the  urlLink Royal Armouries museum  in Leeds the other day, teaching him the basics of parry and riposte. I forgotten how much strain a fencing stance puts on my thigh muscles and the vein along the top of my left leg is now throbbing horribly.   It didn't help when a large dog came bounding up to Barney this morning causing him to wrap his lead around my legs trying to get away. He's fine most of the time, but some dogs really spook him for some reason and gets really defensive and snarly. I have to anticipate which dogs are going to worry him and get him to sit down at the side of the path out of the way, but this one was too quick for me at seven o'clock in the morning.  Alicia was struggling to get out of bed as well. She has PE first thing on a Monday morning and suffers from Start-the-week-itis, having to be chivvied to collect all of her school stuff, make sure she has her phone, purse and PE kit and be reminded that her mp3 player is not her top priority when we need to get out of the house. Teenagers, eh? Can't live with 'em, and, er - no, you just can't live with 'em ...  Finally, I have discovered the delights of  urlLink Feedreader . It's a tiny, efficient app that monitors RSS and XML feeds on blogs and news services, and pops up headlines every so often. If you see a headline you want to read more of you can click through to the webpage behind it. For some reason, it only seems to display the headline of the atom.xml files from blogspot accounts but it is a useful little pointer that a blog has been updated and is ready to be read.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, a new housemate in the house. Becki has already shown an ability to dissemble quite effectively, pretending to be an Italian from the Italian Big Brother and then lying about her age, so it looks as if she is going to be an effective game player.  The real question is, how much has she seen of the housemates activities so far - particularly the nominations? If she has, then the obvious tactic will be to follow the strong alliance of the jungle cats in the diary room but to play the field in the house. She has already said that she expects to be 'last in and first out', and previous series would seem to support this theory but I don't think this will happen in Becki's case. If she really does cause havoc by flirting with the cats and teasing the harem, then I think she may be nominated but will win the public vote to stay in.  As for the nominations this week my predictions are : Ahmed : Marco + Nadia, Dan : Nadia + Jason, Jason : Nadia + Marco, Marco : Jason + Victor, Michelle : Jason + Victor, Nadia : Jason + Victor, Shell : Michelle + Victor, Stuart : Nadia + Marco, Victor : Nadia + Marco  This should make Nadia a cert for nomination with Marco and either Victor or Jason as the others. Jason's strategy of acting as the grumpy outsider seems to be a deliberate strategy to split the anti Victor vote which could just pay off.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've just walked past the kids playground in the field that backs onto our garden. Hanging around in the playground was a group of about six or seven teenagers, dressed in black with Slipknot and Korn tee-shirts. One of them had a short piece of metal in his hand and was using it to hit the climbing frame with. He had long, greasy hair and reminded me of the ape at the start of 2001 discovering the use of a bone club.  Several of the group were shouting at each other. Face to face, separated by no more than a couple of centimeters they were literally screaming, incomprehensible, gutteral noises. I've heard them before, off in the woods but never seen it at quite such close quarters. I couldn't understand a single word in the din. They just seemed to be determined to make as much noise as possible, in some sort of primative display of agression.  I felt completely bewildered and threatened by their behaviour. I hurried past, my eyes downcast so I wouldn't catch their attention. I'm pretty sure that they are the gang that has been vandalising the playground ever since it was installed two years ago. The equipment is now almost completely covered in graffiti - DIE, HATE and KILL THE KIDS are amongst their more literate efforts.  Why would somebody want to stand in a playground in the rain and shout? Answers on a postcard ...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh, that's better.  A hot bubble bath, with a cold glass of Cava Rosada and grapefruit juice, does the trick when it comes to unwinding.  Work has been mostly staring at my task list and trying to divide up the jobs into trivial, boring, interesting and impossible. Guess which ones I'm going to tackle first? I also got to chat to Creepy on IM for a bit which broke the day up nicely. I promise myself little treats for each tick on the list - get this bit of code working and you can have a mug of java and read some blogs ...  Big brother tonight will be interesting. It looks like Becki is the one to go which will be a damn shame as all Ahmed ever does is smash things up when he thinks he needs some public sympathy. Becki is a communicator and a game player, which would make her ideal for the long game - it's a real shame she wasn't in from the start instead of Emma or Kitten. As far as I can tell the public animosity is because she nominated Michelle  ... er, and that's a bad thing? Digital Spy are reporting that extra security is being brought in for the eviction tonight to ensure her safety - booing I can (just about) understand, but physically attacking somebody for playing a gameshow?  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blimey.  I was woken up this morning by the sound of rain hammering on the roof at the front of the house. Walking in the woods saw me and Barney getting soaked by large, cold, heavy raindrops blowing horizontally in the wind that was approaching gale force.  I checked the traffic news on the RAC website to see what the motorways looked like - it had changed from four reports on the list at seven o'clock to several screenfulls by ten to eight. The travel bulletin on the wireless was reporting an accident southbound on the M1 at Chesterfield that had been cleared to side.  Hmmmm, I was supposed to be in Birmingham today.  I got as far as junction 30 before the heavy spray reduced visibility to less than twenty meters and the traffic started to queue. So I turned around, so I'm a wimp, so sue me ...    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's a  conundrum for regular bloggers - what do you write about when you've had a  boring day?  I've set myself a target of posting something every  day, for fear that if I miss a day my usual procrastination will take hold and  the one day will turn into a couple of days and then a week or more, and then  I'll be into fear of posting because I've not posted for so long.   However, the problem is this - I've not done much  today.   I could write about my useless postman delivering letters for next door,  and a letter for somebody who lives on a Drive rather than a Grove. I could  write about my tour around my regular blogs this morning when I was drinking my  coffee and how I was wondering why Creepy hadn't updated since Friday but that  I'd seen her on instant messenger and in Emma Kennedy's guestbook so I wasn't  too worried. I could even write about how much I detest the Wallchart report  writer, and how it completely fubar'd the headings on a report I was working on  when I did an export to Excel. How about how glad I was that the local gang of  chavs weren't in the woods tonight shouting at each other? I've not done an  update on Big Brother recently, but that's mainly because I can't believe that  Jason and Victor haven't been nominated when the harem had a free run at them  this week, and I will be disappointed if Becki goes on Friday.  So, what do I do? Just pontificate for a bit, and  see if inspiration (or anything interesting) strikes me tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A meeting in Bourne End today, so an early start is the order of the day. The wood is a very different place at six o'clock in the morning. It's much quieter, with the distant rumble of the M1 conspicuous by its absence and a different chorus of bird song filtering between the trees.  I stood and watched a chaffinch on a low branch a meter or two away from the path for a minute or two, before it took fright and flew away. Coming back down from the top of the woods, a couple of squirrels were sat in the middle of the path, confident that Barney was safely on his lead.   The final early morning denizen was encountered just as we were leaving the woods. A middle aged man, with a spaniel trotting along behind him, was walking along shaving with an electric razor.   Strange ...  So, a three and half hour drive to Bourne End. The M40 is a very different motorway to the M1. I was cruising comfortably, somewhere around 70 miles an hour, and I was passed by a constant stream of Beemers and Mercs all doing well over a ton with no police in sight. Similar behaviour anywhere else would result in the swift appearance of a flashing blue light in the rear view mirror.  The meeting is to look again at a contracts management system that one of our group companies is flogging, so it is now the preferred option for our inhouse systems. I'm not sure quite how well the client server architecture will scale to our WAN - there was talk of getting every body to enter timesheets and expense claims through a browser tool, but the demo that we saw crashed several times and was missing a lot of detail that we need.  I've got a bad feeling about this one ...  I got taken out for lunch at a rather nice pub called the Bounty down by the Thames. It can only be reached on foot, via the bridge that runs alongside the railway bridge and along the tow path or by boat. We were sat out in the sunshine watching geese and ducks skimming along the river, and cruisers and narrow boats pootling up and down.  Another three and half hour journey home, so I reckon a bottle of wine from Tesco's is called for, and true to form just as I pick up my glass of Chardonnay I notice a black fly ... ironic, don't you think?  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I get SFX magazine on subscription. It's a bit fan boyish, but  on the whole it's ideal for those moments of quiet reflection in the smallest  room of the house. For the current issue the publishers have decided to bundle  it in with two free magazine - a crappy Playstation magazine (I don't have a  PS2, thank you very much) and a sub literate film review thing. This bulked the  package up to the size of a phone directory, and still the postman decided to  try hammering it through the letter box, ripping the front cover and the first  six pages of SFX (no, not the PS2 and film ones - they were pristine).  Is  it worth complaining? Probably not, but I will do so if only to vent my  irritation.  Alicia was due at the dentist's this lunchtime and the Tesco  van, booked for&nbsp; the slot from 10:00 am - 12:00 pm turned up with ten  minutes to go. Just time to pack the frozen stuff, jump in the car, find that  the cd I'd tried to write this morning hadn't worked properly, drive 5 miles to  Alicia's school, pick her up, field a call on the hands free from Alicia's  mother wondering where we were, drive through Hillsborough, get diverted round  the long way onto the A61 by road works, drive to the dentist's, find somewhere  to park and get to the reception desk only being five minutes late. Not bad  going, but by the time I got home my officially designated lunch hour was nearly  over.         
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A rainy sunday afternoon with nothing on the telly but tennis, so a trip to the cinema to Shrek 2 was the order of the day. It was a step up from the first film with a plot line that made some serious points about the nature of identity and conforming to people's expectations to find acceptance. Is there a shortcut to 'happy ever after', and does such a thing even exist?  The animation was simply stunning, the voice acting spot on (with Jennifer Saunders standing out as the Fairy Godmother) and of course there were plenty of gags that went over the heads of the kiddies with parodies of Alien, From Here to Eternity and Flashdance for the adults to chuckle knowingly at. Go see it now!  The sun's out now, so it could well be time to take Barney the wonderdog for a walk before it starts raining again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We were browsing in PC World looking for a new server this afternoon - well, to be honest looking at TFT screens with a view to buying one more cheaply on line somewhere, but we couldn't resist buying something to take home. Jan found a wireless optical mouse for her laptop and a search through bargain corner found this for me - a  urlLink Hauppauge Media MVP    I plugged it into the network, hooked a scart cable into the TV and installed a bit of software on the server upstairs and in less than five minutes I was watching MPEG files on the server through the tv with a remote control from the sofa. It also plays MP3s and does slideshows of JPGS. Picture quality via the RGB scart is very good and there is a breakout audio connection to play the sound via an amplifier. This is very cool bit of kit.    There is a beta version of the server software that will play divx files directly, but our current server is not quite fast enough to cope with it. We'll be getting a new machine shortly, but in the meantime it is no great hassle to convert the files for playback.   The best bit about it? PC World were selling them for £50. Recommended if you have a home network and want to access media files through your tv.   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let joy be unconfined -  urlLink weebl  has a new  urlLink toon     
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink        I just thought that I'd try out the new blogger editor and upload a picture of Barney on his sofa ... here we go. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had another disturbed night last night. I was having a classic anxiety dream of being at University but not knowing what my timetable was, or where to get any information about what I should be doing. In my dream I was sharing a flat with Shell from Big Brother who was being an insufferable girly swat who just kept telling me I should have been more organised and written down my timetable in a planner or something at the start of term. Where's the Dreamweaver Lady B when she's needed - she seems to have gone AWOL from  urlLink Emma Kennedy's guestbook  again ...  So, I was up and about at six o'clock this morning in case anybody was wondering why I was posting comments so early. I fed Biddy and was wondering where Frank was until I opened Alicia's bedroom door and found him complaining bitterly. He had been stuck in there all night and had widdled on Alicia's chair where she had dumped her school sweatshirt. Way to go Frank ...   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apparently, for Michelle, Stu being voted out on Friday would be the worst thing that could happen for her ...  Vote Stu out - you know it makes sense!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blimey, I'm tired tonight. I've not been sleeping particularly well recently and it has started catching up on me. Alicia was here last night and needed crow-barring out of bed this morning which didn't make for a stress free start to the day.   However, I managed to drop Alicia off at the bus stop, negotiate the roadworks that were stationed at a tee-junction on the way blocking traffic from three directions at once and get onto the M1 for half-past eight. The roads were clear and I caught up time pretty well getting to Dudley for 10:25 in the end - not bad going on the whole.  A busy day though, with lots of niggly changes to templates and trying to solve a persistant excel crashing problem by applying a 50MB service pack (it didn't cure it). As I left, just in time to hit the traffic on the two lots of roadworks on the M6, the rain clouds started to look threatening. By the time I reached the M1 the rain was pelting down and the traffic ground to a halt, crawling all the way from junction 23 to past Chesterfield.   I got home at seven o'clock to be greeted by a frantic Barney, eager for his evening walkies. The rain had just cleared, and the woods were clean, green and chav free tonight.   So, I'm just watching Big Brother with a glass of Greene King IPA which I think will send me off to the land of nod in short order. Good night one and all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apparently the BNP is a violent racist organisation - who'd have thought it, eh? Will the BBC be undertaking an undercover investigation into the religious convictions of the Pope next? ;-)  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As an addendum to Monday's rant about my car the garage decided that they were going to spend the whole day playing telephone ping pong with the leasing company and Renault trying to decide who was going to stump up for the replacement valves on my car. I called them at 4:30, confidently expecting the work to have been done, only to find out that they hadn't actually started it yet.  "My colleague is on the phone to Renault as we speak, sir" I was assured.  "You're not actually going to get this work done by half past five, are you?"  "Well, er, I'm not sure"  Hmmmmm .....  They did actually finish it this morning, apologise for the delay, deliver it back and have it cleaned so I can't grumble overmuch. Just a pain in the proverbials I suppose, and it means I really need to go to Dudley tommorrow. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to admit that  urlLink this story  from the BBC news of a man shooting himself in the knackers when drunk made me chuckle more than somewhat. He sounds like a possible candidate for the  urlLink Darwin awards  as well ...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is really just an exercise in geekery but I couldn't resist it. I've just been to drop off my car at the garage and I'm currently on the bus back to Chapeltown from the center of Sheffield. I'm writing this on my visor palmtop and making respectable progress with the grafiti handwriting software. I usually just use it for reading documents and playing solitaire on the loo but I've got half an hour to kill, so what the heck.  I do miss the keyboard on my old psion revo though - I'd still be using it if it had a usb cable connector and reliable sync software. The palmtop before that was my favorite - the HP200LX was a genuine PC that would run just about any bit of dos software that didn't need more than CGA graphics and would just fit in your pocket. The built in apps ran from the rom and as well as the usual pda stuff there was a full implementation of Lotus 123 - arguably the best pre windows spreadsheet. It also had an infrared port and a pcmia slot for a modem, and  would run for weeks on a set of AA batteries. Mine must have been getting on for being nine or ten years old when it conked. *sniff*  Surely there must be a market for a handheld pc, with wi-fi connectivity, decent battery life and a usable keyboard? I'd buy one for a start.   Nearly home now. I'm not actually going to try and send this via infrared and my phone so I'll just sync it to my laptop. Here we go ...  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An early start this morning, to drop Alicia off at her mums and go to the dentist. It's Jamie's turn with the cold bug that has jumped from Jan to Alicia, and has now left him with a raging sore throat, so he's coming with me as well.  As I started the car the tyre pressure warning lights started flashing on all four tyres. That's odd, I thought, although the warning light switched off after a minute or so. Must check them when I get back.  The dentist only took a couple of minutes, although I've got to go back for a filling at the end of August - first one in four or five years I think. "Ring me if the pain becomes unbearable and we'll do it sooner if necessary" says the dentist. Hmmm, it's just a twinge if I bit on it too hard at the moment, so I'll live with it.  The warning light starts flashing again. Ok, I get the message, I'll check the tyres when I get home.  Except I can't. I had four replacement tyres a couple of months ago, and the metal valve caps have been screwed on so tightly that I can't get them off by hand. I get a small spanner, and the first one comes off ok. Tyre pressure is ok, so go to the next one.  Crack. Oh shit. The valve cap has completely stuck and in trying to loosen it the body of the valve has cracked and the tyre deflated in about twenty seconds flat (ho, ho - do you see what I did there?)  The remaining two tyres are the same, although the valves are still intact on those I get the feeling that they will deflate if I look at them in a funny way.  Call the leasing company.   "You need to call the RAC"  Call the RAC.  "Your car is under warranty - it's the AA that you need for that"  Call the AA.  "We'll send somebody out, although you need to call the tyre company"  Call the tyre company.  "It needs dealer fitted tyre pressure sensors"  Call the leasing company.  "We'll call the dealer and see what they can do"  The leasing company call back and tell me to call the dealer.  "We haven't got the parts in stock, but we might be able to get them for you. Can you call back later?"  Fine, just what I need today.  Taurus, Interstate 76 poetry:  "It's a high pitched sound Hot rubber eternally pressing against a blackened pavement A wheel is forever A car is infinity times four"  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up early this morning and after going to the loo and getting a drink of water I drifted off back to sleep.  In my dream I was in an office. I got talking to a lady who looked like Annie from  urlLink The Smoking Room  about time management systems. She was using a system that I had seen as a possible add-on to our Wallchart system and I asked her about the sort of reports it could produce. Her screen was tiny - no more than four or five inches across and I couldn't focus on it, so I asked her to print a copy for me to look at.  At the other end of the office were a couple of laser printers and a large line printer. I looked to see which printer the report was going to come off of and a green light started to flash on the printer in the corner behind the line printer. As I squeezed past the line printer chuntered into life, but the fan fold paper slipped and jammed with the top sheet tearing sideways into the mechanism.  Somebody that looked like Sally (also from The Smoking Room) came in for the print and started getting angry, so I offered to unjam the printer as it was similar to an old C-Itoh printer that I had used. I opened the case and tried to collect the torn bits of paper, being acutely aware of the smell of paper dust and ink.  As I delved further into the mechanism I felt more and more lethargic - the sun was shining through the windows and it was a hot morning. My eyes started to close and I lay down on the boxes of paper under the printer to go to sleep.  I was aware of somebody saying that I couldn't go to sleep there as a large bumble bee had flown in through the window and I would be stung if I didn't move. I was aware of the bee flying very close to my face but I could not move - I was paralysed. I felt as if I was being suffocated by the heat and the smell of the paper dust and I realised that I had to wake up somehow.  I struggled for a while, starting to panic, and then I pinched my forearm in effort to try and escape. I could feel my eyes opening slowly and I surfaced from the dreamworld, lifting my face from the pillow that had been obstructing my breathing. I had a strange moment of transition from sleep to wakefulness, not being entirely sure of where I was, but that passed and I could breath once more.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Chocolates, alcohol, cards (with an "I'm 39" badge from my brother)  and a new game for my xbox. Excellent! Not even an itchy leg and a miserable ex is going to spoil my day.   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My poorly leg
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Warning - this post contains strong language.    Bastard.    My leg hurts. The cut in my groin gives me a sharp, stabbing pain if I move too quickly. The top of my thigh is bruised and feels like I've been kicked by a horse. Worst of all is the itching.    Fecking. Bastard. Sod.    It feels as if I've got an army of ants dancing a samba up and down my leg. I guess that the hairs must be growing back under the sticking plaster or something, but it is driving me absolutely mental. It's a nice sunny day outside, but that just means that my leg is going to be sweaty which will make it itch all the more. I've got to wait until Monday until I can see the nurse to have it off - ooh, er, missus, fnar fnar.    Godamn son of a bitch.    And it's my birthday tomorrow.    Arse.    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I are been mostly reading " urlLink Living in the box " by Dean O'Loughlin, who with a trace of somewhat justifiable bitterness describes himself as "the boring one from Big Brother 2". It is a detailed, although largely superficial, account of his experience of appearing on Big Brother from the initial application, through the selection process, his time in the house and a brief coda of his fifteen minutes of fame after being evicted. He is currently running a company making  urlLink teabag bins  - make of that what you will.     The book is most interesting when he contrasts how he perceived events in the house to how they were portrayed by the producers when edited down to a half hour nightly show and subsequently reported in the tabloids. The best example of this is probably one housemates cocaine problem which was reduced to the headline "I'm forever snorting - Bubble".     The subtitle to the book is "An adventure in reality TV" and the most telling paragraph is this one:     Safe TV      And where reality TV really scores big time in the entertainment stakes is that we know we are watching a controlled environment, where nothing genuinely bad is going to happen. We can enjoy the carnage without feeling guilty. No matter how heated the argument or how impending the danger we know there is always a camera crew there, or a director, or someone in charge. We are generally not so entertained when watching the harsher versions of reality TV such as the news. We don't enjoy watching people being shot dead or jumping from burning towers for real. That's not nice at all. We want our reality controlled and tempered and served to us in handy twenty-four minute slots on concurrent nights at nine. We want to see page three girls in the jungle, bank managers on a desert island and the bloke next door moaning about pop music. And the public gets what the public wants. At the end of the day if we didn't want it then it wouldn't exist, and that tells you more about our society than it does about anything else.      The current series of Big Brother has been the most interesting one for me, mainly because most of the participants are very aware of what they are doing and are playing it as a game. You could sum the whole series up with the image of Michelle and Emma watching the other housemates from the bedsit, whilst we were watching them.                
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A picture generated by  urlLink typoGenerator 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel rough today. I think when I got home yesterday I must have still had some anaesthetic floating round my system that wore off at around six o'clock. I got up to go to the loo and started shivering with my teeth chattering, even though the sun was shining. I had to wrap a blanket round myself for the rest of the night and cautiously allow Biddy on to my lap as a sort of feline hot water bottle.    Frank was stalking a mouse in the dining room. If I had been feeling a bit more mobile I would have tried to rescue it and put it out in the field, but all I could do was shut the door and let him get on with it. I found the hind quarters neatly deposited on the door mat this morning and Frank looked very please with himself.    I changed the dressing on my groin (the pads look suspiciously like miniature sanitary towels), had a not very successful strip wash (I've got some weird yellow disinfectant stuff on me that has now stained my flannel) and tottered out of the house for a walk.    It was slow going, to say the least. Each step was accompanied by an soto voce  urlLink expletive  but I made it to the woods and back in one piece, and Barney seemed happy at least. I found two messages on my mobile - one from work when they tried to call me in the middle of my operation yesterday, and a bizarre text message from a number I didn't recognize "Bab i dont what you to hurt me bab xxx". Answers on a postcard ...   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Consciousness.    I woke up with a dull ache in my leg and a sore throat. The recovery room was a blur until the nurse found my specs for me but I slowly started to come round. There seemed to be no time between the anaesthetic being administered and the moment I awoke, but according to the clock an hour and a half had passed.    I had a few sips of water from the jug and had a look under the sheets. My entire leg was bandaged in what looked like pink sticking plaster from ankle to thigh, I had a small incision in my groin covered with a gauze and my paper pants had been cut away. So much for dignity.    The nurse brought me a cup of tea and two slices of hot, buttered toast. It was, quite possibly, the nicest toast I've ever eaten.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      10:25 and I'm on the trolley. The anaethetist puts a canula (hey - I've watched  urlLink Holby City , and I know the jargon) in the back of my left hand whilst the nurse attaches pads and wires to my chest. She takes my glasses off my face and the world disolves into a blur. A mask goes over my face and I feel a brief moment of claustrophobia before the anaesthetic kicks in.   Oblivion.    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Big brother nominations this week. Jason's game plan has crumbled and I don't think that he has the nous to change his strategy at this stage. Victor, perhaps surprisingly, has turned out to be a lot smarter and is working on his relationship with Michelle. Will she turn out to be a jungle kitten in the end game? Victor has also covered his back in the wedding task by taking the groom role to Shell's bride.   This week, I expect Jason to be a cert for nomination with Dan as his likely partner. Out of those two, Jason is doomed but at least he should be able to give a more coherant eviction interview with Davina than Ahmed did last Friday.   9:40 now - not long now I hope ...   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things are happening now. I've just got changed into a swit-swoo gown and a pair of paper pants, although my dignity is somewhat preserved by my dressing gown. I feel like Arthur Dent lost in a bewildering alien universe and desperate for a cup of tea ...   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Running narcotics and firearms into war torn anarchy systems is a risky business. My firefly class ship is looking a little bit puny compared to some of the pirates that I've met, but I've cleared 120000 credits (and picked up a criminal record) so I think it is time to find a high tech planet, get some decent shields and a military laser, and find a wormhole to the other side of the galaxy so I can do a bit of bounty hunting and raise my profile from 'mostly harmless'.   Time to see the surgeon. He explains the procedure to me again (that makes five times now) and marks the vein he is doing with a permanent marker. I sign the form and ask about the bit that gives consent for 'any other procedures that may be necessary'. Apparently there aren't any, so hopefully that means they won't be whipping off my leg without my say so.   Back to the waiting room again ...   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bev Stokes day surgery unit is a bright, modern place marred only by the tv in the corner of the waiting room permanently tuned to Trisha. I've just had my details checked by the reception nurse and been tagged with a plastic id bracelet, and the anaethetist has explained the procedure to me again. I'm second on the list this morning, which means I'm going to be sat here till 10 o'clock with only the Reader's Digest for company. I've got my palm though, so a game of  urlLink Space Trader  looks to be my best option for whiling away the next couple of hours.    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's seven o'clock in the morning and we're just about to set off for the hospital. Another disturbed night, but that's not really unexpected. It was hot and humid, and I kept waking up to look at the clock before drifting back to sleep with dreams of ominous rumbling black dice with red spots.    I was up at a quarter to six - a cup of black java on an empty stomach is bracing to say the least, and a walk in the woods with Barney brought me round a bit.    OK, time to set off .... 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess the reason for my disturbed sleep of recent weeks is fairly obvious. No, it's not my impending trip in  urlLink Emma Kennedy's car  - although somewhat bizarrely I've had vivid dreams about three different people from the  urlLink Smoking Room  (last night I was talking to Selina Griffiths who plays Janet the PA). It's the operation I'm having on my leg tomorrow.    Yes, I know it's minor and routine and nothing to worry about. My rational side is perfectly happy with all of that. It's the loss of conciousness and control that scares me. I remember seeing Alicia having an aneasthetic when she was two or three and the transition from being awake to being unconcious took just a few seconds and it was deeply disturbing with little resemblance to the normal process of falling asleep.    On the plus side, I'm looking forward to two weeks of playing video games, ignoring calls from work, feeling sorry for myself ... oh, and I've got my birthday somewhere in the middle of it all as well.   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Banraggum is one of the classical  urlLink entrances to hell . An attempt by Pope Gregory to close it resulted in a temporal backlash that erased 11 days from history. Approach with caution and a big stick.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    What on earth is this bug? Answers on a postcard ...
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is cool beer so nice? Why don't elasticated stockings stay up? What is that weird thing that has just landed on the sofa next to me?
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The big sky
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, maybe not. I'm sat in the lounge with the patio doors wide open, the fan providing a cooling breeze and a grapefruit and cava at my side. Life doesn't get any better than this ... :-)  Oh, and Michelle  has  to go tonight. Vote early. Vote often. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A day out at Whipsnade Zoo today. It was a touch on the pricey side (£42.00 for a family ticket and another £3.00 for parking), and some of the animals were hiding (which was not really surprising given the hot weather) but on the whole we had an excellent time. Whipsnade is a well spread out zoo, with a lot of the animals in large and varied paddocks. You can take your car in, but there is a free bus that runs around the periphery which is probably easier than trying to park at each viewing point. I know that there are good arguments against keeping animals in captivity, but I am happy to support the conservation and research work that the zoos undertake.   Whipsnade is set high up on the downs and at lunch time we had our picnic in a shady spot with a view that stretched uninterupted to the far horizon with nothing but gliders swooping and whirling in the way. Absolutely spectacular.  The highlights of the day were seeing the giraffes - something about them is utterly unlike just about every other animal that I can think of. Not just their extraordinary size but their alien faces and demeanour seem to set them apart. The bald eagle free flying display was spectacular, even more so given the bird's break for a cooler vantage point on top of a nearby chimney. Finally, we saw some newly hatched chameleons that were less than a centimeter long and looked like intricate models until their tiny eyes started swivelling around.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cuddly!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A curiously alien giraffe
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    An impressive wing span
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Apache the bald eagle makes a break for freedom ...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's blog can be found over  urlLink here  ... :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blogging over the next couple of days may be sporadic because I am now down at my Mum and Dad's house in Harpenden. The drive down was as good as could be expected, with just the occasional twinge in my leg on changing gear. The 140 miles or so were covered in just over two hours making the average speed just about legal ... ok, so the two hours included a couple of slow stretches and a couple of miles through a 30mph limit at either end, but we won't mention those.  As is usual, my mum was in a bit of tizz but still managed to provide macaroni cheese, baked potatoes, cold cuts of lamb, salad and grated cheese - I was stuffed, and by half past nine my eyelids were drooping. I explained exactly who Emma Kennedy was for the umpteenth time and then headed upstairs for bed.  Tomorrows blog will be a little bit unusual, but you'll just have to wait and see for that one ... 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Wifi under the pergola
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From  urlLink Bilge Flaps   1. Leave a comment on my blog saying you want to be interviewed. 2. I will respond and ask you five questions. 3. You'll update your blog with my five questions, and your five answers. 4. You'll include this explanation. 5. You'll ask other people five questions when they want to be interviewed.  My interview is as follows:  1. What period in your life were you the most happy and why?  Now, without a shadow of a doubt. My childhood and adolescence were a time of fairly insular loneliness, in my twenties I was mixed up with a weird, abusive cult (it's a long story) and in my early thirties my marriage went to hell in a handcart. Now I have a secure, loving relationship with somebody who understands who I am, I have two fantastic kids, a barking mad dog and two cats, and more computing power than I can shake a stick at.  2. If you had to be a teletubby, which one would you be and why?  The little red one.   3. Where do you want to be in five years (hey it was a good question so i'm repeating it)?  To misquote Laurie Anderson, paradise is exactly like where you are right now, only much, much better. That will do me.  4. Out of all the bloggers, who would you most want to shag and why?  Hmmm, that's a tricky question. I honestly can't imagine having sex with anyone but Jan, but if pushed I would like to cuddle Creepy Lesbo because I think she could do with it at the moment.  5. What do you most miss when your daughter is away from you for a long time(i.e. holiday)?   Listening to the radio in the car when I'm driving her somewhere and setting the world to rights. Most of the time when she's at home she's squirreled away on her computer or is listening to her mp3 player, but the drive to school in the mornings is fifteen minutes of uninterupted time together to talk about stuff, serious and otherwise.  Anyone else want to have a go?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Caloo calay, oh frabjous day - the bandage from hell is gone, as well most of the hair on my leg. I can now see the places where I was cut and the strange little marks where they pulled the vein out in a Clive Barker version of join the dots. It was a strange mixture of extreme pain and blessed relief when it stopped.  The bandage has been replaced with a stocking - I now feel like  urlLink Belle de Jour  and to complete the picture I am currently blogging via wifi from a table under the flower decked pergola with a nice glass of white wine. The best bit of the day was sinking into a hot bubble bath to wash  away all of the surgical disinfectant, bits of plaster and dried on detritus of the last week.  In other news, I took Alicia to the dentist for a check up on her brace. No problems, and she's to go back in three months time for another check up. Hardly worth starting world war three for, was it?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Viewers of a nervous disposition look away now ...
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jamie : "I think I might try being a necromancer"
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the Hauppauge MVP kept crashing and losing it's network settings so it went back in the box. They didn't have another one in stock, so we took the refund. A bit of a pity, but I'll probably get a replacement or something similar at some point. Sony do a similar sort of wireless media server so that's a possibility.    Anyway, the replacement toy was a  urlLink Linksys Wireless Gateway  and a pair of wireless network adaptors for our laptops. It's an absolute doddle to set up and is noticeably faster than connecting through another machine with a USB ADSL modem and internet connection sharing. I can get a decent connection speed anywhere in the house - 54Mbs in the lounge and it only drops to to 12 MBs upstairs in the bedroom at the furthest point away from the router.   I still need to get to grips with some of the firewall settings to get my VPN connection to the office working properly, but I'll email one of the techies next week to see if they know what to do.   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alicia has been on holiday for a week. When her mother told me they were going, I asked when they would be coming back.      "Probably on the Saturday of your birthday, but we should be able to drop her off on the way back"    Fast forward to yesterday. I had a text from Alicia wishing me a happy birthday and I sent one back saying I was looking forward to seeing her and that we were ordering from Pizza Hut for my birthday treat.  A few minutes later Alicia called having had a massive row with her mother and her mother's boyfriend Matt about when she was being dropped off with the upshot that they weren't going to drop her off.    Hmmm.  You do know I can't drive at the moment? Anyway, it's not a problem because Alicia can get the bus or Jan can pick her up. Why the need for a row rather than just saying that Matt didn't feel like driving over to our house ?    Anyway, later on we've been out to Meadowhall spending some money and at four o'clock Alicia calls to say that she's back and can we pick her up? It's a bit out of our way, but not a major problem. When we get there, Alicia's mum is obviously in a bad mood and starts to have a go at me about taking Alicia to the dentist on Monday.  Not, "Happy Birthday" or "How's your leg?" but how I only like the nice side of parenting.  I didn't feel like arguing, but she forgets that I've got Jamie to look after as well, I was the one who ferried Alicia back and forth for six years before they got a car, and actually I took Alicia to the dental hospital for her last appointment and took time off work to do it as well.      She really does make a profession out of being spiteful for the sake of it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Strawberry fields forever ...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Best of friends
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A dog and his boy
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's nearly over.   Seventy one days of screeching, fighting, plotting, backbiting and bizarre nudity (remember the cake bras?) are drawing to a close. This has been a fascinating series for me, mostly because of the overt game playing and the diverse set of characters thrown into the melting pot.   In retrospect there were a lot of missed opportunities. Evil Big Brother went soft after the debacle of fight night, and only really reappeared in the last two weeks when the numbers had thinned out somewhat. The bedsit idea was a great one, but sadly underused. Imagine if every evicted housemate had been sent to the bedsit for a week before coming out of the house and given the opportunity to automatically put someone up for eviction - that could have been very interesting ... :-) Playing the nominations back was a similarly good twist, but it should have happened before the final public nomination session this week. The live challenge and the reward room were also absent this year - the saturday show turned into a bit of flop.  So, out of the remaining housemates it seems that Nadia is the favourite to win. Fair play to her really - it was an incredibly gutsy thing to do. Jason has played the game well all the way through, and was lucky not to have been voted out earlier. Dan is a strange character and probably the most guarded of the remaining four - what has happened to his promise to walk out if he got to the last week? Finally, Shell - terribly nice girl is probably all you can say about her.  What now? Well, Jan is busy making a Sims Big Brother house complete with most of the housemates and special guest visitors including Emma Kennedy and Richard Herring ... I'll let you know when she gets it all working.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Crikey, it's muggy tonight. The atmosphere is really heavy (man) and oppressive, and I feel tired, sweaty and headachy.   I walked into Leeds at lunchtime and the weather changed from a bit overcast to a light shower, to a tropical downpour and then to a blistering humidity not far short of getting into a sauna. I overdid the brisk walking and pulled a calf muscle in my dodgy leg which left me limping on the way back to the office.   urlLink  Pret a Manger  have changed the design of their  urlLink vegetable sushi  - you now get 12 mini rolls rather than 9 mini rolls and two large ones, and they no longer have the mushroom fillings. On the plus side they are slightly cheaper, and you get some really nifty extending chop sticks. Bizarrely enough, it is marked as not being suitable for pregnant women - does the wasabi bring on premature labour or something?  I wish this weather would break ...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This posting is a community experiment that tests how a meme, represented by this blog posting, spreads across blogspace, physical space and time. It will help to show how ideas travel across blogs in space and time and how blogs are connected. It may also help to show which blogs (and aggregation sites) are most influential in the propagation of memes. The dataset from this experiment will be public, and can be located via Google (or Technorati) by doing a search for the GUID for this meme (below).  Please join the test by adding your blog (see instructions, below) and inviting your friends to participatethe more the better. The data from this test will be public and open; others may use it to visualize and study the connectedness of blogspace and the propagation of memes across blogs.  The GUID for this experiment is:  as098398298250swg9e98929872525389t9987898tq98wteqtgaq62010920352598gawst  The above GUID enables anyone to easily search Google or other search engines for all blogs that participate in this experiment, once they have indexed the sites that participate, which may take several days or weeks. To locate the full data set, just search for any sites that contain this GUID.  Anyone is free to analyze the data of this experiment. Please publicize your analysis of the data, and/or any comments by adding comments onto the original post (see URL above). (Note: it would be interesting to see a geographic map or a temporal animation, as well as a social network map of the propagation of this meme.)  INSTRUCTIONS  To add your blog to this experiment, copy this entire posting to your blog, and then answer the questions below, substituting your own information, below, where appropriate. Other than answering the questions below, please do not alter the information, layout or format of this post in order to preserve the integrity of the data in this experiment (this will make it easier for searchers and automated bots to find and analyze the results later).  REQUIRED FIELDS (Note: Replace the answers below with your own answers)  (1) I found this experiment at URL: http://billyworld.typepad.com/  (2) I found it via Newsreader Software or Browsing the Web or Searching the Web or An E-Mail Message: browsing the web (trawling through my blogroll)  (3) I posted this experiment at URL: http://www.planethopkins.com/blog  (4) I posted this on date (day/month/year): 05/08/04  (5) I posted this at time (24 hour time): 19:08  (6) My posting location is (city, state, country): sheffield, s yorks, uk  OPTIONAL SURVEY FIELDS:  (7) My blog is hosted by: me  (8) My age is: 39  (9) My gender is: bloke  (10) My occupation is: geek  (11) I use the following RSS/Atom reader software: feedreader  (12) I use the following software to post to my blog: blogger  (13) I have been blogging since (day, month, year): 01/09/2002  (14) My web browser is: firefox  (15) My operating systems are: windows xp  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jamie in his new Lord of the Rings outfit
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's Jamie's eighth birthday today and he's had a fine time. A trip to the Earth Center in Doncaster had to be postponed due to the bad weather, but we've been out to Brewster Bear's for lunch and he's been playing Lord of the Rings on xbox with his friend Charlie all afternoon. It's a shame Alicia couldn't be here, but she is  urlLink thinking  of him which is really sweet. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A bit of digging around turned up an article on the Microsoft support database and the solution was to update the firmware on the router to 1.02.01 (scary but easy) and then set up port forwarding for ports 47 and 1723 to my laptop. I've been connected for an hour and sent/received 300K/1.2Mb - bandwidth issues? What bandwidth issues?  As a supposedly high tech company, we don't seem to be making a huge effort to get people to work from home. An adsl router and a bit of ethernet cable will connect any of the company laptops at a reasonable enough speed to do most things at the same speed that you could in the office, and probably get more productive time from people if they aren't driving for an hour and half each day. The current habit seems to be for people to work in the office most of the time and lock their laptops in a safe overnight.   Go figure.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Music for the trip to Brum today was the 1995 double cd Axis Mutatis by the Shaman, and  more specifically the second ambient bonus cd Arbor Bona Arbor Mala (which I think translates as Good Tree Bad Tree). I first heard a thirty second clip of this on a William Latham organic art screen saver eight or nine years ago and it buzzed around in my head for ages until I finally tracked down a special double cassette version of the album. I've converted it to mp3s and now finally have a cd to play in the car which is just about perfect for driving under ominous skies ...  Work was business as usual, except the big boss has got a bee in his bonnet about implementing a browser front end for a time sheet system. Our consultancy division has promised to write something in two weeks which I find difficult to believe. This application is going to be internet facing so it has to sit on the other side of the firewall and syncronise both ways with contract and personnel details, and allow work group based authorization of timesheets. It just isn't going to happen, I know it now - the last time I saw a demo of their system it crashed running off a IIS server on a local pc with one user. How is it going to cope with several hundred people updating their timesheets every week? 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The last day of my two weeks sick leave and appropriately enough the sky has turned a rather ominous shade of grey. Alicia is at her mother's house for a whole three days (unless she decides to come back on the bus sooner) - it will be strange without her as she's been with us for nine days in a row. I'm off to Birmingham tomorrow as well, so it feels like things are getting back to the usual routine.  I still can't get my VPN connection to work via the router, and the IT manager was a bit sniffy when I asked him what settings to use. "We're thinking about stopping the VPN service because of bandwidth issues" he said. I transfer maybe 20 or 30 Mb of data in a day - hardly a massive overhead. If a lot of people are using it, then there is obviously a need for it. I am saving the company the cost of providing an ISDN connection (which would be painfully slow in any case) and the security would be pretty robust. To make it even more annoying, I had an urgent problem to resolve last week (when I was supposedly off sick) and in dialling up a 56K connection without a firewall got hit by a worm on my work laptop. At a pinch I can revert to our ADSL/ICS solution for days when I'm at home but it is a bit frustrating and awkward.  Anyone got a Microsoft VPN connection working through a Linksys WAG54G router?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a while since I reinstalled everything on this laptop so I decided to run through the complete windows update to pick up the cumulative security patches. Big mistake. It took an hour or more to download and install everything, and all looked to be fine until my laptop started to randomly lock solid requiring a hard reboot. Not even a windows error to show what the source of the problem might be but a complete freeze.  Bum.  So, I've had to uninstall all of the updates and start again one at a time ... fun fun fun.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As if to  demonstrate that it is capable of cranking out every possible type of climate in  the space of a week the weather turned it's hand to fog this morning. The garden  was&nbsp;draped with cobwebs, bejewelled with droplets of dew. A heavy bank of  mist shrouded the woods curling through the trees and muffling the usual bird  song. It was eerie but more importantly deliciously cool after the humidity of  recent days.  By the time I got onto the motorway the fog had  lifted although some numpties stubbornly kept their fog lights illuminated long  after the last of the warning signs had been switched off. The threat of a rogue  fog bank is sufficient to make them light up their car like a Christmas tree but  apparently not dangerous enough to slow down from their usual 90 miles an  hour.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Crikey. That's the heaviest rain I've seen in a long while. The field was waterlogged, the stream had changed from a dried up creek to a torrent in full spate and a quick turn around the woods was enough to leave both man and dog rather wet.  I was supposed to be going to Birmingham today but the now traditional accident at Chesterfield left the M1 backed up for ten miles again, so I'm going tomorrow. I still feel as if I'm in time off mode and I need to sort out my list of priorities. I've also got another meeting on Friday with the maintenance resellers to sort out a recurring invoice system and the agenda looks ominous. Interesting times ... 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On entry to the house Simbrother treated the housemates to a welcome party complete with a fully stocked buffet table. However they ignored the food provided and Ahmed's attempts at cooking a meal resulted in a kitchen fire. He hasn't cooked since.  Day 2 saw the first task with a painting challenge for the housemates. The task was passed successfully with the reward being a karaoke stage. Stuart's attempts at singing proved less than popular with some of the other housemates.  Day 4 in the Simbrother house. Michelle and Stuart have formed a close relationship and have now laid claim to the only double bed in the house. Similarly Nadia and Victor are growing closer together as they share back rubs although this has had the effect of alienating Victor from the rest of the group. Daniel and Jason have kissed, although Daniel seems to be doing most of the chasing.  Day 7. The first nominations are in with Stuart receiving 5 votes and Victor 3 votes. Who goes - you decide ... 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "My first nomo is Stuart. Defo! He just follows Michelle round like puppy dog.  Totally pathetic.  And the second is Victor.  He is such a bore!  Absolutely."
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Oh no!  Even Michelle can't stand the pain.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    And she likes it
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "My first nomination has to be Stuart.  If I can't have him, that Michelle isn't going to either."
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "My first nomination is for Stuart.  It's making my skin crawl watching him canoodling with his  love interest.  Which brings me to my next nomination which will have to be Michelle.  Stop the squelching, purlease!"
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's chucking it down with rain here at the moment, but the heat hasn't really abated so it is still rather humid. The woods tonight were a little like a tropical rainforest with rain pattering through the foliage, but unfortunately the local gang of neds had chosen tonight to stand in the downpour shouting at each other again. Why do they do this? Are their lives so devoid of excitement that getting wet and making grunting noises is a preferable alternative?   Alicia update : We were looking at my phone this morning and wondering why herself hadn't rung when spookily she did. A rather brusque conversation with the upshot being that Alicia is now here all week until next Monday. Strange. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alicia's usual routine is to stay with us from Thursday night until Monday morning and then stay at her mum's house the rest of the week. It has worked pretty well for the last five or six years, with only the odd bit of 'forgotten' homework to worry about.  Last week I had a call from Alicia's mother - she has a cold and two dogs to look after, so could Alicia stay with me for more of the time next week. Ok, if that's what Alicia wants. She then said she'd ring and sort out arrangements this weekend.  It's now late on Sunday afternoon, and not a peep out of her. She hasn't rung me or even rung Alicia to see how she is. Just what is going on?   In other news, Dan is trying to kiss Jason in the shower ...
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jason and Dan by the jacuzzi
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Stuart and Michelle discussing Dan
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... but I am currently watching Michelle and Stu playing with a basketball hoop whilst Nadia takes a mudbath in Jan's SimBrother house. :-)
     
    
</post>


</Blog>