<Blog>

<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know this is going to make me sound like some kind of tree hugging, tie-die wearing, magic-dragon puffing hippie, but I want everyone to know that I love them.  I've been watching too many movies involving death lately, because I seem to be stuck on it. I've been thinking about what really happens when we die. If you're religious, you have your beliefs, but how can you be sure? I know, I fucking know aleady, it's called faith. Even with faith, you can't be sure. It's comletely possible that when we do die, absolutely nothing happens. It's scary how we can be so uncertain about something so important. I guess we don't really realize how many things we dont know anything about. Of course we wouldn't think of them often, for reasons being....we don't know anything about them. I'm getting confusing now, even to myself. I'll stop.  I seem to have a talent for stating the obvious. See, I did it again!  I've gotten sidetracked now. The point is, when I die, or when the people I love die, I want everyone to know that I love them. Knowing me, the "people I love" include anything and everything then can breathe, blink, and/or hump something.   So, what a good idea it is to post this on my blog! The fact that I am the only person who reads it will help spread the word of love around pretty fast, don't you think? Me too.  Fuck it. I love you.
      
</post>

<date>22,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      "hap·pi·ness  Pronunciation:	'ha-pi-n&s Function:	noun Date:	15th century 1 obsolete : good fortune : PROSPERITY 2 a : a state of well-being and contentment : JOY b : a pleasurable or satisfying experience 3 : FELICITY, APTNESS"   I know that everything exists. The only question is, where does it exist? In the physical world? In knowledge, or an idea, shared with others or kept to ourselves? In the cyberworld? Now I have a question. Where does happiness exist? Can we truly be happy, or do we only believe we can, making it real to us?   "...We hold these truths to be self-evident, that all men were created equal, that they are endowed by their creator with certain unalieanable rights, that among these are life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness..."  Notice how they said "the pursuit of happiness", implying that you may never actually be happy. Is there actually a point of complete happiness and bliss, a point where you believe you couldn't ask for anything more? Or is there one thing someone might want, that dominates all other things, and if that one wish was granted to that person, nothing else would matter? If this IS true, wouldn't you think that the less a person cares about, the happier they would be? The people who don't care about much are usually labeled as unhappy people. Maybe this is because their one wish is so hard to grant, that they will never reach the point of total happiness.  "Ignorance is a bliss."  The less you know, the less you want. The less you want, the greater your chances are to be happy. This way, you don't have to give up what you truly want.  Everyone wants. If you ever find someone who is entirely happy, and wouldn't change one thing about their life if they had the chance, please introduce me to them. Please.  Unless it's not worth it. Unless you figure there's no point in wanting anything but what is. But...who doesn't dream....?  Love you all. Goodnight.
      
</post>

<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have school tomorrow. High school. A place where I kiss ass six hours a day, to get the grades to go to some college, so I can get some job, so I can pay the government one third of everything I make, so they can keep the vicious cycle going. Controlling everyone and everything, so this is the only kind of life to lead in order to survive. A life so unrecognizably, carefully planned, so that the only thing left to honestly worry about is what color socks we're wearing tomorrow (I prefer white). Sounds like a plan. I love it. Don't ask me why.
      
</post>

<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I remember being told so many times when I was little: If someone called and my parents weren't home, I wasn't supposed to tell them that. I was expected to say "He/she/they can't come to the phone right now. May I take a message?". This drilled into my head the impression that if anyone did call for my parents while they weren't home, they were hiding in the bush out front, waiting for the cue to come kidnap me.   Whenever my mom or dad had to leave the house, I sat in the front window waving until I couldn't see their car anymore. I think they thought it was because I couldn't bare to see them leave, but I was actually waiting for my kidnapper to pop out of the bushes.  I don't remember when I stopped waving. 
      
</post>

<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've come across two blogs I've fallen in love with recently. queserasera.blogspot.com and sourmash.blogspot.com. People like this, who can inspire me and make me fall out of my chair laughing four times in one sentence, deserve some kind of recognition. Thank ya guys.
      
</post>

<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      WTF. What's wrong with me? Seriously.....I'm confused as shit. I saw Dan today. And I've been thinking about going back out with him. Honestly, I'm an idiot not to. A guy like him doesn't come along very often. There are a few problems, but nothing that can't be worked out. I think I have a hard time believing he really likes me. I don't know why he would. He probabaly doesn't, after all the shit I've put him through now. I wouldn't blame him. And I don't think I want him to like me. I can't handle this anymore, and I'm gonna cave soon. If we did end up going back out, we'd end up back where we've already been twice. I don't want to hurt him any more than I already have. So I guess it's settled. Me and Dan are over for good...
      
</post>

<date>17,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      1/1/02  I always hear people debating over the nature of man. Is man, by nature, good or evil? I believe man is neither, and at the same time, both. I believe that nothing is certain, it is only what we perceive of it. It depends on each and every person's point of view, and what they believe would be considered good or evil. For someone to categorize behavior is to me, closed-minded and naive. What is good? What is evil? Why are some things "more evil" than others? what these people are not taking into account is that every individual person is different, and capable and incapable of different things. Everybody thinks differently, everybody functions differently. And people need to stop trying to classify and judge things. many do not open their minds and do so. According my theory, every individual person's view is correct. It just depends on who you ask, and what you decide to believe. There is no right or wrong. Not meaning to lower the confidence in my argument, this, to me, is only what I think.  Ya know what's funny? It hasn't even been a year since I wrote this, but now it seems so lame. When I wrote it I thought I was a fucking genius. Just goes to show how much we really do grow over time.    
      
</post>

<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      What 2 do, what 2 do..............
      
</post>

<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      He says I stole his heart the first day he met me.........  .....I didn't know I was capable of stealing hearts....
      
</post>

<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, tonight in an unmentioned person's profile we've got a well done:  now if ur scared of love, dont, dont, dont b afraid, cuz girl im scared to but i gotta have u gonna love u day and nite, yes ill treat u right!  i just wanna b wit u, girl thas all i want to do i just wanna b wit u, girl thas all i wanna do   With a wonderful side order of:  Ive been sittn here cant get u off my mind ive tried my best to b a man and b strong ive drove myself insane wishn i cood touch ur face but the truth remains..  ur gone.. ur gone.. baby ur gone girl ur gone, baby girl, ur gone.. ur gone..  Yeh....um......that sure made me feel better. Great. I hate myself. I'm such a bitch. Atleast I'm an honest one, huh? Fuck this.    
      
</post>

<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have you ever loved somebody so much It makes you cry Have you ever needed something so bad You can't sleep at night Have you ever tried to find the words But they don't come out right Have you ever, have you ever  Have you ever been in love Been in love so bad You'd do anything to make them understand Have you ever had someone steal your heart away You'd give anything up to make them feel the same Have you ever searched for words to get you in their heart But you don't know what to say And you don't know where to start  Have you ever loved somebody so much It's makes you cry Have you ever needed something so bad You can't sleep at night Have you ever tried to find the words But they don't come out right Have you ever, have you ever  Have you ever found the one You've dreamed of all your life You'd do just about anything to look into their eyes Have you finally found the one you've given your heart to Only to find that one won't give their heart to you Have you ever closed your eyes and Dreamed that they were there And all you can do is wait for that day when they will care  Have you ever loved somebody so much It's makes you cry Have you ever needed something so bad You can't sleep at night Have you ever tried to find the words But they don't come out right Have you ever, have you ever  What do I gotta do to get you in my arms baby What do I gotta say to get to your heart To make you understand how I need you next to me Gotta get you in my world 'Cuz baby I can't sleep  Have you ever loved somebody so much It's makes you cry Have you ever needed something so bad You can't sleep at night Have you ever tried to find the words But they don't come out right Have you ever, have you ever  This is from me, not Dan.......
      
</post>

<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'M GOING TO THE NELLY CONCERT!!!!!!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so confused. How many times have I said that now? Not enough. What's this mean?  when i see her eyes look into my eyes then i realize that she could see inside my head so i close my eyes thinking that i could hide disassociate so i don't have to lose my head this situation leads to agitation will she cut me off? will this be amputation?  i don't know if i care i'm the jerk life's not fair  fighting all the time this is out of line she loves me not do you realize I won't compromise she loves me not  
      
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH.
      
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      him:    its not fair... its jus not fair :(  i love u.... y cant u love me back?       I don't know Dan. I wish I did. This is why I've promised myself one thing: I'm never, ever getting married. If you don't know already, my parents are divorced. It's the most fucked up thing I've ever witnessed. Two people, who supposedly "love" each other, make the biggest promise to each other anyone can make, and break it. Not just that, but they fuck up other people's lives too. I hate it. Then, if more than 50% of the people who get married get divorced, and I'm fuckin jinxed or something, which half do you think I'll be on? I don't want to go through all the shit if I already know how it's gonna end up. Plus, who would want to marry me?      Before my parents got divorced, I lived a fucking fairytale life. I lived in Las Vegas. I loved my school, friends, and pretty much everything else about my life. The only thing i would've changed is the fact that i didn't see my dad as much as I wanted to, because he worked a lot. Sometimes, on weekends, or whetever, my bro's and I got to go to work with him. He was the Director of Entertainment at Treasure Island. It was awesome when we did. Once my mom divorced him and moved here w/us, life was hell.      It's hard to believe how much I miss my old life. The thing is, it's not that I don't have my life anymore that gets to me, as much as knowing I'll never have it again. Some people get depressed because a loved one died- well, when my parents did this whole divorce thing, It feels like they did kill someone. Me. My life is gone. Now I have something else. Something, to put nicely, I hate to fucking death. There are the good times. You know, the little things, that allow you to function during the day. But in the long run, the "big things" show through, the shit that really matters. It's all so messed up that you can't handle it, and usually end up crying yourslef to sleep.      I might just be delusional. There might have been a lot of shit going on back when I was a kid that I had no idea about. But ignorance is a bliss, right? Whatever I don't know can't hurt me. I like it that way. 
      
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      sittn in my room last nite starn at the mirror i coodnt find a reason y i coodnt b near her  cuz u r the one that startd to make me feel this way n every nite im thinkn bout the words ud say  pictures goin thru my mind wen were togetha all these long n sleepless nites will i eva get betta  cuz u r the one that startd to make me feel this way n every nite im thinkn bout the words ud say cuz u r THE ONE THAT I WANT  now u kno how i feel this love is forever u make my life seem so unreal will i eva get betta?...  cuz u r the one that startd to make me feel this way n every nite im thinkn bout the words ud say cuz u are THE ONE THAT I WANT  That's his new profile. Help me.
      
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      me:	ill always b there 4 u me:	as a friend me:	... me:	isn't that enough? him:	i want wat we had b4 me:	it would never be the same me:	too much shit happened him:	:'( me:	i like having u as a friend him:	i have to go.... i dont wanna start cryn again.... bye me:	no dan  god damnit. The wierd thing is...it seems like such a big deal now, but in 5 years we'll look back at this and laugh. Hard. There's no getting around this stage in my life though, so I might as well enjoy bein a stupid 14-yr old while I still can, right? Fuck it all.
      
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      IM SO FUCKEN CONFUSED!!!!!!!!!!!! I can't go back out with Dan. I can't. But now it's saturday, and the kid I was pissed at on thursday is stopping my fuckin oxygen flow. I checked his profile and guess what was in there? A song:   i will never find anotha lover, sweeter than u, sweeter than u  n i will never find anotha lover more precious than u, more precious than u  girl u are close to me ur like my motha,  close to me ur like my fatha,  close to me ur like my sister,  close to me ur like my brother  u are the only one my everythin and for u this song I sing   all my life ive prayd for sum1 like u  n i thank god that i, that i finally found u  all my life ive prayd for sum1 like u  n i hope that u feel the same way too  yes, I pray that u do love me too   i said ur all that im thinking of.....baby   said, i promise to never fall in love with a stranger,  ur all im thinking of, i praise the lord above,  for sending me ur love, i cherish every hug,  i really love you   SHIT.....this hurts. It hurts b/c i know how this feels. And to know i'm causing that kind of pain to someone and theres nothing i can do to help.....it kills me. This is someone I really do care about, but not in that way. And i need to prove the pionts I've been trying to prove to him. But look at this:  me:	dan him:	hey me:	this hurts him:	it kills me me:	and thats y it hurts me just as bad me:	say something him:	will anythn chnage ur mind? me:	no i dont think so me:	but i dont want 2 hurt u him:	2 late me:	can n e thing at least make u feel better him:	gimme anotha chance him:	plz me:	i cant me:	dan me:	i wish i could me:	but i cant  SHITCRAPFUCKDAMN what the hell is goin on? Part of me says "God damnit Maddie, take him back". But the other part, that i seem to be listening to, says "you idiot- you kno what'll happen if you do....the same thing that happened last time". And it probably will. If I can't trust myself to make the right descision, who can I trust? I wish nothing I did hurt anyone. Maybe myself, but please god spare everyone else the pain, it's not worth it. It really isn't. I'm going now, but don't worry, I'll be back. Soon. I love you ALL. bye :(   
      
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok. Well, I guess this is my "journal". I had this whole resolution planned out- to start a journal the 1st day 9th grade, and write in it every night until I graduate. Yeh. Bullshit's what I thought too. I don't know what to write. This is hard, because this is a public journal, which kinda defeats the purpose, because a journal is supposed to be private, right? I usually like to write shit that's straight out about how I feel, but I have a feeling that if I do, I'll get sued by someone.       So..... maybe I should start with me. Seems a little self-indulgent, but this is for those of you who don't know who the hell I am. My name's Maddie. I'm a fourteen year old, sarcastic, cynical bitch. Sometimes. I could call myself pessimistic, b/c I sure act like it, but I'm usually just joking around. When things get serious I'm always looking for the good side of things, i guess. When it comes right down to it, I like honesty. A lot. Bullshitting is just a way of getting around the things you need to deal with and don't want to. I have a lot of philosophies and shit, but I'm not in the mood to type em all out right now, so I'll share em later.       I went to the first freshman football game yesterday. We suck. Oh well, it was fun anyway. I saw my ex, Dan, there. It's confusing. We met on his blind date with one of my best friends Joyce. I didn't want to go out with him, because she still liked him, But when she told me she didn't anymore, I said yes to Dan, I found out Joyce still liked him, and a week later we broke up. Then, another week later, I missed him and asked him out again. He said yes, and AnOtHeR week later, he dumped me b/c of reasons I'd rather not mention. Yeh...that gave it away. We "disagreed" on some things. Now, he's asking me to go back out with him, and I can't. I don't feel that way towards him anymore, and I like someone else, which is another topic we'll discuss later. Isn't all this 14-year old drama fun? We're all so....mature! Ahem....anyways.       I'm out. luv you all.bye. :P
      
</post>

<date>13,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      [9/13/2002 7:59:58 PM | Maddie Lauve] Yo...s^? Today was pretty damn interesting. But i can't really explain right now b/c i gotta go pack to go 2 mah dad's. I'll fill u in lata. luv ya. bbyz.
      
</post>

<date>13,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yo...s^? Today was pretty damn interesting. But i can't really explain right now b/c i gotta go pack to go 2 mah dad's. I'll fill u in lata. luv ya. bbyz.
      
</post>

<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Guys.  Guys, guys, guys.  A few years ago, If the guy I liked liked someone else, I'd try desperately to be as much like that girl as possible.  Not anymore.  I'll never reach the point of concietedness, but I'm finally, finally happy with who I am. And fuck anyone with smart-ass comments on that. If a guy doesn't like me for who I am, I'm not gonna change for him.  It obviously wasn't meant to be. If there is such thing, I guess my soul-mate search would continue after this realization.  I want a guy who likes me for me. Not me pretending to be the girl he likes.  Life does go on after all.  I can be so blind sometimes.
      
</post>

<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm over him. That's that.
      
</post>

<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night, my dream was kinda like X-Men. Everyone had these cool powers.  He was in my dream.  He could run up walls.  He could fly.  He liked me.  Yup. It was a dream.
      
</post>

<date>26,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'd like to take this moment of silence to think of all the gods to thank for assisting me in my journey to success in adding comments to my page.  ..........  Moment enough for me.  This kicks ass. Now use it.
      
</post>

<date>26,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I can't get these damn comments to work.   It would probably help if I actually knew what I was doing, but I've fucked around with the code so much, I ended up having to make a new blog so I could copy the template and start over.  I'm not a computer person.
      
</post>

<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I swear I'm over him.
      
</post>

<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've done the impossible. I'm over him. Yeh...him.  I'm done with guys. And no, this doesn't mean I'm a lesbian. Sorry guys.  I hope I'll find the one guy who was "meant to be" and get into some kind of realtionship with him someday. But until then, fuck boys. They make great friends, but if I know I'm not head over motherfucking heels in love, I don't think all the bullshit that comes along with dating is worth it. Not at all. People take everything so seriously. We're only motherfucking freshman at the motherfucking highschool. What's the big motherfucking deal?  I'm done, thank you for listening to my motherfucking ranting (If youre still actually reading..).  :P  On a less premenstrual note, I went to work with my mom the other day. She works in a theater, where a new musical, Marty, is showing. I met all these cool people. The main character was in the Perfect Storm (John C. Reilly), and I met him. The writers also wrote Annie, Bye Bye Birdie, and Applause. I met them too. Just to name a few. Everyone (almost) there is so nice. This made my previously shitty weekend.  The coolest part, though, was hanging out with my mom. Sounds pathetic, I know. But even if I claim to "hate that bitch to death" sometimes, I know I feel exactly the opposite. And it gets lonely when she's working 8AM to 12PM everyday except Monday, and she uses that day to fit in the week's shit-to-do. My daily conversation with my mother usually consists of a reminder to take the dogs out, feed the chickens (yes, chickens), move a load of laundry from the washer to the dryer, and make Bagel Bites for dinner, written on a used Dunkin Donuts napkin. We spent the day together. We showed up at the theater, and I helped her set up for the day. We went and got subs for lunch, which we ate at the table on the set. She had to work during rehersal, and I read my english book (or, the cliffnotes ;P). For dinner break, we walked around for a while, looking for something to waste our money on, and settled for Ben and Jerry's ice cream and Rolos. She got her dawgz to sneak me into the preview show that night, and lucky me, there was an empty seat in the front row. The show was awesome. It's going to Broadway after this, as well it should be.   We spent the day sneaking York Peppermint Patties from the crew's bag of candy.  The next day, she found time to take me shopping.  I feel like a spoiled little mothafucka.  LOVE YOU ALL----bbyz.
      
</post>

<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thanks to my buddy Trung for getting me to realize this.  I know nobody's perfect. Anyone whose heared the dumb-ass cliche knows that nobody's perfect. But is it a sin to try to get there? People are kind of like....buildings or something (I'm talking spiritually here, not writing the script for Invasion of the Fat People). We build ourselves. We take ideas from....just about everything that happens to pass into our little brains and is lucky enough not to fall out the other side. We use these ideas and, basically, build ourselves. From the qualities we already have, that we're constantly striving to improve, to the qualities we don't have, and are desperately trying to attain. We become these collages of shit. Good shit, bad shit, that's for you to decide. The final product is pretty much the person we accept as someone we want to be.   I guess this much thought isn't put into the process, it just kinda happens. But I'm a little obsessive compulsive when it comes to analyzing things. 
      
</post>

<date>12,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here we go. Back to the faith crap. Faith is one of the most beautiful human qualities, because it isn't based on anything. It exists without evidence to support or affect it. It just is. Tell me that's not as fuckin pure as anything gets.
      
</post>

<date>12,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I haven't posted in forever.   Boys will always confuse the shit outta me, but at this moment, I seem to remotely understand that part of my life. Dan's over me. Gone through another girlfriend since the last time I wrote. I'm in love with the same guy I've been in love with for about half a year now. I've realized something though, about Mr. Unnamable. He's different from any other guy I've ever "had a crush on". I'm not occupied with wanting him, but wanting him to be happy. He's one of the, with lack of a more descriptive word, BEST people I've ever met. In my six months shy of a 15 year life span, I can count on one hand the number of people who have impacted my life like he has.   I love him.  But I can't have him. He doesn't like me. Even if he did, IF, (and he doesn't..), nothing could ever happen. Reasons: age difference, criminal record. Sorry for the detail deficiency.  This gives me two choices. 1) to say, "I hate my life. I love him, and he'll never feel the same way towards me. Even if he does, theres no way anything could happen between us. There's no reason to live anymore. Find me a cliff." or... 2) to say, "I love my life, thanks to him. Even though nothing could ever happen, I should be happy I got the chance to have him in my life, even just as a friend. I don't regret anything in my life up to the moment I met him. I can't imagine what my life would be like if I didn't, and to have him as a friend is better than nothing."  It might just be me, but the second one doesn't seem as messy. 
      
</post>

<date>25,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I haven't posted in FOREVER- and I have a very convincing excuse.  I've been taking this playwriting class associated with the Huntington Theatre, where my mom works. I've been there almost every week day for the past two weeks. Therefore, my lack of blogging has been made up by my play. It's a simple play. 10 minutes. It's gonna be stage read by BU seniors January 16th. Fun.  Believe it or not, a whole shitload of....shit...can happen over a two-week Maddie period. The stories I could tell....  Let's start with...my play:  PLAY TAKEN OUT   That's my play. Yup. I don't like it. I don't even have a title. Tell me if you have any suggestions.  I'll finish with the stories tonight. I gotta go to the class now.        
      
</post>

<date>09,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      There are few things I love more than seeing/talking to someone I haven't seen/talked to in a long time.  I talked to Kris today! He lives in Las Vegas, and I haven't seen him since last summer. He sent me pictures...of his sikk new tattoo and him on his dirtbike.   I forgot just how much I miss everyone there. Which would be...  A lot. 
      
</post>

<date>08,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      OHMYGOD.....8Mile is fucking awesome. Cassie's mom got me and my friends tickets this morning because otherwise, we wouldn't have gotten in, and we would've been watching some shitwad like Santa Clause 2 or something. I wouldn't trade that ticket for ANYTHING...the movie kicked elephant ass.  I love Eminem. Love, love, love. L-O-V-E......love. Get it?  That word looks weird when you look at it long enough.  
      
</post>

<date>06,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hitman #1: if any1 harasses u n forces u 2 do things u dont want Hitman #1: ill beat em up 4 u Me: lol Me: i could do it mahself Me: n i would Hitman #1: but u mite get hurt Hitman #1: i dont want u to  Hitman #2: but you tell em that the mass counterfeiter will get a piece of em also if they fuck with you, ok? Me: lol ok Hitman #2: aight Me: thnx Hitman #2: seriously......................? Hitman #2: i mean it Me: seriously what Hitman #2: bout ne1 fucking with you Hitman #2: and ill bring bout 5 of my college friends to kick their ass(es) Me: lol  You hear that? Don't fuck with me, because If I don't stop you (very, very improbable), somebody else will.....  LOL 
      
</post>

<date>05,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Those motherfuckers stole our weight room. The football team's in deep shit now...
      
</post>

<date>05,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Fresh from the bookstore:   urlLink Prozac Nation   urlLink The Screwtape Letters   urlLink Einstein's Dreams   urlLink Philosophy: The Basics   urlLink The Varieties of Religious Experience   urlLink Fearless: Special Edition  
      
</post>

<date>02,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wierd day.  Eventful.  Dan hugged me...again. Normally, this wouldn't be much of a problem...but those hugs hurt, man! He tries to squeeze me to death. I think his goal is to one day sqeeze me so hard that he actually, non-figuratively speaking, squeezes the shit outta me. I know when he has a girlfriend I'm safe from the hugs...help me find him another girlfriend...please.  I stayed after school, and was arm wrestling with people. Two guys beat me....and oh....that made me mad. I went to the weight room and worked out. I love that place. Everyday after school from now on, I'm so there.  I also got asked out today. By who? Don't have a fucking clue. He's older, probably a senior. I'm guessing he was just joking around...but it was still wierd. Apparently, he's "seen me around... lots of places". Now....who the fuck is he? 
      
</post>

<date>02,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I like to rap.
      
</post>

<date>02,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Talking to Trung:  Me: i kno this is gonna sound wierd but... Me: have u eva been sitting in a room Him: ...? Me: and you're sitting there looking at the ppl and u realize something u dont always realize even though it's about the most obvious thing in the world... Me: ..that all the ppl are just like u Him: ... Me: theyre all lookin around the room thinking things just like u Me: and feeling stuff just like u Me: and since all u really know is what u think and feel.....u dont pay much attention to the fact that they are exactly the same Me: I mean... maybe they are thinking bout different things Me: but the big picture is still the same Me: so to u they're just other ppl...u do respect them n treat them like ppl should be treated... Me: but even when u go to bed at night thinking bout stuff Me: u kinda forget that... Me: they're all in their beds ...thinkin bout stuff 2 Me: it makes u feel so small...but..like.. part of sumthin so big Him: ... you make this up maddie??? Me: lol Me: yeh Me: like it? Him: itz good Him: really Me: me 2 Me: lol Him: really good Me: thnk u Him: i never thought that deep Me: I'm amazed I have...... 
      
</post>

<date>31,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Retroperspective    I would assure you that I'm not schizo beforehand, but I can't promise anything.   What's up?  You know that's the evil question. But I'll be nice and, just like everyone else does, say: Nothing, what's up with you?   What were you New Year's resolutions for 2002?  You didn't answer my question.   *muffled 'bitch'* Oh, nothing. Now, What were your New Year's resolutions for 2002?  I didn't make any.   Did you follow through with these resolutions?  Yes, every single one of them.   I'm proud of you.  Really?   No. What were the best movies you saw this year?  The Matrix for the thousandth time, Memento, Donnie Darko, The Mothman Prophecies, XXX, 8mile, The New Guy, and A.I. (despite the fact that everyone else hated it.)   What was the worst movie you saw this year?  Jason X, hands down. *soggy, soggy*   What was the best song of the year?  Hailie's Song by Eminem, If I Can Go by Angie Martinez feat. Lil Mo and Zicario, Roll Out by Ludacris, The Whole World by Outkast, and I Know What You Want by Busta Rhymes and Mariah Carey.   What were the best resurrected songs you heard this year?  Have You Ever by Brandy, Don't Wanna Miss a Thing by Aerosmith, Motown Philly by Boyz II Men, and Always Be My Baby by Mariah Carey.   What was the worst song you heared this year?  Still Fly by Big Tymers. I love it anyway, though.   What was the stupidest thing you did all year?  Fell down the stairs when getting off Bomee's bus once, and spent the next half hour trying to laugh it off and making myself look even more stupid. It's a talent of mine.   What was the most stupidest thing anyone said to you all year?  "You're too young to be in love." ties with "Don't get your bellybutton pierced, you'll become infertile."   What was the best advice given to you this year?  "Be yourself."   What was the best thing you did for yourslef all year?  Hang around the Huntington Theatre, playwriting workshop and all. And trying my hardest to be nice to everyone.   Who are the most interesting people you've met this year?  All of them.   What was the worst month of 2002?  August.   What was the best month of 2002?  August. Long story. And...April...   What are your resolutions for 2003?  To improve my vocabulary, to trick the CIA into recruiting me, to join the football team my sophmore year, to get my hair cornrowed at least twice, to figure out a way to keep my single-rhinestoned-thumbnail "style" going, to learn judo and aikido, to get the damn  urlLink Manolo Blahnik boots  (they have them at Baker's and Steve Madden, definitely not as nice but at a hell of a more reasonable price), to be more outgoing, to trust my feelings more, and to keep at least two of these resolutions.   Happy New Year.  You too, sexy.  
      
</post>

<date>30,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Not that you care, but...    I took two fudge mint covered Oreos up to bed with me last night. Now, I hate skim milk, but it was the only kind left in the refidgerator (I'll be very surprised if I spelled that right..), so I poured myself a glass.  I swear to god my skim milk was glowing in the dark.
      
</post>

<date>30,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Poor Red    No conversation taking place at my dad's house ever fails to amuse me.  Breakfast. We ate omlettes and [exceptionally baconly bacony] bacon. The conversation started with a corny joke referring to a corny joke in The Producers. My dad, who has never actually seen the show, but whose Producer's soundtrack listening count probably exceeds that of Bill Gates' yearly income's George Washingtons, made the joke. The joke was about Dad's grandmother's pig Red. Supposedly, Red one day mysteriously ran away. His family ate very well for the next two weeks. It was never made clear whether this Red actually existed or not, but I'm assuming it doesn't matter much, considering the fact that five minutes later, the conversation had somehow slyly shifted to discussing the color of the sky in the eye of a tornado or a hurricane.  Apparently, it's green.  Only in my family... 
      
</post>

<date>30,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      haha.
      
</post>

<date>29,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       hola 
      
</post>

<date>29,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       hi 
      
</post>

<date>29,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        When Advil would come in handy...    My head hurts.
      
</post>

<date>27,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Before Christmas    I had fun last weekend. Last friday night was Joyce's 15th birthday party. A lot of shit happened, a lot of people cried, but we definitely had fun. THANK YOU JOYCE.  Nina, Cassie, Joyce and I went to Fun n Games a few nights later. The car ride there was spent making jokes about coming home with eight-year old boyfriends after spending our night at an oh-so-mature arcade. Once we got there we wasted money in those Wheel of Fortune "games", and played a few rounds of air hockey. We played those Anti-Zombie plastic-gunned games and drove around what was supposed to resemble Las Vegas in "cars". Nina and Cassie didn't want to play laser tag (which mas the main reason why I went- it has to be the only game in the world that can compete with football.) After being begged for an hour they agreed to play, and they didn't regret it at all. We took part in that masochistic Adams Family game, where you hold your hand on the handles and electrocute yourself. Sounds fun, huh. I had exactly 40 tickets, which was enough to buy a pink football. Im tellin' you, everybody needs a pink football.  I spent the rest of the night in the photo booth with my girls (taking pictures, pervert), falling off tables that otherwise  would  make good beds (non-purposely, believe it or not), and throwing my precious pink football at people's heads.   We spent the car ride home talking about the hot guy who worked there and looked  exactly  like Keanu Reeves. Damn...  The morning after that we went down to B. Field and played football. I may hate Christmas, but I think I've fallen in love with Christmas vacation.
      
</post>

<date>27,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Yo Dan    Dan is my buddy.  Now he's in my blog again.  :P   Update:    AND...he's so cool...and so hot.... rite dan? LOL
      
</post>

<date>27,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Sexy     Like I said in  urlLink Sarah's blog :  Legolas and Aragorn are sexy motherfuckers.  But:  No one will EVER be sexier than Johnny Depp.  Oooooooooh.....  urlLink Johnny Depp .
      
</post>

<date>27,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        I'm gonna start putting headings on my posts.    I'm gonna start putting headings on my posts.  That was a little repetatively redundant, wasnt it.  I don't care. As you can probably tell, I'm bored as fuck right now. I just posted three times in like, five minutes. That has to be breaking some kind of I-have-no-life record. I actually think I've broken that record more than once. About a year and a half ago, I found out how many licks it takes to get to the center of a tootsie-pop. I think it was like, 365 to get to the actual tootsie-roll center, and 984 to get all the hard-candy shit off so all you have is a tootsie-roll on a now limp stick.  You know what cereal I haven't had in a long time? Cap'n Crunch. I love Cap'n Crunch. Or, at least, from what I remember, I  think  I love Cap'n Crunch. I remember they have (or had, for all I know) the peanut butter kind, and the kind with the "berries", and then they made the kind with the berries and the green things. I want some of those green things. Next time I'm this bored I might walk to the store and buy some. I'm too lazy right now.  I'll shut up and stop taking my boredom out on you.  Cap'n Crunch fucking rocks.
      
</post>

<date>27,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      My archives are back.  You know what that means?  You won't have to listen to me complain anymore, and I might actually post something  worth reading .   Hey, it could happen.
      
</post>

<date>27,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so confused, I don't even know why.
      
</post>

<date>27,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ummm
      
</post>

<date>24,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       What the fuck...does anyone know how to fix archives?  I still have all the posts, I asked it to show my last 100 and it shows all the posts I've made in this blog so far. But I try every suggestion and my archives won't re-set and they won't show more than two weeks' posts, even if I set it to "monthly".  If you have any suggestions or solutions PLEASE PLEASE comment.  Thanks. 
      
</post>

<date>24,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      test
      
</post>

<date>24,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      test
      
</post>

<date>24,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      OK....my archives are gone...
      
</post>

<date>24,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'll have a new layout up I don't know when.  But let me just tell you now- it's fucking awesome.
      
</post>

<date>23,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate Christmas.  Too stressful. Especially when:   -your parents aren't talking to each other and you have to spend 3 hours in a car on Christmas Day to be able to share the holiday with both of them.  -you have no money at all (I mean like...none...) and you want to buy everyone you know a present and donate thousands of dollars to charity to give other people some kind of Christmas (OK...I lied about the no money thing a little....I had about $15 to donate and I happily did so).  -the two presents that would make you so incredibly extremely joyously delightfully happy you'd never ask for anything again are so completely out of reach it's not even worth trying to use a telescope to see 'em, let alone figure out a way to attain them. (Yes- one of those presents is a pair of  Manolo Blahnik Okla-Mod boots ; I don't think I've ever wanted anything you can buy with money [$700 of it] THIS MUCH in my entire life.)  I don't want to make this Christmas about me, though. I want to know that I did the best I could to make everyone possible happy- after all, besides doing the hokey-pokey and turning yourself around, isn't that what it's all about?   I don't want presents this year. Instead, give me money to buy yours.   ;P  Despite my bitchy, cynical, bah-humbuggy mood towards the holiday, I love you ALL, and hope you have a Merry commercial and/or religious Christmas.
      
</post>

<date>23,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      How do you kno if you're in love?
      
</post>

<date>23,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, so I HAVE been a bad girl and haven't posted in, like.....OHMYGOD....two whole weeks! Get me a priest- I gotta confess my sins! Shit -I'd rather not get molested! I forgot-I'm not male! I'm gonna shut the hell up now because this isn't funny it's just annoying!  I went shopping today and took on the HUGE responsibility of picking out my mom's presents for reasons being I apparently misunderstand her taste less than my brothers.  I got her some weirddddd shit.
      
</post>

<date>10,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      People have been getting pissed off at me for not posting.  This is a post.  Happy?  Good.  You can all shut up now.    I'll be happy too. 
      
</post>

<date>10,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      What strange kind of person am I?   A dreamer is your type. Seen as "not quite there", you see things that few do. You make people think, and your friends turn to you for insight.   urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>08,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Where did my soul originate?  You come from Heaven. You're the purest of pure, a saint. You're probably an angel sent directly from Heaven.   urlLink     Where Did Your Soul Originate?     This one made me hit my head on the wall when I fell over laughing.
      
</post>

<date>07,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      My sexual appeal is:   urlLink     What's your sexual appeal?"    Fooling everyone...  Hmmm...
      
</post>

<date>07,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Apparently, I am a:   urlLink     What Kind of FLIRT are you?     
      
</post>

<date>04,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       The Devil's Dictionary   You need it. Go buy it.
      
</post>

<date>03,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      2pac is so dead.  *Soggy soggy* (Nina, Joyce,  I know you feel me).   (Not like that.)
      
</post>

<date>03,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      What a lovely welcoming; the first thing I see when I open Internet Explorer...  CNN Top Stories:   Five Amish Children Killed in House Fire    FAA: United Airlines Used Tape to Repair Wings    Science: Mice and Men of the Same Genes   Now, is it just me, or is CNN in desperate need for some serious shit to write about?  Well, now we know what goes on in THIS country.  Gosh darn, am I proud to be an American.
      
</post>

<date>03,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I also have this thing with llamas...
      
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      You probably don't, but for lack of anything productive to do (or money), you might want to know about my fascination (read: obsession) with the CIA...
      
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just want to say:  Cassie,  First of all, I am NOT a better writer than you. You also shouldn't be envious of the fact that I was stalked. I'm not too proud of it myself.  You have a life. Sure, a different one than mine, but definitley, in no way worse. You're a beautiful fourteen-year-old girl with boys all over her and the best part is that you don't care. Because you have a boyfriend. One that you love to death, who loves you to death. Drew's different from any other guy you've dated. I have great expectations for you two (Oh fuck, the book got to my head. I didn't just say that...).  You have plenty to write about, just BE YOURSELF. Be the Cassie we all love.  Regarding the whole feeling-left-out thing, I'm happy you said all the shit you did, because it's not shit. I can see how this might piss you off, and you have every right to be pissed off. I never want to make you feel left out, and now that I know why you are, I'll do everything I can to fix it.  Luv ya girl, The Llama
      
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      IT'S A PIECE OF SHIT. THE PLAY IS A PIECE OF SHIT. Now that that's out of the way...  I DO have a lot of stories to tell, The problem is, if I tell half of them I'll probably get arrested. The other half would put me in a mental institution. I think I'll stick to one of the very few safe ones for now.  My class was in Boston, and I took the train there a lot because my mom wasn't always there waiting with her car and driver's liscense (God- two noun's I'd love to own...). Now, I know that roaming around downtown alone at night, roaming around Boston alone at night, taking the subway alone at night, and doing a whole bunch of other shit alone at night isnt exactly the safest way to go, but I definitely know how to handle myself. I was prepared for any fuckers who might try to screw with me (no sick, demented pun intended). But I never actually expected anything to really happen.  Well, it did.  So there I was sitting at the train station, waiting for the...um...train maybe. There was this blond-haired, bown-eyed, middle-aged, tall, scraggly looking guy who was probably kicked out of AA and issued a restraining order twice in the past six weeks. He was smoking a pack of Malboro Lite's. The guy can't even get a manly pack of cigarettes, let alone set of balls. Knowing my paranoia extremely well, I didn't believe myself when I thought it seemed wierd how often he would look over at me. I got on the train. He did too.   Still holding myself back from the panic attack I was sure to have seconds before I beat this guy's ass to the ground, I sat down and watched him take a seat two behind me. The conductor came to me and asked where I was getting off. Hesitantly, I said Back Bay, the first of two stops in Boston. When he asked the creepy guy, he also said Back Bay. It took a hell of a lot of convincing to make myself understand that it was NO BIG FUCKING DEAL. Lots of people were getting off at Back Bay.  Next, I did the stupidest and simultaneously most unconciously ingenious things ever. I fell asleep and missed my stop. I woke up at the next stop, South Station. As I stepped onto the platform, I was slapped out of my still-dreamy state. Creepy Guy was behind me. I was definitely nervous at this point. I started to walk around, making sure he was following me before trying to figure out what to do with him when I was finished. I turned and started to walk towards another train. Still behind me. I turned again and headed towards the subway. Yup, he was as fucked up as I imagined forty-five minutes earlier at the station I got on at. I turned one more time and ran right into this old guy who was on the train with me and Asshole.   "Excuse me miss, can I help you?"  I saw him glaring at Fuckface with the meanest and most disturbing look I have even seen a senior citizen give another human being. That look would make you picture Osama Bin Laden wearing a halo and singing an Amy Grant song. Dickwad walked away, and the guy's face softened.  "Was that man bothering you?"  "Not yet. Thanks."
      
</post>

<date>28,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I only found out a few days ago.    I't weird when it's someone you knew: http://www.boston.com/dailyglobe2/021/metro/BC_High_junior_16_dies_in_car_crash+.shtml  Not only someone you knew, but someone you cared about.  Not cared,  care .  Someone who stands out. In a good way. Many good ways.  Someone you like more each time you talk to them.  Someone you want to get to know better. A few weeks in a playwriting class isn't enough.  Someone who's definitely a someone.  It's like a slap in the face. It makes you think about so much, and re-evaluate your entire life.  Ryan, I didn't know you for very long or very well, but what I do know is that something like this can't happen to someone like you.  But it did.  You'll live on, kid. And yeah, it does look like japanese.  So, I know I "don't have to", but I don't care. I now dedicate this entire blog to Ryan Flannery.  
      
</post>

<date>26,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        XXXVII    Wow...crazy, crazy game.  Wow.  As much as I wanted the Raiders to win, I can't help but be happy for Tampa Bay. Man, did you see their faces?  Crazy.
      
</post>

<date>24,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I    am so sick...
      
</post>

<date>24,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Let Me Rant Please    I've been going insane.  The past few weeks I've been so overwhelmed by everything. Everything. Like, everything. Yeah.  Did I say everything?  OK. Let me explain this everything. Homework. Tests. Essays. My revised-but-still-sucky-play. Mid-terms. Mid-terms. Mid-terms. Mid-terms. Mid-terms. Mid-terms. Mid-terms. Family. Friends. Boys (please leave me the fuck alone, because that should be the last thing for me to worry about, even though it's definitely not.)  To add to that, my school's doing Grease for the spring musical, and I tried out today. School got out at 10:45 am. I got home at 4:30 pm. The auditions were unbeleivably long. I tried out for Frenchie, but told them I'd take any part, lines or no lines. I did pretty well with the singing, although I could've been louder. I started out okay with the acting, but lost my place about three times by the end of the dialogue. I messed up at the beginning of the dance part, but I don't think she saw. I finished up fine, though. What really pisses me off, though, is that I  know  I could've done SO much better.  I fucked up, but it's not the end of the world. I know I'm not getting Frenchie, but I don't care that much. Well, it's not that I don't care, it's just that I'm not gonna break down for not getting the part I didn't expect to get in the first place. I hadn't eaten in over 24 hours by the time I got home today, not by choice, so I had some soup, sunny delight, and sleep.  Mid-terms have made me want to crack my head open AND snap my neck, both, just to make sure the job's done.  I need some serious sleep.  I've felt like a peice of shit lately. I had a cold with itchy, watery eyes, but I thought it went away. Guess I was wrong. I've been so tired, even on the days after 12-hour nights of sleep, which I used to get twice a week, but now get about twice a month. A normal night's sleep these days consists of about four an a half hours.   This is the most unbelievably boring post I've posted in a long time, and I think I'll end it now.  Oh yeah, and my little Raiders are gonna beat the fuck out of Tampa Bay.                 
      
</post>

<date>16,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Why Be Professional?    I had to fill out a sheet for my playwriting class, answering questions about my experience, so they can write an introduction for when the play gets performed.  Dude, I was so damn tempted to answer like this:  YOUNG VOICES PLAYWRITING WORKSHOP  STAGED READING BIOGRAPHY  NAME: Maddie L.  SCHOOL: FHS  GRADE: 9  HIGHLIGHTS OF YOUR WRITING EXPERIENCE/THEATRE WORK: No, I usually used a pen.  WHAT BROUGHT YOU TO THE YOUNG VOICES PLAYWRITING WORKSHOP: A Honda Odyssey.  YOUR INTERESTS/HOBBIES: Music, theatre, writing, art, football, llamas. Flamingos.  FUTURE PLANS: I want to study journalism at Columbia University, then become a UPS truck driver.
      
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        One  Fine  Fucked Up Day    Ok, so I'm not very up-to-date, but what  don't  you know already?  Friday was the first day I missed school my entire freshman year.  It also happened to be the day everyone was dismissed at 10am because of a gas leak.  Why do I always miss the excitement? Shit, I'd rather be the one who inhaled too much gas, passed out,hit my head on the wall, and fell into a coma for twenty-five years than be the one who was in bed that day because her mom couldn't wake her up (apparently I wasn't even breathing.)  Oh well, maybe another day...  >:) 
      
</post>

<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Almost Orgasmic...I Guess...    The best feeling in the world has to be when you lie back down in your bed after turning your alarm clock off in the morning... for the second time.
      
</post>

<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        A Bit Sadistic But: Die, Dreams, Die    So, even my teachers have been noticing. My english teacher keeps threatening to call my parents because she's "concerned". It's not like I want to feel all depressed.  I'm confused. About a lot.  But I've figure out what might help ease the confusion.  I need to let go of some things. Some things that I can't live with but can't live without. The living-with part is out of my control, but I'm letting myself stop wishing and proceed living-without.  Some dreams aren't chaseworthy.  Will I finally let go this time, or get sucked back into dreaming, like I have a countless number of times?  If the latter of the two occurs, please slap me. Hard.
      
</post>

<date>06,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        According to the Dalai Lama...    Fine, I admit it. I took that stupid Dalai Lama forward test (Cassie.)  The results were kind of interesting, which is the only reason why I'm posting this.  Apparently...  These are my priorities, in order of importance: -Love -Family -Career -Pride -Money  I am LOYAL. My partner is MYSTERIOUS. My enemies are BRAINDEAD. I interpret sex as INTERESTING. My life is POWERFUL.  JOYCE is someone I will never forget. I consider NINA a true friend. I really love *******. CASSIE is my twin soul. I will remember KATIE for the rest of my life.  Well...  I loved this test, for the sole reason that they compared sex to coffee.
      
</post>

<date>06,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Beats the Shit Out of the 'Dog Ate It' Excuse    I had this dream last night:  I was feeling like shit for a while, and finally decided to go to the doctor's. On the way there, I heared the song "Don't Want to Miss a Thing" by Arerosmith. The song just ended as we got to the office.  I heared the song again on the way home from the doctor's.  I returned home with a new peice of news; I had Leukemia, and had 10 months to live.  I told Joyce, Nina, and Cassie on the bus the next morning, but couldn't keep from laughing when I saw the looks on their faces. They didn't believe me, until I passed out in chorus and had to go home early from school. They went to my house to see me after they got off the bus, but i was lying in bed staring at the wall. I wouldn't talk to anyone. I stayed like this for about a week, until Someone I Wasn't Expecting came to visit me and talked to me. He got me to understand that I needed to spend the time I had left having fun, and spending time with the people who might actually miss me.  I was ready to die, that's the weird part. The reason I was so zoned out was not because I couldn't get over the fact that I was dying, but that I was O.K. with it, and ready to die. I felt it when I woke up from the dream, though. Not just in the dream.  I used this readiness and new advice to start my new, 10-month-long life.  I sold everything I owned and donated the money to some kind of charity.  I forgave anyone I was ever ever mad at.  I conviced someone to fuck with the NFL and made them let me in as wide receiver for the Dallas Cowboys when they played a game against the New England Patriots, and we kicked Pat ass.  I apologized to every single everyone I ever did anything at all mean to in any way ever at all. There's a sentence for ya.  I told all my teachers that because I would be dying in 10 months anyway, I didn't see the point, so I stopped doing my homework (I like that part.)  I had a Halloween Party, something I think I've talked about all fifteen years of my life but never got around to following through with.  I spent time with a certain somebody I dislike not spending time with.  I visited my everyone. Anyone I loved and hadn't seen in more than a month.  I even let myself cry a few times.  The last thing I saw before I died was a Friends episode in the hospital, and I hate Friends.  I was happy when I died.  It makes me wonder.   Don't worry that doesn't mean I'm feeling especially suicidal (at this moment, anyway.)  But... I could feel what I was feeling in my dream. I knew I had a certain amount of time left; an exact limit on my life. And I spent it not worrying about a damn thing except having fun, and giving EVERYTHING I had to help people.  And I was happy when I died.    
      
</post>

<date>03,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I want  urlLink one     And  urlLink one .  And  urlLink one .  And  urlLink one .  And  urlLink one .  And  urlLink twelve .
      
</post>

<date>01,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        The First O' The Year    Happy 2003, yo.
      
</post>

<date>24,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I Know: I'm a Bad, Bad Girl.    More than a month. Wow. I beat my non-blogging record by, like, twice what it was before. It's not that I haven't wanted to write, and it's incredibly, undoubtedly not because I haven't had anything to write about.  Let's just not make this post be about how I haven't posted in a long time, because that shit belongs not in this blog.  I'm in Grease. The rehersals consist of singing, dancing, and blocking, seeing as I am "just chorus people". Despite the fact that I am an inferior being upon the stage, I love it, and I'm sticking with it. Three hours a day, three days a week. I'm spending a lot of time-I-didn't-have-in-the-first-place on this musical.  Guys: the usual. Sometimes, they make me so happy I'm alive, I wouldn't trade it for anything (not that I have much to trade my life for...but that's beside the point.) Other times, they make me want to cry until it is literally, physically impossible to cry any more. Yet most of the time, they just make my want to kick them in the balls repeatedly until they're too numb to feel a school bus crawling up their inner thigh, slice their stomachs with the dullest blade I can find (perhaps a foil would do...or maybe...a rusty spoon...), artistically disembowel them, and let them marinate in their own blood for a few hours before hanging them from a streetlight and entertaining myself by seeing how far their tongues would come out of their mouths. Whatever, boys will be boys.  I read  urlLink Forever...  by Judy Blume. Very graphic.  urlLink My next victim.   I didn't get to watch the Grammy's because I had to finish my English term paper. Words can describe just about anything with the exception of how pissed that made me.  I need a shower. See y'all soon, I promise.        
      
</post>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #2:   I have a scar at the very top of my nose. I got it when I was younger, from swimming into the side of the pool. Twice.
      
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie    This isn't completely possible. But to help you get to know me, and to give me something to write when my brain isn't working, I'll post random shit about myself.  Sounds fun, huh?  Enjoy.   Random Fact #1:   My preschool teachers thought I was dyslexic because I used to like to write my name backwards on everything.
      
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Pardon My  French  Freedom    You know what fucking sucks?  When you have to try  so  goddamn hard for  so  fucking long to get over something and just let it go.  Especially when, once you finally do give up on that something, you find out that it hasn't given up on you.  It doesn't suck, it blows.  Hell, fuck it, it sucks  and  blows.
      
</post>

<date>23,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I Wanna Read...     urlLink this.   I've heard interesting things about it...
      
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Bomb Iraq    Alright now children, here´s a merry little song:   (Sung to the tune of "If You're Happy And You Know It Clap Your Hands")  BOMB IRAQ !   If we cannot find Osama, bomb Iraq. If the markets hurt your Mama, bomb Iraq. If the terrorists are Saudi And the bank takes back your Audi And the TV shows are bawdy, Bomb Iraq.  If the corporate scandals growin', bomb Iraq. And your ties to them are showin', bomb Iraq. If the smoking gun ain't smokin' We don't care, and we're not jokin'. That Saddam will soon be croakin', Bomb Iraq.  Even if we have no allies, bomb Iraq. From the sand dunes to the valleys, bomb Iraq. So to hell with the inspections; Let's look tough for the elections, Close your mind and take directions, Bomb Iraq.  While the globe is slowly warming, bomb Iraq. Yay! the clouds of war are storming, bomb Iraq. If the ozone hole is growing, Some things we prefer not knowing. (Though our ignorance is showing), Bomb Iraq.  So! here's one for dear old daddy, bomb Iraq, From his favorite little laddy, bomb Iraq. Saying no would look like treason. It's the Hussein hunting season. Even if we have no reason, Bomb Iraq.  -Kindly stolen from http://www.domdummaste.se/bomb_iraq.html
      
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        A Little Familiar    My dad took me, my big brother, and himself to Foxwoods and Mohegan Sun (the only two casinos found in extremely exciting New England) today.  Foxwoods seemed like someone ate dinner at a buffet before they stuck their finger down their throat and threw up a casino.  But Mohegan Sun was absolutely gorgeous. Everything had a larger-than-life feel to it, yet it was intimate and personal in all the right places, in all the right ways at the same time. It was great. It was perfect. That's simply  how it's done.   My little feild trip today brought back a shitload of memories. Just being in that kind of atmosphere again- It's no Vegas, but I won't be getting any closer anytime soon. Who would've guessed that even the dirty parking garages and ashtrays would make want to cry. The noise in the casinos- a hum of people talking, chips clanging, machines beeping and playing their annoying as fuck little songs- It's something you can't get anywhere else, and I love it.  But now I miss home.
      
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Where's the plane...    I wanna protest this war.  Fly me to Iraq.   I'll stand in front of a fucking American army and let them shoot me down. Maybe that'll change their minds, save the lives of everyone else.  
      
</post>

<date>12,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        The Great Things in Life     urlLink This  is perfect.  Check the title bar...
      
</post>

<date>06,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        "Dead Battery" Audience Reflections    (In case you were wondering... Dead Battery  is the 10-minute play I wrote for the Young Voices program- part of the Huntington Theatre Company's education department. There was a staged reading of it and a handful of other students' plays or play segments, read by B.U. acting students. It was pretty damn cool.)   What did you like most about this particular moment of the script?   -"Captures strong emotions" -"The line: 'It wasn't anybody's fault'" -"When the female character explains to the male character that he was actually responsible for the dead battery" -"How the story unfolded gradually through the aid of dialogue...we didn't know what had happened initially and I like the suspense this created." -"Good to deal with friendship in the context of tragedy" -"The setting" -"The scene was something I could easily visualize" -"A great turning point and opportunity for character and plot development was created when he tried not to remember the battery swap" -"The guilt" -"The intensity of the situation" -"The portrayal of a person shut down by grief" -"The build up to 'Chapters 3 and 4' (or whatever the homework assignment was) so that those simple words could carry such weight" -"The flowing of the scene" -"The argument about the parents' deaths" -"How the story unfolded" -"The closing scene" -"The true feelings that are shown" -"How 'Dead Battery' had such a deep meaning" -"I like how the characters work off each other. My favorite part was: 'No, I lost my best friend.'" -"The raw emotion" -"Liked the use of the photo to symbolize something more" -"The dialogue and the resolution"   How would you describe the characters?   -"Despite the strong conflict between them, they need each other" -"Real, sad, meaningful" -"sad-frustrated-angry-depressed-withdrawn" -"Yearning for comfort and love" -"Real" -"Typical teenagers, changed forever by a tragedy" -"Just like you and me" -"Young and tender with room to grow...I would love to see where this could go" -"Angry and guilty with repressed issues" -"Believable, sounded realistic" -"Honest and real" -"Depressing" -"Well-gauged and realistic" -"Hurt and isolated" -"Sensitive and responsive" -"Honest" -"Pained from a great loss" -"Thoughtful, sorrowful and lonely"   What words would you use to characterize the work?   -"Emotionally stimulating" -"Bittersweet" -"A tale of reconciliation" -"Powerful" -"Tragic- but the end was so sweet, I almost cried" -"Important" -"Very emotional" -"Real and very moving" -"Room for lots of soul searching" -"Displaced anger" -"Moving" -"Touching" -"Deep and charming" -"Poignant and real" -"Clever and thought-provoking" -"Sad and touching" -"Complex" -"Scars only beginning to heal" -"The characters made me care about them; has the feel of real adolescent interactions"    
      
</post>

<date>04,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Pathetic, Yes, But Way to Promote Self-Assurance!    Do a google search for "baconly".  You'll see. 
      
</post>

<date>04,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        As for You, Troy Donahue...    I know what you wanna do.
      
</post>

<date>04,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I Feel Your Pain    This might sound kinda (or really) stupid, but I think the guy I end up falling in love for life with will have divorced parents.  It's not like I'll judge a guy less for having a non-disfunctional family, but one of the things I look for in someone is the capability to understand me (if that's even possible).  He'll know what if feels like, and know how much it hurts. He wont be one of those people who tells me to "just get over it, Maddie, it happened years ago".   I'll be able to talk to him about one of the most fucked up things, and he'll listen and  get it .  I mean, admit it, if the guy can do that he deserves  some  brownie points, right?  
      
</post>

<date>03,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Finding Myself...and Letting You All Know That if I Ever Use Title That Corny Again, Permission is Granted to Shoot Me on the Spot    When someone asks me what I want to be when the time comes to get a job, I can't honestly answer. I'm completely serious when I say I want to be a UPS truck driver ('cause if you know me at all by now you know I'm just odd like that), but I don't want to do that and only that. I want to do something else, where I can help people in ways other than delivering cardboard packages (....gorgeous ones...may I add....*cough*...) to them.  I do want to go to Columbia. With the current academic position I'm in, what I want quite possibly won't be what I get. I am trying to change this. I think I'm going to start taking more english honors classes during the summer, and start engaging in more activites that might look good on my college application. Unfortunately, one of these activities isn't creeping through a parking lot with engine-hungry-sugar, exhaust-pipe-happy-potatoes, and a baseball bat, but with the right medical care, I think I'll manage.  One thing I definitely will keep up with is writing on a regular basis. I have no proof of this, but I feel like putting my brain on paper (or computer screens...whatever) helps me analyze myself more easily. Putting my thoughts into words comes natrually to me, and I guess I should be thankful for that, if self-analysis happens to be a good thing. But, dude, look back at my posts from the beginning of my blogdom and compare them to what I write now. I amaze myself with how much I've matured. Don't get me wrong here- I still am an immature, naive freshman, but at least I recognize it, and if not embrace it openly, I accept and tolerate it. Just think- six months ago I though I knew everything my brain would allow. Now, I look back on my "old" (by half a year) self and laugh. And hell, I'm not even fifteen yet.   (OK, I realize that at this point I'm sounding a bit egocenteric, but go with the flow.)   Will I ever reach a point where I stop learning and put my knowledge to use in life? In ways, I guess not. Life's not about reaching goals like that. It's about working as you go along, putting the knowledge you've gained so far to good use, and being open about learning more. You can never know enough, and if you think you have it's only because you don't know that you don't know the things you don't know yet because you don't know them yet. Get me? Didn't think so (and I don't blame you...try figuring it out when you're really bored one day because it's not worth wasting valuable time on. Like that riddle.....How can you use only a jug that holds exactly 3 gallons, a jug that holds exactly 5 gallons, and an unlimited water supply to get exactly 4 gallons in one jar? Keep in mind the only exact way of measuring is by filling the jars- they don't have gallon marks on them.)   Off topic, off topic, I don't give a fuck.  My overall point: Life's wierd. But isn't that the point to everything? 
      
</post>

<date>05,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        The Best Word in the English Language    "Main Entry:	de·fen·es·tra·tion  Pronunciation:	(")dE-"fe-n&-'strA-sh&n Function:	noun Etymology:	de- + Latin fenestra window Date:	1620 : a throwing of a person or thing out of a window - de·fen·es·trate  /(")dE-'fe-n&-"strAt/ transitive verb"  ...http://www.m-w.com/   Update:   Oh, and theres  urlLink this...             
      
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Dude    Wow.  Ok, let's start with Grease. True, it happened a month ago, but I have neglected to sign onto Blogger and express my feelings during this time. Better late than never, man. The day of opening, we advertised in the cafeteria during all three lunches using our very own singing and dancing skills, so not a single person in school that day could say they didn't know about Grease. I also stole a Grease flyer off the wall. I couldn't help myself. My kleptomania took over when I saw that purple-and-yellow-polka-dotted poodle. Especially when it said "Tickets: Wedensday, $5.00. Thursday-Saturday, 8:00." underneath the beloved, diseased canine. I then went home to get ready. Opening night was awesome. It's completely impossible for words to do justice to the energy of opening night. That goes for any show. The next night, my family came. My dad had a telegram delivered to me backstage, along one dozen red roses later during the show. My mom gave me another boquet of roses. Fuck, I was just in the chorus. I'm honestly afraid to imagine what they'd do if I had a lead. I love them. Friday night's performance was probably the worst of the four, even though we still kicked some seriously obese ass. After the show, everyone went to Applebees and hung out 'till midnight. Saturday night, closing night, was pretty extreme. Despite the sadness of the last show, we had a full house and a standing ovation. We also all got programs. I played  Follow the Whoever-the-fuck-was-the-Leader  and had everyone sign my program. Directly after the show, we had strike, then all decided to go to Ruby Tuesday's. No....wait....Applebees. No, Bickford's. Hold on...T.G.I.Friday's. Dude....we went to Bickford's. That's right. Bickford's. After an hour of confusion, Joyce and I got a ride from Katie, one of the funniest people in the whole fucking Milky Way, and went to Bickford's.  Now, I'm not sure of the rules, but I don't think you're supposed to go to a restaurant, be seated, and order nothing but a water. Whoops. On the other hand, because of the fact that I was there with a hundred other people, I don't think they really noticed nor cared. La Fin. Well...of Grease, anyway.  Stay tuned. More of  Maddie's Life During Her Insanity-Leave  to come.
      
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Welcome Back, Maddie    Ok, so I wasn't exactly crowned 'Most Frequent Blogger of The Month' this time around, but can you blame me? Well, yeah, you kinda can. But I  have  been busy. Very. Busy.I'll catch you up, but it'll take a while. Be patient, please.
      
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Belated A Week and A Half    Happy Birthday to me, Ann Margaret, Jay Leno, Penelope Cruz, and yes, Saddam Hussein. (April 28)
      
</post>

<date>01,May,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I Know    I'm horrible.
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #6:   I shake the milk before I pour. I shake my yogurt too...
      
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #5:   I like cheese.
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Why I Love Yanina    Nina (9:48:09 PM): im a cow look .....BAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA Nina (9:48:14 PM): i mean listen
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #4:   I can't sleep with socks on.
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #3:   I suck. Not...literally....
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #9:   I sleep with a rhinoceros.
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #8:   I'm daft like Jack.
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #7:   I like to memorize liscense plate numbers.
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Excerpts From My 8th Grade Diary    So... Freshman Year is over and done with. Actually, it's been over and done with for more than a month now, but being the procrastinator I am, I can't write about anyting until it's a month overdue.   I wanted to look back on who I was before I started the school year, to see how much I've changed...and if you can think of a better way than this, by all means, comment your ass off.  Just hindsight on how stupid I really "was" *cough*...  (names have been changed to protect the innocent)    5/7/02  "OMG. Okay. Kathy read my entry from last night, and she says she'll help me change. That's kewl. The only thing is, I donno if everything I wrote last night is what I really want, or complete bullshit? I know I'm bored of myself, but I know I don't want to 'fit in'. I want to be my own person, not somebody else. Do I need to say any thing else? Okay°°" , yes, I decorated my writing with degrees,  "Boy time. James likes me. This isn't good. He's Kathy's ex, and I personally, this might just be me, I think he's just saying he likes me to get Kathy jealous, cuz we're such good friends, AND she's going out with his best friend Dick now. IF (big if...) he actually does like me, then I'm also screwed. I don't want to be any less than good friends with James, but I don't want to be any more either. Of course, I've gotten myself into the kinda shit I hate. You know the shit. The 'soap opera' shit...."   Oh, but you haven't seen anything yet...    6/9/02  "...My picky list: WHAT I LOOK FOR IN A GUY... -hes like a best friend, but we can be more than friends -he's very, unconditionally nice to everyone -very forgiving -loving/caring -smart/ 'deep' (like....I can get into big discussions with him) -completely completely honest -we can joke around and we both know when we're joking around with each other -but we can still not joke around sometimes -romantic but not lame -has a great sense of humor and loves to play around but also knows when to be serious -can admit when he does something wrong -isn't afraid to tell me when I do something wrong -doesn't let his ego get in the way of his thinking -can open up to me -will listen and talk to me when I open up to him -can practically read my mind -into the same things as me -can sing or dance or maybe even both -is perverted -confident but definetly not or concieted or self-centered -witty but not cocky -i can trust him with my life and he trusts me with his -WONT try too hard to impress me -doesn't lose his temper -gives good advice -likes grapefruit juice -respects my descisions -cares about me as much as i care about him  I'm a little bit picky, but only a little."   To top it off, my all-time favorite...    5/18/02  "...I want someone to love me. Not like my parents, because they have to. I want someone to want to love me. Can you imagine how that could make you feel? To know that by your mere existance, someone is happy? That you could make someone feel better by just being you, because they love you? You would feel so important and responsible. So loved. The word 'love' is tossed around so much, I don't think people understand just how powerful and precious it is.  Love, Mel  P.S. Spiderman is an awesome movie!"   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Not Too Bright Myself    I just noticed that I spelled Vegas wrong in one of my first posts. You'd be surprised at the number of people who actually search for "Las Vagas".
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Happy 4th of July    'Tis the season to blow shit up. Fa la la etc.
      
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        It Was 62° Last Night    Take me back to Vegas.
      
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        "The Pimpest Mix Ever/ Viva Las Vegas"    1) Adema...The Way You Like It 2) Rascal Flatts...Mayberry   (Watchin those cows roll by...)   3) Rascal Flatts...These Days 4) Rascal Flatts...Movin' On 5) Rascal Flatts...Too Good Is True 6) Rascal Flatts...Melt 7) LFO...Summer Girls   (I know....don't even bother saying it. Good song, though.)   8) Incubus...Warning 9) Jason Mraz...Curbside Prophet 10) Fenix TX...All My Fault 11) SR71...Right Now 12) Fenix TX...Surf Song 13) Beatles...Revolution   (Hehehe.)   14) Sugar Cult...Pretty Girl 15) Starting Line...Best Of Me 16) Yellow Card...Star Struck 17) 3 Doors Down...When I'm Gone 18) Mest...What's The Dillio 19) Mest...Fuct Up Kid 20) Lit...My Own Worst Enemy 21) Phantom Planet...California 22) The Ataris...Takeoffs And Landings  Go on....go dowload. Good dog! ;-P
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        *Sigh*    I've been infatuated since first sight.  The picture gives me goosebumps.  I even dream about our future together.   urlLink I think I'm in love. 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        LMAO     (on the phone)   Cassie: Seriously Maddie, you're every guy's wet dream.
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Remedy for a Really Bad Day    1)  urlLink Dirty Dancing ....over and over and over and over... 2) bacon  
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Different...But Not, Really    Over the past month or so, I've had quite a few encounters with people who...are not mentally the same as me.  Some people would say they're sick.  But they're not sick. They're just different, and there's nothing wrong with that at all. Hell, we're all different.  The people I have run into were all so friendly and outgoing. They just started talking to complete strangers like myself. I think this admirable, really. I smiled and talked with them. I didn't treat them with any less respect than I would show anyone else. I don't know why anyone would.  Some people do, though. And it actually hurts me to see it.
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #11:   My obsession:  medium Dunkin Donuts iced coffee with cream and 2 sugars (or sugar substituses, for my time on Atkins)
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Windows    It's so funny when you do something every day, but never truly realise what you're really doing, or what it really means.  Actually, the funny part is when you do realise.  I'm talking mutual recognition here. Like..when you brush up against someone or talk to someone. The one that gets me the most, though, is when two peoples' eyes meet. It could be purposely or accidentally, willingly, or not. Whatever the reason, or lack thereof, it happens all the time.  Forgive the cheesy names, but for example:  Little Tommy could be looking Little Dorothy in the eyes, telling her how lucky he is to be with her. Of course, he was staring at Little Cindy's ass five seconds earlier, but that's completely not the point.  Or...  Bored Student could be optically wandering the room while Mr. Tohkaloht's voice sings on without her. Longing for something to indulge in, Bored Student's eyes wander up to Tired Student's eyes, and for a moment, their eyes lock. Bored Student is also a victim of Social Anxiety Disorder, so the moment is not quite a moment, but a quarter of a second.  Or...  Suzie could be sitting in her room, thinking about why she had re-decorated the newly painted white kitchen walls with landscapes of greem and orange crayon. Hr cat walks in the room and stares right at her. Suzie takes this as a sign that it's time to play Princess Fluffy, and pulls out her doll clothes and nail polish.  What about...  Ms. S could be in a black-walled chamber with Mr. M. She smiles as she looks at him, his arms chained to the wall, and she takes out a whip.....You know what? We're gonna skip this one...  Well, I was thinking about what is actually going on when people's eyes meet.  By my looking you in the eyes, I would sort of be recognizing your existance, while at the same time, you're recognizing my existance and the fact that I'm recognizing yours. I'd recognize the fact that you'd recognize the fact that I was recognizing your existance, and...  Restrain yourself, Maddie. New paragraph.  ...you'd...  Now.    Anyway, it's pretty cool. It's like...for that that moment, however long it may last, both people are kind of reading each other's minds. They're kind of thinking the same thing, and they both know it.  (You know the 'they'...those people we always talk about, but never see?) They  do  say that eyes are windows to the soul... 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #10:   I think blood is the prettiest thing in the world.
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Oh, boy.    The excruciating persistance of sexually driven teenage boys never, ever ceases to amaze me.
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Danke, Herr Orff...    ...and now, we switch to latin...  "Amor volat undique, captus est libidine. Iuvenes, iuvencule coniunguntur merito.  Siqua sine socio, caret omni gaudio; tenet noctis infima sub intimo cordis in custodia;  fit res amarissima."  "O Fortuna, velut luna statu variabilis, semper crescis aut decrescis; vita detestabilis nunc obdurat et tunc curat ludo mentis aciem, egestatem, potestatem dissolvit ut glaciem.  Sors immanis et inanis, rota tu volubilis, status malus, vana salus semper dissolubilis, obumbrata et velata michi quoque niteris; nunc per ludum dorsum nudum fero tui sceleris.  Sors salutis et virtutis michi nunc contraria, est affectus et defectus semper in angaria. Hac in hora sine mora corde pulsum tangite; quod per sortem sternit fortem, mecum omnes plangite!"  -Carmina Burana 
      
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Life    It just likes to tease me.  And it keeps on doing it...
      
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #12:   I play dumb. A lot.
      
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Just Thought I'd Stop in and Say Hi    SirenXOX:	they usually avoid me too,, Her:	oh yea as evident by this past year Her:	no as evident by this past month SirenXOX:	but now just sit in their path so they cant avoid me SirenXOX:	 either hafta walk over me or stay n chat SirenXOX:	lol SirenXOX:	metaphorically speaking here Her:	right Her:	you just have this thing that attracts guys and i must have lost mine Her:	maybe its under my bed SirenXOX:	i just dont give a fuck n e more SirenXOX:	i dont attract shit SirenXOX:	other than dog hair Her:	maddie don't argue with me, just sit and stay quiet Her:	cause i think that's bullshit SirenXOX:	its not Her:	one guy [CENSORED], Her:	then you [CENSORED] Her:	and then you're [CENSORED] Her:	don't tell me you don't attract shit Her:	cause its not true SirenXOX:	honestly, if i didnt just stop giving a shit wat they thot n say fuck it if they like me they do if they dont they dont, if i didnt start takin chances id still b where i was a yr ago Her:	it just used to be so easy for me and then i got to highschool... SirenXOX:	i used to just be too worried ab wat ppl thot n id never take a chance n get to know a guy SirenXOX:	its all in ppls minds SirenXOX:	everything is SirenXOX:	i finally realized that n sed fuck it, im taking chances whether i liek it or not SirenXOX:	lol SirenXOX:	thats what the rf is all about hun Her:	rf? SirenXOX:	RF Her:	rf??? SirenXOX:	the permanent marker thats been on my wrist since january SirenXOX:	well SirenXOX:	ink anyway Her:	oh right Her:	and what does rf have to do with not caring what ppl think? SirenXOX:	i coulda gotten to know him SirenXOX:	he was one of the coolest guys ive ever met Her:	and then you woulda been more depressed SirenXOX:	but i was stupid n shy SirenXOX:	no Her:	when he died SirenXOX:	cause i woulda had the chance to share stuff with a person that awesome SirenXOX:	but i was all ohh no, hell never like me, nevermind SirenXOX:	well im not gonna let that happen again SirenXOX:	who knows, i might not even make it to graduation Her:	yes you will SirenXOX:	u cant promise that SirenXOX:	u couldntve promised him SirenXOX:	all im saying is, life is too short, have fun while u can SirenXOX:	and with things like that, getting to know people, what do u really have to lose Her:	i'm just not who i used to be Her:	not on the inside anyways Her:	i'm so sad all the time SirenXOX:	i know how that feels hun SirenXOX:	lol truuust me SirenXOX:	ive been thru it SirenXOX:	u just hafta make up ur mind SirenXOX:	u can be happy if u want Her:	about what SirenXOX:	u have control over ur emotions Her:	how can you be happy if you don't know why your sad SirenXOX:	there r so many things to be happy ab SirenXOX:	just SirenXOX:	look at the good side of things SirenXOX:	theres one to everything SirenXOX:	its how we make it thru life SirenXOX:	u can make ur own happiness  Auto response from Her: Her:	I dunn want to talk online cause no one's on... call me. SirenXOX:	its all in our heads hun SirenXOX:	everything   True: this would have a much stronger effect if we typed like humans, but what can I do? 
      
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        School Sucks    Sorry about the essays and shit that have been floating around here.... I need a way to send my essays to myself at school so I can print them out there, and they don't let us use our email there.  The essays suck too, I know.
      
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         What Music Can Do to You    Scratch the previous post :-)
      
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        The Freakin Queen of Boredom    I feel weird. Slightly...bored. With life.  I feel like nothing impresses me anymore. For a while, my life really was very boring. But then it got crazy and unpredictable, and now I'm so used to it being that way. I've become desensitized to the unattainable. It's like gaining a tolerance for a drug: the drug of life.  Now, everyone and everything just seems to be. Not good or bad. It's like I can see everything, but I can't see the beauty in it all.   Beauty can be either good or bad; it's mysterious. Mystery has seemed to disappear from my life. Nothing feels larger than life anymore.  When you're sad and hurt by things, your emotions are pulled to an extreme. When you're happy and amazed by things, your emotions are pulled to the opposite extreme. Your emotions get exercise, and the good makes up for the bad, leaving you, at the least, releived.  Dealing with so many things and not being affected by them can be very overwhelming. When nothing brings out much emotion in you, it all builds up. It all builds up in the middle, and you have no way of expressing how things affect you.  I can describe tons of things. But I can't describe how this feels.  I don't like it, though.
      
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Get Me Out of Here    Get me out of this town, get me out of this state, get me out of New England.  I need to be able to think.  I need to be able to breathe.  Get me out,  I can't handle it all anymore .
      
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        I Dove In At First    Then I backed off.  Then I dove in again, head first.  Then I got scared.  But now, I'm starting to warm up.
      
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Taking a Step Back    It feels like closure is coming to this whole situation.  It's funny, cause if I had had a choice, it's not the ending I would have chosen in the beginning.  But looking back on it all, this ending satisfies everyone. It's a good thing, which proves that I can't tell what will be for the best and for the worst when I'm so wrapped up in things.  I've stepped back and looked at the whole picture, and I like what it looks like.  It's a good ending, and still just a beginning ;-)
      
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Bear With Me, And Don't Mind All the 'Maybe's    I think I'm turning into an emotionless bitch.  I don't feel things that I used to.  Some people could argue that this is a good thing, but I just found some things out. Things that should make me jealous. But I'm not. I'm not jealous. I can't feel this emotion that has driven me to do the stupidest things in the past.   Is it because I can't care enough about something to cry when I know it's not, and never will be true? Do I just not have it in me to love something so much that once it's no longer mine, I feel worthless and lost?I hope that's not true. Maybe it's not. Maybe I'm finally becoming the person I want to be.  I've always had this ability to love. Atleast, people think I have. If I can't be counted on to do anything else, people count on me to love them, be there for them, and  care  about how they feel.  This is the person I wanted....want to be. I want to be selfless and generous and caring. I want to be someone who will put others' feelings before my own.  All the time .  I've pretended to be this person for so long. I felt so fake, though. This wasnt natrual. I felt like I was forcing myself to care about other people and forget about myself. People would ask me sometimes: "How the hell are you always so nice?". I'd tell them that it was just how I was.   I lied.  I want everyone (who cares) to know this: It's hard. It's so hard for me to be the person everyone sees me as. It's not who I am. It's who I wish I was. I don't know...it's hard.   Maybe there is some truth to the Maddie people see. There has to be something inside me that makes me want to be like this so badly.  I want to care.  I really do.  Maybe this lack of jealousy isn't because I didn't care enough about what I lost. Hopefully it's because, finally, I'm truly being who I want to be. And I'm happy for my friends, because I know they're happy.  And that's all I could ask for.  That, and for the snow to fucking stop!  
      
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Helloween and Other Business    I have so much to say, and don't know where to start. Maybe the beginning would be good.  Allright, let's get all chronological on their asses. Or something.  Friday, Massachusetts decided to be unbearably cold, trying to give us all frostbite. Almost every single school in the state was closed, but considering the fact that the highschool was the only one in the town open in the first place, we had to suck it up and go anyway. I took my A and C period exams and went home. Shaina came with me, and we hung out at my house for a while, which was awesome because I haven't really had a chance to just hang out with her in forever. I wanted to go out that night, but didn't have a ride or a destination, so I stayed home.  Saturday's morning and afternoon were both pretty boring. I just sat around, took a shower, talked to people, and oh yeah...one of my best friends decided he hates me. I don't know, he said some things that really made me think that he was just expressing what everyone else thought and was afraid to say. Some of my friends disagree with him. I really have no idea what to think. I dunno, but it hurt me to find out that he felt that way. I guess I have to try harder, and I will.  Saturday Night: I'll admit that I actually wanted to go to the Linkin Park concert, and probably would have if it wasn't sold out. I don't regret not going, though. All That Reamins and a couple other bands opened for Helloween, this English heavy metal band from the 80's. The show was at the Worcester Palladium, and I went with Catie. We got there a little late, and they made Catie take her jacket off cause it had spikes in the hood, so we missed the first band, but it was cool. We met some of my big brothers friends there. I talked to Pat for a while, but the other guys literally jumped straight into the mosh pit the second they got there, and disappeared after that. We saw Blistered Earth, and I thought they were really good. They did a good job getting a reaction outta the audience, considering most of the crowd hadn't shown up yet, and people were still just getting into the show. All That Remains was up after that. I always enjoy their performances, and I know other people did too. They've got some really good stuff, and are all really talented guys. They're goin' places. I still dunno what's going on with Matt :\, I didn't even talk to him last night.  Anyway, this crazy Helloween band was amazing! I loved them, and next time they come around here, I'm definitely going to see them. They were so awesome. Without a doubt- and Catie agrees- best concert I've been to all year. The guys were hilarious onstage; they were all complete characters. There was one guitarist with an ashtray attatched to his mic stand and just smoked and rolled his eyes the whole time. He looked real comfortable up there in his leather pants. The drummer had some crazy mohawk thing goin on, and went completely insane up there, the poor drums. The bassist had long, crazy, curly, layered 80's hair and had so much energy, he seemed inhuman. The lead singer was hilarious, comparing the audiences energy to his boner. He had this awesome voice, and was so....how do I say this....odd....onstage. It was perfect. Then there was the gorgeous guitarist who was smiling the ENTIRE time. Oh boy.  Anyway, it was fun, and the crowd cracked me up. They were all either my favorite people; psychotic teenage metalheads, or older helloween fanatics. There was this one guy who looked like he was in his late forties moshing with the younger guys, and he had to be drunker than anyone I've ever seen. Hilarious. Great night.  Of course,this morning completely sucked, but I won't get into details. I'll get over it. I hope.  Blah.    
      
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Thank You Bri!    I copied and pasted from  urlLink Bri's  blog. I'm filling this out in place of my little retrospective thingymajig. I have no new year's resolutions anyway, but Happy 2004!!  -Basics- Full Name: Madeleine Eileen Lauve Nickname: Maddie, Mad, Mads, Mel, Mad cow, Mango, Mamat, Llama Birthday: April 28, 1988 Eye color: Brown Height: 5'1 haha Natural Hair Color: Brown..? Nationality: American! 1/2 Irish, 1/4 French, 1/4 Mexican...or close enough to that Lefty/righty: Righty Glasses: Nope Braces: Not yet  -Preferences-  Coke or Pepsi: I don't care Wake up early or Go to bed late: Go to bed late  Red or Green apples: Green BSB or NSYNC: Can I pick the "or"?  Pants or Shorts: Shorts Bath or Shower: Hmm...I'd pick shower but I love bubble baths....both Black and White or Color: Black AND white Hot or Cold: HOT Winter or summer: SUMMER Sing or Dance: ahhh, both Ocean or pool: Ocean Pool or Hot Tub: Both.... Sunrise or Sunset: both are amazing but its easier to watch the sunset..cuz then i dont have to get up early  Ski or Board: Board  Love or Lust: You need some of each.....but love Cats or Dogs: both....and chickens Read or Write: write Kiss or Hug: both Night or Day: both :) Roller Coaster fun or scary: awesome One or Two Pillows: one Rich and Unhappy or Poor and Happy: Poor and happy CD or Tape: CD Pen or Pencil: Pen Money or fame: fame Mustang or limo: mustang 7up or Sprite: I still don't care Looks or personality: Looks help....but personality wins  -Random Questions- Were you named after anyone: My middle name is for my mom's mom Do you wish on stars: yes  If you were making a movie about yourself, would you play you: I wouldn't make a movie about myself...lol Do you like your handwriting: not really What is the 1st priority in your life: i'm not sure...probably same as Bri......making sure everyone is happy What is your main goal in life: to change the world in a positive way...even for just one person Any bad habits: oh man What store would you never be caught dead in: If you know me at all you know this question doesn't apply to me If you were another person, would you be friends with you: Depends on who I was Do you pray: Not much anymore... Do you trust others easily: incredibly Do you have a journal: No....  Do you like sarcasm: Of course not... What is your name spelled backwards: Enieledam, sounds like a disease :) Do you have a special someone: :)  If so who: :) If not, do u have a crush: well,  on him ^ haha If so, who: :D Who is the prettiest person you know: hard question Do you watch a lot of TV: Not really What is your favorite show: Smallville, Gilmore Girls, Niptuck....that one's fun, haha. Buffy!  -If you were stranded on a desert island...- Who's the one person you would want to be stuck with: at this point...Matt If you could bring 5 people who would they be: monkey, llama, flamingo, rhino and mango! What 3 things would you bring: a cell phone, something that makes music, and a cruise ship Do you believe in fate: I don't not believe in it  -FAVORITES- Color: Red and Gold Time of day to eat: I don't care Book from your childhood: Definitely not those Madeline books Coloring utensil: does paint count? :) Food: kfc popcorn chicken, chocolate, mango, macaroni and cheese, italian, chinese, MEXICAN, brazilian! Drink: non-alcoholic? grapefruit juice, water, chocolate milk... alcoholic? anything with tequila, rum, whiskey or brandy :) Snack: chocolate Dessert: chocolate Animal: i like em all :-P....humans!  Holiday: 4th of july, even though I'm not patriotic at all Sports: swimming, FOOTBALL, soccer...yeah School Subject: chorus! oh...academic? then...english for now Day: Saturday Place to vacation that you've actually been: Vegas...but that's more like going home than going on vacation...so...San Diego Movie: Memento, Donnie Darko, Matrix lol, Moulin Rouge! Movie Quote: "Don't take life too seriously...you'll never get out alive." "The greatest thing you'll ever learn is just to love and be loved in return."  Number: 7, 13, 93 Song: House of the Rising Sun, Have You Ever, Don't Wanna Miss a Thing, California, I'm Movin' On (thank you Katie :P)...and others for now, those are my long term faves... Band: I don't know, I like too many diff. kinda of music to pick a fave band... Singer: same^^^ Flower: orchid Card game: poker!  -WHAT COMES TO UR MIND WHEN U HEAR- Money: stupid and pointless Gum: I hope he liked it :) Blue: the color of the thingy when I go to erase bri's answers! lol Frogs: Cassie Candy: I want some Weird: me too Santa: What I wanna be when I grow up, haha Duck: squeak. wait...ducks dont squeak... Cookie: Yummmm   -Yes or No- Do you believe in love at first sight: Not exactly Get married: nope Do you want kids: I'm not sure If so how many? lkdlihflijsdfolajslfjlsjfj! Do you like anyone at the present time: YES Do you eat chicken fingers with a fork: haha no Do you sleep with a stuffed animal: If I feel like it! Do you type with your fingers on the right keys: lolol nope Do you like sleeping: yeah...but I wish I never had to do it...does that make sense? Didn't think so... Do u have anything pierced? ears, trying to get eyebrow Do you pluck your eyebrows: nope   -Family...- Who are your siblings: JJ...I mean Jules, and Nicky Do you get along with your rents: every once in a while. lol...we get along usually, too bad they don't. Do you have any favorite cousins? I love em all, but Jessica is my sister! Are your parents together or divorced: divorced In your family who are you closest to: My cat Do you associate with other relatives: yup  Lol..I added a few.
      
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Heeere we go..    I have so much to catch up on. I guess I'll do each subject seperately. Oh man.
      
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Pain    Physical pain is so funny.  You can just tell yourself that it's not real and it goes away.
      
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        There's This Boy...    And I kinda like him.  I think.  Only problem is, he might have a girlfriend.  Oh, and he doesn't know I exist.  Yet.
      
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        On Drama    Oy.  .6 score and 22 days ago, my highschool hosted a little annual event we like to call Theatre Exchange. Pretty fuckin' cool. We had the school to ourselves for the entirety of a Saturday. Starting at 6AM. Oh boy. It was pretty exciting though, having drama companies that were full of kids that were EXACTLY LIKE US only from Ashland, or Reading, or something. There were six schools there, ours included, and we hung out acting like idiots for a while. Then, we grouped off into workshops where we learned about improv, stage combat, character development, and dance. We ate lunch (thank you, Subway) and we sat in the auditorium watching each others' plays for HOURS. It was really amazing. Our play, the one we would soon be taking to the Massachusetts High School Drama Guild Festival, was  Creation of the World and Other Business , by Arthur Miller. It seriously kicked ass. This drama company is the only thing I will be conceited about in my life. It's  that  awesome. Anyway, after the plays, we all gathered back in the cafeteria for a pizza party/dance thing. I met a few really awesme guys. One of them was adoreable, and I ran outside before he got on his bus to leave in the freezing cold in a tank top to get his screenname. I then found out he had a girlfriend, but it's been really cool to talk to him anyway, hes a good guy.  We took the show to prelims, and we didn't move on. One of the judges had us as her #1 choice, but the two of them couldn't agree on which plays to send on to semi-finals, so they didn't send any of their top three choices. That's bull, but we loved our play, and everyone else did, and we are incredibly proud of everyone. Sorry, I sound like Suzie Sunshine or something, but we had too much fun to be sad about the experience. Fun, fun time. The handcuffs only heightened the fun.  O:)  Now we're working on  Fiddler on the Roof , and trust me, it will be worth seeing, so come if you can. I'm only ensemble, a "daughter", but I'm havin a blast, and our main cast is so cool. I love you guys.  I saw my mom's play at New Rep,  Threepenny Opera . A very weird show, but it was so, so great. This is the same group of people (mostly) who put on the production of  Sweeney Todd  last year, which my mom also worked on, and that was THE best peice of theatrical art I have ever experienced. Hey, I'm not the only one who thought so. It recently won, like, 10 Ernies.  I'll keep you updated. I think now I'm supposed to say something along the lines of "Go Drama". So... Go Drama.  Ok, that sounds stupid. You get the idea.
      
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        So, Um, Yeah.    I was looking at my friend Adrienne's blog today, and I finally missed mine. It's been a while, yeah, and I kept saying "I'll update" and saying "I'll update" and, what a shocker; saying "I'll update."   I'm updating.  So, ha.  Now, let's get this party started. 
      
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        A Little Info on My Favorite Song     The lyrics we all know:   There is a house in New Orleans, They call the Rising Sun  And it's been the ruin of many a poor boy, And God I know I'm one   My mother was a tailor, She sewed my new bluejeans  My father was a gamblin' man, Down in New Orleans   Now the only thing a gambler needs, Is a suitcase and trunk  And the only time he's satisfied, Is when he's on a drunk   Oh mother tell your children, Not to do what I have done  Spend your lives in sin and misery, In the House of the Rising Sun   Well, I got one foot on the platform, The other foot on the train  I'm goin' back to New Orleans, To wear that ball and chain   Well, there is a house in New Orleans, They call the Rising Sun  And it's been the ruin of many a poor boy, And God I know I'm one.   The traditional lyrics:   "There is a house in New Orleans They call the Rising Sun. It's been the ruin of many a poor girl, and me, O God, for one.   If I had listened what Mamma said, I'd 'a' been at home today. Being so young and foolish, poor boy, let a rambler lead me astray.  Go tell my baby sister never do like I have done. To shun that house in New Orleans they call the Rising Sun.  My mother she's a tailor; she sold those new blue jeans. My sweetheart, he's a drunkard, Lord, Lord, drinks down in New Orleans.  The only thing a drunkard needs is a suitcase and a trunk. The only time he's satisfied is when he's on a drunk.   Fills his glasses to the brim, passes them around. Only pleasure he gets out of life is hoboin' from town to town.  One foot is on the platform and the other one on the train. I'm going back to New Orleans to wear that ball and chain.  Going back to New Orleans, my race is almost run. Going back to spend the rest of my days beneath that Rising Sun.  When I was young, a few years back, us lads who thought we could play guitar had to master the first few bars of this tune. Back in the early 1920s, the name "Rising Sun" was attributed to brothels. The traditional version of "The House of the Rising Sun" speaks, not of a boy's experience, but of a girl's. Fact was, the Animals did not write "The House of the Rising Sun" If you look at the really small print on their 1966 album, The Best of the Animals, you'll find it was only arranged by Burdon / Chandler / Price / Steele / Valentine. According to folklorist Alan Lomax in his book Our Singing Country (1941), the melody of "The House of the Rising Run" is a traditional English tune and the lyrics were written by Georgia Turner and Bert Martin (both from Kentucky). Above are the traditional lyrics from Lomax's book. Did the House of the Rising Sun ever really exist? A guidebook called Offbeat New Orleans asserts: 'The real House of the Rising Sun was at 826-830 St. Louis Street, between 1862 and 1874 and was named for its madam, Marianne LeSoleil Levant, whose surname translates to The Rising Sun'. But no one knows for certain..."( http://www.houlston.freeserve.co.uk/houseoftherisingsuntraditionallyrics.htm )
      
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #14:   I've fallen in love with the entire human race.  People are  so  cool.
      
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #13:   I always use those optional commas.
      
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        What About That Dude Named God?    Religion....where do I start?  Both my parents were raised in catholic families, and attended catholic school some point. In my Mom's case, that point would be her entire life until college. Anyway... of course, my parents raised me and my brothers as catholics, taking us to church every sunday and holiday, and ensuring our reception of first communion.  I guess that all kind of fell apart when my parents' marriage did. We still attended church, but only on special occasions. After a couple years, we stopped going altogether.  But, in the past six months or so, I've begun to become increasingly interested in religion again. The only problem is, I've decided that I don't particularly like Catholicism. Watch Stigmata. That's kind of how I feel, only a tad bit less extreme. I'm still kind of confused.  I go to The Root every once in a while, which is a religious group that meets once weekly after school. I have some good friends who are avid participants. Really frickin awesome kids. A couple of them, who attend a Protestant church, invited me to go with them, and i went a couple of times. It felt really good to be involved with religion again, but I still wasn't sure if that was the path I wanted to be on. So I tried the UU church with Mom. Very, very interesting. But definitely not what I'm looking for. So, I kind of stopped going to church for a few weeks because I didn't know where I wanted to go, and I didn't have anyone to go church-taste-testing with, because my mom started working again.  Then: the rally. The kids from The Root put together a Christian rally, and had bands play, kids tell their stories, and an evangelist change people's lives. I'll admit it, during his  little  speech, some things he mentioned hit so close to home that I started to cry. At the end, he had kids come up to the stage who weren't "right with God". I'll let you define that for yourself. I went up. It was really cool, because all the kids at the stage were kind of proclaiming in front of everyone the fact that they were going to try to live their lives for God from that point on. There was such a sense of spiritual unity. Plus, it was just fun :)  So, I'm going back to my Protestant friends' church again. I went tonight, for the Good Friday service, and I'm going for Easter, and hopefully the sunday following that, and the one following that, and the one following that....  I'm still not sure if this is exactly where I want to be, but I really do like it, and I love my friends for being so inviting and helpful.  God rocks.
      
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Why I Slept Until 2:00PM Today    Cause this time I actually have a reason.  I usually hate blogs that are just "So this weekend I....", but it's all I really have to write at the moment.  So this weekend, I had fun.  After school Friday, my neighbors gave me two tickets to the WBCN River Rave. They were looking for someone to give them to because they won the tickets and weren't planning on going. They were box seats. I wasn't complaining. I need to bake some cookies for my neighbors or something...that was too cool of them. Then my mom took me to the mall to buy presents for my friend Erin and my friend Nina. Then I went to Erin's house for her birthday party. It was really cool, cause she's homeschooled, so she dosn't go to my school. Obviously. So she had a bunch of very different friends from many different places, and I didn't know any of them. I loved it. I met a whole group of new people, and thye were all really great kids that I'm glad to know. I'm also really happy for Erin, I think she enjoyed the party a lot. So, I spent the night there, and went home early Saturday morning to start getting ready for my friend Nina's sweet 15.  She's Mexican, so instead of a sweet 16, they ahve a sweet 15, and it's s big deal. It was a formal party, and she had a group of friends who were kind of her bridesmaids of the occasion. I was one of 'em. SO...Afetr I took a shower and stuff, I went over to Joyce's house and we got our hair done. Then we stopped by my house to pick up our dresses and stuff, and went down to Nina's house. We got dressed and took pictures, then took a limo over to the party. We did this big enterance thing, where we all came in in couples, lined up, and held roses over Nina as she walked in with her "guy". Then we gave Nina her roses, and sat down at our special little table. In came the Mariachis. Those guys were so cool. That's what I wanna do when I grow up. They sang to her, and she cried, and they kept singing, and then they went onstage and sang some more. She had her dad change her shoes in this big chair thing, from slippers to silver heels, to symbolize her growing up. Then we ate and danced. At 10:00 we, her special friends, did the waltz. It was cool, even though the DJ messed up the song at the end, nobody could really tell. Then we sang to her and she cut the cake, and we ate more, and danced more, and everyone went home at about midnight. We cleaned up and got to her house by 1:00, then hung out there while she opened presents and watched a movie and listened to her parents' friends play guitar and sing in spanish in the kitchen. I loved it. I'm so happy for Nina, cause she spent such a long time planning the party, and I think it kicked ass.  We got to sleep at about 5:00 AM, then woke up at 9:30 cause Joyce and Devan and Jorge and his friend Jose had to go home. Then Shaina left, then Nina and I slept for a couple more hours. Then we walked to Burger King, then ate, then slept. Then slept. Then we got ready and drove down to Mansfield to go to the River Rave. One of my presents to her was one of the tickets. We were a couple hours late, but we still got there in time to see most of the good bands. Box seats are so cool. It's VIP, so they were really good seats, and we had our own   little waitress lady come around to take our order. We ordered drinks and a pizza and a smoothie. Fun stuff. Bands? The Darkness was AMAZING, as well as The Offspring, who was headlining. Dashboard Confessional had good music, but, performance-wise they fell a little short. New Found Glory was fun. P.O.D. Kicked A-S-S. I honestly wasn't expecting them to be that good, but they were. AMAZING performance. Wow. Then we waited in the parking lot getting hit on by drunken boys and watching people set off fireworks for an hour until my mom came to pick us up. Let me just tell you, I love drunk boys at rock concerts. They are SO funny. Then we drove back to my house, and fell asleep in our clothes 'till 10:00, when my mom woke up up to go upstairs cause she had someone coming over, and we were drooling on the couch. We went up to my room and slept until 2:00PM. Then Nina went home.  There you have it; my Memorial Day weekend. 
      
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Happy Birthday to Me.    Let's just forget the fact that my next 12000 posts will be of things that happened loong ago. Let's rewind to April 28.    Okay, I'm done.  So, I wake up Wednesday morning and go downstairs to find presents and cards all over the kitchen table. (I won't go into detail with the presents, but I got a LOT of DVDs and a LOT of money. Kinda.) $160 from my dad, $210 from my mom, and $30 from my godmother. All going towards my guitar. I'm hoping to get a Schecter. I still need more for that, though. So, I clothe myself and leave the house.  I get on the bus, and Cassie hands me a large-buttocksed bag (like my attempts at cutting down the swearing?), with two cards from her, one from her mom, and two funny as hell shirts. I love that girl.  I get to school, and we have an AM collaboration day. For you non-Hamtown-High-School-go-ers, they just means we have an hour of free time in the morning. The students do, anyway. So I'm sitting with my friends, and Shaina comes to school. She knows how badly I want a guitar, and she promised me she'd get me one. She kept her promise. She hands me a little box with the card written on the outside in glitter-pen, and inside is a little guitar case. I open it up, and, lo and behold, I have my very own 10 inch Fender Strat. It even has its own little stand you can put together. I love that girl as well.  Then, Vanessa went around the school with David putting posters up that had a picture of me two years ago, and said "If you see Maddie Lauve, wish her a happy sweet 16!" and so on...I love them as well. I love them too.  THEN, Kristen went around putting stickers on people that said "HAPPY B-DAY MADDIE!" on random people.  I just love my friends. ALL of them.  It was kinda funny, cause people I didn't even know would wish me a happy birthday in the halls.  Crazy.  Anyway, after school I had Fiddler rehersal, and then i ate with my family. THEN we went to the grocery store and i picked out everything i wanted for my cake, and got more sugary food to eat that night.  I also spent the entire day wishing people happy birthday after they did so to me. Cause when it's Maddie's birthday, it's everyone's birthday. It only confused about 98.12% of them.  Everyday should be my birthday.  
      
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Spring Break    I can't remember half the week.  The other half of the week I spent sleping in the back of the car while my older brother, my dad, and I drove from Hamtown to Rochester, NY...then to Amherst, MA...then back to Hamtown. I went with my brother as he checked out a few colleges he's been accepted to. University of Rochester and UMASS Amherst are definitely going to be possibilities when I apply. Great schools. He chose Rochester, by the way.  On the last Saturday of vacation, I went to my second cousin's bridal shower. She's so beautiful, and I wish her and her soon-to-be husband the best. They're both the kind of people who seem slightly shy, yet polite, friendly, and engaging (no pun intended). Like...people who, though they won't tell you so, they know more about life than you do. I like those people. And it was cool to see my family. Although watching someone open gifts of kitchenware and lengerie for hours on end isn't the kind of opportunity I'd jump at any Saturday, it was great to see my cousin so happy. The day wasn't for me, it was for her, and what matters is that she enjoyed it. I think she did.   That night, I went to a dance practice for Nina's party, and she threw my a surprise birthday party. I love her. I was sitting in their basement on the couch, and her older sister Erica came in with an ice cream cake that had "Mango" written on it, and a big vanilla scented candle on top. :). Then I opened my present and card, and I have to say it again: I love Nina.   Too bad I corrupted her.  After that, Erica drove us to the Rufio/ Senses Fail concert at the Palladium, and first of all, it kicked ass. I tainted innocent Nina, and got her crowd surfing. It was good fun. I can't even remember how many times I went up that night. Then she spent the night.  Then, sunday was slightly less hectic, and on Monday: back to school.  Good times.   
      
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Mango    I've been SO busy lately, but I want to record it all. So...I'll be writing a lot in the next few days. Enjoy, I guess.
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Ok     1. take your blurty (blogger) username and replace each letter with the corresponding number (a=1, b=2, etc.). if your name contains numbers, you'll need to convert them to letters first before you can convert to numbers.  sirenxox=(19, 9, 18, 5, 14, 24, 15, 24)   2. add all of the numbers together to create a kind of super number.  128   3. make a note of the first digit of this number, then add the digits of the number together.  11   4. find the post of this number in your blurtay (blog). if you don't have that many posts, add the digits together again. keep doing so until the number is smaller than your pathetic number of posts.  09-16-2002   5. take the digit you noted in step 3, and count that many words into the post.  1 = "He"   6. use the resulting word in a google image search, and select a picture from the first page.  7. post the results for us all to see!  since i can't post pictures...  http://www.home.no/andreasaa/he.jpg  too bad I couldn't open the picture with the crossdresser....
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Part One    There's a family from Vegas that my family has always been very close with. My mom's best friend Joni, her husband Rodney, and their son Joey.  Joey scared his parents when he popped outta the womb. He was born with Spina bifida. He had to have surgery right after he was born, and even then, the doctors thought he would never be able to walk, and that he would be severely hanicapped, both mentally and physically. Joey got very lucky. He's now eleven years old, and he's turned out to be one of the smartest, funniest, nicest, and most responsible little boys I have ever met in my life. He's a very healthy kid, and a very cool kid. He has had some problems, though. A lot of the same problems that my older brother had....socially and fundamentally and what not. He's going to be tested for Asperger's Syndrome, which is what my brother has. It's a form of autism, and given the signs, Joey is very likely to have it. Anyway, there's a school that's great for kids with this disorder, which is the school my brother went to for four years and eventually graduated from. It helped him  so  much. Joey and his mom Joni visit us a lot. they come down at least four times a year and spend a week or more with us each time. They love New England, and think there would we so many mor opportunities for Joey here. So, they were planning on staying here for the summer and looking at houses, then once Rodney had finished up with work in Vegas and Joni had picked out a house up here, They'd have Rodney come up with all their stuff, and live here. Joey came about two weeks ago with Joni, and Joni stayed for a while, then left Joey here so she could finish up some business in Vegas.  This was totally cool, cause Joey's like a brother to us.  Then Rodney got sick. Joni called a few days ago from Vegas to tell us that Rodney was in the hospital. They had found blood clots in his leg, and they were going to have to perform surgery to remove them. She didn't want us to tell Joey yet. I guess she didn't want him worrying. She was waiting until after the surgery.  I heard the phone ring at 1:30AM this morning, cause I was still awake, but I didn't think of much besides the fact that since my mom had woken up, she'd be coming downstairs to yell at me for not being in bed. She came downstairs, but she didn't yell, she just asked me to sleep so I'd be able to wake up for school. This was weird, but I was just relieved that I wasnt in trouble.  When my mom came into my room this morning to wake me up, she told me. I laid in bed for another twenty minutes trying to understand what she had said. The words that came out of her mouth were perfectly clear and understandable. What I didn't get was the idea the words formed.  I got on the bus, and cried.  I daydreamed my way through algebra, and skipped chorus with Erin to go to the library. She helped me a lot, and gave me some really great advice. She helped me find bible verses that made more sense of the situation, and we prayed.  I went to support during French and talked to Mrs. MacDowell. The I went to french and cried with my friends. I went to lunch, but I couldnt eat. Then I went back to support because I needed somewhere to sit and think. And cry. I just sat on the couch for an hour and a half. I had so much going on in my mind, I was shaking.  Then I went to gym to take my final exam, then eat, then sit. And think.  And I didn't even have the hard job that my brother and mom had. How do you tell an innocent eleven year old boy that his dad is dead?
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #16:   I'm afraid of commitment...
      
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Haha.    It's funny.  The people who say they don't care what people think about them are lying. Cause if they  really  didn't care what people thought of them, they wouldn't be anouncing it to the world. When people say they don't care what people think of them, all they really want is for people to think that they are the type of person who doesn't care what people think of them. But that's not really the type of person they are. Because obviously, they want people to think that they are a certain type of person.   If they really didn't care what people thought of them, they'd just shut up.  Yeah.
      
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #15:   This blog has gotten  so  lame.
      
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        ...And Party Every Day...    I got a guitar.  I got a guitar!!!!!  OK, so it's not  urlLink the one I wanted , but it's  urlLink a really, really nice one .  My mom was talking to my brother's friend's dad about how i wanted to spend a lot of money on a nice guitar, and he told her not to let Guitar Center rip me off. He brought her this guitar, which he bought on E-Bay for $60.00, and he gave it to me. He said I can learn on it, and if I like it, I can buy it for no more than $60.00, or I can borrow it until I know what I'm doing and I know what I really want in a guitar, and then I can go buy something bigger if I'd like. He's so cool.  So, I went and got it restrung at Centre Music, and I taught myself a song when I got home. I've never really played guitar before, so I have no idea what I'm doing, but I know one thing; I've fallen even deeper in love with tablature.
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Sunday:   Church Learning 7 worship songs an hour before service Funky basslines BBQ Burnt Dunkin' Donuts Chocolate Johnny Depp Chocolate and Johnny Depp (Chocolat :) ) Back massages Can return Seeing Lizz and Joe for .5 seconds Laying on the ground outside the mall Farts Chasing down boys with an SUV and pretending to make out in front of them Pizza Hut Orange Julius under a tire Not trying on dresses at David's Bridal "I think about 'chocolate' with you" Skinny Dipping Kind of..sort of accidently streaking Playboy    Monday:    Physics Getting really pissed off No Shaina :( Complaining to Cassie :) Walking to Jordan's Furniture Kelly's Kid's Meals Falling asleep in the reclining chair Mardi Gras Rocks and tunnels 3 cents short of not dehydrating Walmart "I care." "wooooah" Christina at McDonald's Walking up to hot guys in Target and asking for help: "We know the first part goes 'head and shoulders, knees, and toes'..." Drinking warm, old diet coke from the trash "If you get killed, I'll never talk to you again"    Tuesday:   Physics..again Shaina! Cassie...and Dan....and Nina! Sitting on the roof The Lighter Club Invigor8 Poor little red car on Rt. 30 Double sticks DSW minus Joe plus strange man plus strange shoes A. C. Moore plus Michele :) minus body paint Toys R Us shopping cart Jackass stunts Hobo's home....not a shortcut! Finally getting to Guitar Center...with the shopping cart Sexy Gibson Les Paul that looks like my Schecter but it's hotter cause it's not a Schecter it's a Gibson Les Paul :) Blue Ibanez Paul! "Hey listen...it's a rainforest!" Paul's good! So is the dude with the dreads! Holy shit, the dude with the dreads is playing the 6 string! Holy shit, the dude with the dreads is amazing! Lying against the bass amp :) Dave! Soloman and Sam...and some other people! "WILL ENTERTAIN FOR FOOD" Getting Paul in trouble because he let Nina speak over the intercom :) Finally leaving Guitar Center...with the shopping cart Tuning the guitar on the wall of McDonalds  :) 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Im at maddies house now, and its cool, cassie put an orange icsicle down my shirt.  Fun... We went swimming at larneds, so maddie let me borrow a bathing suit...or shall I say a dental floss?  Because for something that was worn last year....  lets just say tsk tsk madeleine, for shame!  Anyways not we are back, watching somethjing on vhs about 1992.  Have you guessed who this is?  Do you care?  YES! you do...so ill be nice and tell you that it's shaina.         who?
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Yeah    People are amazing and beautiful.  But they're not perfect.  They're just people.  Which makes them even cooler...
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Cognize Maddie     Random Fact #17:   I'd rather completely lose sanity than completely lose innocence.
      
</post>


</Blog>