<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Canadian Anglican Church's top governing body on the weekend elected an openly gay Vancouver priest as second-in-command for its historic General Synod, at which delegates will be holding a contentious vote on same-sex blessings...
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The governing body of Canada's Anglican church is meeting to discuss the highly divisive issue of same-sex blessings...
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bishop John Bryson Chane, head of the Episcopal Diocese of Washington, was to formally bless the relationship of a gay priest and his partner Saturday...
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bishop John Bryson Chane, head of the Episcopal Diocese of Washington, plans to formally bless the longtime relationship of a gay Episcopal priest and his partner next month at a ceremony in Maryland...
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of Washington will perform a blessing service for a gay couple at a Glenn Dale church in June, the first time a bishop has conducted the service in the diocese...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Don't miss the June 8 edition of the Advocate!  On page 20 is a brief story (with photo) of Bishop Otis Charles and Sanchez Paris' wedding.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On May 18, the Most Rev. Robert H.A. (Robin) Eames, Archbishop of Armagh and Primate of All Ireland, addressed the 117th dinner of the Church Club of New York at the Harvard Club in New York City, addressing the crisis in the Anglican Communion. A transcription of his recorded remarks follows...
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On May 18, 2004 Archbishop Robin Eames of Ireland spoke to the annual dinner of the Church Club of New York. Eames chairs the Lambeth Commission on Communion, appointed by the Archbishop of Canterbury following the meeting of the Primates of the Anglican Communion in Lambeth Palace, London, in October 2003.   Before his address, he met with ENS deputy director Jan Nunley, staff writer Matthew Davies, and Diocese of New York communications director Neva Rae Fox. The following is an edited transcript of their conversation... 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A conservative Episcopal group will protest a same-sex "wedding" taking place today on church property in the rural community of Leonardtown in St. Mary's County, Maryland...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As Presbyterians prepare to gather for their General Assembly in Richmond, Va., next month, a band of determined conservatives is advancing a plan to split the church along liberal and orthodox lines. Another divorce proposal shook the United Methodist convention in Pittsburgh earlier this month, while conservative Episcopalians have already broken away to form a dissident network of their own...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      May 18, 2004  A Response to the Oasis/California Advisory Board   I appreciate your letter and the clarity it aspires to. Let me take the categories that you raise and respond.   (1)“Marriage of a bishop”  In order for there to be a marriage of a bishop, the General Convention of the Episcopal Church alone has the authority to determine if bishops of the same sex can be married. When the headline of the San Francisco Chronicle states, “78 year old cleric marries same-sex partner,” I either have to embrace that as a fact on the ground or distance myself and the Diocese of California from the assertion. Mayor Newsom took a preemptive strike approach to licensing civil marriage. Were I to embrace the assertion of Bishop Charles’ marriage, I would be doing the same thing in ecclesiastical terms. I would be saying that the final arbiter of the Constitution and Canons and General Convention is Otis Charles.  This matter has many ramifications, but the essential one for me has to do with the episcopacy. Our Church puts great weight on the episcopacy. People who are gay or lesbian are ordained to the diaconate or priesthood regularly, and the Episcopal Church hardly notices. But when Gene Robinson is consecrated as Bishop of New Hampshire, the foundations of the Anglican Communion shake. When a bishop takes a bold step, it needs to be well thought out, authentic, and the author needs to be aware of the consequences. As long as Otis Charles is an assisting bishop of the Diocese of California, any bold thing he does, I do. He represents me and represents all of the people of the Diocese of California. If this 78-year-old cleric marries, it appears that I have authorized the marriage of a bishop outside the authority of the Episcopal Church. Then I position this Diocese and myself to be in the path of all the turmoil that follows and myself to be rightfully disciplined by the Church. I can’t have it both ways. Either I embrace his “marriage” or distance myself from it. I marvel that you claim that there is “nothing unusual” about Bishop Charles being married. Surely you realize that the Episcopal Church has not authorized same-sex marriages of bishops or priests or deacons or laity.  One more thought on this point. I wasn’t sending any signal to the clergy of this Diocese about our clergy. This was entirely and only a bishop-to-bishop matter for me. Obviously there are ramifications, but the central matter is between a diocesan and an assisting bishop.   (2) You ask, “Why is he no longer an assisting bishop?”  Two responses. One has to do with accumulated frustration. When I discovered that he is an advocate for taking enthogens such as Ecstasy and for taking hallucinogenic mushrooms to have a closer experience of God and for encouraging Christians to do the same, I was deeply disappointed. I wrote an anti-drug statement to the Diocese to distance myself from his position.  Second, when I was asked, I told Donald Schell that Otis could have a celebration of his relationship with Felipe with two conditions. By no means was it going to be called a “marriage,” and Otis was supposed to stay away from the press. I didn’t want him to use this moment to send conflicting messages and/or to create a celebrity status for himself. I just wanted him to gather with his friends and loved ones for a blessing and celebration. When I picked up the newspaper and read about his “marriage” and his comments to the press, I felt deeply betrayed. Also it made me feel that I had betrayed the people of the Diocese of California by authorizing Otis Charles.  It turns out that there was a critical moment. Bishop Charles had been approached by the press for an interview. At that moment he could have telephoned me out of courtesy, collegiality, respect. But he chose to call a public relations expert instead. To be dismissed by an assisting bishop as having no episcopal relevance regarding the most volatile church issue of our generation is a gesture that hits its mark squarely. This did not seem to be the way an assisting bishop should relate to a diocesan bishop.   (3) Public relations  You write that it was “a public relations debacle . . . an embarrassing fiasco.” I agree. His article incensed many people. My actions incensed many people. Once a bishop of this Diocese “marries” in the newspapers, the mess begins. It did not have to be this way. But this is the reality that was set in motion with counsel from his public relations expert.   (4)Unofficial versus official policies concerning same-sex couples  Up to now, I think it has been important not to have a Diocesan policy. The Diocese of New Westminster (Vancouver) carefully adopted a policy a few years ago, and all hell broke loose. A great deal of the energy and resources of that diocese have since been used up in dealing with the aftermath of having an official policy. Also the former Bishop of Kansas adopted an official policy for the diocese and quickly retired. That diocese is still digging itself out from that action.  At the last General Convention we voted in such a way as to make official policies acceptable. One of the things it means is that every diocese is now free from having protracted conflicts over this matter or threats of discipline. If the clergy of the Diocese of California would appreciate an official policy, I would be glad to call together a group to work on the details. Or if you would prefer guidelines, I would be glad to elaborate on the ones now in place. At Clergy Conference I will give everyone an opportunity to be heard.  I take exception to one point in your open letter. At no time have I striven to make same-sex blessings a “dirty little secret.” One of our same-sex blessings was carried nationwide on ABC “Turning Point” during prime time. What I have worried about is the possibility of exploitation when the culture of the blessings services would be frivolous rather than sacred.  One of my items was left out of the present guidelines. I have always insisted that the couples have proper counseling prior to their commitment. I am deeply sorry that Oasis is not aware of that.  (5) Shame  You would want me to feel shame because of what has happened. “A little more shame.” I don’t feel shame. I am sorry that all of this unfolded. Ordained ministry holds together around trust. Sometimes people you trust prove not to be trustworthy. Bad moments happen. The tension surrounding the issues of same-sex couples that was there before this “embarrassing fiasco” remain for us to live in and to journey through in the power of Jesus’ Holy Spirit, who is our unity and strength. I don’t intend for us to be a people of shame. We are complicated and conflicted. But in the midst of our chaos moments there is still mercy and the call to achieve justice and the potential for new life and all the promises from our Saviour. Divine Presence. I am convinced that the day will come when the whole family of faith will honor in the best way the authentic relationships of love wherever they spring up.  God bless Otis Charles and Felipe Paris. God bless the wonderful conservatives. God bless the press. God bless Oasis. God bless the Diocese of California. We will all get there!  Faithfully in Christ,  The Rt. Rev. William E. Swing Bishop 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A STATEMENT OF THE BOARD OF TRUSTEES     OF EPISCOPAL DIVINITY SCHOOL                       MAY 20, 2004     On May 19-20, 2004, we, the members of the Board of Trustees of Episcopal Divinity School, met during an historic moment for the people of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts. Only two days before our meeting, the right of same-sex couples to obtain marriage licenses had become legal. Hundreds of people were responding to this unique opportunity and were already in the process of seeking the blessings of matrimony. For those of us within the Episcopal Church, however, there was a serious issue of obedience to the canons which bind us into community. The Diocese of Massachusetts had asked its clergy to refrain from performing such marriages in keeping with the national canons of the church. Thus, we were in the midst of a time of both intense celebration and of equally intense controversy. Like all Episcopalians, we were in the tension between matters of conscience and questions of community. In short, we were in a time of need for reconciliation.   Our first response was one of deep prayer and deep listening. We invited men and women from our faculty, students, staff, and alumni/ae to join us for dialogue and discernment. We heard the voices of our Gay and Lesbian brothers and sisters for whom this is a profoundly personal concern. We heard from those who supported a strict adherence to the canonical interpretation on marriage and from those who counseled direct action to allow our clergy to perform same-sex marriage. We heard the thoughtful opinions of ethical, theological, and ecclesiastical positions that comprise the parameters of justice on this issue. We prayed for the guidance of the Holy Spirit in making our shared response.   In solidarity with all those whose aspirations for full equality before the law have for so long been denied, in support of the Church to which we all proudly belong, and in the spirit of the mission of our school as a reconciling community, here is what we believe will engage a process of reconciliation in the days to come:   1. We endorse the statement of our President and Dean, the Rt. Rev. Steven Charleston, as published in his remarks to the "Blessings on the Eve of History" Interfaith Celebration delivered at Christ Church, Cambridge, on May 16, 2004, as accurately expressing the sentiments of this Board in regard to the issue of marriage. 2. We respect the authority of the Bishops of the Diocese of Massachusetts to ask that their clergy refrain from performing same-sex marriages at this time and request that EDS facilities be used consistent with that authority. 3. We respect the dignity of Gay and Lesbian Episcopalians who will consequently be denied the benefit of marriage services at EDS, and therefore, join the Ordinary of the Chapel in announcing that St. John's Chapel will not be available for opposite-sex, Episcopal marriages until further notice. 4. We recognize and will honor other Christian traditions that do permit same-sex marriages. 5. We pledge our support to the EDS faculty in immediately undertaking the task of preparing a strategy for actively supporting a change to the Canons of the Episcopal Church to either permit the marriage of same sex couples or to remove the Episcopal Church from the position of being agents of the state in performing any marriages. 6. We pledge our support to the EDS community in developing a specific educational resource to engage people of faith in overcoming the fear of same sex marriage by helping them to understand the moral, theological and social dimensions of this issue of human rights. 7. We invite the Diocese of Massachusetts to join us in an intentional dialogue to consider options for justice in support of GLBT persons. 8. We reserve for ourselves the right to review progress on each of these steps at our next and subsequent meetings and to determine if further actions may need to be undertaken to both accelerate the process of reconciliation and/or to express solidarity with the GLBT community.   In conclusion, we know that our decisions will not please everyone. We accept that reality as a prerequisite to any meaningful effort at reconciliation. We offer this statement not as our "last word" on the subject, but rather as an invitation to all persons of faith to join us in actively pursuing justice while maintaining community. Knowing how difficult that challenge is, we invoke the blessings of God through the power of the Holy Spirit, to help us as we pray together:    O Jesus Christ, you have called those of us who are near and those of us who are far  on the question of holy matrimony to come to the healing center of your love. For the  sake of that love, give us the gifts of your justice, your compassion and your reconciliation  as we work together to build your faithful community. For it is in you that we trust and  in your holy name that we pray. Amen.     
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      May 17, 2004 NY Times Op Ed Integration Day By ANDREW SULLIVAN     WASHINGTON- Today is the day that gay citizens in this country cross a milestone of equality. Gay couples will be married in Massachusetts - their love and commitment and responsibility fully cherished for the first time by the society they belong to. It is also, amazingly enough, the day of the 50th anniversary of Brown v. Board of Education, the Supreme Court ruling that ended racial segregation in schools across America. We should be wary of facile comparisons. The long march of African-Americans to civil equality was and is deeply different from the experience and legacy of gay Americans. But in one respect, the date is fitting, for both Brown and this new day revolve around a single, simple and yet deeply elusive idea: integration.    It is, first, a human integration. Marriage, after all, is perhaps the chief mechanism for integrating new families into old ones. The ceremony is a unifying ritual, one in which peers and grandparents meet, best friends and distant relatives chatter. It's hard for heterosexuals to imagine being denied this moment. It is, after all, regarded in our civil religion as the "happiest day of your life." And that is why the denial of such a moment to gay family members is so jarring and cruel. It rends people from their own families; it builds an invisible but unscalable wall between them and the people they love and need.    You might think from some of the discussion of marriage rights for same-sex couples that homosexuals emerge fully grown from under a gooseberry bush in San Francisco. But we don't. We are born into families across the country in every shape and form imaginable. Allowing gay people to marry is therefore less like admitting a group of citizens into an institution from which they have been banned than it is simply allowing them to stay in the very families in which they grew up.    I remember the moment I figured out I was gay. Right then, I realized starkly what it meant: there would never be a time when my own family would get together to celebrate a new, future family. I would never have a relationship as valid as my parents' or my brother's or my sister's. It's hard to describe what this realization does to a young psyche, but it is profound. At that moment, the emotional segregation starts, and all that goes with it: the low self-esteem, the notion of sex as always alien to a stable relationship, the pain of having to choose between the family you were born into and the love you feel.   You recover, of course, and move on. But even when your family and friends embrace you, there is still the sense of being "separate but equal." And this is why the images from Massachusetts today will strike such a chord. For by insisting on nothing more nor less than marriage, the Massachusetts Supreme Judicial Court has abolished that invisible wall that divides families within themselves. This is an integration of the deepest kind.    It is, second, a civil integration. That is why the term gay marriage is a misnomer. Today is not the day "gay marriage" arrives in America. Today is the first time that civil marriage has stopped excluding homosexual members of our own families. These are not "gay marriages." They are marriages. What these couples are affirming is not something new; it is as old as humanity itself. What has ended - in one state, at least - is separatism. We have taken a step toward making homosexuality a non-issue; toward making gay citizens merely and supremely citizens.  This is why I am so surprised by the resistance of many conservatives to this reform. It is the most pro-family measure imaginable - keeping families together, building new ones, strengthening the ties between generations. And it is a profound rebuke to identity politics of a reductionist kind, to the separatism that divides our society into categories of gender and color and faith. This is why some elements of the old left once opposed such a measure, after all. How much more striking, then, that the left has been able to shed its prejudices more successfully than the right.   I cannot think of another minority whom conservatives would seek to exclude from family life and personal responsibility. But here is a minority actually begging for a chance to contribute on equal terms, to live up to exactly the same responsibilities as everyone else, to refuse to accept what President Bush calls the "soft bigotry of low expectations." And, so far, with some exceptions, gay citizens have been told no. Conservatives, with the president chief among them, have said to these people that they are beneath the dignity of equality and the promises of American life. They alone are beneath the fold of family.    But this time, these couples have said yes - and all the president can do (today, at least) is watch. It is a private moment and a public one. And it represents, just as Brown did in a different way, the hope of a humanity that doesn't separate one soul from another and a polity that doesn't divide one citizen from another. It is integration made real, a love finally come home: after centuries of pain and stigma, the "happiest day of our lives."    Andrew Sullivan is the editor of "Same-Sex Marriage, Pro and Con: A Reader."   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Address to the Trustees of the Episcopal Divinity School, Cambridge, MA The Rev'd Elizabeth Kaeteon, rector and pastor  The Episcopal Church of St. Paul, Chatham, NJ Co-President of the AEC   I am pleased and privileged to be here with you this afternoon to be a representative voice of the alumni/ae of this wonderful, outstanding seminary.  I must leave early to catch a flight back home for a Vestry meeting tonight, but I would not have missed the opportunity to be with you today because I care deeply about this school and am passionately committed to its mission.   There are many ways to address the question of the use of the EDS Chapel as a sanctuary - in the fullest sense of that word - for the marriage of same sex couples.  I want to very briefly address three components: legal, theological and vocational.   In terms of the legal issues involved, I want to begin by stating what I learned from Dan Stevick in a course on Episcopal Liturgy and Polity.  In his wonderful succinct way, which quite correctly assumed that short statements were easier to learn and retain, he taught:  "National canon always trumps diocesan canon.  And, national canon is always trumped by the rubrics." He also taught that "liturgy precedes theology." I may not remember what I had for breakfast this morning, but here I am, 18 years later, still able to recite lessons learned in seminary.   I completely understand the logic of the bishops in this diocese in their decision.  The national canons are clear in defining marriage as being between a man and a woman.  And, one might rush to say that the prayer book is also clear.  However, I direct your attention to the rubrics found on page 13 of the BCP - specifically the third paragraph:  "For special days of fasting or thanksgiving, appointed by civil or Church authority, and for other special occasions for which no service or prayer has been provided in this Book, the bishop may set forth such forms as are fitting to the occasion."   I think this is the rubric which trumps national canon.  It allows for the development of an interim liturgy - until the national canons can catch up to the reality of the church - which may creatively and legally address the "special occasion for which no service or prayer has been provided in this book" for the "special day . . . appointed by civil . . . authority."     I want to stress the INTERIM nature of this liturgical development.  I do not wish to create a situation of segregation which insists that the living waters of our faith be distributed from separate but equal fountains.  Rather, I believe that this is the kind of creative, generous, and reconciling response that allows justice to be served without delay (and therefore not denied) and yet within the parameters of our institutional life of faith as defined by canon and rubric.     It also proves Dr. Stevick's well-taught axiom:  "liturgy precedes theology."  Thank goodness Mary said yes to God before the church could define the theology of the Incarnation or develop a theologically sound liturgy of baptism! Liturgy, indeed, precedes theology. But bold, decisive, prophetic action that is obedient to God's call precedes even liturgy.   And yet, it is directly to the point of theology.  What I learned here about the nature of God is that God's first impulse is always to love.  That Jesus, Emmanuel, God-made-flesh, is both love incarnate, love divine.  And, that the Holy Spirit, God's own Ruach which God breathed over the chaos which was before creation, continually inspires us to "do a new thing" and empowers us to take our place as co-creators (and, Blessed Sue Hiatt would say, "co-conspirators") with God.   What I learned here about the nature of leadership in community is that I am to model that understanding of God - to have as my first impulse the generous, gracious, inclusive love of God. To incarnate that love in every fiber of my being.  To be inspired and empowered to do a new, creative thing whenever the church-as-institution (as any institution is wont to do) seeks first not the risky Realm of God but rather, the security of its own salvation and preservation.    I learned that "perfect love casts out fear" in ways that are too numerous to mention here in this very short amount of time. Suffice it to say that it allowed this second generation Portuguese-American woman, who came to this prestigious (and then, very WASP-y) seminary with her partner and six children, to dare to dream the dream of God that I be one of God's priests.  I learned that fear makes one miserly and stingy, constantly in search of the "bottom line," willing to cry "Peace, peace, when there is no peace," able to sacrifice justice on the altar of expediency, content with even the illusion of security rather than embrace "the peace of God, which is no peace, but strife clothed in the sod."   It was here, living and working and learning in the seminary which loved so perfectly it cast out the fear of merger and joined with another seminary, that I learned about the important merger of the pastoral and the prophetic. It was here that I witnessed a seminary which had cast out the fear of retribution when it hired two of the eleven women "irregularly" ordained in Philadelphia that I dared to dream the dream of a God of full inclusion.  It was here, on my way to chapel, where I daily passed the statue of Jonathan Myric Daniels, who was martyred for the dream of God of racial equality. He is dead, but it was here that I learned that they can - and will - kill the dreamer, but they cannot kill the dream.    If other generations of seminarians will learn these lessons, then you, as Trustees, must not focus simply on theology or solely on the legal implications of this complex issue.  I understand that you have a sacred trust as fiduciary agents of this most amazing seminary and that your first impulse is one to protect and conserve, and I thank you for bearing the burden of that responsibility.   I urge you, however, to consider carefully the vocational implications of the questions raised by the use of the chapel as a sanctuary for ALL God's people.  What is it that God is calling us to do?  In the midst of this Kairos moment in the church, what is God's dream for this seminary and the role it will play in the church?  Can we dare to dream that dream?  Can we find the creativity, the generosity and the reconciling nature of God which is within each one of us and use it, not for our own glory or the glory of this seminary, but rather, for the glory of God?  That all who see and know of our deeds will give God praise - and even enthusiastically send a seminarian to this school, or make an additional and substantial contribution to enable our mission?   Once we respond faithfully to these questions of vocation, the theological, legal and even fiduciary implications of our decision will be in service of what God is calling us to do.    At least, that's what I learned here as a seminarian.  And, I trust, this vocational response remains the primary lesson that this seminary teaches - by word and deed and example.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, boys and girls, here's all the news that's fit to print from EDS:  In terms of presentation to the Board, Joan Martin was absolutely BRILLIANT.  She presented the "Ethics of Justice." I don't have my notes here, but essentially she said that the definition of justice must arise from those who are outside of the "norm" and the "norm" is defined by those in power.  She was at her teaching best.  Gay Jennings was the quintessential horse trader - we got +Gene and it cost us blessings.  Isn't that a better deal?  (How white and straight of her!) She went on from there to her "theology of chicken little" - if the chapel becomes a "sanctuary" then we'll strain our relationship with Bishop Shaw, we'll piss off bishops and loose seminarians, we'll piss off our benefactors and loose money, blah, blah, blah.  (Does someone know her enough to get to her?)  When I left at 3:45 PM, +Steve stood up and said he was hearing two options  1.  Declare the chapel a sanctuary and open it for ALL weddings.  2.  Declare a moratorium on ALL weddings and work with the Diocese of MA to develop creative liturgies AND changes in canon law in 2006.  A trustee stood up and said there was a "third way" - the middle way of not either/or but both/and (BLESS HIM FROM THE TOP OF HIS SHINY BALD HEAD TO THE BOTTOMS OF HIS PINK FEET!)  Declare the chapel a sanctuary and open it for ALL weddings while we work with the Diocese of MA to develop creative liturgies AND changes in canon law in 2006.  There was a good vibe in the room about that when I left.  I just heard from Alcurtis Clark who said that the jury was still out - no decision made yet - but that she felt that the board was leaning toward the moratorium (the safe bet) and working to create liturgies and changes in canon.  My take is that ain't nothing gonna happen like that at General Convention.    Bottom line:  It's a recommendation from the Trustees to +Steve.  It's +Steve's call.  It would be wonderful if some of you might find the time to call and/or email him and give him your support.  scharleston@episdivschool.edu  1 - 866 433 7669.   Film, as they say, at 11.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My favorite quote of all times comes from abolitionist and suffragist, Frederick Douglas:   Those who profess to favor freedom,  and yet deprecate agitation,  are people who want crops  without plowing up the ground.   They want rain without thunder and lightning;  they want the ocean without the awful roar of its waters.   This struggle may be a moral one;  or it may be both moral and physical;  but it must be a struggle.   Power concedes nothing without a demand;  it never did and it never will.   Find out what people will submit to,  and you have found out  the exact amount of injustice  which will be imposed on them.   The limits of tyrants  are prescribed  by the endurance  of those whom they oppress. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bill Wylie Kellermann and Ched Myers have a compelling article on  Same-Sex Marriage and Sacramental Unity , which starts with this:   In 1963, William Stringfellow - movement theologian, Sojourners mentor, and gay man - had the following to say about mainline churches who were pondering whether to join the struggle for African-American civil rights:  The issue here...is not some common spiritual values, nor natural law, nor middle axioms. The issue is baptism. The issue is the unity of all humanity wrought by God in the life and work of Christ. Baptism is the sacrament of that unity of all human life in God.   It's particularly good to see  Sojourners  publishing this piece.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I checked Lesser Feasts and Fasts - May 17th is open. And it seems to me that we could do no better thing than snap it up now before someone else takes it and make it a day to celebrate with grateful hearts the blessing of an Activist Judiciary. We just finished observing - with much attendant hoopla and festivity - the tremendous gift America received from the activist judges who in 1954 dared to overrule majority prejudice in favor of minority rights with the Brown vs. Board of Education. It was not a “quick fix” by any means: the decades following were filled with racial strife as the struggle for equal rights continued in the courts and in the streets. But it was undeniably a huge step forward: and one we look back on now with pride and gratitude and with some sense of amazement at the idea that the “wrongness” of the institutional, systemic bigotry that kept children from equal access to education had gone for so long unchallenged.   And so it was with bewilderment that I watched CNN on May 17th -- listening to President Bush - speaking live from Topeka - saluting the 1954 decision while the “crawl” under the live footage read “Over 1000 gay marriage licenses issued in Massachusetts. Bush reiterates call for constitutional amendment to ban gay marriage” - and soon we got to hear from our President another diatribe launched at “activist judges who dare to overrule majority opinion on this important issue.”  Excuse me? Isn’t that PRECISELY WHAT WE’RE CELEBRATING IN TOPEKA?  And I submit that it’s precisely what we’ll be celebrating 50 years from now when we observe the anniversary of the Massachusetts court decision that paved the way for making civil marriage available to same sex couples. The next few years - decades - will probably be as messy as the ones following the historic 1954 decision but the outcome will be the same: and I propose we get ahead of the curve for a change as a church and get a Feast in the calendar. Let’s be ready so when we get to the point where we look back with pride and gratitude and some sense of amazement at the idea that the “wrongness” of the institutional, systemic bigotry that kept gay and lesbian families from equal protection under the Constitution had gone for so long unchallenged. Let’s get some prayers and litanies, hymns and collects together and let us pray: Thanks be to God for the gift of the Activist Judiciary!  ==================  Susan Russell  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      “How could I not?” reflected Bishop Jon Bruno of the Diocese of Los Angeles, as he prepared to bless the union of The Rev. Canon Malcolm Boyd and writer Mark Thompson on the twentieth anniversary of their life partnership. And so he did, making history as he gave thanks for the surprises of human love.  This was the first blessing performed by Bruno as the Bishop of Los Angeles and since the “local option” blessing resolution passed at General Convention last August. In the past, the bishop blessed unions as a parish priest and has always supported the full inclusion of gays and lesbians in the church. Bruno also expressed personal reasons for blessing this couple. He and Boyd are old friends who protested for civil rights together in the south. Bruno added that there was just no way he could refuse a friend and colleague like Boyd, who has been a champion of human rights for most of his 80 years.  The service, based on the New Westminister rite, allowed for Malcolm and Mark to reflect on the occasion. Mark, admittedly nervous, expressed his happiness with his life with Malcolm and his knowledge that they stood up for many gays and lesbians in the church. Malcolm mused that for most of his 80 years, this blessing would never have been imagined, let alone possible. But, he confessed, convention has never colored their relationship. On his first date with Mark, twenty years ago, they danced together at in a fancy, upscale restaurant that didn’t even have a dance floor.  Bishop Bruno invited Malcolm and Mark to stand in full view of family and friends to declare their covenant to one another : promises to live together in love, to be faithful to one another, to support one another so that they might grow into maturity of faith in Jesus Christ and to do all in their power to make their life together a witness to the love of God in the world.  The bishop then instructed the couple to clasp each other’s hand so that he could wrap them with a beige silk scarf presented by Mark’s brother, John, and painted by Malcolm’s mother, Beatrice, half a century ago. The bishop pointed out the painted image on the scarf – a flock of cranes – and noted it symbolized good health, prosperity and the uniting of two families. After tying the scarf in a knot around their hands, Malcolm and Mark took turns pledging their love for one another.  The invited guests prayed for the couple and gave their promises to celebrate with them and stand by them in times of trouble and distress. Then, all, many with tears of joy in their eyes, raised their hands and joined the bishop in the blessing the union of these two loving and gracious men. How could they not?  ================================================= Written by Louise Brooks: All Saints Church, Pasadena CA   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One of our readers recommended this site.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here are the key paragraphs...  "We commit ourselves to ongoing prayer for the work of the Lambeth Commission recently appointed by the Archbishop of Canterbury and respectfully submit the following for their consideration:  "The Commission should include in its Report a specific call to ECUSA to repent; revoking and rescinding their decision and action regarding the election and consecration of Gene Robinson as a Bishop in the Church of God.   "Should ECUSA fail to comply within three months, the Archbishop of Canterbury and the Primates should then take appropriate disciplinary action, which should include the suspension and ultimate expulsion of ECUSA from fellowship and membership of the Anglican Communion.   "Recognition and full Episcopal and pastoral oversight should be given by the Archbishop of Canterbury and the Primates to those dioceses, parishes and laity within ECUSA who continue to uphold the historic faith and order of the Anglican Communion.   "Similar measures should be applied to the Bishop and Synod of the Diocese of New Westminster, Canada for their unilateral approval and implementation of rites for the blessing of same sex union."  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Remarks by The Right Reverend Steven Charleston, Dean of Episcopal Divinity School “Blessings on the Eve of History” Interfaith Celebration Sunday, May 16, 2004, Christ Church Cambridge Episcopal Sponsored by the Religious Coalition for the Freedom to Marry 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Integrity Welcomes Historic Day:  May 17, 2004 IntegrityUSA, an organization of lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people in the Episcopal Church, applauds the state of Massachusetts in its landmark decision to stop excluding its gay and lesbian citizens from the civil right of marriage. On the 50th anniversary of the end to racial segregation, history will also mark the beginning of the end of segregation based on God-given sexuality.  While we rejoice with our brothers and sisters who finally have an opportunity to live fully as citizens of the world, we deeply and profoundly regret the decision of the Episcopal bishops of Massachusetts to prohibit their clergy from officiating at a service of marriage for same sex couples, thereby limiting the fullness of their citizenship in the City of God.  We trust that the Spirit of the Living God, who loves all of creation abundantly and without restriction, will visit the hearts and minds of faithful people in Massachusetts, who are the church, the Body of Christ, and assist them in finding a gracious, generous, and creative response to the fearful, miserly and political reaction of the institutional church. Contact:  The Rev. Susan Russell, President, revsusanrussell@earthlink.net 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      NOTE:  You will be asked to subscribe/login to washingtonpost.com.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      VIA MEDIA USA  FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE  Contacts:  Dr. Christopher Wilkins (412) 831-1737 (412) 760-8817 (cell) ciwilkins@juno.com  The Rev. Dr. John Sorensen (518) 569-1494  http://www.viamediausa.org   Pittsburgh, Pa., and Plattsburgh, N.Y. — June 29, 2004 — Via Media USA (VMUSA), an alliance of groups seeking Episcopal Church unity, mourns the loss of a New Hampshire congregation but lauds efforts by two bishops who tried to prevent it.  Members of the Church of the Redeemer in Rochester, N.H., recently left The Episcopal Church because of their unhappiness that the Bishop of New Hampshire, V. Gene Robinson, is openly homosexual. A number of efforts were launched to keep the congregation together, including arrangements for oversight by the Bishop of Albany, Daniel Herzog, but to no avail.  “In spite of what has happened, there are hopeful signs in this unfortunate story,” said VMUSA Steering Committee Facilitator Christopher Wilkins. “In this case, two bishops worked together to try to help one parish stay united. We at Via Media USA are dedicated to efforts to maintain unity within the church during this difficult time in the full belief that there is room for everyone at God’s table. These bishops’ efforts are a sign that we can and should work together.”  Recognizing unrest in conservative parishes because of Robinson’s election last year, the Episcopal Church’s House of Bishops created a Designated Episcopal Pastoral Oversight (DEPO) plan to allow such parishes to be attended to by like-minded bishops. In an effort to keep the Church of the Redeemer from splitting, Bishop Robinson made arrangements for Bishop Herzog to oversee the parish and offered to return a popular priest who had been removed by a previous bishop.  The congregation apparently was advised to accept the arrangements by Dean William Murdoch of the Northeast Convocation of the Network of Anglican Communion Dioceses and Parishes, a group unhappy with sexuality issues in the national church.  “We are pleased that there was Network support for using the very generous DEPO plan devised by the House of Bishops, and we hope that the Network will now let the disgruntled parishioners depart in peace to find a more compatible church home on their own,” added Dr. Wilkins.  Via Media USA is pleased that both Archbishop of Canterbury Rowan Williams and the chair of his Lambeth Commission, Archbishop Robin Eames, were impressed with the generosity of Bishop Robinson’s proposals. The alliance is particularly grateful for the role played by Bishop Herzog.  The Albany diocese, home to two Via Media groups, recently joined the Network. Bishop Herzog argued that the move was designed to preserve, not to split, the Episcopal Church.  “Bishop Herzog has shown grace and charity, seeking to use the network constructively to enable the House of Bishops’ DEPO plan to provide episcopal pastoral oversight,” said Fr. John Sorensen of Albany Via Media.   Concerned Episcopalians of St. Lawrence Deanery likewise commended Bishop Herzog for his “effort and cooperation” shown in the attempt to resolve the New Hampshire conflict.  “Via Media USA prays that, should a similar opportunity arise for a parish to utilize the DEPO plan, all parties involved will find a graceful way to remain within our beloved church,” added Dr. Wilkins.  -end-
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gays and lesbians moved a step closer to ordination in the Presbyterian church after a legislative committee approved a measure that would partly lift the church's ban on gay ministers...
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The governing board of an Episcopal church in Durham voted unanimously this month to allow the blessing of same-sex unions among members of its congregation...
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Parishioners from the Church of the Redeemer in Rochester, New Hampshire, worshipped separately Sunday, June 27, after failing to reach a common ground following a yearlong dispute about Bishop Gene Robinson, the first openly gay priest to be elected bishop in the Episcopal Church...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We gathered at St. John the Evangelist in San Francisco on Sunday night for Evensong -- ending a grand day of Pride celebration by doing what Anglicans may just do best: immersing ourselves in the rhythm of our historic liturgy, surrendering ourselves to the beauty of our musical offerings, opening ourselves to the words our Lord has for us in our holy scriptures.   And these were the Living Words our Living God spoke to us in the gospel according to Matthew:   Do not think that I have come to bring peace to the earth;  I have not come to bring peace but a sword.  For I have come to set man against his father  and a daughter against her mother  and a daughter-in-law against her mother-in-law.  Matthew 10:35 – now THOSE are good old Biblical Family Values! Not that it was one of the texts that showed up on any of the picket signs on the Pride Parade sidelines this year – at least not that I saw. But while it may not be a text that the “family values” folks have latched onto, I suggest it is a text you remember the next time someone suggests that returning to “Biblical Values” would solve all our problems. Remember that these Holy Scriptures we treasure as part of our spiritual inheritance have never offered a quick fix -- an easy answer – a “sound bite” solution to complex questions of faith and family. And remember that no one knew that better than our Lord and Savior, who spent a great deal of his earthly ministry preparing the disciples ... unpacking the scriptures they inherited so they could apply them to the challenges in front of them … TEACHING them about what to expect when He sent them out as apostles.  And what is the teaching Jesus offered them – and us – in this text from Matthew? Well “peace at the price of justice” doesn’t seem to be on the list. “Don’t ask, don’t tell” doesn’t seem to be there either. Rather it’s about the cost of discipleship – the task of truth telling – the hard work of coming out … as a Christian.   I led a retreat not long ago with that title “Coming Out As A Christian” for the gay and lesbian community in Los Angeles and found – somewhat to my surprise – that for many participants coming out to their families as gay or lesbian was easier than coming out to their community as Christian. Let’s face it – Christian values have gotten a very bad rap.   We are surrounded by those who think they already know enough about being a Christian not to want to be one – and if their only encounter with Christian values is Jerry Falwell spouting off on Larry King Live or George Bush’s determination to write discrimination into the Constitution who would blame them? The sad truth is that the Good News of God’s inclusive love – entrusted to us by our Lord and Savior as His body here on earth – has been distorted by a kind of selective literalism that ignores the totality of the scriptural message and focuses instead on a few isolated and usually misinterpreted texts which are used to judge, to shame and to exclude.  Our task – our challenge – our call – is to offer our voices as an alternative to what I am going to name as that MIS-representation of Christian Values by those who preach judgment rather than justice, scarcity rather than abundance, hostility rather than hospitality. Justice – Abundance – Hospitality – THOSE my brothers and sisters are the Biblical Values we inherit – celebrate – are called to incarnate.   Values as old as the prophet Isaiah: “I have given you as a covenant to the people, a light to the nations, to open the eyes of the blind, to bring out the prisoners from the dungeon, from the prison those who sit in darkness”   Priorities as clear as these final words Jesus sends out with the disciples: “Whoever welcomes you, welcomes me ... and whoever welcomes me, welcomes the one who sent me. Whoever gives even a cup of cold water to one of these little ones in the name of a disciple, truly I tell you, none of these will lose their reward.”   "Whoever welcomes you, welcomes me." I take this to mean that hospitality is not an option for those who would love God. Those who love God must first love their all too human (and sometimes less than lovable) brothers and sisters. The reality of our faith is bound up in down to earth relationships – whether we like it or not. Here’s a story shared with me years ago by a woman named Dolores when I served her parish as a brand new deacon. It’s one of my favorites because it illustrates for me both how hard and how incredibly simple it can be to truly live into the Biblical Family Values we inherit.   Dolores writes: “I was raised in Ohio in a deeply religious Roman Catholic family where bias against those of different faith or color was not tolerated. Early incidents in my childhood had impressed upon us the fact that my father would not tolerate such behavior among us in his household. He often told us “We are all God’s children. God doesn’t discriminate … neither do we.”  Shortly after the start of World War II our local parish sponsored a Japanese-American family deported from California. Their two children – Joe and Amy -- were with our family until 1947. To me they were just another younger brother and sister to put up with … but to my sister Dorothy, Amy was her best and closest friend. They were inseparable. And it came to pass that a classmate of theirs was having a birthday party … and everyone from the class was invited … except Amy. When Dorothy protested, mother forced to bring her face-to-face the harsh reality from which our family life had shielded her: there were places that Amy wasn’t welcome because she was different than we were. Because she was Japanese.  Dorothy’s response was to refuse to attend the party herself. Her explanation? “If Amy’s not invited, I’m not invited.” I was so proud of my little sister … proud to be part of a family that took its stand against bigotry and bias. And I’ve always tried to go through life remembering the lesson my little sister taught me … and remembering all those “Amys” who aren’t invited to places I’m included without a second thought … and to remember that until we’re all invited everywhere, God isn’t finished with any of us yet.”  Indeed … God is NOT finished with any of us yet – but has certainly begun a good work as we celebrate our pride in who God made us to be and our joy in the work God has given us to do. But even AS we celebrate, let us not forget what is perhaps one of the greatest challenges we face: remembering those countless strangers still left at the gate yearning for a word of hope.   Our hearts must ache for those in parishes and dioceses, congregations and coffee houses who experience the Christian Gospel not in words of invitation to the banquet we share as God’s beloved but in words of exclusion, shame and judgment. Let us commit to take the joy and pride we feel in being God’s own – in claiming the blessing of God’s love for ourselves and for each other – and proclaim it with renewed energy wherever we can to this world in such desperate need of it. Let us refuse to settle for being invited ourselves – let us not rest until “we’re all invited everywhere.”   In the words of one of my favorite hymns:  "Nor let thy spreading Gospel rest,  till through the world thy truth has run Till with this Bread shall all be blessed,  who see the light or feel the sun."  My prayer is that we be given the strength and courage … the faith and fortitude … NOT to rest until that work is done – that dream fulfilled: that we be given the grace to live our lives in accordance with the Biblical Values we inherit -- with God’s requirements which are the marching orders for our spiritual journey.   What does the Lord require? The prophet Micah says it best: Do justice. Love kindness. Walk humbly with your God. And how do we do that?   · Do justice: By remembering … with Dolores … that until we’re all invited everywhere, God isn’t finished with any of us yet.  · Love kindness: like Dorothy, standing up when we encounter bias or bigotry … speaking out on behalf of those without power to speak for themselves.  · Walk humbly with our God: trusting that the gifts God gives us will be sufficient to accomplish the work God calls us to do … and allowing God to use us to be agents of change – to participate with God in making this world the place of blessing it was created to be. AMEN.   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bishop V. Gene Robinson of New Hampshire spoke to ENS's Matthew Davies about the decision of members from the Church of the Redeemer, Rochester, to break away from the Episcopal Diocese of New Hampshire...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Parishioners and vestry members from the Church of the Redeemer, Rochester, New Hampshire, decided June 23 to leave the Episcopal Church rather than acknowledge the authority of the Rt. Rev. V. Gene Robinson as their bishop. The parishioners' decision to break away from the Episcopal Diocese of New Hampshire followed more than two hours of conversation with Robinson at the church...
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Eames Commission has been accused of excluding the voices of gays and lesbians from its deliberations in trying to keep the Anglican Communion together...
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      An American diocese has dealt an “extraordinary”blow to hopes of keeping the Anglican Communion together by proceeding with the blessing of a same-sex couple...
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The consecration of the Anglican Church’s first openly gay bishop could be annulled in a bid to save the Communion from splitting over the homosexuality issue...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Archbishop of Canterbury's office has described as "extraordinary" a decision by the Bishop of Washington to carry out a "blessing" service involving a gay priest and his partner of 12 years...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Anglicanism's first openly gay bishop was invalidly consecrated and must be stripped of his post if the worldwide Church is to avoid schism, a leading conservative demanded yesterday...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In a time of great discord over the sanctity of same-sex unions in the Episcopal Church, Chane arrived, June 12 at St. George’s Episcopal Church, a progressive house of worship in Glenn Dale, to perform a same-sex blessing ceremony — the Episcopal faith’s equivalent of a civil union...
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       In his first public comments on the same-sex marriage controversy that has divided the Anglican Church, the Archbishop of Canterbury Rowan Williams expressed solidarity last night with the American Episcopal Church. But he stopped short of taking sides in the divisive issue...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Episcopal Diocese of Vermont unveiled new guidelines Friday for the performance of civil union ceremonies for same-sex couples, sparking a swift denunciation from conservatives in the 70 million-member Anglican Communion, which has been riven by issues related to homosexuality in the past year...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On the afternoon of June 15 I met with members of the Lambeth Commission under the chairmanship of the Most Rev. Robin Eames, Primate of All Ireland. Participating with me in this conversation were: the Very Rev. George Werner, President of the House of Deputies; the Rt. Rev. Arthur Williams, former Vice-President of the House of Bishops; the Rt. Rev. Charles Jenkins, the President of my Council of Advice; David Beers Esq., my chancellor, and Barbara Braver, a member of my staff...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Concerns about the effects of Ohio's new Defense of Marriage Act on plans to hold the 2006 General Convention in Columbus...  In response to Ohio's recently enacted Defense of Marriage Act and a proposed amendment to the Ohio State Constitution, which would deny rights and benefits to domestic partners, the council resolved to send a letter of objection to Governor Bob Taft of Ohio, the mayors and directors of the visitor and convention bureaus of Columbus, Cincinnati and Cleveland, and to the media.  The 2006 General Convention is scheduled to be held at the Greater Columbus Convention Center in Columbus, Ohio.   The letter states the position of the Episcopal Church as expressed by its General Convention, emphasizing that "domestic partner rights are basic human rights."   The council explained that the Act and proposed amendment "go well beyond banning same-sex marriages" and "may prohibit rights for domestic partners being granted by the state and its municipalities, counties, universities, and school districts." The law and amendment may also "prohibit Ohio courts from interpreting and/or enforcing domestic partnership benefits granted by private employers."...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Episcopal Diocese of Vermont on Friday unveils vows and liturgy to bless same-sex unions. Vermont is the only state to legalize civil unions. The church's decision is already drawing rebukes from conservatives. NPR's Barbara Bradley Hagerty reports...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Vermont's Episcopal Diocese has become the first in the country to develop a liturgy - a script for a religious service - in response to a state law making same-sex unions legal...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In a move that is likely to further inflame tensions in the global Anglican Communion, the Episcopal bishop of Vermont today will introduce two new rites, very similar to the liturgy for Episcopal weddings, for priests to use while presiding at civil unions of gays and lesbians...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Contact: Nancy Davidge at: ndavidge@episdivschool.edu  EDS CELEBRATES COMMENCEMENT  Honorary Degrees Awarded to Robinson and Peers, Among Others  JUNE 16, 2004, CAMBRIDGE, MA: Episcopal Divinity School concluded a banner year with its Commencement ceremony on May 20, awarding honorary degrees to such church leaders as The Rt. Rev. V. Gene Robinson of New Hampshire and The Most Rev. Michael Peers, retired Primate of the Anglican Church of Canada.  Archbishop Peers delivered the commencement address and used the opportunity to compliment Anglicans in the United States for resisting the war in Iraq and working for peace. “By knowing your church in your country, I know that the stories of your country which I see in the media are not the whole story,” said Peers, who was honored for his own stands for justice and equal rights.  Peers urged the 32 graduates to assemble a “survival kit” for work in the church today, including a commitment to “meeting” as Anglicans; the patience to invest time in efforts for social change; and a willingness to truly lead God’s people in discernment and action.  Peers was one of four distinguished figures who received the honorary Doctor of Divinity degree at the commencement service. The school also recognized The Rt. Rev. V. Gene Robinson, Bishop for the Episcopal Diocese of New Hampshire; Ms. Katya Fels, founder and executive director of a non-profit serving women who are homeless and in crisis; and Dr. Charles Willie, a  professor emeritus at Harvard and noted leader in the national church.   Robinson was recognized for more than being elected the first openly gay bishop in the Anglican Communion – and for weathering the ensuing storm with faith and grace. In her citation, The Rev. Karen Montagno, Dean of Student and Community Life and of the Chapel, noted Robinson’s emphasis on creating healthy congregations, resolving conflict, helping dioceses within Province I to collaborate, supporting clergy wellness, and advocating for housing, health care and justice for marginalized people within and beyond the church.  Fels was recognized for her work with On the Rise, a Cambridge-based nonprofit that responds creatively to the needs of women in crisis are unable to get adequate support from traditional social service providers.  She created the organization based on “the dream of a more humane and relational way to connect abused and chronically homeless and disenfranchised women with one another and their own inner resources,” according to Associate Professor William Kondrath, who offered words on Fels’ behalf. “You found ways to form relationships, build community, give voice and strength to women, and reward them for advocating for themselves.”  The final honorary doctorate went to Willie, a former national church leader and sociologist who taught at the Harvard Graduate School of Education. He was a major consultant for school desegregation cases nationwide and, in 1974, preached at the irregular ordination service for the first eleven women priests in the Episcopal Church.  Professor Carter Heyward, one of the priests ordained in that historic service, offered the citation of her friend and colleague. “Throughout [your career] you have had the amazing capacity to combine advocacy with academia and Christian faithfulness with prophetic ministry on all levels of the church’s life,” she said. “We honor you today, however, for your particular role as a ‘drum major for justice’ in the areas of racial equality, women’s ordination, public education, and social justice.”  Episcopal Divinity School is a respected center of study and spiritual formation for lay and ordained leaders with a strong commitment to justice, compassion, and reconciliation.  Formed in 1974 with the merger of Philadelphia Divinity School and the Episcopal Theological School, EDS offers doctor of ministry and master’s degrees, as well as certificates in theological studies. Located on an eight-acre campus just a few blocks from Harvard Yard, EDS is a member of the Boston Theological Institute, a consortium of nine eminent theological schools, seminaries, and departments of religion.  ###  Photo caption: EDS president and dean, the Right Reverend Steven Charleston with honorary degree recipients the Rt. Rev. Michael Peers, Dr. Charles Willie, Ms. Katya Fels, and the Rt. Rev. V. Gene Robinson on the steps of St. John’s Memorial Chapel.  Nancy J. Davidge Director of Communications Episcopal Divinity School 99 Brattle Street Cambridge, MA 02138 Voice: 617.868.3450 x302 Fax: 617.864.5385 Email: ndavidge@episdivschool.edu www.episdivschool.edu    
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As the Lambeth Commission on Communion prepares to meet, I want to put forward three perspectives from my part of the 'Global South' which I hope will offer support to the Commission in its challenging task. My prayer is to find restorative processes that open doors beyond painful division. We must develop new means for handling conflict and finding new beginnings, to share with the world for the good of the gospel...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Two members of Executive Council, sent as observers to a meeting of Via Media leaders, reported back to the council's Burlington, Vermont meeting in June that they were warmly received and thanked profusely for their presence at the gathering...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      At its annual diocesan convention June 12, the Diocese of Albany (New York) approved a resolution to join the Network of Anglican Communion Dioceses and Parishes (NACDP)....
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In a surprise 65-33 vote, the U.S. Senate passed legislation in June that would extend the Federal hate crimes law to include hate crimes based on actual or perceived sexual orientation, gender and disability, according to the Episcopal Church Office of Government Relations. The law currently covers race, religion, and national origin...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Eames Commission is meeting this week in Kanuga with Presiding Bishop Frank Griswold and three prominent leaders of the schismatic American Anglican Council.   Not invited and repeatedly rebuffed from contacting the Commission charged with finding a solution to the crisis in the Anglican Communion are two key groups that oppose the conservatives' schismatic agenda.  Though Eames has claimed publicly to be speaking with all parties, that is clearly not what is happening. In fact, Eames’ commission's only direct communication appears to have been with Griswold and conservatives.  When AAC leaders Bishop Bob Duncan of Pittsburgh, the Rev. Martyn Minns and Diane Knippers of the Institute for Religion and Democracy make their case this week in the gentle-shaded hills of the North Carolina denominational retreat center, they will have the floor to themselves. That's because none of the ‘Via Media’ groups that have organized in conservative-run dioceses in Pittsburgh, Albany, Ft. Worth and a handful of other places have even had their letters answered by Eames, much less been invited into dialogue.  It's the same story with Claiming the Blessing and Integrity, the coalition of gay advocacy groups that led in getting same-sex blessings recognized by General Convention last year and supported the election of Gene Robinson as the first openly gay bishop in the Episcopal Church. Similarly, Robinson himself, along with the New Hampshire diocesan nominating and standing committees have not been able to get through to talk to Eames.   "I have begged (on numerous occasions and via different venues) to meet with the Eames/Lambeth Commission, as have my Standing Committee and the Co-Chairs of our Search Committee," Robinson said. "It absolutely astounds me that they would only be talking ABOUT us, and not to us," Robinson said. "How would the African primates feel about a meeting on the treatment of people of color, with no people of color present?"  With no seat at the table as decisions are being made, the groups not invited to Kanuga are understandably anxious. "We are ready, willing and able to participate in the process and we respectfully request that Archbishop Eames enable us to be part of the solution rather than allowing us to be scapegoated as the source of the problem," said Claiming the Blessing Executive Director, the Rev. Susan Russell.  While Rosa Lee Harden, Executive Director of Every Voice Network, received an email from the Secretary of the Commission requesting a statement, “there has been no response to our follow-up requests for more information or conversation. As far as we can tell from our reporting, no other progressive groups have even been contacted to that minimal extent.”  In contrast to the way he's actually conducting his inquiry, here is what Eames has said publicly on multiple occasions about what he's doing: “I've been several times to the States. I have had open communication with most of the main figures. I have met most of those who wanted to speak to me personally, and in the next weeks I'll be meeting some others. I don't want anyone to feel that they're not being listened to. My ministry at the moment from the Commission's point of view is to listen and go on listening and in that process to ask the searching questions, as I can.”  Gay and lesbian activists say they have been told that they are not part of the conversation because the real issue is about ecclesiology: how the church can live together with differences, rather than homosexuality. And, they have been told, that framing of the issue comes directly from Archbishop of Canterbury, Rowan Williams himself.   From the continual stream of denunciations of Robinson's election from African and Latin American primates and their consistent focus on that single issue, along with the rhetoric from Duncan, et al, the claim that the fight is about how we do church rather than homosexuality is, frankly, hard to believe.   How we do church may be what Williams wishes were under debate. But the trio of conservatives partisans who were invited into the exclusive confines of the Eames Commission talks this week in Kanuga are openly using the single issue of homosexuality to try to create an alternative structure in the Anglican Communion where their conservative splinter group would be officially recognized.   Taking a leap of faith for a moment to imagine that it's a fight about how to do church and not a dispute over whether it's a sin to be a homosexual, then a second question arises. And it is just as troubling. Why has the growing network of ‘Via Media’ groups been excluded from Kanuga? Why have their requests to talk to Eames been rebuffed and their letters to the Commission gone unanswered?   Their problems are exactly those that Williams say are the real issue; how to stay connected when you disagree with church leadership. The leadership that the ‘Via Media’ groups are troubled by is that of their own conservative diocesan bishops, but if Eames' mandate is to talk about how to do church then why aren't the ‘Via Media’ groups at Kanuga?   Progressive Episcopalians of Pittsburgh, the first of what was to become the network of ‘Via Media’ groups, sent a page of testimony to Eames in February. Even though the Pittsburgh group formed in opposition to hard line tactics of Duncan himself, they got no response, while Duncan was invited to Kanuga.   The Rev. John Sorenson, a leader of Albany Via Media, emailed a Commission member to ask if he could speak to the Commission. He got no answer. Remain Episcopal, a ‘Via Media’ group in the diocese of San Joaquin, has also written a letter and heard nothing.  We know who is at Kanuga this week. What we don’t know is who Eames means when he says he's talked to most of the key parties. Every Voice emailed the Eames Commission to ask that question, and like everyone else received no reply. Eames has not talked to lesbian and gay leaders, even though even conservatives both here and internationally are clear that the question of their full inclusion is what is at the heart of the Anglican Communion dispute. He has not even talked to straight people in the leadership of the Diocese of New Hampshire, which is at the center of the storm.  And if, as Archbishop Williams apparently fondly wishes people to believe, the fight is really about how you stay united when you disagree, then seems to be no explanation for why Eames has not talked to the ‘Via Media’ groups.  When Eames says he is listening and asking searching questions who is he really asking?  Looking at what Eames says and comparing it to what he's actually doing, a searching question comes to mind. How reliable or accurate a report the Eames Commission can produce if they are only talking to one side?  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This new musical tells the story of Lucretia Crowell, a lesbian seminarian struggling to find her voice in a Christian church that won't ordain her. At Harvard Divinity School Luc meets Jane, a PhD student and falls in love. When she is honest about her lesbian identity she learns that her loving and supportive church will not ordain her if she is out.  Mary, her home pastor, advises her to stay closeted while Jane, her new lover, challenges her to speak the truth. For the first time, Luc is faced with defining her own voice and relationship with God, risking the loss of her new love or her lifelong dream to be a pastor.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A small but ardent group of unsettled Midwest Episcopalians gathered for a two-day conference on conservative thought at Christ Church Cranbrook, Bloomfield Hills, in the Diocese of Michigan on May 21-22. Approximately 200 people from Michigan and the surrounding states attended "A Place to Stand in the Midwest," to hear from and question some of the movers and shakers of an increasingly bellicose rebellion against the decisions made by the Episcopal Church last August, most prominently the consent to the election of New Hampshire Bishop Gene Robinson...
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Washington Bishop John Chane's blessing here late this afternoon of a same-sex relationship between the rector of St. George's  Episcopal Church and his long-time sexual partner prompted a protest across the street from the church and a prayer service nine miles away in Bladensburg...
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of Washington conducted a blessing service yesterday for one of the country's top homosexual rights advocates and his partner while protesters stood outside holding crosses swathed in black fabric...
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A church pastor and a Web page designer yesterday got as close to marriage as two same-sex Episcopalians can in Maryland.   During a service led by the Right Rev. John Bryson Chane, bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of Washington, the 12-year relationship between the Rev. Michael Warren Hopkins and John Clinton Bradley was blessed and their relationship recognized by the church...
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      MOST THIS AMAZING DAY: A Sermon for Michael & John Clinton St. George’s, Glenn Dale MD ~ June 12, 2004 ~ Susan Russell I Samuel 18:1-4, Romans 12:9-21, John 15:9-17  I can think of no better way to begin than with this poem of celebration, which does double duty as a prayer of thanksgiving:  i thank You God for most this amazing day:  for the leaping greenly spirits of trees and a blue true dream of sky;  and for everything which is natural  which is infinite  which is yes (i who have died am alive again today, and this is the sun's birthday; this is the birth day of life and love and wings: and of the gay great happening illimitably earth) how should tasting touching hearing seeing breathing any- lifted from the no of all nothing- human merely being  doubt unimaginable You? (now the ears of my ears awake and now the eyes of my eyes are opened) e e cummings  What an extraordinary privilege it is to stand before you today as we share with Michael and John Clinton most this amazing day – as we celebrate that which is natural which is infinite which is yes! What could be more natural than that two people should find each other, find love in each other and find themselves all dressed up on a Saturday afternoon -- standing in front of God and a church full of friends and family to declare that love in a service of blessing and commitment. Most natural – most familiar – and most amazing.   It is always amazing when two people find the courage to say “yes” to love – “yes” to commitment – “yes” to each other in this profound and public way. Yet on most THIS amazing day we celebrate not only the yeses that Michael and John Clinton will soon say to each other – but all the yeses that have paved the way for them to share their joy with us today … and for all the yeses that will follow in the weeks and months and years to come as other couples celebrate “that which is natural that which is infinite that which is yes” in their love for God and for each other.  There may be many yeses ahead of us before we come to the blessed day when blessed days such as today are finally more ordinary than extraordinary – but even while we recognize that there is much work ahead of us, I pray that we be given the grace to ALSO recognize just how much we have to celebrate with Michael and John Clinton – with the parish of St. George’s – with the Diocese of Washington – with the Episcopal Church. On most this amazing day I recall in a particularly meaningful way the words of my favorite modern-day prophet: Joan Chittister.   Sister Joan famously said, “We are each called to go through life reclaiming the planet an inch at a time until the Garden of Eden grows green again.” And that is precisely what we are doing in this service of blessing and covenant: witnessing the reclaiming of an inch growing very green indeed as Michael and John give us the chance to stand with them as they take their place in that arc of history that Martin Luther King assured us “bends toward justice.”   And lest you flinch at the word “justice” – fearing that the preacher is about to “get political” – let me hasten to contextualize what I believe is the motivating essence that bends that arc in the first place.  “Justice,” as described by former presiding bishop John Hines, “is the corporate face of God’s love.”  The justice we see realized today in this community gathered – this couple blessed – this bread broken and shared – is nothing less than the corporate face of God’s love. What we are witnessing today is not only the celebration of the love these two beloved men have for each other but the most amazing love that God has for all of us – love that is so much wider, broader and more abundant than we can either ask for or imagine.    For the love of God is broader than the measure of the mind. And the heart of the eternal is most wonderfully kind. If our love were but more faithful, we should take Him at his word, And our lives would be thanksgiving, for the goodness of the Lord.  “If our love were but more faithful” … Michael and John Clinton’s love – for God and each other – HAS been that faithful … they have taken God at God’s word and managed – sometimes against most amazing odds – to live lives that are thanksgiving for the goodness of the Lord – lives that are examples to us today of the covenant love between two people which is an outward and visible sign of an inward and spiritual grace: of what it is to live into our full humanity as creatures created in the image of the one who’s very essence is love – in the image of the God who created us, redeemed us and sustains us.   The love we celebrate on most this amazing day has nothing whatsoever to do with the gender of the couple committing themselves to God and to each other and everything to do with the covenant love celebrated in I Samuel between Jonathan and David, the genuine love extolled in Paul’s letter to the Romans, the love that our Lord and Savior gave to us as his own commandment in the Gospel according to John. We here stand before God firmly rooted in the tradition we inherit – embodying the historic faith we profess – chosen to go and bear fruit as we proclaim the Good News we have been given to a world aching to hear it … as we lift our voices to tell the “old, old story of Jesus and his love.” (And no, I’m not going to sing again!)  Our context for telling that old, old story is a culture where we are surrounded by those yearning for spiritual community but convinced they know enough about being a Christian not to want to be one. They are those who have heard Jerry Falwell on Larry King Live -- and hearing words that that are narrow, judgmental and exclusive hear nothing what is represented as “Christian Values” that they want any part of. Nor should they. Nor should we.   What we have to offer instead is a unique and God-given opportunity to provide a different vision of what the Christian life and faith are all about. We have the chance to witness to our experience of a God who is about justice rather than judgment and whose inclusive love is available to all people, to a community of faith that asks not “who do you love” but “DO you love?” Yes, there is some controversy around our actions here at St. George’s today – but there is also much joy, support and excitement … and an extraordinary opportunity to tell that old, old story. It is, my brothers and sisters, an opportunity for evangelism!  And boy howdy have we had opportunities! Last week I had a phone call from a Washington reporter who called and asked what I was going to preach about today (and no, such press inquiries are NOT routinely part of my preaching preparation!) Turns out the answer was easy – even though there was yet to be word one on paper. “I’ll be preaching about the transformative power of God’s love and what it means to be blessed in order to be a blessing,” I said without hesitation. I was aware that I was once again exercising what a colleague refers to as “the spiritual gift of the theological sound bite” – but I knew as I heard the words coming out of my mouth that they contained the essence of what most this amazing day is all about – a day not just about Michael and John Clinton but about all that is natural, all that is infinite, all that is yes. As Michael said in his most recent sermon – the one he preached because he couldn’t preach THIS one:  What we propose to do … is to bless God and for God to bless us within the community of faith. It is not a private matter. It is not “our special day.” It is a day to give public praise and thanks for showing up in this community of faith in the lives of two faithful people. And that is what we intend to do.  Far from undermining the sacrament of marriage, I believe what Michael and John Clinton intend here today builds up ALL relationships How it must grieve the heart of God that the Body of Christ has gotten so caught up in whether or not it should be acting as an agent of the state it has neglected its high calling to be an agent of blessing. So I take heart that while the church and culture continue to wrestle through questions about marriage and unions and sacraments and sanctity, the blessing Michael and John Clinton are claiming today enriches not just their lives but all of ours.   Blessed to be a blessing, they help us experience the transformative love of God – blessing us so that we may be a blessing in return and draw others in to be blessed by being part of this community of faith. It is a grand and glorious circle – and it is the work we should be about – MUST be about as the people of God if this Garden is ever to grow green again.   Finally, on most this amazing day let us rejoice and be glad in the inch reclaimed and let us pray for strength to continue the struggle until the ears of all ears awake and the eyes of all eyes are opened – til everything has breath gives thanks to God   for all that is natural   all that is infinite   all that is yes.  Amen          
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Anglican Communion in New Westminster (ACiNW) is shocked and grieved by the actions of General Synod regarding the blessings of same sex unions...
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This will be an event for all to gather together to hear personal witness and to pray for the bishop, the diocese and the wider church.  The unauthorized same-sex blessing service, with Bishop John Chane officiating, will occur at St. George's - Glenn Dale MD at the same time. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wednesday, June 09, 2004  'Plano West' meeting issues call for censure, recognition of alternative network  By Pat McCaughan  ENS 060904-1  [ENS] At least 830 people, meeting in Long Beach, California, for the June 3-4 "Plano West" conference co-hosted by the Los Angeles and San Diego chapters of the American Anglican Council (AAC), were alternately urged to leave the Episcopal Church USA and to press the worldwide Anglican Communion to censure ECUSA for its "ongoing ungodly actions."  The statement also asked the primates for recognition of the Network of Anglican Communion Dioceses and Parishes--sometimes called the Anglican Communion Network--a group seeking to "realign" themselves with conservative primates throughout the Anglican Communion.  Los Angeles Bishop J. Jon Bruno--who exchanged correspondence with planners about arrangements for the Long Beach event--was nevertheless barred from welcoming the group to Southern California after he refused to sign an AAC statement, required of all attendees. Bruno told the Los Angeles Times he declined to sign the statement because it "excludes all people of Judaism, Islam and Buddhism as being within the love of God."   Network may 'grow more slowly'  "ECUSA is infected with disease DNA," declared the Rev. Bill Thompson, rector of All Saints, Long Beach, and dean of the network's Western Convocation. "In the network we have the opportunity to change that. Much of ECUSA has lost its way. We must get that way back for ourselves," he told the gathering, to enthusiastic applause.  Thompson's remarks were aimed at inspiring additional congregations to join the network, which is growing more slowly than organizers had hoped. Citing a projected $1.1 million budget, Thompson called for donations to assist the fledgling convocation.  "We're beginning to develop income streams, and there are some grants that have been given," he said, noting a $150,000 matching grant from the AAC.  The Rev. David Anderson, AAC national president, predicted the network would continue to grow. "It's just going to grow more slowly," he said. "I think people are treating it very seriously." Anderson said membership in the AAC has been growing steadily since January.  Seven of the Episcopal Church's 113 dioceses have voted to join the network, with two other dioceses expected to vote on affiliating this year. Fewer than 70 of the 6,800 congregations in non-affiliated dioceses have joined. Some evangelical bishops sympathetic to the network's goals are reportedly reluctant to join while their parishioners are divided on the issue.   'Water walkers' called to action  In the conference's opening address, the Rev. Ron Jackson, rector of St. Luke's in-the-Mountains, La Crescenta, California, compared ECUSA to the historic Queen Mary ship, docked nearby.  "It represents the grandeur of an age gone by but is now dry-docked. It can't go anywhere," said Jackson, who is also the president of the Los Angeles AAC chapter. "It's a place for tourists, not sailors ... a place you can buy souvenirs, but it isn't the kind of ship Christ is trying to build."  He cited the Gospel of Matthew's account of Jesus walking on water during a storm, and challenged the gathering to become "water walkers."  "I believe Jesus is building a ship to take us out into the water. I believe Jesus will teach us to sail by the wind of the Holy Spirit. I believe Jesus is saying to us, 'get out of the boat. Don't let the wind and waves terrify you,'" declared Jackson.   Blessings draw reactions  Jackson and other speakers also criticized Bishop Bruno for recently blessing the union of the Rev. Malcolm Boyd and his partner of 20 years, author and counselor Mark Thompson. Bruno's action is believed to be the first time a sitting bishop has presided at such a ceremony since General Convention, meeting in Minneapolis last August, acknowledged the practice as part of the life of the Episcopal Church.  "How do words begin to describe the scope and the depth of the offense against the church catholic, against the communion members, against the Gospel itself that this is?" Jackson asked. "What kind of message are these bishops intending to send to the primates? They're sending some kind of message, and it's pretty loud and clear."  Bishop John Chane of Washington said he will bless the union of the Rev. Michael Hopkins and John Bradley on June 12 in Maryland. Hopkins' term as president of Integrity, the Episcopal Church's gay and lesbian advocacy group, just ended.  Claiming the Blessing (CTB), a coalition of organizations favoring same-sex blessings, issued a statement applauding the pastoral sensitivity of Bruno and Chane "in choosing to both authorize and preside at the blessing of unions of same-sex couples in their dioceses. We believe such celebrations of holy love give glory to God and are examples to us all, and we give thanks for the witness and ministry of the bishops presiding and the couples committing themselves to Christ and to each other." CTB includes member organizations like Integrity, Oasis, Beyond Inclusion and the Episcopal Women's Caucus.  "We reject the American Anglican Council's characterization of the actions of the bishops of Los Angeles and Washington as 'unilateral,' noting that such blessings are in accord with the actions of the majority of the duly elected representatives of the mainstream Episcopal Church meeting in its General Convention," the statement read.  Meanwhile, AAC leaders at the conference also condemned the actions of the General Synod of the Anglican Church of Canada, which affirmed the integrity of same-sex unions June 4 at its meeting in St. Catharine's, Ontario. Anderson and other speakers issued a call to evangelize and to minister to grieving conservatives in that church.   Harder times ahead?  To strong applause, Anderson said he would like to see the ECUSA censured by the primates and the Archbishop of Canterbury. He also told conference-goers that, rather than conservative Episcopalians leaving the ECUSA, those whom he said committed the schismatic act should be the ones to go.  "I would like to see the Episcopal Church censured, put on a probation status and called to repentance and if they do not repent, then certain things need to happen that are of a long-term nature. Some of the revisionists have implied: why haven't we just left, we're so schismatic anyway," Anderson said. "I believe that we gathered are the orthodox historically Anglican Christian faith within the United States. The cemeteries have our loved ones laid to rest. The nurseries have our children and our godchildren in them. This is our church and I want to see this church reformed, renewed, called to repentance, to experience the full grace of God's forgiveness.  "We are here to push back heresy and apostasy and claim this Episcopal Church for Jesus Christ the one and the only."  Anderson predicted times will get harder before they get better, and advised participants to stockpile diocesan and parish directories.  "There may come a time when the AAC chapter in your diocese may need to do direct mail into every home in the diocese, when they may need to replicate the local bishop's power to place a message in every living room," he advised participants.   'Radical individualism' cited  Bishop Joseph Wasonga of the Diocese of Maseno West in Kenya received a standing ovation when he addressed the gathering.  "We know we need to walk hand in hand with you as you bring the light of the Gospel to your country," he said amid cheering and shouting. "We will not receive money from anybody not acknowledging the authority of Scripture and that Jesus is the way, the truth and the life. No part of the Body of Christ is allowed to make a unilateral decision that affects the whole Body of Christ, that creates disunity and schism and we cannot say we are working together. We are all members of the Body of Christ and we must be subject to the lordship of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ. We are not to conform to culture, to tribalism, to racialism, or the radical individualism found in the West."    Third in a series  "Plano West" was the third in a series of AAC-sponsored gatherings for Episcopalians who are at odds with the consecration of an openly gay priest as Bishop of New Hampshire and with the blessing of same sex unions. An October 2003 gathering, planned for Plano, Texas but moved to Dallas to accommodate 2,600 attendees, was followed by "Plano East" in Fairfax, Virginia, attended by more than 2,000 in January 2004.  According to the AAC, those attending "Plano West" came from a variety of western states including Nevada, Arizona, Texas, Washington, and California, as well as some participants from the East Coast.  A featured speaker was the Rev. Michael Green, a well-known evangelist and a senior research fellow at Wycliffe Hall in Oxford, England who is an advisor to the Archbishop of Canterbury. Green helped formulate the charter that birthed the NACDP. Other speakers included the Rev. Kendall Harmon, canon theologian for the Diocese of South Carolina, and the Rev. Alison Barfoot, recently appointed assistant for international relations to Archbishop Henry Orombi of Uganda.   --The Rev. Patricia McCaughan is senior correspondent for the Episcopal News of the Diocese of Los Angeles. A former state news desk editor for the Detroit News, she and her news team received a Pulitzer Prize in 1994 for a series of stories exposing corruption in state government. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Archbishop of Canterbury, the Most Revd Dr Rowan Williams, has welcomed the decision by the Canadian General Synod to defer a decision on the question of same sex blessings until 2007...
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A year after the election of the first openly gay Episcopal bishop, the church remains intact - splintered but not split. Most Episcopalians have stuck with their church and a dissident network of conservatives is growing more slowly than its founders hoped...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Two Greenbelt men are preparing to have their ten-year relationship blessed by the Episcopal Diocese of Washington...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In his sermon last Sunday, the Rev. Michael Hopkins replies to the Rev. Canon David Anderson's recent quotes in the L.A. Times and explains why he and John Clinton Bradley are having their relationships blessed by the Bishop of Washington. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Michael Hopkins and John Clinton Bradley have been in a committed relationship for more than 10 years, longer than many marriages...Now, after years of waiting, what the two Greenbelt residents had hoped for is about to happen...In an afternoon ceremony Saturday at St. George's Episcopal Church in Prince George's County, the Episcopal bishop of Washington, the Right Rev. John Bryson Chane, will publicly bless their relationship, establishing a new level of formal acceptance in the diocese for long-term gay relationships...   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      June 3, 2004 - We applaud the pastoral sensitivity of Bishops Jon Bruno and John Chane in choosing to both authorize and preside at the blessing of unions of same-sex couples in their dioceses. We believe such celebrations of holy love give glory to God and are examples to us all, and we give thanks for the witness and ministry of the bishops presiding and the couples committing themselves to Christ and to each other.  We reject the American Anglican Council's characterization of the actions of the bishops of Los Angeles and Washington as "unilateral," noting that such blessings are in accord with the actions of the majority of the duly elected representatives of the mainstream Episcopal church meeting in its General Convention.  Since that General Convention in 2003, the Episcopal Church has faced the challenge of an unprecedented assault on its unity by the leadership of an American Anglican Council committed to a course of polarization and division. We are deeply saddened that their continued refusal to engage in reconciliation-focused dialogue with those with whom they disagree has lead to the current state of affairs. We re-state our assertion that responsibility for any looming schism lays firmly at the feet of the leadership of the AAC who have rebuffed every effort to mediate the differences between us, forsaking the historic via media for a theological absolutism antithetical to traditional Anglicanism.  As the Lambeth Commission strives to balance the unity and diversity that are hallmarks of classical Anglicanism we urge them to balance as well the pastoral and the prophetic. Had Rosa Parks listened only to pleas for restraint and not heeded the call for justice we might well have been spared the tumultuous challenges of the 1960Â¹s but at the cost of abandoning our baptismal call to strive for justice and to respect the dignity of every human being. We believe it is never too late to embrace the high calling of living out the good news of God in Christ Jesus made available to all people. We give thanks for the privilege of offering that witness to the world.  Contact information: The Reverend Susan Russell Executive Director, Claiming the Blessing 132 North Euclid Avenue Pasadena, CA 91107 626-583-2740 revsusanrussell@earthlink.net 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Conservative Episcopalians called on the world's leading Anglican archbishops Friday to recognize their emerging network as a separate church within the worldwide Anglican Communion unless the Episcopal Church reverses its liberal views on homosexuality...  [You will be asked to register/login to latimes.com to read this story.] 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      RealAudio of an interview with Gene Robinison on NPR's "The Connection."
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Anglican Church of Canada affirmed the "integrity and sanctity" of same-sex relationships Thursday, a move that stops short of authorizing blessing ceremonies for gay couples but still may provoke rancor in the global Anglican Communion...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A proposal authorizing Anglican Church of Canada diocese to provide blessing ceremonies for same-sex couples has been withdrawn, delaying the vote for years...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Anglican Church of Canada approved a measure Thursday to "affirm the integrity and sanctity of committed adult same-sex relationships..."
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Archbishop of Canterbury’s envoy urged the Canadian Church not to endorse the blessing of same-sex unions, warning that such a move would imperil the Anglican Communion’s existence...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One day after delaying a decision on whether to bless gay relationships, Canadian Anglicans approved a statement that "affirms the integrity and sanctity of committed adult same-sex relationships..."
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Deeply divided over liberalizing church attitudes toward homosexuals, Canadian Anglicans meeting at their triennial governing convention here voted to defer a decision on whether gay relationships should be blessed in church....
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      June 1, 2004  Dear Sisters and Brothers in Christ:  On Saturday The Washington Post published an article on the front page of the Metro section regarding my intention to preside at the blessing of the relationship between long time and faithful partners, The Reverend Michael Hopkins and John Bradley. It was not my intention to have you learn about this development in the media, but the press became aware of the story before we planned to release it.  Given the actions of General Convention meeting in Minneapolis last summer relating to such blessings, I am ready to move forward as your bishop to affirm and bless Michael and John's relationship and also to provide the diocese with an order of service for the blessing of covenanted relationships that could be useful to clergy of the diocese who choose to bless such relationships.  The writing team which I appointed in late January has done a fine job and I thank them for their hard, sensitive and dedicated work. Appropriate guidelines are also being shaped and will be forwarded to all of you so there will be no misunderstanding as to how this diocese and its clergy may proceed in using this order of service.  In all things it is time now for us to re-examine the nature of Old and New Testament covenants between God and humankind, and to understand in a far deeper way what it means to be in Baptismal Covenant with Jesus Christ.  Faithful relationships with God and each other, imbued with the Divine gift of inclusive love, are at the very heart of defining who we are as God's children." It is this love and faithfulness in relationship that I affirm and bless and that has been lived out for so many years by so many who have waited so long for Christ's Body, the Church to say Amen: "So be it."  In Christ's Peace, Power and Love,  The Rt. Rev. John Bryson Chane, D.D.  Bishop of Washington and Dean of the Cathedral 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A Statement by the Steering Committee of the Claiming the Blessing Collaborative  Claiming the Blessing (www.claimingtheblessing.org) is a collaborative of justice organizations and individuals in the Episcopal Church. Established in 1998, CTB is committed to securing the authorization of liturgical rites of blessing for lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender couples who enter into a covenant to live together in relationships marked by mutuality, love, faithfulness, respect and lifelong monogamy.   Members of the CTB Steering Committee met May 26-28, 2004 in the Diocese of Dallas, in the Name of Jesus and seeking to be guided by the Holy Spirit, to evaluate, assess, and plan our work together. Our time was framed by prayer, song and laughter, which inspired creative strategies to accomplish the high prophetic call to do justice, love kindness and walk humbly with God.  We celebrated the initial success of the educational and evangelism tool, via media. We are excited by the reception it is receiving – especially in those places where progressive Episcopalians are marginalized and trivialized for their beliefs. Clearly, there is great spiritual hunger for the solid food which has been prepared in the classic Anglican style of scripture viewed thorough the lens of tradition and reason. Other educational programs such as an Instructed Eucharist are in development and we applaud and support the Every Voice Network (www.everyvoice.net) in this important ministry.  We also rejoiced in the status of asylum recommended for approval by U.S. immigration authorities to a lesbian from Africa who has been sponsored to live in this country by several members of CTB. Research on homosexuality in Africa, published in The Witness (the Episcopal Church Publishing Company, www.thewitness.org), has helped to document both her case and that of another African lesbian who recently received asylum. Despite the "Ashcroft climate" of xenophobia and homophobia, such outcomes for lesbians and gay men encourage us that sound judgment still exists in this country and its institutions.  We continue to study the reality of the health of our church and, despite the dire predictions made after General Convention and the very real challenges we continue to face, we believe that it is good. In Dallas, we received with encouragement the report that in one AAC-affiliated diocese a small band of moderate and progressive parishes, determined to be faithful, are pledging tens of thousands of dollars to the National Church. Others in that diocese who have sought to negatively impact the National Church have failed to do so, since that diocese had not been paying its assessment previously anyway.   Our fervent prayers remain with Bishop Robinson and the people of the Diocese of New Hampshire. We urge Archbishop Eames and the members of the Commission he leads to enter into meaningful conversation with the Bishop and Standing Committee of New Hampshire, as well as Bishop Ingham and the Diocese of New Westminster, before making their recommendations.    We also continue to pray for Archbishop Rowan Williams, our own Presiding Bishop, Frank Griswold, and for all bishops, priests, deacons and members of the laity as they provide effective leadership in this time of Kairos in our lives of faith.   The development of liturgical rites of blessing is ongoing in many dioceses around the country, as well as the blessing – by priests and bishops – of same sex relationships.  We are preparing a map to identify the dioceses engaged in this endeavor, which we suspect will mirror those dioceses which supported the election of the Bishop of New Hampshire.  We are deeply committed to continue to work for authorization by the Episcopal Church of rites for the blessing of same-sex couples in committed relationships.  We are overjoyed at the marriages of same-sex couples now occurring, but our joy is tempered by the decision of some bishops to prohibit clergy from officiating at such marriages.  We believe the lack of separation of church and state regarding marriage needs to be carefully scrutinized. We will work for change in the Church’s national Canons on marriage, and in the marriage rites in The Book of Common Prayer to make the canons and prayer book rites gender neutral.  As all of these issues are considered and addressed, we will stand in solidarity with those who feel called to acts of constructive disobedience by officiating at the marriages of same-sex couples.    The Steering Committee of Claiming the Blessing: Peggy Adams, Pasadena CA Ed Bacon, Pasadena CA Cynthia Black, Kalamazoo MI Kim Byham, Guttenberg NJ Louie Crew, East Orange NJ Ethan Flad, Oakland CA Rosa Lee Harden, San Francisco CA Michael Hopkins, Glen Dale MD Elizabeth Kaeton, Chatham NJ John Kirkley, San Francisco CA Joseph Lane, Belmont CA Christine Mackey-Mason, Pasadena CA Katie Sherrod, Fort Worth TX Jim White, Pasadena CA 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bishop Jon Bruno, Diocese of Los Angeles, recently presided over the same sex ceremony of the Rev. Canon Malcolm Boyd, poet laureate of LA, and his long-time “partner”. Bishop John Chane has announced plans to preside at the same sex blessing of former President of Integrity Michael Hopkins and his “partner” June 12, 2004.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Less than a month after much of the congregation left an Episcopal church over the election of the first openly gay bishop to head a diocese, members are getting the church back on its feet again...
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      29 July 2004 FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE  30th ANNIVERSARY OF THE ORDINATION OF WOMEN  Integrity celebrates with great joy the 30th anniversary of the ordination of women as priests in the Episcopal Church.  We recognize that the mission and ministry of the Episcopal Church has been enlivened and enriched by the fuller inclusion of women in all orders of ministry over these past thirty years.  We commit ourselves to continue the struggle for justice and equality until all the baptized are fully included in the Body of Christ.  (The Reverend) Susan Russell, President	 revsusanrussell@earthlink.net 714-356-5718 (mobile) 626-583-2740 (office)  John Clinton Bradley, Director of Communications johnclint@comcast.net 301-437-8628 (mobile)  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      (Amendment 2 is the attempt in Missouri to change the constitution to  define marriage as between a man and a woman)  I believe in the sanctity of marriage and its ability to let two people discover God's love in their shared life. I believe that marriage is both hard work and an unearned gift, that it comes to two people for better for worse, for richer for poorer, in sickness and in health. I believe that marriage is by definition a lifelong commitment between husband and wife.  I have said, countless times, the words from my Church's marriage rite, telling all hearers that this holy union between husband and wife "is intended by God for their mutual joy; for the help and comfort given one another in prosperity and adversity; and, when it is God's will, for the procreation of children and their nurture in the knowledge and love of the Lord." I believe these words.  I myself am married and the father of children, and I am mindful of the covenant relationship I have with my beloved as part of God's claim on my life, and my joy.  I also know that the dominant culture surrounding us does precious little to support married persons in their vocation.   I cannot believe, however, that amending Missouri's constitution will fix what ails us, when it comes to the legacy of marriage. The impetus to vote "yes" on Amendment 2 next week may well come from a desire to "do something" for the sake of marriage. What might be done effectively, however, is in truth both more ordinary and more demanding: spend good, old-fashioned quantity of time with spouse and family; build networks of support in faith communities and extended families and neighborhoods to sustain people in this bold covenant vocation; dig deeper into the traditions of faith, the disciplines and the feasting alike; practice living open handedly with one another and in all things, for God's sake.  All things considered, it is easier just to vote "yes" on a referendum. I am arguing instead for the hard work marriage demands of us all.  I would also be remiss if I were to omit naming two dire circumstances around this proposed Amendment.    First, let us be sure that the body politic receives no good fortune in the opportunity to cast a vote on this divisive issue. Human sexuality has become a wedge issue in American society, used deftly at times by those on both sides of the issue. Forcing a "yes" or "no" vote divides even further an already polarized electorate. I write as someone whose Church has faced divisions in the aftermath of a vote on human sexuality one year ago. I am not eager to vote one more time on this matter, but I am even less eager to give into the power of a wedge issue.  Second, there is the witness from gay and lesbian persons in our communities, and from gay and lesbian believers in my own Church. The prospect of Amendment 2 leaves them with an ill foreboding. It gives them a message of unwelcome in their own neighborhoods. It makes them feel marginally less safe; some even feel considerably less safe. A few have received hateful messages in the mail or on the phone on in person over these past weeks, when they have never before heard such things around here. I ask you to consider whether this is what we want, in a place we rightly love.  They hear that the Amendment is supposed somehow to protect marriage; they know, however, that it is really about them.   I am in favor of marriage. Supporting marriage, however, takes more than a tick on the ballot. Let us not allow wedge politics to define what is essentially a matter of the heart, and a costly commitment.  Polarizing the electorate in this matter is hardly helpful—and the politics of polarization turn dangerous whenever the language of hate becomes permissible.  I fervently ask you to support married persons in their vocation.  I ask you with equal fervor to eschew hatred.  The Rt. Rev. George Wayne Smith Bishop of The Episcopal Diocese of Missouri
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Unable to accept their bishop's homosexuality, some Episcopalians have left their church. To others, Gene Robinson's consecration last year served as a powerful magnet...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I guess I come by my love of parades naturally. I grew up a stone's throwfrom the parade route of Pasadena's Rose Parade and one of the firstmusicals I ever saw was the "Music Man" -- and I loved all seventy-six trombones of it! Wherever it comes from, I love a parade -- and I love that this summer gave me the chance to be part of two very-different-but-each-spectacular-in-their-own-right parades.  The first was June 20th -- the Los Angeles "Christopher Street West" GayPride Parade -- where the Diocese of Los Angeles once again took to the streets to offer an outward and visible sign of the inward and spiritual grace of God's inclusive love to the approximately 250,000 folks gathered along Santa Monica Boulevard. This year we had nearly 300 marchers -- in turquoise "The Episcopal Church Welcomes You" t-shirts -- marching along with "The Float." Made possible by the generous donation of our Diocesan ECW President's family business (isn't it great to have a float builder in thefamily?) it carried an enormous stained-glass image of Jesus as the GoodShepherd in front of an Episcopal Shield along with clergy and laity from all over the diocese -- including diocesan Bishop J. Jon Bruno -- waving and clapping to music that ran the gamut from "The Halleluiah Chorus" to "This Little Light of Mine."  The second was July 4th -- the annual Independence Day Parade -- where the good people of Forest Lake, Minnesota (and surrounding communities) marched just about every one and every thing they could lay their hands on down MainStreet in celebration of America's Birthday. The sidewalks were crowded with lawn chairs and baby strollers as we gathered to watch -- for nearly two hours -- as the John Deere Tractors rolled along with high school bands,polka clubs and local-dignitaries-in-convertibles. From the residents of the Shady Nook Rest Home waving from the windows of their minivan to the DairyQueen holding court from a 1968 Mustang it was, in its own way, another kind of "Pride Parade" - pride in all that's best about the American dream of life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness.  I checked out the Merriam-Webster online dictionary and one of its definitions of "pride" is "a reasonable or justifiable self-respect." To take pride in our work, in our history, in who we are as a particular kindof people or what we are as a particular kind of nation is what these two very-different-on-the-surface parades were all about. We DO have much to be proud about - as the Episcopal Church USA, as gay and lesbian people living fully into our stature as God's beloved children, as Americans proud of alegacy of liberty that is far to precious to be taken for granted. It seems to me that where we go wrong - when we fall short of the mark - is when our pride - our "justifiable self-respect" - becomes separated somehow from our sense of connectedness to those whose experience is different from ours; when we lose the deep sense of the privilege and responsibility that come with these gifts we have been given.  Pride without responsibility quickly becomes arrogance. The fruits of this spirit of arrogance are unilateralism, absolutism and fundamentalism -- and I suggest that much of the havoc being wrecked around us in this country and this communion has its roots in precisely that disconnect. And I further suggest that the challenge in front of us is how to be part of the solution rather than part of perpetuating the problem. The work ahead of us is finding the means to reconnect - to reconcile - our justifiable self-respectwith those whose equal measure of justifiable self-respect emerges out ofvastly different cultural, faith and community contexts. It is hard, exhausting, sometimes demoralizing work, but it is the work we have been given to do by the God who gave us the spirit of reconciliation in order todo it.   The vision we work to realize is a country where "liberty and justice forall" truly means ALL: the kingdom we pray to come is one where "loving yourneighbors as yourselves" is not just a dream but a reality. Impossible? Last Sunday's reading from Genesis reminded us that "Nothing is impossible for God" - and next Sunday's Gospel urges us to "ask, seek and knock" until the door is opened. That is the legacy we claim: one of hope and one of pride -of justifiable self-respect that is worth celebrating - parading, even.   And did I happen to mention that I LOVE a parade? 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      by Bishop Carolyn Tanner Irish      Recent statements of Utah leaders in both the dominant church and the dominant political party supporting a constitutional amendment to ban gay marriage prompt me to respond publicly. I do so as a leader in the Episcopal Church but I do not speak for this church or its members...  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      14 July 2004 FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE  Integrity is gratified that the Federal Marriage Amendment failed in the U.S. Senate today.  Although the country as a whole is still divided on same-sex marriage, our elected senators have wisely rejected an attempt to write discrimination against gay and lesbian couples into the Constitution—the foundation of liberty for all the citizens of this nation.    Integrity applauds Presiding Bishop Frank Griswold and the Episcopal Church's Office of Government Relations for their work on this issue.  Integrity also thanks those Episcopal senators who voted to block the measure.      (The Reverend) Susan Russell, President	 revsusanrussell@earthlink.net 714-356-5718 (mobile) 626-583-2740 (office)  John Clinton Bradley, Director of Communications johnclint@comcast.net 301-437-8628 (mobile)  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Uncertain of what might greet us when we walked through the doors of the Office of the Town Clerk in the Municipal Building of the Borough of Chatham, NJ, to register for Domestic Partnership, Barbara and I stopped, looked at each other for assurance, and took a deep breath before crossing the threshold  This, after all, is a predominantly conservative Republican town. What were we thinking? We instantly regretted not having gone to Maplewood on July 10 for the statewide registration "event" as one of a sea of over 500 couples who had registered in the celebratory atmosphere of friends, family and children. A modicum of anonymity accompanied by a large dollop of community support suddenly seemed far superior to the very public and intimidating space we were about to enter.  We needn't have worried. A member of our congregation sat at the desk, looked up at the two of us (we must have looked a fright!) and, in her best deadpan said, "Oh, let me guess.  You're not here for a garage sale permit. Let me get the Registrar." As I listened to the gale of giggles that followed, I knew the Holy Spirit had previously arranged our reception.   The "Deputy Registrar" greeted us, flustered and apologetic because the Registrar was out for the day and she had no idea where the forms were kept or how to fill them out.  She said if we gave her a few minutes, she'd hunt them down and we'd work on this together. We all giggled nervously and allowed as how this was our first time doing this, too, and we were happy she was joining us on this adventure. It was then that a sign caught my eye: 'You must have an appointment for a marriage license or certificate of domestic partnership. Minimum 24 hour notice. No walk-ins.' Apparently, the Deputy Registrar didn't know about the sign, either.  In less that 15 minutes, the files were found, the questions asked, and all the forms filled out, signed, notarized, and sealed.  In the process, we discovered that we were not the first registered domestic partnership in Chatham.  Turns out, one of the elected members of the Town Council had come in with his domestic partner the day before, so they bore the distinction of having been "the first."  That seemed fitting and appropriate to us.  After all, we've been at this for twenty-eight years, and although it's been awhile, it's far from the first time we've had to appear in court about our relationship.    When I returned to the office, I slowly began telling my staff and some of the volunteers what Barbara and I had just done. The word spread like wildfire. I was surprised and taken aback by the emotional responses I got. What are you doing back at work, they all wanted to know? You should have at least gone out to breakfast or something!  It's your wedding day, they said.  No. No, it isn't. Well, then, what? I found myself describing it as "jumping the broom" - a ritual created by slaves to honor their unions because they could not legally marry. Some - but by no means all - slave owners respected couples who had 'jumped the broom' by not using the women as convenient objects for their sexual gratification. It was a first step toward being seen not as objects or classifications, but for their essential humanity. It was the first step to the security and protection society affords those who make a lifelong, faithful commitment to each other.   Now, at least, I will no longer have to worry, as I did eight years ago when Barbara had surgery, that I will not have access to information about her health status when she is in the recovery room because I am not "related."  Now, at least, we have the option of filing joint tax returns, like other good citizens. Now, at least, if one of us precedes the other in death, we don't have to worry that the IRS will claim the major portion of our inheritance because we are not "related."   As the reality of my words took hold, one person shook her head and quipped, Gee, I better rush home to check if the status of my marriage has eroded any. Another began to weep.  No, it's right that you came back to work, she said, because we still have much work to do, don't we?  We do, indeed.  'Liberty and justice for all' is an ideal which has not yet been realized.   And now, at least for now, it's back to work. But, for one breathtaking moment this morning, we jumped the broom toward securing the basics of "life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness," for ourselves and our families. For one brief and shining moment, the vision of the Holy City filled my heart with the deep joy the disciples must have felt when Jesus said: Blessed are you when people hate you, and when they exclude you, revile you, and defame you on account of the Son of Man. Rejoice in that day and leap for joy, for surely your reward is great in heaven.    Surely, a little piece of heaven came very near to us today on the other side of that broom.  Blessings,  (the Rev'd) Elizabeth Kaeton St. Paul's Episcopal Church 200 Main Street Chatham, NJ 07928 973 635 8085 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Episcopalian senators were evenly split on the issue when the U.S. Senate defeated an attempt July 14 to amend the U.S. Constitution by defining marriage and prohibiting same-gender civil marriage...
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Episcopal bishop of New Hampshire, who has drawn both admiration and opposition because of his homosexuality, urged gays, lesbians, and transgendered people to return to the church. Bishop V. Gene Robinson delivered a sermon on Saturday at St. Paul's Cathedral in Burlington, Vt., as part of the gay pride celebration. Robinson told some 300 worshippers at the service that many churches have become more accepting of gay men and lesbians. "You and I have spent a lot of time with folks that don't know a God," Robinson told the congregation, many of whom sported gay pride buttons, stickers, and T-shirts worn earlier at a downtown parade. "You and I have to come out to our homosexual brothers and sisters as well about God." 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Episcopal Church, for example, has faced an insurrection by conservative parishes since its ordination of a gay bishop in New Hampshire last year. But marketers see an opportunity.   'Among 20- to 30-year-olds, everybody's heard of the gay bishop. And in focus groups, the words that keep coming up are that we are a 'progressive,' 'open' and 'nonjudgmental' church,' said Daniel B. England, the church's director of communication.   Thus, the Episcopalians will launch their first national TV ad campaign on Election Day with a 15-second spot that pivots off the presidential campaign to appeal for new members.   'We think this could be a very divisive election,' England said. 'We're saying to people, 'If you're fed up with all the divisions, you might want to take a look at us, because we're in the business of inclusion, not division.'...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On any given Sunday, you can hear the same prayers, readings, psalms and devotions at Church of Our Saviour, St. Luke's Episcopal Church and Hudson Anglican Fellowship.  But while they all look like Episcopal churches -- using the Book of Common Prayer as their primary guide for worship -- there is something very different going on in each one a year after the Episcopal Church's painful debate over homosexuality... 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bishop V. Gene Robinson delivered a sermon Saturday at St. Paul's Cathedral as part of the gay pride celebration...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints' endorsement earlier this week of an amendment to ban same-sex marriage was short and simple. If there was any debate or hand-wringing that accompanied the church's decision, it wasn't apparent in the 25-word statement.  But gay marriage and the proposed federal amendment outlawing it has proved more divisive for some churches, many of whom have had to do their soul-searching in public...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A private same-sex ceremony in April between two Episcopalian women has escalated into charges of deception, "secret protocols" - and even a taunt of perjury against a retired Colorado bishop....
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      LEXINGTON, Ky. - This notice appeared on the front page of the Lexington Herald-Leader's Sunday edition.  "Clarification: It has come to the editor's attention that the Herald-Leader neglected to cover the civil rights movement. We regret the omission. John Carroll, the editor of the Los Angeles Times, who edited this newspaper from 1979 to 1991, recently proposed a correction like the one above during a speech on journalism ethics. Today, as the nation celebrates its liberties and marks the 40th anniversary of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, this report looks back at the hidden history of Lexington's civil rights struggle - and how this newspaper covered it. Or failed to."
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In recent weeks, ACNS has received a large number of queries about the progress of the Lambeth Commission on Communion (LCC). ACNS managed to catch up with the Chair of the Commission, the Most Revd Robin Eames, as he passed through St Andrew’s House this week. He agreed to give some personal reflections on the work of the Commission, given that it is impossible for him or the Secretary of the Commission to respond to the large number of individual enquiries that we have received..
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HERE COME THE BRIDES It's not often that a wedding guest gets a standing O, but then Margaret Marshall's no ordinary guest, is she? If not for the chief justice of the state Supreme Judicial Court, there's a good chance Diana Eck and her partner, Dorothy Austin, would not have been hitched Sunday. (And, no, it wasn't a coincidence that Eck, a professor of comparative religion at Harvard, and Austin, an Episcopal priest, were married on Independence Day.) In a toast at the reception afterward, Marshall, author of the landmark decision legalizing same-sex marriage in our great state, told the crowd, "If there ever was an affirmation of any decision I've made," the Eck-Austin wedding was it. (Marshall, by the way, was with her spouse, former New York Times columnist Anthony Lewis.) Officiating the ceremony at Harvard's Memorial Church were Bishop Steven Charleston, president and dean of the Episcopal Divinity School in Cambridge; the Rev. Claudia Highbaugh, chaplain at Harvard Divinity School; and the Rev. Thomas Mikelson, the parish minister at First Parish Church in Cambridge. (Charleston blessed the couple, but in keeping with Bishop M. Thomas Shaw's prohibition against Episcopal priests solemnizing gay marriages, he didn't sign the marriage license.) In his address, the Rev. Peter Gomes, the Plummer Professor of Christian Morals at Harvard, said "no governor, no constitutional amendment" could rend the union of Eck and Austin. (Hear that Mitt Romney? The wedding's closing hymn was "America (My Country, 'Tis of Thee)."...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a chance to think anew about all this recently when Otis Charles, former Episcopal bishop of Utah and, until recently, assistant bishop of California, spoke at a forum at an Episcopal church in Kansas City. Charles and his domestic partner, Felipe Paris, participated in a public commitment ceremony in April at an Episcopal church in San Francisco, after which the bishop fired Charles. The ceremony was meant to be private, but the San Francisco Chronicle learned and wrote about it afterward - with the eventual cooperation of Charles and Paris...
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One year after the Episcopal Church USA affirmed its first openly gay bishop, that denomination also remains painfully divided over issues of homosexuality. Pro-gay votes at last year's General Convention provoked huge controversy within the U.S. Church -- and within the 70-million-member worldwide Anglican Communion, of which the Episcopal Church is a part. Church leaders have been looking for a way to resolve the rift, but schism is still a strong possibility. Kim Lawton has our update...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The bishop of the Episcopal Diocese of North Carolina sent a letter to area ministers this week telling those who want to bless homosexual unions that they can do so under certain guidelines...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Presbyterian clergy and laity from the Columbia area say last week’s vote against ordaining gays and lesbians will not halt consideration of the issue in the denomination’s churches and classrooms...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      By Ellen Goodman, Globe Columnist  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Conservatives in the Presbyterian Church warned that a vote in favor of gay ordination at the national legislative assembly this week could cause the largest schism in the church since the Civil War...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Most parishioners in Rochester’s Church of the Redeemer have walked out rather than accept the leadership of the openly gay Bishop V. Gene Robinson...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When Gene Robinson, a divorced gay priest living in a partnered relationship with another man, was consecrated an Episcopal bishop of New Hampshire in January, schism was widely predicted, both within the national Episcopal Church and in the broader Anglican Communion...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Disagreements over tradition have led to a break within one Austin church. St. Barnabas the Encourager, a congregation founded in 1998, will leave the Episcopal Church because the church does not condone certain practices or believe in the Bible as the sole instrument of salvation...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Conservatives upset about an openly gay bishop and same-sex blessings in the Episcopal Church have suggested to an emergency commission that global Anglicanism should shun both the bishop and the denomination if things don't change...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last November, the Episcopal Church U.S.A. approved the consecration of Gene Robinson as Bishop of New Hampshire, the first openly homosexual bishop in the Church. That decision has now had repercussions in Nashville...
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Human Rights Campaign President Cheryl Jacques took time off from her crusade for same-sex marriage to tie the knot herself Sunday.  Jacques, 42, and her partner of nearly seven years, Jennifer Chrisler, 33, were married in a Boston hotel in a ceremony presided over by sister-in-law Katherine Jacques, a justice of the peace, and their friend, the Rev. Miriam Gelfer, an Episcopal priest...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      More than a hundred people trickled into Mobile's Washington Square on Sunday night to remember a man most had never even met.   The candlelight vigil -- a mix of religion, gay and lesbian solidarity and a political call-to-arms -- served as a release valve for folks whose frustration and anger have boiled over the past week as news accounts detailed the July 18 slaying of Scotty Joe Weaver.   According to law enforcement investigators, the 18-year-old Pine Grove man was strangled, beaten and stabbed before his body was carried to a wooded area off a dirt road and then set on fire...  
     

    
</post>



</Blog>