<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Can you name these totally awesome chicks from the 1980's?
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      someone once said that satan is a great sociologist. i think that might have been jon randles...anyway, it's true. he watches our trend patterns and trips us up in the worst way possible.  i don't know everything that's been going down, and i don't need to know. but GOD DID NOT GIVE US A SPIRIT OF TIMIDITY...we are here to fight the good fight.   please pray for us as we are all battling our own demons. i know that i, personally, forget how real spiritual warfare is, and that there's a constant battle for our souls.   what a great Dad we have upstairs. psalm 60:12 says, "With God we will gain the victory, and he will trample down our enemies." i belive this to the fullest and i know just as the flowers in the field, and the birds of the air, He will meet our every need.  thanks to everyone who has supported us financially, through prayer and encouragment. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      today all the girls got to move across campus into apartments!! we are so blessed to have such a ridonkulous amount of spacious goodness, and a beautiful view of the lake/pond thingy.  props to all the men here...they were all amazing in helping us pack up our millions of shoes and make up bags. they even carried purses. it was magical.  ps. here's a sweet verse i wanted to share. enjoy!  Romans 15:5-6 (NASV) "For everything that was written in the past was written to teach us, so that through endurance and the encouragment of the scriptures we might have hope. May the God who gives endurance and encouragment give you a spirit of unity among yourselves as you follow Christ Jesus, so that with one heart and mouth you may glorify the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Went to Chicago this weekend with the D-group. We got this sweet deal at the Westin, a nice 5-star hotel right on the Chicago River, with many ritzing posh people staring at us poor college students with our Jansport backpacks and Thrift Store t-shirts. It was way amusing, especially hearing our neighbor's phone conversation about the 3 pairs of shoes he bought "for only $1600." Sheesh... some people just need to write a check to OU with my name on it so I can get to class!.... Anyways.... Went to the Sears Tower, John Hancock center (went to the 95th floor and to take pictures), the Art Institute, the Chicago Public Library (biggest library in the nation), Navy Pier, and, by far the coolest thing ever: WRIGLEY FIELD! That has been my dream since a baby, and I got a picture outside of it with a sign that said "Hey Dad" to send to my dad for Father's Day. It was so great. I have a completely new appreciation for public transportation, that's for sure.  But anyway.... we're starting our fourth week here in Elgin, and it's been great... besides the hordes of pre-teens who have moved into Judson for soccer camp. There were about a billion moms in vans dropping off their soccer kids.... I could just imagine them saying "soccer" with an Illinois accent.. you know what I mean. Other than that chaos it's been pretty great. Well, I've ramled on enough. I'm off to start some intense inductive that I need to get done by tomorrow! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This last weekend was D-Group weekend. All the groups went on some sort of road-trip/outing fri. night through Sunday night. Most of them got a phat deal on a hotel of Hotwire.com... and toured the downtown area. I went to the famous metroplex of Des Moines, Ia to hang out with my grandpa.  One the way home I stoppped by the place where they filmed " urlLink Feild of Dreams "  It was pretty cool!  I even bought some "Dream Dirt" from the gift shop...
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Right now it's 5:45 in the morning. Shane and I are staffing the fitness center here at Judson. The fitness center isn't open in the summers, but we persuaded them to let us in in the mornings for just the project to use it. Well, after much hassle with going through all the proper channels etc, we come to work out yesterday, and they didn't tell us that the free weight room is being remodeled.  So, Since the weight room is out of commission, we're left with some elyptical machines and some cable weights.  What's so funny about this post, you ask yourself?  34 people raised there hand to say they wanted to work out here, but right now I'm watching Shane do push-ups, and Tygre on the elyptical....
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      One thing that really encourages us if you post a comment.  That lets' us know that y'all are reading what we write. I understand if the post is not comment-worthy. I'll try to make them substantive!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I too feel like I'm getting used to the hilly, green surroundings and strange accents!  I just hope everyone else is starting to settle down. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay...this is going to sound really cheesy, but tonight was the first night I felt like I could call Judson, "home." We had a fiesta night, donned with crepe paper, tacos and a human pinata!--and the feel of the room was so real...like a family.   "Let the peace of Christ rule in your hearts, since as members of one body you were called to peace. And be thankful."  Colossians 3:15  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As of today, all but 6 people have jobs! That's such a praise!  Thanks for praying, and if you haven't, please start. Also, many folks need to raise lots of money, so be good stewards and help these peeps out!  urlLink Email me  if you want to know specifically how much someone needs.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Welcome to the Project Imapct Blog!!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey guys! I miss you terribly! Enjoy your last days in Chicago! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yesterday when we went evangelizing, three of our guys led someone to Christ. we now have a new brother, ricky!  YEAH!!!  be excited...i think that's four or five for the summer...    "We talk of the second coming, half the world has never heard of the first."             - Oswald J. Smith  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We gave our 2 weeks notice to the boss the other day. It was terribly sad... especially since the other girls wrote a note to tell the bosses and didn't just talk to them in person. I thought that was pretty hilarious, like a break-up note or something, too shameful to talk to them in person. Anyways... I can't believe there's only 3 weeks left... or in my case, 2 weeks (I have to leave a few days early... new news for me!). This place has become so dear to me and it feels like I haven't known this whole entire time that Project Impact will end at one point. Hopefully they'll have it here again next year. BUGS. I abhor them like Romans 12:9 tells us to abhor sin... well, maybe not that much. I was sitting in my rocker chair that I found for only $7 at Goodwill facing the window, and I was munchin on some really good ice cream. Well, there was a hole in the screen, so Sarah thought it would be a bright idea to put our fan in front of it so the bugs wouldn't come in. Well much to our dismay this hole-covering-fan actually turned out to be a huge suction for tiny little bugs just minding their own business flying past our window. I was about to take a bite of my fudge-revel ice cream from Meijer's when I see it... it was like slow motion... this bug flying through the fan through the hole.... we made eye contact as he was hurled head first into the pit of ice cream dispair. I let out a yell like there was no tomorrow as we watched the poor creature struggle for his last breath amidst the sweet creamy pool of melted Meijer ice cream....  We taped up the hole right after that.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well...we have a third of the summer left. it seems so long, yet so short.  i would like to share with you, my top five of the summer, so far. in no particular order.  1.  the steak and shake experience.  i admit, it is quite humbling working a drive thru for Jesus. i'm so glad i've done it. other perks include, the magical dishwashing machine you can get a facial from through the flying food particles and steam, thin and crispy fries, and the fun pins we get to add to our uniform as we get certified in different areas. sewiously. i have three, and they better not want them back.  2.  campus prayer.  i'm so spiritual for including this. it's been really neat learning about the lives of students around the country and knowing that we all share in the same struggles, yet are unique in our own way.  3.  shan and dane.  i wonder what will happen to dan and shane when the have to break-up at the end of the summer? you guys are a funny pair, though, and i'll always appreciate the time after amber's surprise party when we shared "special stories".  4.  deep dish pizza goodness.  i couldn't make a top five and not include this. it has forever changed my life and is the passion of my heart and the theme of my praise. not unlike the holy spirit, cheesecake and kite flying.  5.  the amazing two-story carousel at the st. charles mall.  it was the best dollar i've ever spent. enough said.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For lack of any other posts, here I am!  Ok, I gotta go type up something for the social.. nevermind!  Leave some love.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      today was great! really, our festivities began last night, with a paddleboat ride in st. charles. we had a boat to ourselves...very relaxing. except for those who rode the pony. i think they were pretty tired by the time we docked. :) click  urlLink here  to check out a few pictures.  today, we had an awesome prayer walk time around campus. we had six different stations we prayed at, for missionaries from our respective college campuses. i prayer walked with miss sarah dudley and mr. stan woo...pretty cool.  tonight we all ventured out to a park across the street from campus. we cooked hot dogs and played baseball, typical american things, in honor of the birth of our country. and don't think we didn't sing happy birthday to the u. s. of a., because we did.  hope everyone had a fantastic, magical and enchanting fourth of july, as well. we're HALFWAY! i can't believe it. gotta go do more inductive...seriously. more group dates! less inductive! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's over!  We are all at our homes.  It was a great summer!  Those of you who want to post experiences of the summer on here,  urlLink email me  and I'll send you an invitation so you can post here. All in all, project impact was a huge success. We will most likely be returning to Chicago next summer. 
     
    
</post>



</Blog>