<Blog>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Arun:  I'm not deviant! Mell:  You're Canadian! Arun:  It's morally sound world domination!  (yes, these are two of the main influences in my life... now you wonder why I NEED a weblog...)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today on piano:    Phantom of the Opera   Today on guitar:  everything I know how to play...  Today on TV:  Debate about Iraq resolutions.  Lots of words were said, few were actually communicated.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I went to the LACMA today with some ex-C2 buddies (that's ex-C2, not ex-buddy).  I had a really good time.  Ricky got to look at his piece of Southeast Asian Art, Olga and I got to see our century of fashion, and Lucas got to see George Washington even though the rest of us weren't too keen on that.  THEN... and THEN... we saw the Donald Blumberg exhibit!!  It was amazing!!  I had never heard of this guy before, but his work was absolutely amazing.  The exhibit is mostly black and white photography (simple room, basic black frames with white mattes).  My favorites were the TV series and the Daily Series... If you get a chance before January 5th, hop on over to the LACMA ($5 for students).  Here's a little clip from the LACMA press release:     Described as a “consummate technician” and “photographer’s photographer,” Blumberg is an artist whose signature style rests not in his selections of subject matter or in how those subjects are portrayed, but in the manner in which his images address issues of the photographic... The importance of Blumberg’s work lies in its reconciliation of the cognitive with the visual, the conceptual with the visceral, and the common with the exceptional. Donald Blumberg’s art is an art of integration.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been trying to figure out what to research for my final paper for my education policy class.  I always have the hardest time deciding on a project when the assignment is left so open-ended.  On first inclination, I started thinking about race issues.  This all links to affirmative action, the definition of racial subgroups in terms of evaluating public schools, the upcoming Racial Privacy Initiative that will be on the 2004 ballot.  Then I turned my focus to reading curriculum.  Think about how you learned how to read.  I can't remember exactly how I did.  California just implemented a phonics-based reading system in 1999.  LAUSD specifically uses what's called the "Open Court" reading system that is a rigorous 3-hr a day phonics-based curriculum.  Now that sounds like a good thing, because for decades people were leaving high school with a diploma but without basic reading skills, so this was an issue they knew they had to attack from the beginning.  But we're looking at a rigid curriculum that has improved reading scores, but that must take away from other things important to an elementary education, say, science, social studies, history, music, art...     Then I realized that there was an underlying issue beneath all of this.  Quick-fix policy vs. long-term-change policy.  Everything that is implemented is quick-fix.  Kids can't read, so let's do something drastic that may take away from other education opportunities, but it's ok as long as their reading scores go up by the first year.  There are racial injustices, so let's reverse that by accounting for the hardships that minorities face in admissions processes.  All quick-fix.  In the long run, these systems don't hit the core of the problems.  But what's the alternative to quick-fix?  There really is no alternative.  We have government officials who are in office for such a short amount of time that they have to prove themselves in two years before election time rolls around again.  So if you were in office what would you want to do?  Implement some policy that will show significant results before it's time for people to vote for you again.  Then it looks like you actually did something.  And think about if you were the person in charge of all the money.  You have such a limited pool of resources to work with, how do you decide how much goes where?  You give a system a certain amount of money and that system has to prove itself worthy before it comes time to redelegate money, otherwise it risks losing that funding for the next term.  So again, what does it have to do?  Produce significant results in two years.  But things really don't work this way.  Nothing can be fixed in such a short amount of time.   Long-term change happens slowly... results may not show up for years... Now that I've complained about that, do I have a solution?  Nope.  Kinda sad though.     "Because you can't change the world, but you can make a dent in it."    from Death to Smoochy  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      "everytime she sneezes I believe it's love."     from Anna Begins, Counting Crows  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      the LIST is now officially in three locations:  on a sticky, on a shrinky-dink, and now here.  the LIST, v 1.3  1. the after shower smell 2. filtered light (both through a window and through clouds) 3. cumulus clouds (indicative of a smog-free sky and clear weather) 4. the driver's "thank you" wave  (rare among LA freeways) 5. the look on JTs face when mom comes home (absolutely precious) 6. eye contact (among strangers, indicative that others matter) 7. feeling independent  8. morning  (freshness and renewal that cannot be experinced by  				sleeping in til noon) 9. a hand-written letter  (shows the extra effort made by a personal  						touch) 10. innocence  (lost too young too frequently) 11. a newly-made bed 12. freshly sharpened #2 pencils 13. "just because" gifts 14. listening to the same song as the person in the car next to you 15. reflections (from the water; thinking back--demonstrates the 			importance of your previous experiences) 16. being understood 17. natural light 18. learning to learn 19. acoustic guitars 20. being picked up at the airport  (it shows that you were missed, and  	 someone wanted to get you home as quickly as possible) 21. perfectly feathered drop shadows  (the aesthetics of details) 22. Friday afternoons  (a time to fully relax) 23. e-mails written at half past three  (it just had to be said at that  						moment) 24. having faith in people  (rarer than you think) 25. Rent 26. doodles: ink on narrow-lined notebook paper 27. not wanting to go to sleep 28. being told it was the nicest thing anyone has ever done 29. seeing someone stop to smell the flowers 30. feeling emotion  ("I don't own emotion I rent") 31. lack of boundaries  (the ability to be completely honest and  					vulnerable) 32. waiting up for the birds with someone who thinks it's selfish 33. being checked up on 34. walks with mom in the evening fog 35. the endless possibilities held by a sheet of clean, white paper 36. something so beautiful they should've sent a poet 37. sharing a book with someone 38. not being afraid of tanning your left arm  (actually enjoying an  				extended commute on the 405) 39. listening to someone sing who doesn't know you're listening 40. reminiscing with an old friend 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Elizabeth:  "Do we need our neighbor's business cards?"   Arun:  "No, and we certainly don't need four of them."  Leah:  "I certainly feel ridiculous writing a three dollar check."  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Monday, September 2, 2002.  Dundas Square, Downtown Toronto, Ontario, Canada.   Random Guy on Street:  "What's the most important thing in life?"  Arun, Amy, Ang: (long pause)  Ang: "Meaning"  Random guy: "I've asked this question for years to hundreds of people on the street, and that was the first time I've ever heard that answer." 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      go see Bowling for Columbine.  now.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      To Dance: no way to make a living, masochism, pain, perfection, muscle spasms, chiropractors, short careers, eating disorders.   Film: adventure, tedium, no family, boring locations, darkrooms, perfect faces, egos, money, Hollywood, and sleaze.   Music: food of love, emotion, mathematics, isolation, rhythm, feeling, power, harmony, and heavy competition.   Anarchy: revolution, justice, screaming for solutions, forcing changes, risk, and danger, making noise, and making pleas.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Lone guy with a guitar genre has just turned into not-so-lone girl with a borrowed guitar genre.  :)  Arun just got new speakers for his computer and hooked up some audi-whati device to it... and BAM our very own recording studio (after playing back at 300% amplification).  It's so cool!!  No matter how lame we sound (and trust me, after playing for only a few weeks we're no Clapton's), the raw sound of an acoustic guitar is utterly indescribable.  Ok, our acoustic guitar sounds are not quite indescribable yet, but it'll get there.  And when it does, and we're on tour or posing for the cover of Rolling Stones or something, we'll be able to listen back to the beginning days, when it was just us, two borrowed guitars, and the bedroom above the living room in the house on South Barrington street.  Poetic, eh?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      a hopped-up on caffeine stressed-out UCLA first year taking Psych 10 and thus a part of the psych subject pool student just told me that my job is boring...  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So, yes, I've been asian since August 4, 1981... but I still have not yet gone to one of Mell's asian parties that she's always trying to drag me to.  Tonight almost counted.  She'll say it didn't, but let's pretend it half-counted.  We went to Q's in Pasadena.  Thursday night = Asian night... It was quite the experience.  Let's just say that my parents better settle for a white guy cuz' I am so not attracted to asian ones... I don't know what it is.  Maybe cuz' it somehow seems incestuous or something.  Well whatever.  Regardless, I actually had a decent time.  Cage-dancing with Cindy was part of it.  But that doesn't mean I'm going back... :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      yet another GORGEOUS southern california morning...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      never take your family for granted.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      my Roman blind is my canvas.     Today for lunch:  sliced turkey on toasted 12-grain bread Today on the stereo:    you seek up any monster for him to fight your wars for you   --Dave Matthews Today in paint:  Observation.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      a couple of interesting quotes from my policy reader:   Even the most damning indictment of a policy is almost certain to be met with the response: "But what would you replace it with?"... Such a question confuses rather than clarifies... No one who extinguishes a fire or removes a cancer has to "replace" it with anything.  We are well rid of evils.  	--Thomas Sowell  (this next one intrigues me... but I really don't know what to think of it... what do you think?)  Treating everyone equally does not mean treating everyone identically.  --F.J. Crosby
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      42. a photographic image that you really didn't know you were capturing 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Fun things that I did today (well, technically yesterday):           -slept for over thirteen hours           -watched 8 Mile with Matt            -made a collage of Two and Three           -cooked with Leah           -got the electricity bill           -had a green tea latte from Rooms Cafe           -almost made the non-dynamic waiter at Jerry's smile           -pondered such issues as appearance at the Getty lot, intelligence, articulation, curriculum, child            development, affirmative action, alien abductions, a fifth dimension...           -saw the stars
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been reading stuff on Michael Moore's website.  For those of you who know me, I have what I call a "calm and collected" stance toward information.  You'll rarely ever see me visibly react to something I hear or read.   It doesn't mean that I don't care... trust me, I definitely care... it's just my way dealing with the millions of sensual perceptions we encounter every day.  I hear it.  I read it.  I think about it.  Then if I choose to do something about it, that's when you'll see my reaction.  Here's a link to an    urlLink  online chapter addition     to Michael Moore's "Stupid White Men."  Warning: it may piss you off.   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      never take your health for granted.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      41.  The post-rain sky in Southern California.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's been six whole days since the last time I "blogged."  That was definitely a change from, I don't know, 3 posts a day.  Well I'm STILL here, and I'm STILL posting, so I hope you don't think I've given up.  A lot has happened in a week, some good, some bad... well, mostly bad.  It's been really rough actually the past few days.  Really rough.  But I won't get into that now.  That'll be saved for the next rainy evening.  :)  For the time being...  It's time to start www.losetoledo.com.  No, really.  The one redeeming factor of today's oh-so-humiliating "thrashing" or "trouncing" or whatever else ABC 5 o'clock news (which happened to be absolutely ridiculously poorly produced) wants to call the USC/UCLA football game was the hope that FINALLY they will get rid of Bob Toledo.  Those who had a sliver of support for him should look at what happened today.  And last year.  And the year before.  And the year before.  I'm not really as upset as I sound (though I did sit down and hung my head in shame during the 16th second of the first quarter), but I'm at a friggin division one school, and I would've liked to have enjoyed the sweet victory of beating SC just ONE year... just ONE year... And without fail, the minute the game ended I got a nice little phone call from a darling Trojan Enginerd named   urlLink Melissa Hsieh  .  I let her have her fun.  I was a good sport about it.  After all, she has to live the rest of her life knowing she threw away tens of thousands of dollars for a halfway mediocre education... :)  yeah, I'm going to die for that comment.  :)  But anyway, football is now officially over in my mind.  Time for basketball.  Speaking of which, check out    urlLink  LoseLavin.com  .  Palabra. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      smile against the weight of your shoulders.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I fell asleep with my noodle bowl in my hand today.  Sure, laugh.  It's quite humorous.  Everyone I've told today seemed to chuckle a little.  It's Angie being funny...  I'll agree with that.  How often do you get to interject this kind of a statement into a conversation?  I fell asleep with my noodle bowl in my hand today.   But really, it's not that funny.  I fell asleep because I'm so fucking exhausted.  All of the time.  Not just some of the time anymore.  All of the time.  And then I wake up.  In pain.  Recently it's been headaches, but usually it's just muscle aches.  I either fall asleep again because I'm so exhausted I can barely figure out where I am or what time of day it is.  Or I lie there, unable to sleep anymore, but still, I'm to exhausted to move.  Of course I can't just lie in bed all day.  Even if I had no school, or no commitments, or nothing to do, I'd go crazy lying on my ass all day.  So I get up.  The pain usually somewhat subsides. Then I get ready for whatever it is I have to do that day.  And I go through the actions.  And most of the time, I don't notice the headache.  Or the fatigue.  And there are times, usually for about thirty minutes, maybe a couple of thirty minute sessions a day, when I feel about 75% healthy.  And there were actually two days this week, Tuesday and Wednesday, when I felt about 80% healthy most of the day.  We'll forget about the part where I fell asleep for 3 hours on Wednesday afternoon.  But those were two days out of the last three months.  And there were probably less than a dozen of those out of the last six months.    I trivialized it for a long time.  I denied it for a long time.  Then I thought I came to terms with it.  I was proud of myself for dealing so well.  I thought it was a waste of time thinking about how I felt.  But then I did start thinking about it.  It's subtle, but it's there.  I lose concentration on anything after a couple of hours.  I read at the rate of about a page every five minutes.  I lean on the side of the elevator to support myself.  It doesn't even occur to me to go to bed unless it's bedtime, no matter how I feel.    I didn't care before.  My rationale is that we all have our shit to deal with.  We have family issues and insecurity issues and financial issues and relationship issues.  I've been blessed to not have dealt with any of those problems, so I have this instead.  And there are so many others out there who have it so much worse than I do. So what if I can't go snowboarding this year.  So what if I can't dance all night at a club.  So what if I can't carry in a bottle of laundry detergent from the car. So what if I can't take the stairs up to the third floor without worrying about not being able to get out of bed the next morning.  I'll deal.  If only it weren't so fucking annoying.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Fun things that happened today (well, technically yesterday... you know, days really need to switch later in the evening, like at 4am): -talked on the phone w/ an old friend until the wee hours of the morning -ate way too much fake Cinnamon Toast Crunch for breakfast -learned about a new element of Baddeley's working memory model -rode the bus home with Professor Holyoak -ate dinner with Leah -watched both Will & Grace and Friends -observed an fMRI experiment -chatted with my cog sci lab TA Bas -chilled with Pauline on her quaint but cavernously echoic balcony -hung out and had some superficial fun at 2-for-1 with Jesse and Scott -took the last bus home (and got there in only 5 minutes) -saw the stars -posted to my blog  :)  sometimes you just need to put aside all your worries and burdens and just chill...    
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So I've deduced that the most important thing in life (see blog on 11.7.2002) is "meaning."  The most common answers to that question were love, family, friendship, relationships... what you would expect.  I also asked the guy who approached us with the question what he thought.  His answer: "truth."  Eh, I think even truth has its faults because the interpretation of truth is subject to individual variance.  But back to meaning... life is full of activity and information and people and emotions.  It isn't until you attribute meaning to these things, though, that they actually affect you and thus have an importance in your life.    So what's my meaning?  I am still in the process of figuring that out.  I once heard a soc professor speak about how the meaning of life is efficacy.  I think there's a lot of value behind that statement.  What is important to us is that we are in some way, shape, or form important to someone or something.  It can be importance to people, to professions, to disciplines, to culture, to bodies of thought... basically the rest of the world.  Perhaps this is why we so often identify ourselves by our profession.  "Hello, what's your name?  What do you do?"  We are defined by what we do; our sense of importance is derived by what we do.  We all desire to have an effect.  Efficacy isn't my meaning per se, but it's potentially the basis behind it.  I'm searching for the rest.  I have experienced though, in the past week, how we affect others in the grandest ways and how we can be so unaware of it.  It's seeing another "list" on a friend's blog.  It's being asked about #6 in your list by someone you didn't realize actually read your blog.  It's getting a letter from an old friend thanking you for something you did years ago.  It's finding out that a letter you wrote so many months ago is still being read.  It's realizing that you were never the same after something someone else said to you years ago.    We all have so much effect on each other, so much more than we could ever realize.   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today for lunch/dinner: Tuna Helper Today on TV: the non-upsetting Bruin loss to Washington St. Today on iTunes: Gasoline by Jann Arden    Yesterday as toasts: Arun - "Facing with others what we don't want to deal with alone"  Ang - "Understanding when no one else would and when no one else could" 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      We went out to celebrate Arun's birthday yesterday.  First it was dinner at Buca di Beppo, which is nice because in a family-style restaurant you can just order a few large dishes and don't have to sit around waiting for everyone to decide on their entree.  And did you know that Beppo = Joe and Buca = (literally) hole?  So Buca di Beppo (para los que pueden hablar espanol, buca no significa "boca") means Joe's Apartment or Joe's place... but literally Joe's hole.  I wonder what atrocity C&O stands for now...  Then we went to North on Sunset blvd.  I really enjoyed that place.  We had a nice corner booth reserved for us, the same one that Dr. Dre sat at the last time Tony went there.  It's a nice loungy bar, with really good music, a totally eclectic crowd, and a good looking waiter.  :)  But seriously, people watching was so far there, and we had the prime seats to people watch.  The booth next to ours went through nice transitions... first it was the old crew (grandma and grandpa basically) then the fancy crew (this couple wearing a tuxedo and evening gown) and then the J.Crew crew (really, straight out of the catalog, sweater tied around and everything).  The tux crew was nicely contrasted when two guys walked by us wearing sweatshirts, jeans, and sneakers.  Nice, eh?  I myself was wearing a semi-skanky yet tasteful see-through lacy shirt with a black bra underneath.  The waiter at Buca (who really didn't deserve as big of a tip as we gave him because not only did he spill Diet Coke down my back he denied it tried to play it cool) commented on how he could see my underwear... which started a whole what kind of underwear, upstairs, downstairs, uptown, downtown, northern hemisphere, south of the equator conversation.  Then somehow the Lindsa(e)y H(e)artma(e)n story came into the picture.  Then, absolutely pricelessly, a table of 24 of her happened to sit down to dinner near us.  That was fun.  Overall, crazy evening.  No need for more details here, but you can definitely ask about them later.  Be sure to bring up marischino cherries, Shivani's three men, Ty the waiter, the Love Potion, Ginger-ific!, and non-discriminatory cruising along Sunset.  Peace. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I am: not defined by one statement I think: realistically  I know: the world is fucked up  I want: to learn how to play the guitar I have: respect for those who follow their dreams I wish: for others' happiness I hate: not being able to fulfill that wish I miss: having energy I fear: failure I feel: insecure at times I hear: everything from my loft I crave: attention I search: for meaning I wonder: when things will actually change  I demand: to be taken seriously I regret: not taking risks I love: a clear sky after the rain I ache: all over I long: for sponteneity I care: too much sometimes I always: look over my shoulder before changing lanes I am not: superficial I believe: in giving people the benefit of the doubt I dance: the running man I sing: loudly in my car I cry: when I lose hope I do not always: make my bed in the mornings I fight: preconceived expectations of myself I write: when I want to be heard I win: every time I learn something new I lose: my train of thought   I never: want to think that I've wasted my life                                                                                            I envy: those who know and follow their passion I confuse: myself all the time I listen: to the Rent Soundtrack during commutes I can usually be found: in Franz I am scared: that I won't find a passion to follow I need: to be understood I am happy about: life's simple pleasures I expect: nothing I should: relax more  (thanks Randall)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Arun found Jesus at the ripe young age of three.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      3 units a day, some consecutive, some not.  Though recently there have been many more than 3 units, which is definitely hopeful.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been thinking I've been thinking I've been thinking too much I just want to live now for a little while And cast my dreams to the wind Don't wanna wonder Don't wanna wonder what it's all about I'm just working for a living singing with my friends As I cast my dreams to the wind  Maryland, I'm coming home Never worry about what I did wrong And that I'll never be what my daddy wanted me to be And I'll never see what my mama's dreams were But I will sing...  I wanna fly I wanna fly down the highway to my home away from home This funky funky club on Fairfax Avenue to see you I'll never give up Because what is there to give up anyway I'm just working for a living, working for my pay In Maryland it's raining somewhere in some cafe  Maryland, I'm coming home Never worry about what I did wrong And that I'll never be what my daddy wanted me to be I'll never see what my mama's dreams were But I can sing...  - Vonda Shepard 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Every girl needs a   urlLink Mell   in her life.  There are so many times in our life when we're so blind to what's really going on or what we're really doing.   (we can be blinded by a lot of things, but usually it's our stubborn - hard - headed  - of - course - I'm - always - right - and - I - know - what's - best nature).  There needs to be someone out there who you trust and who you know always looks out for your best interest and who will be completely honest with you even if it's the last thing you want to hear.  Those who have a Mell may get upset initially, but it will be for the better in the long run.  Those who don't have a Mell... well... good luck.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Why I haven't slept well the past few nights:  4:00am- a cell phone on NY time beeped and vibrated its wake-up call 3:26am- the kitchen door blew wide open with a gust of wind 3:45am- the temperature of our house dropped about 15 degrees 3:09am- my overabundance of blankets decided to start capturing my body heat 5:01am- Pascal's van is ready for pickup 5:16am- I overhear a conversation between Elizabeth and the Super Shuttle guy 5:19am- An automated Super Shuttle call arrives 8:36am- The FedEx guy presses the gate buzzer way too long  I'm just bitching and whining... there's no other justification.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The intricacies of the letter P...  "Give me a P!  Go P!  Go P!" The three P's: pen, planner, positive attitude. The three P's: pink panty pullovers. Madame P. P. Diddy. Being P.O'd.  (can you tell I don't want to write paper #3?)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Two down, two to go.   Sorority girls take SO many pictures of themselves. Airport LIES.  It LIES I tell you.  There's something to be said about crisp, cold evenings. (Having said that) It was so cold here that I had to sleep with one down comforter, one regular comforter, and a huge sweatshirt. Mom called me "shao bao bey."  One of my peer mentoring students gave me a hug.  Nobody knows me, no one will ever see the distance between what is and what will never be.  A bird will break his wings, like a heart will cut her strings.  And there isn't anything to comfort me.   --Jann Arden There is something to be said about the $5.60+tax chicken special from Maya Japanese food. What is most upsetting is hating something about someone, and then realizing that what I've despised all along is a part of myself.    
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ugh, once again.   urlLink FireToledo.com  !!! hopefully that'll link right.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ok that didn't work right:  Also note in the navigation section of the page:    urlLink  FireToledo.com   !!!  Did I call it or what?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      One of life's simple pleasures (from   urlLink LoseLavin.com   ):  ---------- Dear Mr. Guerrero,  We would like to applaud your decision on the firing on Bob Toledo. Clearly, it was time for a change. Your quick decision has given us confidence to think that you would not hesitate to do the same thing to “Coach” Lavin. While we may have gotten a win yesterday against a crappy Long Beach State team, behind a monster performance from Kapono, it looks to be a long season for all fellow Bruin fans.  We hope that we are wrong, but clearly Lavin thinks the same as we do. After the game “Coach” Lavin made this comment…  “Clearly, we're a work in progress…We've got a long way to go but I really think that by mid-January or mid-February, we have a chance to be a pretty special squad.''  Mid-February?!?!? What?!?!? Is he kidding? It seems that Lavin is once again looking for a sweet sixteen berth to save his job. In our eyes, and in the eyes of all of our supporters, that is not acceptable. This is UCLA, not USC, not Southern Illinois, not Pepperdine. We expect more than to be a “work in progress” at the beginning of the season. Memo to “Coach” Lavin – That’s what the off-season is for!!!  Sincerely,  The Lose Lavin Guys ----------  Also note in the navigation section of the page:    urlLink FireToledo.com  !!!  Did I call it or what?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      From   urlLink Mell's blog  .  Ha.  "told my friend it was okay to be a slut as long as she was proud of it   and emotionally stable enough to handle it" (Angie=friend)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The tides have turned.  The shoe is on the other foot.  Potato potato.     I haven't changed.  I've developed.    Brainstorming sessions must be without boundaries in order to produce creative thought.  There's buzzing about firing Toledo.  finally.   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's Friday, December 20, at about 5:18 in the afternoon.  I'm hungry.  I just took 71 pictures at the Getty.  I'm sleepy.  I have a runny nose.  The house is empty and cold.  I have laundry to do.  I have the GRE to study for.  I have Christmas presents to buy, Christmas cards to write, and Christmas presents to wrap.    You're dead inside.  There are so many things about you that only I understand, because it's me.  But there are so many things inside you that I never will understand, because it's me.    So just to make this as disjoint as possible, who wants to hear my Vegas story?  It's too long for me to write here, but I'll give you a hint: Rain, getting into a private party for free, winning $135, my lucky dealer Shawn, Studio 54, the thong, salsa lessons, and my bargain jacket.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      During my last LACMA visit, I realized what it was about artwork that really captures my attention: contrast.  It's all about contrast.  Take a canvas--standard, two-dimensional, rigid boundaries--add contrast, and you've suddenly created the illusion of something dynamic and three-dimensional on an otherwise limited surface.  There was one painting in particular at the LACMA that made me realize this.  Of course I don't remember who the artist was, but it was a piece of American art showing a national park landscape.  There was such a distinct contrast between the mountains in the shadowed foreground and the lightened-almost-hazy background mountains creating the unmistakable illusion of depth on an otherwise depthless plane.  There was a piece of modern art that Vinita really liked.  It was an elongated diamond with a blue semi-circle painted onto it.  Vinita commented on how the shape was so dynamic because of the blue paint, but how it was ultimately just a diamond.  What created that shape?  Contrast.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So let's see what Angie's been up to lately.  :)   Christmas Eve: went to the doctor's, viral count from November negative- woohoo!, feeling much better fatigue-wise, just dealing with daily headaches now, possibly being prescribed narcotics but trying to avoid that, baked rum cake, prepared tiramisu, had some family friends over for dinner, some people never change...  Christmas Day: woke up early to open presents, got my Brookstone tempur-pedic swedish foam pillow that I've been asking for for years, helped Joshua move all sets of car keys from location to location, made mashed potatoes, creamed corn, and rib roast rub, watched our Bowl game, read up on UNM's freshman fake-ID debaucle (if you're going to color xerox fake IDs at Kinkos, the least you could do is NOT LEAVE YOUR TRASH), fell asleep during the third quarter (when the Bruins actually scored their touchdowns), had dinner with extended family, saw "catch me if you can" (excellent story, love Tom Hanks, could've been executed better though, overall thumbs up)  Day after Christmas: rolled out of bed around 11, read the LA Times cover to cover, ate salad for lunch, gave Vinita a quick guitar lesson, watched part of "Center Stage" (with someone who can actually appreciate the accuracy of portraying dancers),  went to South Coast Plaza w/ DPe and Shiv, ate at the Rain Forest Cafe (overrated food, good-looking customers), watched ER, watched Friends, watched Edward Norton on the Tonight Show (love him as an actor, not impressed with him on TV, even though he owns an iPod), watched Roberto Benigni on Conan (Conan wears boxer-briefs)  Day after the Day after Christmas: rolled out of bed at 11:30, had a leftover Christmas ham sandwich for lunch, went to the LACMA w/ Vinita, perused the Donald Blumberg exhibit again (I'm newly inspired to create photo collages), walked around the Grove, ate at Corner Bakery (thumbs up), went to The Lounge (Asian night- thumbs down)...  Actually, I'm going to pause for an "Asian Night" commentary: What the hell is all of this Asian business about?  I went with Mell, Jess, and Wendy.  I think Wendy had a pretty good time, but Mell and Jess were as bored as I was.  I can't put my finger on it though.  I have never had a "bad time" going out before--it doesn't matter all that much who I'm with or what I'm wearing, I usually have a good time regardless.  The night was SO LAME though.  I blame it on the music--very boring, monotonous, choppy, boring, non-dynamic, boring.  I guess I blame it on the crowd, though it's not like I was out there to meet people so I don't know what it is about Asian people that bother me so much.  I suppose it's the air of image-oriented-ness/I'm hard... but I don't know.  Mell's comment of the evening semi summed it up for me.  As we were walking out of the restroom, some girl was walking in so she semi-slammed the door into me.  She apologized right away, and I said "oh, it's ok" and Mell scorned me for saying "that's ok" instead of giving her the "whatever, bitch" glare... is that everyone else's mentality too?  I still firmly hold onto my belief that "typicals" are the most insecure people on this earth, with the males being much more insecure than the females.  Whatever.  Perhaps I'll have something more profound to say on this topic later... for now I choose to avoid such settings.  Today: Went to the bball game with Matt, had a really good time, even though we lost, newfound love for Jon Crispin even though he scored less than a handful of points today, he just needs more playing time-- did you hear that Lavin??, went online to order my Lose Lavin t-shirt but found out they don't have smaller sizes, had my car searched while trying to watch a movie (Chicago but it sold out just before we got to the front of the line)  I love break.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      on thermostat: not sure, but definitely not more than 60 deg on TV: Sweet November (tried but couldn't watch it-- too painful) on iTunes:   this bed is on fire with passionate love/the neighbors complain about the noises above/but she only comes when she's on top   on me: fleece sweater, jeans, blue UCLA shirt, khaki UCLA cap 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      12 people.  200 dollars in cash.  the Rio hotel.   Vegas baby, here I come again...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       New Year's 2003 a success.      Dish of the night   : toss up between the Linguine Pollo Marsala (courtesy of C&O Trattoria) and Angie's spinach salad (courtesy of Angie)  Drink of the night : Vanilla Stoli and Coke  Photo of the night :  Jenn and Jon after uncorking the champagne... suck suck suck suck suck!  Story of the night : Perry Choi's, um, girl he picked up from the BART station, um, we don't know her last name... but he threw her out the front door!!   Joke of the night  (courtesy of a very drunk Adrian Saura... and I apologize for the lewdness, but it was just too funny of an Adrian moment to forget): What's the difference between a slut and a bitch?  A slut sleeps with everyone, and a bitch sleeps with everyone but you.    Dance contest winners of the night : the guys, courtesy of Alex's handstand-from-sitting  Reading material of the night :  the Victoria's Secret Semi-Annual Sale catalogue  Best afterparty moment  (afterparty = the next morning):  "Dueling Banjos" aka Dueling Guitar and Piano    Quote of the night #1 :  "So is Matt trying to get in your pants?" courtesy of Ryan  Quote of the night #2 :  (as Mell and I are walking down from the loft together) "If anyone asks, yes, we were making out." -Mell  Thanks to all of you who drunk-dialed me that night... I am honored that you consider me so special that you'd call me first... I guess it helps that with an A name, I'm the first in so many people's list of contacts... Those at the party definitely got a kick out of me answering my cell phone.  "Hello... Hi  !!... Are you drunk?..."  Prize goes to Corey... it was only 9:45 when you called buddy!   email me if you have others  :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      43.  spontaneity
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Driving up the 101, there's this section of land that curves around into the ocean somewhere between Camarillo and Santa Barbara.  The freeway is literally feet from the ocean, and you can see die hard surfers parking their car along the side of the highway and bringing their longboards into the waves.  There are tall green hills on one side of you, and the calm, sparkling, lapping ocean on the other.    Absolutely amazing.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Fun things that happened today: played guitar engaged in self-discovery with    urlLink Mell   began relearning "Doktor Gradus ad Parnassum" and "Deux Arabesque" on the piano made eye contact with complete strangers and smiled recovered from last night with a two-hr nap had a fun conversation with Mell's security guard  quote of the day: "this one's about sex... it HAS to be about sex..."
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Highlands.  Crazy.  It's funny how LA works sometimes.  It's such a necessity to be on the guest list or the VIP list to get into these high-trafficked, posh clubs, yet even if you are on one you'll still be standing around waiting for an hour with the rest of the crowd.  Had a really good time dancing with my girls and meeting Jenn's cousins and some of Stacy's ex-boyfriend's friends.  Played a little game with Ian where we picked people for the other to mack on (obviously he picked guys for me and I picked girls for him)... I happened to have to hit on this guy who recognized me from over at the bar earlier because of my butt... now that's a new one.  He was from Miami.  What's with all these Florida guys all of a sudden?  Didn't dance with him much though.  Ended up meeting the assistant vice president of GE capital commercial equipment financing because he was wearing the same striped shirt as 4 other guys on the dance floor... it must've been the after-Christmas sale at J. Crew.  Overall, Highlands gets a thumbs up from me but only if you actually get there early enough to not have to wait in the huge crowd.  Well-mixed crowd.  No one too incredibly shady. Huge dance floor so there was plenty of room most of the evening.  Oh!  And I got to see this one girl lunge at and punch another- think Lilo & Stitch, but with hooched-out women instead of little hawaiian girls.  Ok, ears are starting to ring a little less.  Time for bed.  Peace. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jon Crispin, if you're reading this, I'm your biggest fan!  :)  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Most painful Swingers moment: Mike calling Nikki within 30 min of leaving the Dresden. Best Swingers LA moment: "818?"  "No, 310."  "Ohhhh..." Favorite Swingers moment:  "I grew up in LA!"  "Anaheim..."  Favorite LA Story quote:  "I'll have a double half decaf half caf with a twist of lemon." Favorite LA Story moment:  Steve Martin roller skating through the contemporary section of the LACMA.   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      (09:11) Mell: miyagi's tomorrow. (09:12) nuttyprncs: a girl should never accept a date for friday after tues (09:12) Mell: yes (09:12) nuttyprncs: so have fun (09:12) Mell: like never saturday after wednesday (09:12) Mell: hahaha (09:12) Mell: oh please. i'm a GIRL (09:12) Mell: we're not going out on a date (09:12) Mell: haha (09:12) nuttyprncs: damn (09:12) nuttyprncs: and I have plans (09:13) Mell: hahaha. funny funny angie (09:13) nuttyprncs: I do (09:13) nuttyprncs: you think I'm just going to sit around waiting for you to invite me out? (09:13) nuttyprncs: I have a life you know (09:13) Mell: yes. (09:13) Mell: oh please (09:13) Mell: i AM your life (09:13) Mell: you are nothing without me (09:13) Mell: you think you can just go out and make new friends?! (09:13) nuttyprncs: bitch (09:14) Mell: hahahahaha
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Everyone needs a   urlLink Matteeo   in their life.  I mean, with what other friend can you act like a complete idiot and not fear judgment nor ridicule in the least?  Ladies, he's single.  And he plays the guitar.   That makes him a player.   (emphasis courtesy of Matt)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      more signs that this is a parallel universe:  G-love disappears and his deceased body is found a car runs a red light and almost hits 4 pedestrians I open our garage door directly into the Horowitz's spotless Volvo a truck almost rear ends a car backing out of its driveway two cars collide at the intersection of Veteran and Gayley
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I didn't pay for excitement.  I paid for a victory.  4/26 overall from the 3-point line.  Kapono is the epitome of UCLA sports -- INCONSISTENT.    So let's see.  Ray Young (as painful as it is to say) is on fire.  What does Lavin do?  Take him out.  Cedric Bozeman is on fire.  What does Lavin do?  Take him out.  Jason Kapono absolutely sucks (4/15 field goals).  I don't care how many points he scored in Washington.  What does Lavin do?  LEAVE HIM IN.    And Jon Crispin did not get ANY playing time.  This is personal.    At least our soccer team is good... 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So it's official.  I'm graduating at the end of winter.  Crazy stuff.  Degree conferred:  March 2003. Bachelor of Science in Cognitive Science with a minor in Education Studies and a specialization in Computing.  I wonder where I'll end up.  Probably LA.  I've grown to love it.  Everything about it.  Really, it's 80 degrees.  I'm wearing a skirt and a tank top.  It's the middle of January.  Well actually, I stand by my theory that we're throwing our homeostatic abilities out of whack.  But that's besides the point.  I love it here.  The ocean, the pretty people... It's not a desert with sprinklers... they took a desert and made it into their dreams.  Yeah, I just watched LA Story.  Excellent LACMA scenes.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Things I've resolved to do  (not the same as New Year's Resolutions, because we all know those are a load of crap): 1. not flip off Mell 2. develop my creative side through music and photography ("and if there are THREE kids in the family, then good luck to the youngest one... hopefully they'll be an artist or something") 3. watch SportsCenter 4. stay updated on current issues 5. stop being quite so harsh on Asian people (that's a tough one)   more to come... 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today was the first day of my last quarter here as an undergrad at UCLA.  I got somewhat nostalgic, especially after talking to a first year in my class who has his entire academic career ahead of him.  I hope I made the most of my time here.  I think I have.  There really isn't much that I would have done differently, short of being more involved or following my gut instinct earlier on...  I got to spend time with old friends tonight.  It's funny how you can go through so many life changes and be apart for so long, then get back together and chit chat the night away as if nothing has changed.  I think it's sad when people don't enjoy what they're doing and where they are, when they resent all of the studying or how far away from home they were or what the weather was like or what type of people they spent time with... Well final quarter, here I come.  And I'm going to make the best out of you.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      12 people.  loss of over 1000 dollars in cash.  lots of driving, little sleep.  oh Vegas.  The Rio hotel is a blast- definite recommendation... Huge suites, fun atmosphere, shows every hour, fun dance club that's free for hotel guests, pools that are actually open in the winter... The only thing that sucks is it's off the strip, which makes strolls along the strip less accessible.  It IS near the Palms Hotel though, which is nice.  And it hosts the Chippendales... definitely the highlight of the trip!  Remind me to show you the poloroid and the strip of wet t-shirt that I have as souveniers... The guys on our trip were none too amused though (insecure I tell ya)...   ok, I'm off.  Vegas again in 13 days... 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A wise friend tells me there are two forms of communication: a loving response or a cry for help.  Fuck weblogs as a cry for help.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       It’s time for Guerrero to put Lavin, fans out of their misery   By Jeff Eisenberg DAILY BRUIN SENIOR STAFF jeisenberg@media.ucla.edu  With every errant pass, every wayward jumper and every chorus of boos, it has become increasingly clear.  Dan Guerrero cannot allow the Steve Lavin era to endure any longer.  Although Saturday's demoralizing loss to St. John's may have sealed Lavin's fate, it is not enough that he be replaced at the end of the season. The imposing mystique that once embodied UCLA basketball has taken more hits than ... well, has Bob Marley ever toured in Amsterdam?  And like Marley, the damage may be irreparable if changes aren't made immediately.  As the Bruins' NCAA tournament prospects continue to grow dimmer than a Chico State cheerleader, the environment at Pauley Pavilion fluctuates between caustic and apathetic. UCLA (4-7) is just 2-5 at home this season, and empty seats – like inexplicable December losses – are now taken for granted.  The Bruins are averaging just 8,000 people per game; only high school sensation LeBron James has played before a sold-out Pauley Pavilion.  Those fans that have chosen to attend have not exactly been supportive. The student section has been dotted with LoseLavin.com T-shirts all season, and the crowd has often booed the Bruins off the court after losses.  The die-hard gravediggers have even openly rooted against the team in hopes that every loss is another nail in Lavin's coaching coffin.  Although Lavin has somehow avoided the unemployment line during each of his mercurial seven years as UCLA head coach, flames have virtually engulfed his hot seat this season.  In the past, the Bruins have rallied around their embattled leader in classic "win-one-for-the-Gipper" style, easing the pain of an early-season malaise by reeling off a winning streak in February or March.  Most of the players on this year's squad appear to enjoy playing for Lavin, but the two notable exceptions could be the most crucial to the future of the program.  According to the Los Angeles Daily News, sophomores Cedric Bozeman and Dijon Thompson are unhappy with Lavin and the direction that the team is headed.  Bozeman considered quitting after the Bruins' second exhibition loss of the season, but decided to remain with the team. Meanwhile, Thompson is the central figure in one of the great unsolved mysteries of our time. How he lost his spot in the starting lineup earlier in the season is as bewildering as trying to figure out who shot JFK.  Despite being UCLA's second-leading scorer on the season, Thompson played just 24 minutes against St. John's, registering five points on two-of-four shooting. He did not enter the game in the second half until only 12:41 remained in the contest.  Just the threat of losing the two most talented players on the squad ought to have Guerrero chasing Lavin through the halls of the Morgan Center, mace in hand. But the first-year athletic director has already stated that he has no intention of making a change prior to the end of the season.  For his part, Lavin appears much like a prisoner on death row who has used up all of his appeals. He has already contacted several friends at Purdue about taking over the program, once Gene Keady retires, and has also expressed interest in working in broadcasting in the future.  Regardless of Lavin's future plans, the facts surrounding this season at UCLA remain as clear as the chants at Pauley Pavilion calling for his demise.  A declining fan base, a diminishing talent pool, and a squad that appears listless and lethargic have exposed all that is wrong with UCLA basketball and appear to have spelled the end of the Lavin era in Westwood.  "I've been here seven years as a head coach, five as an assistant – I know the landscape," Lavin said after Wednesday's loss to USC. "They've lined up to execute me for seven years, but they keep missing."  Here's hoping that it's Dan Guerrero who dons the executioner's hood this time and not the media. And here's hoping he acts quickly.  The regular season ends March 8. That's 61 more days – can you wait?  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ok so what if he tried to take ridiculously illogical 3-point shots... we'll ignore that for the moment and glee in the fact that we're one step closer to losing Lavin.    SB was tons of fun.  IV exactly demonstrates the University of Casual Sex and Beer stereotype.  All I can say is if you are female and have a beer gut (= I'm addressing over 50% of the female population there) then please don't wear the same hooched out shirts that you wore back in high school when you didn't have a beer gut.  And please don't wear those low-rider cut-off jeans that let your belly hang out even more.  Please Please Please.  Please Please Please.      Time for Tony's guitar lesson.  peace. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       excerpt from v3, v1:   Konstantin, the Russian waiter with the faux-French accent serving us Italian pasta (taken by the Portuguese from the Chinese) at Le Provençal, a French restaurant inside the hotel Paris, an "I am France" establishment in the middle of the Nevada desert (Vegas), USA.   > "Look at me, I am French." - Arun imitating Konstantin (back in LA).  note for future reference: his name wasn't really Konstantin
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      current reading list:   Balzac and the Little Chinese Seamstress   -Dai Sijie   Stupid White Men   -Michael Moore   Talk about Sex:  The Battles over Sex Education in the United States   -Janice M. Irvine  "I always knew Michael Moore would come between us."
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       So much has happened, so little time to tell:  v3, v1 in publication... no more Vegas please Bill Viola's "Passions" opened at the Getty -- must see potential/probable relapse in progress Roscoe's Chicken and Waffles still satisfying tastebuds and clogging arteries Jon Crispin made a 3-pt shot against Cal the Circle Bar: where college boys go to pick up on grown up chicks full-time work with Megan to begin spring quarter living location for next year beginning to be secured Randall's fragile psyche theory -- never say anything to screw anyone up, especially your kids Adaptation: the best movie Hollywood ever made about itself.  It's about flowers. "Hey, you see that girl?  Yeah, I fucked her up the ass..."   "I'm just kidding" beware of harming your gums while brushing American Idol -- depressing proof of how many delusional people exist in this world 1 part Pimms No. 1 to 3 parts Lemonade with a slice of lemon the Raspberry martini: raspberry pucker, fresh lime juice, absolut citron "I grew up in LA!"  "Anaheim..." cloud panorama framed 8x10 and awaiting display -- thanks again Arun IKEA birch dining table as desk: still just something to keep all my shit from sitting on the floor next to figure out on piano:  Hands by Jewel   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      being called Miss Angela  Went to 99th St today.  These kids are so bright and have so much potential, but won't have the opportunities to realize it... how do we make those opportunities exist?  I don't know exactly.  Clinton was on Larry King Live last night.  All political schmoozing aside, one of the greatest things he said was: yes, he's making TONS of money right now, and it's because of the greatness of America that he was fortunate to have those opportunities to succeed, and because of that, it's his time to give back to the nation.  People don't all earn their wealth through hard work; it's because the doors are wide open for them.  Eh, more on this thought later...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Because my father is under the impression that people go through clutch plates like clean underwear.  long pause, looks upward...  So, quickly.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Too much hype usually kills everything for me... but not so much here.  Saw  Chicago  tonight.  Overall very good.  Very true to form.  Broadway hits Hollywood with a bang.   Richard Gere as Billy Flynn in a tap dance sequence montaged with a performance of pure law genius.  Worth the entire $7.00.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      more fun stuff... I'm on a roll...  There supposedly was an Affirmative Action Bake Sale on campus yesterday.  Someone PLEASE tell me you saw it... and tell me ALL about it...  Now I feel lame in asking this, cuz' I feel like I should know these arguments, but isn't affirmative action (in its current implementation) based on the same foundations as racial profiling?  How can people argue that something that is so blatantly wrong in one case can be right in another case?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wow, so diggin deeper, there's SO MUCH behind all of this stuff.    1.  Have conservatives been fighting all along in higher education to get their side of the story included?  It's a very noble fight.  These are institutions that are supposed to train people to think.  If they're being taught to think within the constraints of a bounded body of thought, then they're not really fulfilling their purpose.  2.  How does this all relate to other schools of thought, say, high school biology?  Do they teach both evolution and creationism in these classrooms now?   How do we expand curriculum to include other cultural perspectives without going way over our heads?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Editorial: Professor bias doesn’t always hinder learning    look, even the Daily Bruin is talking about this... and don't you love, like all editorials, how the title will say one thing, the bulk of the article will say otherwise, and it'll all try to wrap up to the conclusion that the title designates... yeah...    The question of whether students' education is compromised by the political biases of their professors has come up recently in various media. Concern emerges from the belief that students will mold their intellect and ideology around the ideas communicated by their professors, rather than formulate their own belief system based on an unbiased education.  Professors are biased; that's the bottom line. At UCLA, about 90 percent of professors in the political science department registered with a major political party are Democrats. It's understandable why conservative students might feel they are in the minority, when so few openly Republican professors teach their classes.  But a professor's political preferences do not necessarily inhibit him or her from establishing a productive, diverse learning environment. Bias exists because professors are just as human as students, and so have developed sets of values throughout their careers that often affects the orientation of their research. Often time these biases may not come through at all because the subject matter for many disciplines, such as engineering or the physical sciences, does not actively ask students to think about controversial issues as much as classes in the political science, sociology or public policy fields would. That the biases exist, though, should not be regarded as the problem: biases become problematic when they lead to unintelligent political banter that can hinder student education.  Many professors and teaching assistants of liberal persuasions are known to off-handedly joke about the president or the Republican Party for the sake of joking, not education. Though seemingly innocent, unsubstantiated humor has the effect of belittling the values students in the classroom may hold. When their values are made the subject of professors' amusement, students will be less likely to voice those values and challenge the positions taken by their professors. Conservative students are already "surrounded" by liberal peers; to have the professor make light of the classroom minority is unfair. It defeats the whole purpose of college. College should be a safe place for the free interchange of ideas leading to personal intellectual enrichment.  Professors cannot separate themselves from their ideology, especially when teaching about politics and contemporary social issues – and there's no reason why they should try to. Teaching students about the research they have done supporting their ideas about society will help students on the same ideological plane develop a foundation for their own ideas. However, professors must also make certain to create an environment where students who disagree with them have no reservations about contradicting them in class. Having an open, frank debate about political issues where multiple ideological frameworks are analyzed and students are allowed to grow no matter what their political persuasions are is the ideal.  It's not productive for professors to pretend they are neutral, or to compromise the extent of the research they present in class in an effort to seem unbiased. Intelligent debate is key. And this can be accomplished through a relationship of mutual respect between professors and students which emphasizes student learning regardless of personal biases. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Disclaimer: This is just a fun little semi-superficial exercise I choose to engage in. To all the potential husbands out there, do not let this deter you.   Good god I sound like Mell... :)     Reasons why Randall is my ideal man  (feel free to add): 1. He's SO ROSS, but won't admit it.   2. I fit 9/10 of his "What makes a woman attractive list."  Next on my agenda: learn how to drive stick. 3. He's childishly funny, yet captivatingly profound. 4. He's interested in the complexities of the human brain, both physical and superphysical. 5. He has a true appreciation for his background and his future. 6. He's a Bruin. 7. My parents would actually approve for once.    to be continued...   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      plastic tubing at 23 cents/foot  .23 x #of feet  purchasing spray-on shellac  $5.99  saying "I should sleep with this!!"  free   being funnier than an episode of  Friends   Priceless  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've found one of my paper topics.  ADHD and its treatments.  Am I really that interested in this topic?  Not really.  Then why am I writing about it?  Because I'm pissed off that today's class was so incredibly one-sided in discussing the issue.  Even when I was fishing for a sliver of support for the other side of the argument, I got no answers to my question.  I mean, it really shouldn't be that big of a deal, especially since I generally agree with what the professor and random-guy-in-back-with-degree were saying, but the implications of it all really began to piss me off afterward.  We're in an institution of higher learning where we should be encouraged to do just that: learn.  There are very few topics in the social sciences that can be conclusively decided upon one way or another.  Each side has its supporters, and each side has its adversaries.  I fully believe that we should be taught to search through both sides of the argument before coming to conclusions for ourselves.  I agree that professors and the like should have their own opinions about the topic and should be able to voice such opinions, but I also think that they should be qualified as opinions and not be discussed as if they were absolute fact.  They know we're impressionable, they know we're barely educated about any of these areas which they study with years of experience and expertise.  But their experience still does not justify this narrow-mindedness when it comes to not allowing students to explore all sides of the argument in order to form their own opinions.  And this is just an education class.  I can't even begin to fathom what goes on in the realms of more controversial disciplines.  Last week there were tons of articles talking about academia's reaction to Bush, revealing that over 90% of poli sci professors here who identify with one of the two major political parties are democrat.  Yes, I need to watch my influences, especially lately, but really, some diversity here please?  Fuck all this racial business.  Skin color does not equal diversity.  It's a diversity of ideas that really matter in an insitution of higher education, and granted these ideas may stem from a variety of experiences including being of a minority status, it's not all about race.  So stop fixating on it.  And now that we're looking at people's ideas--and political affiliation governs so many aspects of these ideas--we see how grossly unbalanced this department is.    I've never taken a poli sci class before (cuz' you all know how much I detest politics), but I'd imagine that one-sided arguments can be much more prevalent than in my ed classes.  It makes me sad, then, if this is really true, because as much as we'd like to think we're perpetuating the concept of learning and discovery, we may just be feasting on these spoon-fed opinions with little thought otherwise.    So note to self when I'm a professor: express opinions, justify them as opinions, empower students with the resources to form their own opinions, and for the love of god, fucking answer questions when asked.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      "That would be the BEST DAY!  Ang would knock out a cow and we'd eat it!"  -Arun  "Is your computer making sexual advances toward you?" -Tony "I don't care about wind blowing through trees, you eighty year old moron"  -Tony "With that tan-in-a-bottle shit" -Arun "That's a shaky palm tree.  That's funny." -Leah  I love my roommates.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      reading in the hot tub downstairs.  (just kidding)  "So Helsinki is beautiful this time of year..." "Yes it is" (long pause) "Uh, I gotta get going"  "So Helsinki is beautiful this time of year..." "Yes, especially the snow."  and his name really WAS Konstantin
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Other things that need to self-clean  (besides the oven): -my room -the dishes (dishwashers do not count) -the counter -the stove -the kitchen floor -all floors, especially carpeted ones -the coffee table -bathroom counters -toilets -my car
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      1 week, 4 trips to Ralphs, 2 with Matt, 1 with a matching scarf and knit hat set.  :) 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       this application has unexpectedly quit my ass. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I haven't written in a week and a half.  That's a record for me now.  It's ok though, cuz' I'll get in the groove again.  I have four term papers to write in the next three weeks (one which will be submitted to a cognitive science journal) so I know I'll be looking for tons of ways to procrastinate at my computer.  And here is one of them!    So there's been lots going on lately, both in my life and in the world.  I woke up this morning feeling absolutely amazing (after a piece of toast, a One-A-Day, and a raspberry Emergen-C).  I attribute that to almost-good health and to over twelve hours of sleep last night.  Yup, I went to bed before most eight-year-olds do.  It was a good day though, so it was a good wear-me-out feeling.  Corey and I gave our major presentation in front of an education class in NWCA.  The auditorium seats around 250-300, but it's eighth week, so I'd say we spoke in front of a good 100-150 people.  Not bad eh?  When I'm a professor I know I can fondly look back to yesterday as my first lecture-sized teaching experience.  I had been on campus all day either in work or in meetings or attempting to put together my term papers, and then I helped out with Bruin up Books for a bit.  I started filling out my paperwork for my REAL JOB, so that was exciting.  Anyway... so what else is going on... well there's Ryan, so you'll have to meet him if you haven't already.  Weekends in Santa Barbara have been nice, almost like a vacation at the end of the week (not that I've really been doing all that much work otherwise... and I know that pisses you off...)  He took me out to this dinner at Lawry's on Valentine's Day, and it was quite the adventure.  #1, we didn't have reservations, #2 it took him over three hours to drive down to LA because of Friday afternoon/long weekend traffic.  Anyway, as we're tredging along Olympic Blvd. towards La Cienega, we astutely notice these helicoptors (ok, I thought they were planes flying directly towards us) and wisen up and start listening to the news.  It turns out the Wash Mutual over in the Flint Publications building on Wilshire and La Cienega had been robbed.  They gunned one robber down and were frantically searching for the other one.  So they police blockaded portions of the streets off around the intersection of Wilshire and La Cienega.  And where is Lawry's located?  Good ol' Wilshire and La Cienega.  :)  It sucked that it took so long to drive there with all this police traffic, but we got smart and parked in a residential area and walked over to the restaurant.  We walked right in and were seated within minutes... lots of people completely missed their reservations because of all the traffic, which was prime for us.  :)  I had the English cut, a side of spinach, and a glass of 2001 Pinot Noir.  It was all very romantic (police sirens and all).    So how about that war, eh?  I've been trying to have intellectual conversations with people about this war business.  Basically this is what I have concluded.  Is there a threat?  Sure.  Is this threat worth killing thousands of innocent civilians along the way?  I'm not so sure.  Shouldn't we not be doing stuff without the support of other countries?  Generally yes, unless their only reason for not supporting us is to keep lines of trade open.  What do I think of the millions of people who marched through the streets all over the world in protest of the war or in support of the war?  Arun put it best (leave it to the Canadians): "those who know the least shout the loudest."  Does all this focus on the middle east take away too much from important domestic issues?  Hell yeah.  So should we go to war?  I can honestly say I do not support nor oppose it.  Why can't I form an opinion?  Because I believe there is so much going on behind the scenes that we as common Americans are oblivious to.  The media filters what it wants to tell us, and what it does tell us it skews in every which way possible.  Thus I find it extremely difficult to form decisive opinions on such matters.  And it doesn't help that I think everyone in power (Democrats and Republicans alike) are rich old white men who will hurt anyone in order to keep things peachy keen for themselves and their families.  AND (this is unrelated to the war) people need to realize that "diversity" is such a fucking buzz word that they don't even know what they're talking about when they use it.  Yes diversity is important when it comes to institutions of higher education.  But this is a diversity of experiences, beliefs, and perspectives that we're talking about.  If this diversity is related to or a result of racial differences, then great, we have racial diversity.  But on it's own I think the focusing the importance on strictly racial diversity is a load of crap.  Master status or not, it's not race that defines us; it's how our environment around us deals with our race and how we choose to embody the element of race into our lives.  Take Mell and I for example.  On paper, when talking about race, socioeconomic status, level of education, and educational opportunites, we're exactly the same.  But if you talk to us, you'll very quickly realize that we have very different experiences, beliefs, and perspectives.  So stop focusing solely on race.  Why don't you take the time to hear what people actually have to say about their lives?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      3 down, 37 to go. Talking back to ritalin and then heading to bed.  :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So this was my afternoon today... my very first car accident.  Not my fault, no one hurt. (yeah, don't worry, everyone is ok)  Lexus guy ran a stop sign, directly into me.  Poor BUB.  Though the bumper just chillin in Arun's car is just priceless.  :)      
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Those who know the least speak the loudest.   There was this really cool guy at the anti-war rally today who had his own bullhorn but unlike all the tools on stage was actually speaking coherent intellectual thoughts.  It was a nice change.  He's sorta pro-war because we've reached that point, and he's very anti-radical-loud-yelling-catchy-slogans-that-mean-nothing-you-don't-know-what-the-hell-you're-even-protesting. I wish I got his name down, but hopefully he'll show up again.    War = cut AAP funding??  PUHLEASE!
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I feel like David Rigsby; I've been awake for so long, I'm beyond over-exhaustion, and I can't for the life of me think clearly.  I don't understand how people do this repeatedly.  Anyway, it's about to be over.  My "up yours" paper is about to be turned in.  Kinko's at 3 in the morning was quite the opposite of an action-packed adventure.  Arun deserves a fucking medal.  We'll put something about Canada on it.    Now, the current problem is: how do I keep the neighbors who like to drive into the garage gate and hit on unsuspecting women half their age, from staying awake and talking loudly well past 4 am (when I attempted to go to bed)?  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
         mother fucker   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Matt and Arun actually went to Ralphs today without me.  Oh I'm quite the matchmaker.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      What I learned from Education 181B (the paper I'm working on now): -what NOT to do as a professor -how NOT to design a website -there's an organization out there for Christians with ADHD..."This site is an acknowledgement that those who have these differences, or challenges, are not unspiritual, backslidden or living in sin (although they might be depending on the condition of their relationship with the Lord just like anyone else)."  -pharmaceutical companies are not allowed to advertise directly to consumers in Canada -it sucks to live in the LAX flight path  that's about it...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I just watched Girl Interrupted (yes, in the midst of all this paper-writing, stop judging, you know you do it too, AND you try to whine about it to me).  Anyway, the movie.  Well done.  It made me sad.  "What's wrong with you?  You don't look crazy..."  "I'm sad."  "Well everyone's sad."    Why is that?  No, really.  What could possibly be that wrong that would make the world sad? That's a lame question.  I guess I'm just confused.  I mean, in contrast to everyone else in the world (suffering, starving, being oppressed) those whom I know and care about and interact with lead cushy lives, including myself.  But they still feel sad.    Maybe it's not sad, just misunderstood.  I mean, that was the premise of that movie.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      10 PM ET, 7PM PT, 6AM Iraqi Time.  Bombs over Baghdad.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Time it took AAA to call me back... 5 working days (48 hours my ass). Walking 20 city blocks from the body shop... horrendous (and way unhealthy). The smirk on the body shop guy's face: "oh, the bumper is INSIDE the car"... priceless. Adjuster estimate price to bring Bub back to life... $5,000. Adjuster estimate time to bring Bub back to life... 12 working days. This whole experience... one huge headache.  One recent perk though: I now meet all of Randall's "what makes a woman attractive" criteria-- Ryan taught me how to drive stick!!   So hey, I'm a hot commodity these days (let me pretend for awhile...)  :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      mother fucker.   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's been a long time.  Being home sick makes you want to do things like blog again.  So let's update.   boyfriend:  Ryan Sturtevant, currently in SF... but absence only makes the heart grow fonder.  :)  roommates:  Arun, Leah, Stacy (officially); Tony, Alex (unofficially)  new family members:  Bethany Chan! (DOB: 11/10/03)  job:  Administrative Specialist in UCLA GSE&IS Center X, working on the NSF Algebra Project   future plans:  Applying to UCLA PhD program in Psychological Studies in Education... or culinary school... :)  health:  really good for the past 6-9 months... but really bad for the last month.  yuck.  current events:  war in Iraq still on.  Arnold as CA governor.  Democratic presidential candidates campaining.  what I did today:  stayed home from work with a fever.  learned lots of stuff on the guitar and piano.  cooked.  and now this.  we'll see where this goes. :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Fun  Cranium  moments: 1. Tony: Gay men love me.  I have a big nose.  I'm Jewish.     Leah: Adam Sandler! 2. Arun: It's Stonehenge!     Leah: It's Stonehenge (with one piller of misshapen clay) 3. Leah: What's that geyser?-Old Faithful! 4. Alex: What's the name of that gorilla?     Ang: What??? And many more.  What a bitchin' game.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The end of yet another day with my ass firmly planted on the couch.  Arun and I are quite the 007: Nightfire team, though, I may add.  The ninja assassin is SO Kiko (and scary)... I wouldn't be surprised if I had nightmares of her.   The salad I ate today was pale in comparison to yesterday's spectacular turkey dinner, but then again most meals would be.  I have yet to really get my appetite back however, so it doesn't really matter.  it  really sucks   being sick.    things fall apart.  yes they do.  so how do we put them back together?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I feel (slightly) better today.  :)   Though I'm still upset I haven't been able to go see my new niece.  Wanna see what I'm missing?       Career change:  I want to go to culinary school.  And the media is just going absolutely insane over this Michael Jackson thing.  Disgusting.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      My new nickname is NOT whoopi.  It might be time to go back to the doctor though.  Not that the doctors really know what to do with me.  But today was bad.  I can't remember a lot of it.  I can remember barely being able to hold down "1" on my cell phone to check my voice mail.  That was scary.  It's ending better though.  I had a couple of good hours at the end of the day.  Now for a good night of rest.  In a semi-clean room.  Hopefully.  Can you believe how long it's been?  I miss my family.  And Ryan. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Things that suck:   -spam -the Grove tree lighting ceremony  Ok, let me just say that out of my last 20 emails, only ONE was non-spam.  Absolutely ridiculous.  Want a taste? ----------     Thank for your recent Viagra Order.   We are currently giving upto 80%! off on all new orders due to huge demand!    We guarantee complete satisfaction with your performance. Or your money back no questions asked!     We are running out of stock fast! Buy now while our stocks Last!   ---------- Needless to say I DID NOT purchase any Viagra.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today was actually tons of fun.  I did more today than I have in the past two weeks (unless you count sitting on my ass -- I did lots of that).     the game  We weren't shut out.  That's all I was really looking for.  And when it came to the last two minutes of the fourth quarter, I was really hoping that we'd break into the 22-point spread.  That didn't happen, but few pipe dreams come true.  UCLA falls down a lot.  USC completes almost every pass.  What happened was supposed to happen.  It was still a very exciting game though.  I'm glad I watched it (in the privacy of my own home).  More happened, but I'm tired now.  Good night.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      My work holiday party was actually a lot of fun... well, I still don't know most of the office, and none of my direct coworkers were actually there, but the gift exchange... Let's just say there's a certain amount of satisfaction reaped when you steal a gift from a tenured-professor, and when the gift is actually Bacardi Limon with two fluted cocktail glasses... too bad the gift was stolen from me (damn you webmaster guy!) :)  My spinach salad was a total hit!  I should definitely stop giving away the recipe and keep it for my catering business.    
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      wow, I just reread some of my blogs from November.  That month really sucked.  It's funny how it's so easily to forget things sometimes.  I mean, I was absolutely miserable, and yet I recollect very little of it.  It gave me a nice buffer on my credit card bill, however, since I spent very little that month... that's nice, given that it's the holiday season, and that I lost money in Vegas, and that I'm trying to save up for France.  I'm glad to say that I'm feeling much better overall these days, minus a few notable incidents (i.e. the De Neve dining hall).  I think I love Christmas shopping.  There's just something to buying a gift for something that you know they'll like (of course, that only applies when you know they'll like it, and when you actually know what to get them, when they are actually possible to shop for...)  And yes, the malls are practically war zones every day, but that's ok... because it's fun being the eye of the hurricane.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      more things that suck: - getting shot from two directions at once  "snipe me now"  and bond music in elevators
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's been almost a month... Let's update.  :) 1. Application done and submitted! 2. Vegas trip number... 5?  (they only count since I've turned 21) last weekend... BLAST... absolute blast!  Bellagio buffet-- kobe beef (and I'm not talkin the bball player)... late night pai gow... afternoon pai gow... morning pai gow... too many rum and cokes to count... a GRASSHOPPER (finally! and like the bartender described... they're badass)... late-night running around the hotel... (ice from floor 15, ice from floor 14, no shoes/ice = service, but with scaring of old women)... the Denver/Cleveland game--heart attack!!!... willing the cards blue, or green, or red... all the cowboys... "So what are you doing here in Vegas?  Here for the rodeo convention, aren't you?"... 3. my Amelie list dislikes: a) partially-dressed mannequins. b) uncomfortably warm feet.  c) abbreviating over and never (it's NEVER YOU FUCKER, not NAIR!)  d) (what's the last one?) 4. 007 Nightfire beat.  007 Agent Under Fire... kinda ghetto, but we'll keep at it.   the guy from Better Luck Tomorrow is doing Dell commercials?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Recent observation:  movies are so long these days.  And I'm not just talking The Neverending Story 3, I mean, Lord of the Rings 3.  Here's what's playing at the PV theaters:  1. 21 grams - 125 min 2. Bad Santa - 91 min 3. Cheaper by the Dozen - 115 min 4. Elf - 97 min 5. The Last Samurai - 144 min 6. Lord of the Rings - 201 min 7. Master and Commander - 139 min 8. Mona Lisa Smile - 117 min 9. Paycheck - 119 min 10. Peter Pan - 113 min 11. Something's Gotta Give - 123 min 12. Stuck on You - 118 min 13. Cold Mountain - 155 min  Now, as I said above, we're going to leave LOTR in a league of it's own (and after Alex telling all about people LAUGHING at how long it was and CHEERING at how it ended, I think it's had enough).  But let's look at the "dumb comedies" category... Elf and Bad Santa are exactly as expected at about an hour and a half... but Cheaper by the Dozen and Stuck on You at almost 2 hrs??  (though I really do want to see the Farrelly brother's new one...)  And the "I want an oscar" category... (Cold Mountain, Samurai, Master and Commander)... does winning an oscar mean being the longest?   Maybe the movie industry has laid off all its editors.  Maybe it's trying to justify charging up to $10.50 (plus parking, at the Grove) per movie.  But really.  No wonder Arun won't watch movies.  :)   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Merry day after Christmas.  Thank goodness it was a 48-hr bug.  I only spent half of Christmas day in bed... though it did break my heart to hear Joshua ask "Gu-gu, why are you so sleepy?"  After spending almost four straight days with the little ones, I'm going to miss them a lot.  The house really does feel more filled and cozy with kids around.  Don't worry, I want NONE of my own yet.  I need my sleep way too much for that.  Patient Cal actually got up in the middle of the night and stormed into the closet to get some rest.  It's always fine and dandy so long as mommy and daddy can take them away at the end of the day.  I am going to miss all the attention, though, at Grand China Buffett... people were having a field day watching Joshua walk on my feet.  You should try that restaurant sometime.  $10.99 for all-you-can-eat decent chinese food and sushi.  Just don't eat the raw chicken-for-mongolian-bbq raw...   so UCLA IS in a bowl game.  I forgot what it was called... I think it's Tuesday.  Some fan I am.  Oh, the Silicon Valley Bowl game vs. Fresno St.  woo.  Eh, hopefully it'll be fun to watch.  All are welcome to join, though I do yell loudly.  So best case scenario: in a limo, on the way to the casinos, watching Swingers, having a drink, after lunch.  very witty.      
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      being sick sucks.  merry christmas eve to all.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      These last few days have been really tough.  Really tough.  But I know it was for the best.  It really was.    Thank goodness for family.  I got to hold Bethany for the first time (and I got spit up on by Bethany for the first time).  I got to spend an entire day and a half with Joshua.  It was really amazing.  I mean, when else do you get to race a 2-year-old (to where? everywhere), eat Honeycomb and Cheerios all day, and drive while only listening to the Sesame Beep Beep song?  :)  Mom said Joshua wouldn't sleep and kept asking "where did gu-gu go?" Priceless.  I get the genius (jeenyus) award for picking up Mell from the airport. :)  Now let me interrupt all this cherriness with a lament.  Given my recent moving violation experience, I have been driving rather minimally and rather exactly at 1mph below speed limit.  Needless to say there is no way I can get another ticket.  So I'm not really worried there.  But today, driving from my apt to PV, I saw no less than 7 cop cars!!  Let me list them out for you... 1) behind me on the 405 south near Rosecrans, then passing me quickly... 2) driving south on Hawthorne as I wait at the light to turn onto Hawthorne from the freeway... 3) turning from Redondo Beach Blvd. to Hawthorne, as I wait at that light... 4) following me from the Galleria all the way to (not 190th, not Torrance, but) Carson blvd! and stopping to assist 5) who has pulled someone over just south of Lomita... then #4 reappeared because #5 needed no assistance, and I was going so slowly that he quickly caught up until 6) who pulled someone over just south of Lomita blvd (this one needed assistance)... then there was 7) who started driving behind me at about PCH (who could have been #4, but I can't be certain)... lastly there was 8) pulled over to the side of Hawthorne near Hesse Park with his lights on... that's all, no one pulled over or anything.  absolut ridiculosity.  can't they better utilize their time?  by, say, stopping dangerous drivers and catching the robber?  one last thought before bedtime.  his gift came in the mail for me today.  it's perfect.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      1. Jude Law is HOT.  I'd wait for him on a cold mountain any day. 2. I am a master chef. 3. Poor Leah has been stuck at the airport for almost 12 hours!!
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's a wonder what leave-in conditioner and molding wax can do for your hair.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So I went to an Asian party tonight.  Mell's going to kill me.  In my defense, I went under a couple of conditions: 1. I really wanted to go out tonight and was actually feeling better. 2. I wanted to spend time w/ my girls, especially Chris. 3. I didn't really know it was going to be an Asian party... just kinda thought it.  If I really knew, I would've worn flats.  Having said all of that, I actually had a really good time.  It was a bday party for three people who all decided to rent out the Santo Coyote on Melrose.  At least, that's what I think it was... I'm not exactly sure.  And there was a guestlist that I was supposed to fudge my way onto, but I actually just valeted my car, stepped up to the door, smiled at the bouncers, and walked right in.  Go me.  It was a blast dancing with my girls, and I got to meet some friends of friends.  And then I kept running into people I knew from way back when... from church... from the dorms... from Cambridge... from high school... I felt old, and tall, but oh well.  There was also one big almost-fight stirred up by none other than a PV alum.  Who knows what it was really about, but an hour later he was still all pissed, spitting on the curb, making an absolute ass of himself.  Grow up.  Why don't you really throw a punch and see where that brings you.    All in all, fun night.  Great music.  Room to dance, room to sit, but crowded enough to keep the energy level high.  So do the ditty if you want to because then I can see if I want to.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I awaken this morning at the dawn of a new year, nose unstuffed and tummy grumbling.  The 120mg of pseudophedrine I took at 6pm last night made the awakening so much more joyful and refreshing feeling than it really should have after only a few short hours of sleep.  I head down to the kitchen to chat with mom as she packs her vitamins, and casually peruse the sports section of the LA Times.  Trojans... Michigan... blah blah blah.  My interest is piqued by a front-page article, not discussing the teams and potential victors of the game, but discussing the battle of the fight songs.  Apparently Michigan and SC have two of the best fight songs... like, ever.  WHAT??  Now, I'm actually looking forward to hearing the Michigan fight song for the first time this afternoon.  But the stinkin' SC fight song?  The one with three notes?  The article proceeds to talk about how they played the SC fight song during WWII during some attack in a Pacific island... how it's practically a classic pub song...  blah blah BLAH.  There was one great part of the article aligned with a firm belief of mine that I'd like to mention.  :)  "The problem with the USC song is that they play it too much," Studwell said. "It seems like they play when they score, when they don't score, when they feel good, when they feel bad. Many people feel it's overdone."   ME INCLUDED!  :)  Now after that extensive rant, I have to admit I probably will sit and watch the game and almost cheer for the... gasp... you know... because I appreciate good football and don't appreciate lame ass sucky we might as well be a JV HS team cuz' we suck and can't do anything football.  tear.  I now digress from the newspaper to reflect on the events of New Year's Eve 2003... is that New Year's Eve 2003 or New Year's Eve 2004?  Interesting conundrum.  (I don't think I've ever used the word conundrum before, ever.)  It began with some ass-kicking at Super Monkey Ball 2 in the good ol' Chan PV house in front of the good of Chan PV HDTV.  It then moved to Hermosa Beach... to my favorite bar of course... Molloy's... There was some drinking, streamer-throwing, dancing at the table, pizza eating next door, puking... :)  We won't get into details but we hightailed out of there by about 10:45.  :)  It all worked out though with all of us being able to spend New Year's together, rather than running in and out of the bar to the patio area.  We then moved over to Stacy's pool-not-billiards-cuz-it's-a-different-game room and counted down there.  It was cozy and chill, the way New Year's is meant to be.  I shot pool and didn't suck at it!!  We counted down, uncorked the sham-pog-nuh, and just relaxed our way into 2004.    It was a nice night.  Definitely memorable.  And I need to get back to the pizza place so that I can sing Journey loudly and not be the only one!  Did you hear that?  The people eating at the pizza place actually stopped their chomping and started singing along to Journey!  I love Hermosa! 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Four possessions without a single first down, a miracle TD pass after a "running into the kicker penalty," pushing Fresno St. all the way back for a penalty... but sadly we did not prevail.  Even the hot coach didn't make it all ok.  The two minute focus on Matt Ware screwing up helped a little.  Well here's to next year.    It's been a long day.    
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      An ode to   urlLink Mell  :  she rocks.  Any girl who can keep guys on the edge of being utterly terrified of her and drop dead in love eating out of the palm of her hand has got some magical prowess.  Thanks for the December 11 card, you absolute freak who keeps track of anniversarys like THAT one.  I look forward to being able to send you one.  haha.  But for now, I'll settle for morning (well, past noon) chats with sultry voices.  Sat nite was fun.  Good cheese pizza.  Good yummy-but-strong drinks.  Lots of dancing.  And the ladies' lounge lime green phallic-shaped veranda.  I need to do the going out thing oh, once every full moon.  It takes me that long to recover.  Now for some quality mother daughter time at Del Amo.  :)  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      i still don't know how to listen, but i'm trying.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      i sit in my newly-organized room.  pile of clothes still lingers on the floor behind and to the left of me.  screen is dimmed to 50%.  flylight brightly illuminates center of keyboard from an angle.    life is a scary thing.  i know how i feel, yet i still don't know how to feel.  how i should feel, that is.  it's so easy to be angry, to focus on the unfairness and the injustice and the lack of mercy and the prevalence of trials.  i can't ever imagine what it must be like.  perhaps it's easiest just to focus on the to-do list:  contact travel agency for itinerary.  contact uncle lee's cell phone.  set up return flight.  reschedule next week's tutoring.    maybe it's bedtime.  i feel sleepy.  it's just hard to think about sleep right now.    
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      oh no... DPe and Kristy want to go to Pachanga tonight... the addiction ensues.  :)  and it's RUNAWAY TRAIN by Soul Asylum.  I can sing the entire song!
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Lots of stuff going on.  lots of work this week.  second job.  first client tonight.  new trivia games.  new cold.  killer apple martinis.  and check out   urlLink  Matt's Site  .  Haha.    Oh, and I caught Bravo's Celebrity Poker last night... Even though Paul Rudd is potentially more adorable and won all the money, I want you  Ron Livingston ...  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Winter break comes to an end... I should feel fortunate enough to be in my line of work, given that I actually HAVE a winter break... I guess I'm ready to go back to work.  Fun night w/ the roomies tonight.  Alex and I are "trivial" and Stacy almost bought a giraffe for us... which Arun and I would've actually gotten a kick out of.  So when do I get to watch someone mako fish?  And halibut are crazy looking m-fkers!  Note to self: do not have male cousin sing Elvis operatically at wedding.   Second note: where the heck is my level? 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      LITRES AND LITRES!!  GEEZ!
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      As Leah was about to take off (on her changed AND delayed flight) from Ft. Lauderdale, she heard this loud sound on the left side of the plane... The flight attendant quickly got on the phone and asked what the sound was... THE THING THAT STEERS ON THE LEFT SIDE OF THE PLANE FELL OFF!  What the hell!!  2 minutes later, they would have had to crash land the plane! They had to be pulled back to the gate cuz' the plane couldn't manuver itself back.  Geez!  I told Leah American Airlines needs to kiss her ass.  Needless to say they just lost a couple of customers today.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      high bar recording studio, session one:  friday january 16 approx. 2:30pm cover of ani difranco's you had time electric guitar: AB vocals: AC
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      on my way to wiping away all high risks for heart disease in my body...  Ok, so I said I wouldn't weigh myself while on this diet for a variety of reasons... weight doesn't tell you body fat:muscle, just how much water you have in your system... and maybe I didn't want to jinx myself because, well, I've been doing that a WHOLE lot lately... but I think I'm down 5 pounds since I started 5 days ago.  That's quite the drop.  I don't really believe it all... and I won't cry myself to sleep if it doesn't stay off or nothing else comes off... but it's kind of a notable difference.  Just wanted to share that.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      good steak.  good salad.  good company.  good.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The funeral was this morning.  It was really sad.  I don't know what I was expecting, but I could definitely feel that it was a tremendous loss.  Chris was so strong as she spoke and as she walked out of the chapel.  There were lots of old friends and coworkers who talked about a side of her dad that none of us had ever known.  What hit me most about all of this is how little you actually know of someone until you attend their funeral.  Ironic how life works that way.  And depressing.  I'll never forgot the song that Jenn's mom sang.  It has so much meaning now.    "Remember today and be sad,  but remember tomorrow and be happy."  yes, it means so much more coming from who it came from.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today was absolutely exhausting, but extremely productive.  I'm pooped.  The funeral is tomorrow... taking a moment of reflection in preparation.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      the weekend was good.  caught up with old friends.  kicked some gamecube ass.  pondered blond jokes around the campfire and playing spoons in the dark.  i am absolutely exhausted, however, after the half night of sleep I got on Saturday night.  long day today.  and day 2 of south beach.  here goes.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I wonder how to describe  Death: or, the playground .  I'll have to think about that.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      bless long lunches with friends in the noon sun of kerckhoff patio.   statement of the day: "that's going STRAIGHT back to Amy..." so iowa caucases eh? and health insurance? oh America.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      so is THIS what it's like for a day in the life of a non cfids-person?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      confidence and renewal... (and awaiting truth serum to really let loose)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      oh the sounds coming from our house.  :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      so potentially extremely awkward situation tonight at Q's was really tons o' fun.  pv reunion part 2?  and center of attention on a bar stool amidst a group intently standing around?  who knew.  overall fun day.  hanging with the girls.  recording studio take 2.  wedding singer.  guitar lesson.  tacos-at-home dinner.  notable thought: learning different sides of people in such short amounts of time. moment to remember:  the guy who actually followed me first south beach-prohibited craving: vanilla latte and ANYTHING dessert related from the coffee bean.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      tonight was quite possibly one of the most drama-filled going out nights... ever.  thank god for easy-going personalities (for the most part).    things i've learned from this experience: -never bring guys when you want to get into a club in hollywood -never get on cecile's bad side -adam garcia is hot (right cheek still unwashed) -young is still cute after, what, 7 years?  quote of the evening: "If I ever see that mother fucker again, I'm going to rip out his nuts.  I want to go home.  Anyone have a cigarette?" moment of the evening:  Jon Han running up to my car saying "just get outta here before something happens!" and a subsequent Josh running after the car.  overall, i'm sad though.  tonight just made me see a lot of things.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       BIG ROCK IS UP!!     as I said before, my roommates rock.  that's all.  overall it was a good/eventful weekend.  including the funeral.  lots of great family time.  especially with mom at del amo.  good times at the farmer's market.  good times at vibe 9.  great taco salad as always.  anxiously awaiting new roommate.  and a good night's sleep.  peace.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      it's bright.  i did not experience refreshing sleep.  and i have four non blonds stuck in my head.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       my roommates are the best  so they were going to *surprise* me with BIG ROCK, on an 8 ft plexi-glass mounted foam board... and camp out in the living room so that they could see my surprised reaction at 6am.  i think i'm going to cry.   or rather just sleep.    here's to rapping old white men.  and the smitten-iliciting cure guy.   and to 97 years.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ok it's been awhile since I posted, but tonight was such a  dear diary  night!!  oh I hope I remember it all in the morning...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      next on the wine rack to try: 2002 Chateauneuf-du-pape, 9.99, x2 2001 JW Morris Pinot Noir, 2.99 yes I read about it in the Times, thanks for getting it from the back for me.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      words I've been frequenting.  - nervous-ing - racy - jovial - lament 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      night #2 of sleeplessness was actually quite eventful.  oh the stories to be told.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       o·blit·er·ate        tr.v.   o·blit·er·at·ed, o·blit·er·at·ing, o·blit·er·ates  1. To do away with completely so as to leave no trace. See synonyms at abolish.  things we need to  obliterate : 1. tax loopholes that favor the extremely wealthy 2. computers that can't recognize their own fucking hard drives 3. nausea 4. oblivious drivers who put themselves and others in grave danger
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Stay or Leave  Maybe different but remember Winters warm where you and i Kissing whiskey by the fire  With the snow outside And when the summer comes In the river Swims at midnight Shiver cold Touch the bottom you and I With muddy toes  Stay or leave I want you not to go But you should It was good as good goes Stay or leave I want you not to go But you did  Wake up naked drinking coffee Making plans to change the world While the world is changing us Was good good love You used to laugh under the covers Maybe not so often now But the way I used to laugh with you Was loud and hard  Stay or leave I want you not to go But you should It was good as good goes Stay or leave I want you not to go But you did  So what to do With the rest of the day's afternoon hey Isn't it strange how we change Everything we did Did I do all that i should  That I coulda done  Remember we used to dance And everyone wanted to be You and me I want to be too What day is this Besides the day you left me What day is this Besides the day you went  So what to do With the rest of the day's afternoon hey Well isn't it strange how we change Everything we did Did I do all that I could  Remember we used to dance And everyone wanted to be you and me I want to be too What day is this Besides the day you went babe What day is this 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Mad World  Verse 1 All around me are familiar faces Worn out places, Worn out faces Bright and early for the daily races Going nowhere, Going nowhere Their tears are filling up their glasses No expression, No expression Hide my head I want to drown my sorrow No tomorrow, No tomorrow  Chorus  And I find it kind of funny, I find it kind of sad These dreams in which i'm dying, Are the best I've ever had I find it hard to tell you, I find it hard to take When people run in circles it's a very very Mad World, Mad World  Verse 2 Children waiting for the day they feel good Happy Birthday, Happy Birthday And they feel the way that every child should Sit and listen, Sit and listen Went to school and I was very nervous  No one knew me, No one knew me Hello teacher tell me whats my lesson Look right through me, Look right through me  Chorus  And I find it kind of funny, I find it kind of sad These dreams in which i'm dying, Are the best I've ever had I find it hard to tell you, I find it hard to take When people run in circles it's a very very Mad World, Mad World  Enlargen your world  Mad World 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      1:40pm  nuttyprncs: arun posted on ur wall! imstraightdammit: i know! imstraightdammit: were international!
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      M: she thanks her lucky stars we are well-adjusted
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       rules of dating  1. there are no rules 2. if you think there are rules, see #1  ups and downs... downs:  -saw the Grammy winner list before the freakin' Grammys.. damn YAHOO... -heard some unfortunate news about a friend of a friend -uncomfortable living situation... kinda counting the days til Feb 29 -totally cheated on South Beach on Sat ups: -steam room and jacuzzi at the new gym (and working out w/ Leah is always a blast) -roommates are still awesome -work can be so encouraging and rewarding -TAHOE BABY -but first... racing turtles... :)  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Morning two in Mtn View.  This weekend has been both relaxing and fun.  And I got to walk right by the blogger guys at Google!!!  How cool is that?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I love February.  The more I reflect, I think it's definitely one of my favorite months.  Yes there's August ("ooot"), and mid-summer birthday months are always spectacular, but it's usually a transitional months where friends/loved ones are not around.  June used to be pretty up there with the end of the school year and a sense of closure wrapping up the previous months, but now June just means quadruple the workload.  December has always sucked ass with holiday panic/mania/chaos/elbows-at-the-mall/let's-make-it-so-trafficky-that-you-can't-get-down-the-street.    So back to February.  The new year has settled, so no rush to get back into things.  Many months remain, so there's no rush to finish things up.  There's a three-day weekend, but not necessarily the most heavily-travelled three-day weekend.  And there are days like these, where it just rained like crazy so all the metro filth has been washed away, where dew is still chillin' on those blossoming trees, where the sky hasn't looked bluer, and where it's bright and sunny out but you still need a light sweater and maybe a scarf.  And the breeze is ever-refreshing.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink tahoe pics   and f*** leg muscles that stop working!
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      allow me to re-emphasize  item 42  on the list: a photographic image that you really didn't know you were capturing  tahoe had a couple of those.  I LOVE IT!!!!!     and even though it's one of my favorite movies, Lost in Translation definitely mis-translated what Scarlett Johansson's character said about photography.  up next: SF/Mtn View then: wedding in the OC, babysitting galore then: NY, NY then: weekend to pack? then: LAX -> CDG... PARIS BABY!! then: JET.  We're sorry, we can only match Angie's request.  So there. then: work then: El Cap, 10-person tent, the everpresent Costco guessing game  maybe I'll get a short nap in here or there...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      VEGAS BABY!  I mean, TAHOE BABY!
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      official SSM.  shhhhhh.  :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      from a craigslist.org sublet listing:  "We are looking for a quiet, serious - no drama individual."  amen 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      drip drop pitter patter drip drop pitter patter neighbor's pond drip drop pitter patter leaky roof drip drop pitter patter drip drop pitter patter late night star 98.7 drip drop pitter patter drip drop pitter patter latimes crossword puzzle drip drop pitter patter cnn articles on consitutional amendment drip drop pitter patter drip drop pitter patter small town mentality drip drop pitter patter abuse drip drop pitter patter dizzy drip drop pitter patter drip drop pitter patter   oh insomnia. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      non-work day accomplishment:  finished Da Vinci Code.  I dug the second one of the "this" ::Rigz and Angie gesture::  tres clever.    to Paris, onward.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      to mud-splattered metal containers.  to sounds of cars and ocean.  and MFCrickets.  to driving there one way and driving back another.  and to that making sense.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      2001 JW Morris Pinot Noir.  Not bad, so long as you keep in mind that it's a $2.99 wine.  It ain't no two-buck-chuck though.  "I ate steak for dinner." "We're two to eight."
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      "leah got drunk and arun wants to watch a movie!  hell DID freeze over."
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      so today was one of the best workouts I've had... well... in a long time.  so that's good.  maybe it's all the tanins (and there are lots) left over in my system?  and I noticed lots of stares...  at my wrinkled/awkwardly-ironed-on "die cat dead i love you" shirt.  I think people were scared.  :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      2 plane trips.  1  enivre .  1 sleep.  2 rounds of double shots of baileys over ice.  8 bottles of wine.  1 2000 wild horses pinot noir.  1 spinach salad.  2 salmon fillets.  5 cab rides.  3 bouncers whom we just walked by with a "oh don't worry, we're with her."  1 credit card in lieu of drivers' license.  1-handed push to get the go-go dancer off the pole stage.  1 zoolander dvd.  2 "arfies??"  2 DDR mats.  2 injured digits.  12 dry-fried chicken wings.  3 double brownie bites.  1 triple grande latte, nonfat, no foam.  sum it all up.  one HELLUVA weekend.    kudos to mell for being the  glue .   urlLink click here for pics 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       (non-french) It's not what it seems but it is.    I think I'm coming out of my daze a bit.  Knowing the sky will be blue is settling.  At least I can somewhat concentrate on things.  Not that things are necessarily clearer, but getting a good night of sleep definitely helps.  And so does book-writing.  And narrow-ruled yellow notepads and #2 pencils.    In the end, it really will all work out.     onward, to NY.  then I can start to plan Paris.   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Stay or leave I want you not to go But you should It was good as good goes Stay or leave I want you not to go But you did  So what to do With the rest of the day's afternoon hey Isn't it strange how we change Everything we did Did I do all that I should  That I coulda done  What have I done?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      this is tough.  well, let's be honest... impossible.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So the downfall to a weblog: some of the most important, most affecting, most life-changing experiences simply cannot be posted.  yesterday was one of them.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      to old friends, to new friends.  to celebrations, to self-reflections.  to scallops and lobster on broccolini.  to the chocolate pyramids.  to secrets.  to secrets revealed.  to the nice couple at the bar.  to the two hour twenty minute risotto.  to cutting one's hair.    and to waking up three and a half hours later.  with a smile.    a perrier jouet toast... to an utterly momentous week.  repeat utterly.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       I got into grad school!!!!!!!   please, can someone hit the pause button?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      DPe said it best:  it feels like everything is in fast forward.  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      perhaps the most rewarding experience is to learn immensely more about someone you already knew.  and the saddest experience is realizing how little you knew to begin with.  and the most growing experience is being able to reflect on them both.    onto book-writing and library.ucla.edu searches...then a nyquil-induced coma... but maybe not in that order...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       things sprawled on bed  ("just to keep stuff off the floor"): opened suitcase, hardly used oil-free acne wash creme cleanser, peacoat, new clothes, old clothes, glasses case, non-scary gloves, tattered Let's Go New York City guide, and me...  uploading 187 pictures...    urlLink click here  	  oh NY.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      3 kinta roll 2 spicy salmon roll 1 spider roll 1 shrimp tempura roll 7 california roll 4 rainbow roll 3 tuna salad roll 2 spicy tuna roll  cucumber salad wasabi and soy sauce to taste  happy st. paddy's day
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      HURRY BACK (or I'll eat all your kinta roll and use all your 24 lb. extra bright paper)!!
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      day three of condo hunting.  pooped.  not going to be living on barry (the street, not the velociraptor)... not going to be living in Stryker's condo... definitely not going to be living where that old woman died...   so where?  (p.s. tomorrow's wednesday!!)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      so what IS  Timothy  about?  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      FRANCE TOMORROW!!!  RIDICULOUSLY STOKED!!!!!!!    "who lives like this?"  :)  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      37 of the 300 photos we took in France:   urlLink click here for pics  	
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      evening two back from France.  still recovering.  and coughing up a lung.  lots and lots of stories to tell... but too tired to tell them now.    paris was magical... but it's nice to be home too.  :)  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      similar to some major influences in my life (M & M)... I'm blogging just to say that I'm still here and that I'm still alive but that I really don't want to write right now.  I completely agree with the "when things are going well I don't blog" comment (because the book-writing has gotten very few hits in, oh, the past month)... life is just kinda rolling along smoothly.  well go us.  :)  maybe it's just because we have significant others.  yes, they're ALL significant so stop denying it.  maybe it's just cuz' we're gettin' some.   I'm kidding.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
        urlLink an assortment of pictures  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      so I guess the Saturday late morning IM conversations with Mell have turned into mid-workday convos... hooray for them!  :)  and hooray for sauteed mushrooms stuffed with crab meat (served in sizzling butter), 16 oz. new york strip steaks medium-rare (served in sizzling butter), creamed spinach (served with sticks of butter melted in), and the golden onion ring.  and a '98 9th house of the pope.  in two gorgeous wine glasses.  and the waitress who ran after us.  clink.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      me:  cuz' you'll be packing mell:  what?!? me:  because you're moving... mell:  hahhahaha mell:  i thought you meant guns!!  only a criminology student... or a republican for that matter.  :)  and an ode to gmail.  for screwing mell's brother over w/ the madonna tix.  sorry.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       MADONNA MADONNA MADONNA MADONNA MADONNA!!!!!  It ROCKED! The Great Western Forum was absolutely insane.  The sets were insane.  The BAGPIPER was insane!!!  BEST CONCERT (I've been to) EVER!! 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ang is back!  so how 'bout those national spelling bee prize winners?    from cnn.com:  A 14-year-old Indiana boy mastered "autochthonous" to win the National Spelling Bee Thursday, outdueling 264 rivals, including one who fainted on stage but recovered to take second place...   In the end, he defeated Akshay Buddiga, a 13-year-old from Colorado Springs, Colo., who had briefly collapsed on stage rounds earlier.  Within seconds of crumpling, Akshay stood up and, to the amazement of the judges, immediately started spelling his word: "alopecoid," which means like a fox. He got it perfectly, drawing a standing ovation.  He was led off stage for a medical check and returned for the next round.  Akshay made it into the final twosome while sitting on a chair at the microphone, looking weak, his questions to the judges barely loud enough to hear.     
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hour 30 in bed/on couch affords lots of friendster/orkut-perusing, education article summarizing, and ofoto album updating...    urlLink pics from Desi's graduation!    urlLink pics from Shirley's Bday wine tasting   note to self:  see the passion in those around you, and let that be your inspiration
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      wow, so many changes.  go blogger.  so I'm sitting in Bentley now, on my newly-delivered amapala sectional w/ chaise, in peat?, having completed some mathematics education reading on peer-directed questions, after finishing a mom-made dinner on the newly-delivered dining set complete with three burgandy-red placemats, and I am inspired by mch to reformat.  I kind of miss the old template, the more I look at it, but I had screwed around with it so much that blogger couldn't auto-update the comments part, and I am definitely not able to do that myself... so here it is.  so we're just a couple of hours away from June.  it is absolutely ridiculous how fast the past few months have jet by.  but they have.  that's all.  I'm hungry.    and annoyed at the stomping neighbor above.  or just at the poorly-insulated floors.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      do the comments work yet?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      how about now?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ahh... good night.  and see you in the morning.  :)
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      so trekking up the "eye-four-oh-five" on an early summer Friday afternoon (with no less than four large IKEA pieces in the back of the family minivan) gives one an extensive amount of time to sing, tan, and reflect on all that is wrong with traffic these days.  as the freeway slowed to its usual 15-20mph slow and go status, I noticed a fire engine slowly trudging along behind me, wedged on the quasi-shoulder between the #1 lane and the concrete divider.  its lights were flashing, but its sirens were not blaring, so I really don't know the severity of whatever situation it was trying to reach, but it's a fire truck.  there's something probably extremely time sensitive going on.  but could the fire truck reach the incident?  well sure, but no faster than I could.  then it hit me.  we need an emergency vehicles access lane.  think about some dude on a motorcycle weaving in and out of lanes or that punk kid in his abomination of a fixed-up car (yeah, I'm getting old)... and think about the medical attention that is oh-so-urgent when there's an accident.  emergency vehicles need to have access to these situations.  even with side streets, there's really no getting around traffic congestion.    now one may argue that this extra lane would be a waste of valuable driving space... and thus one may propose that we use this lane for carpool/emergency vehicles such that the lane would be outlined in special emergency lights and such that in the event the emergency lights began to flash, carpool drivers would be forced to quickly exit that lane until the lights ceased.   yeah... I'm not sure about this idea.  it's no U-turn signal, or windshield wipers that go the other way, but hey, it's a start.    and SPEAKING OF EMERGENCY SITUATIONS ON THE ROAD... I saw the CRAZIEST THING EVER WHILE DRIVING TODAY!!!  I was in the #3 lane going north on the 405, near Carson, and I happened to look in my rear-view mirror just as a light blue sedan reversed across the freeway from lane 1 to lane 4, fishtaled into a complete 360 and then jerked to a stop on the shoulder!!!  ISN'T THAT INSANE?  I am absolutely baffled at what caused the entire thing... Really, the ONLY explanation I have of this is that the guy lost control and ran into the center divider, then tried to back out of it, but slammed on his accelerator instead of his brake, sending him clear across the freeway, and then he freaked out and hit the brakes, locking them and sending him into fishtail mode... really, it was a sight from the movies.  and I don't think ANYONE WAS HURT!!  he didn't hit any cars before he came to a stop on the shoulder...   crazy huh?   ok, LACK and MALM need my attention.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ok it's been a REALLY long time now.  so long that I think I just read through all of the old posts in their entirety.    It's interesting to note just what gets put into a weblog and what doesn't.  I mean, there is so much that is so utterly important in life that is completely left out... and so much that is so uttterly trivial but is brought into the spotlight on more than one occasion.  Not that there's anything wrong with any of that... just a side-reflection.  It's hard to figure out just where to pick up.  It's like when you get together with a really good friend with whom you haven't really spent quality time in a long while (think 4-hour Claim Jumper meal or Parisian train station breakfast/brunch) and the beginning conversation is almost at the level of choppy intermittent small talk punctuated by a "what should I order" here and there... and then that (it's not awkward, but I don't know how to describe it) feeling subsides and the outing develops into one of the best conversations ever experienced in the history of conversations.  Perhaps that's what this is right now.  The (insert proper adjective here) small talk.    Well it's past midnight on a Thursday evening.  I sit in my darkened (yes, I need to buy lamps, I'm going to do that tomorrow) living room on the way-too-big but oh so comfortable sectional + chaise with JT in lap blogging to, on my right, the snoring sounds creeping out of Ryan's bedroom, and on my left, the ever-permeating blare of the building intercom system.  And additionally on this particular evening is the incessant sound of police sirens, punctuated by what has to be a conversation between a cop and a resident (either here or next door) about "the teenagers who threw a chair at me."  I put my money on the drive-by boba-ers in the brand new white Mercedes.    Tony's recovering from his cold with a mean knack for Chexx hockey (and a series-winning score that is too unbearable to report).  Stacy's gone to bed early with an apology.  Brendan's starting a phone conversation with "you dirty, dirty whore."  Alex's left for bed and returned when realizing that he cannot for the life of him sleep that early.  Leah's questioning whether or not Alex's tv watching in the master bedroom whilst Stacy's trying to sleep is bothersome.  Arun's (hopefully) resting up for his grand return home.  Avec le chien.    And here I am.  Nowhere.  (haha.  I'm so NOT Mark, though at times I feel like I am.  why is that?)  it's good to be back.  in more ways than you can imagine.    
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      my new bed rocks!  (as in, "is way cool," not "sways to and fro")  how I managed to put it together by myself is beyond me,  but can we please add this superpower to my list?  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      what a wonderful weekend.  :)    and it's amazing how people can continue to surprise you...
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      so being stopped on the corner of Barrington and Nebraska on the way back from a frisbee excursion wiht Cujo at Stoner park...  :)  
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Mell: but i think i will call you later perhaps Mell: as you are on your back Mell: and you really should make that an excuse for naughty behavior Mell: kidding kidding   I heart Mell.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I am SICK OF LYING AROUND ALL DAY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  So I've watched an obscene amount of sitcom reruns, so many half-movies on HBO, and Bronson Pinchot is on Step-by-Step.  perhaps he's the shark that the show jumped?  yes definitely.  his character's name is Jean-Luc.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ahh, so I didn't get THE phone call, but I suppose an IM suffices. I apologize for the yelling... I suppose I need not say more... except expect an inappropriate card in the mail exactly 364 days from now. haha. :)    ok back to work.  blah.  oh, and happy birthday to mell!  you only have ONE WEEK to be older  (but NOT wiser) than me so live it up!!!   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Pictures of last wkend 	
     

        
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      day 3 in exciting Madison, Wisconsin.  it actually IS very beautiful out here.  crazy ass capital building.  badass ice cream.  surprisingly no experience with WI cheese.  schmoozing with faculty.  discussing research interests.  realizing I know so little yet so much at the same time.  really feeling blessed about my time at UCLA so far.  very blessed.  fun moments from the past few days: Paradise Cove Beach Cafe, motherly Joe, the bowl of clam butter, I mean chowder, the green mojito, the water to go, and a pound and a half of that mofo crab we saw in Redondo Beach.  alaskan king crab.  wow. wePOD!  d.  dropchan. the Seascape Resort.  the late night dinner at the bar.  the band.  peter gabriel. the Bellagio buffet aka tailgating at the SF Giants game.  the garlic fries.  the churros.  the guinness.  the peanut shells.  the peanut shells.  the peanut shells.  Jenny got ridiculous orifices.  Don't ever let Tony Alphabetize. seeing the PV crew (briefly). sleeping every moment on every flight. the brookstone travellers pillow (fleece-lined, with case). Bluefies (arfies?) dinner with Phil, Dora, and Megan.  and can we just say how badass tubing was 2 wkends ago???  :)  
     

        
</post>


</Blog>